Chapter 1508 - Instant After Instant

It was Luo Ji’s first time on the playoffs stage. He was a rookie that couldn’t be more of a rookie. If he knew that Zhang Xinjie was worried about him, his self-confidence would skyrocket.

But no matter how much Zhang Xinjie was looking forward to what was to come from him, Luo Ji wasn’t going to give him face. His Summoner, Concealed Light, had yet to appear on the battlefield.

The viewers didn’t know that Zhang Xinjie was thinking about Luo Ji. If not, the broadcast would have certainly given Concealed Light a few close-ups to see what he was so busy with that he couldn’t give this vice-captain any face.

Luo Ji’s Concealed Light didn’t make any movements, but Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim did.

Boom!

A grenade exploded. Lord Grim tore through the explosion and rushed towards Dancing Rain.

In the end, Su Mucheng isn’t able to hold on and needs to be rescued?

Zhang Xinjie’s attention quickly shifted towards that direction. As a Cleric, his job wasn’t just to keep up his team’s health. Clerics had many useful offensive support skills such as Sacred Fire, Hypnosis, Holy Commandment. This was the difference between Clerics and Paladins. Clerics served a more offensive role, while Paladins served a more defensive role.

When Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed forward, the first person to intercept him on Tyanny’s side was Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock.

Immovable Rock lifted his Silver weapon, Backlight Cross, to his forehead and began casting a spell.

Sacred Fire!

Sacred Fire was a widely used Cleric skill. No one cared about the damage dealt by the skill. What mattered was the three seconds of Silence.

Three seconds!

Ye Xiu would likely reach Su Mucheng within these three seconds, but if he couldn’t use any skills, how was he supposed to rescue her?

Happy’s fans began to feel worried for Ye Xiu, seeing what Immovable Rock was about to do. Immovable Rock’s cast speed was extremely fast. The Sacred Fire was practically cast in an instant. White light radiated from the Backlight Cross. Then, the light seemed to leap across the void and disappeared. On the other side of the forest, a Sacred Fire suddenly burst forth in front of Lord Grim.

It missed!

Right when Lord Grim was about to take a step, he suddenly stopped, the Sacred Fire floating in front of him. Then, he gently circled around it and even took a glance at Immovable Rock.

Was I discovered?

Zhang Xinjie felt that it was a pity, but he wasn’t frustrated by it. Ambushes weren’t his specialty. What’s more, he was trying to ambush someone as experienced as Ye Xiu. Zhang Xinjie never placed all of his hopes on a single skill. The Sacred Fire missed? It was too bad, but it at least disrupted Lord Grim’s tempo.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms seized this opportunity to attack Lord Grim. As for Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust, he stepped to the side, stopping Su Mucheng’s attempt to move her Dancing Rain towards Lord Grim. A Launcher charging past a Striker was not a good idea.

The blossoming light swallowed Lord Grim. Suddenly, the forest seemed to quiet down.

What was missing?

Negative Nine Degrees’ gunshots!

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees had been chasing after Lord Grim, but the blossoming light blocked his view. For a moment, he couldn’t lock onto his target.

Not good!

The sudden pause made Zhang Xinjie realize that the situation wasn’t good. It had interrupted Tyranny’s tempo. Ye Xiu had most likely intentionally let his Lord Grim get swallowed by the blossoming light. He had unexpectedly used his opponent’s offensive as a cover. It was unadorned disdain towards Zhang Jiale.

Zhang Xinjie realized it as did Zhang Jiale. The blossoming light that he had sent over wasn’t a net, but a wall. If Ye Xiu continued to charge towards Dancing Rain, he would certainly suffer heavy damage. With Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust there, as well as a pincer from Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun, they could eliminate him in one go.

That was the best outcome, but Zhang Jiale didn’t think Ye Xiu was so stupid. But it turned out that Lord Grim really did walk right into it. In that instant, Zhang Jiale had been excited, but he soon realized that though Ye Xiu’s intrusion had been shallow. Lord Grim had walked into his Hundred Blossom style, but he didn’t continue moving through the wall.

He’s using me as cover!

Zhang Jiale and Zhang Xinjie reacted almost simultaneously. Zhang Jiale had Dazzling Hundred Blossoms hastily retract the light cover.

Not good! Not good at all!

Zhang Jiale had realized the problem, but his realization had been somewhat shallow. When he retracted the light cover, Zhang Xinjie immediately noticed an even deeper problem.

By borrowing the light as a cover, Ye Xiu had interrupted Qin Muyun’s offensive and Tyranny’s tempo. Then, when Zhang Jiale noticed the problem, he adjusted his Hundred Blossoms style. Didn’t that mean he had interrupted Tyranny’s tempo twice?

The interruptions had come one after the other. Although it was just for an instant, Qin Muyun and Zhang Jiale had stopped their attacks.

Ye Xiu had been looking for this instant!

Boom boom boom!

The sounds of cannonfire.

Sure enough, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain immediately seized this opening. She paved the way forward with her cannonfire. At the same time, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim charged fiercely at Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust.

Having won the title of Best Partners for three consecutive years, the coordination between the two didn’t need to be explained. There was only one final obstacle in their path, Han Wenqing. Team Tyranny’s captain, Han Wenqing.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

No one knew if Han Wenqing had a complete grasp of the situation like Zhang Xinjie did, but when he saw Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu form a pincer onto him, he immediately had Desert Dust activate Reinforced Iron Bones.

Then, he completely ignored Lord Grim.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Desert Dust attacked Dancing Rain, ignoring Lord Grim’s attacks from behind. With Reinforced Iron Bones activated, these attacks would not hinder his movements. Right now, he only had one target in his sights, Dancing Rain, who was heading straight towards him!

Boom boom boom!

Dancing Rain’s artillery shells exploded onto Desert Dust, but it didn’t even phase him. At this moment, everyone experienced the ferocity of a tiger that had rampaged through the battlefield for ten years.

The wind from his fists whistled by. Su Mucheng clearly hadn’t expected Han Wenqing to do this. It was too late for Dancing Rain to retreat. She could only do her best and face the Ferocious Tiger Flurry head-on.

Dodge? Not possible. She could only try to minimize the damage that she took.

A white light radiated from Desert Dust, who could ignore most attacks with Reinforced Iron Bones. The reason that he could bravely charge forward even if he didn’t have a grasp of the situation was because he trusted the person behind him. With him, not a drop of water would leak out. Anything he overlooked would be patched up.

Opportunity was only for an instant.

Ye Xiu had cleverly interrupted Qin Muyun’s and Zhang Jiale’s offensive, but in the end, he had been stopped by Han Wenqing.

Opportunity was fleeting. Negative Nine Degrees and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms started their offensive again. The two characters had rushed over to surround them.

Not only had Ye Xiu failed to rescue Su Mucheng, it looked like he was going to be trapped here too.

Good, it was just a false alarm…

Even Zhang Xinjie couldn’t help but let out a sigh of relief. But then, in that instant, a white light suddenly flashed from the depths of the forest.

White light!

A white light that Zhang Xinjie couldn’t be more familiar with!

Chi!

It was a gentle noise, but in that instant, Desert Dust became enshrouded in white flames.

Reinforced Iron Bones, so what? Ferocious Tiger Flurry, so what?

Sacred Fire!

The Cleric’s Sacred Fire. The skill that Han Wenqing’s most reliable partner was proficient at was now burning Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry was interrupted, and the Reinforced Iron Bones was dispelled.

Lord Grim stepped forward, Falling Flower Palm!

Boom! Desert Dust was sent flying. Lord Grim and Dancing Rain had finally convened. Negative Nine Degrees and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms were still firing at them, but the problem with long-ranged classes were that their control over the battle wasn’t enough. Trying to keep Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng there with just the two of them was too difficult, let alone when one of them had a giant shield…

Happy’s An Wenyi, a rookie Cleric and a fan of Zhang Xinjie, used what Zhang Xinjie was most proficient at to help rescue Happy from a crisis.

A pity!

Zhang Xinjie could only say that it was a pity.

He rarely made mistakes because he faced his mistakes. He wouldn’t get frustrated by his mistakes. It only made him work harder. Fights were always back and forth. Zhang Xinjie knew that it was not possible to have a 100% grasp in any situation.

Ye Xiu successfully convened with Su Mucheng, but the match was far from over! Who knew how many more back and forths there would be! The two had convened, but they hadn’t escaped, no?

The gunfire from the two Gunners continued to weave in and out. Desert Dust, who had been sent flying by a Falling Flower Palm, was on his way back. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder was actively drawing closer to the team, while being on the lookout for Fang Rui.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had broken through the small net, but a bigger net was coming their way.

An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands’ position was now known. Another sneaky move like that Sacred Fire wouldn’t be so easy.

Chapter 1509 - Falling Short

It had only been a short moment, yet all sorts of changes had taken place. The lesser skilled players might not even have been able to recognize what twists and turns had happened.

With help from the Sacred Fire from An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain were finally able to convene. It wasn’t over yet though. The two had established contact with each other, but it was far too early to say that they had escaped from Tyranny!

By this time, Desert Dust had recovered from the Sacred Fire. Again, he took the shortest path and ran towards the two at his fastest speed. In the meantime, the two Tyranny gunners weren’t stingy with their ammunition. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder was also moving towards the front to stop the two from leaving.

The situation looked to be advantageous for Tyranny, but this time, Zhang Xinjie didn’t dare let out a sigh of relief. Little Cold Hand’s save with the Sacred FIre had happened once, and it could happen again.

However, this time, Little Cold Hands was being watched with great attention, making hard for him to even find an opening to cast a heal. Under Zhang Xinjie’s instructions, the two Gunners were keeping an eye on him.

Happy had others though.

Fang Rui? Even if Lin Jingyan, who understood him inside and out, was on the lookout for him, it wasn’t enough to make them feel at ease. There was also Luo Ji’s Summoner, Concealed Light, who had yet to appear.

What is Concealed Light doing?

Finally, it wasn’t just Zhang Xinjie who was wondering, Pan Lin and Li Yibo had started to talk about this question as well. The broadcast also found an opportunity to switch to Luo Ji’s perspective.

Concealed Light was moving.

That was all the information they could get from this angle. For a moment, it was impossible to tell what he was planning. The broadcast could not put the focus on him entirely. After all, there was an intense battle taking place on the other side. Moreover, Luo Ji was a rookie at his first playoffs game. In reality, more people were worried rather than expectant of him.

In the end, the broadcast left a small window for Concealed Light, but not long afterwards, the scene in the small window changed.

Boundless Sea!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was put into the small window instead. The broadcast figured that Fang Rui’s actions were more likely to become a turning point for Happy.

Boundless Sea lowered his body, hiding amongst the underbrush as he moved. He moved slowly but resolutely. His line of sight was fixed ahead of him. He evidently had a clear plan in mind.

The camera focused on where Boundless Sea was looking at: Lord Grim and Dancing Rain.

Tyranny’s two Gunners were controlling these two’s movements brilliantly. Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style interfered with their vision, while Qin Muyun relied on his outstanding positioning skills to predict and seal off their most optimal retreat paths. The two attacked at a wide angle and moved accordingly. As a result, even though Lord Grim had a shield, he was unable to defend against simultaneous attacks from two sides.

“Healer, be careful!” Ye Xiu’s own situation was worrying, but he couldn’t help but warn An Wenyi.

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms formed a wide angle with Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees, while pushing closer to Little Cold Hands. He was no longer simply keeping watch onto him, but preparing to attack him.

Although An Wenyi lacked experienced, he never lost his cool or his ability to reason. He had been taking note of Zhang Jiale’s movements even before Ye Xiu gave a warning. But at this moment, even though Ye Xiu had pointed it out, he still didn’t move.

“What is he doing!!!” Many Happys fans were becoming dissatisfied. Even though An Wenyi had just performed a miraculous save, as a player who had always been deemed as Happy’s weak point, there were still many players who took particular note of him, worried that he would make a careless mistake on the stage. Ye Xiu had just warned him despite being in such a predicament, yet he still wasn’t going to move?

“What is An Wenyi doing? Is he so focused that he can’t see the tam chat? That shouldn’t be right? Could he be too nervous? Uh…” The more Pan Lin talked, the more he felt that he was wrong. Nervous? Did Happy’s rookies ever feel nervous?

Tang Rou, Bao Rongxing, Mo Fan, An Wenyi…

All of them were first-year rookies. There were times where their unfamiliarity with professional play hindered them, but nervousness?

Sometimes, it seemed like Happy’s rookies were tougher than even many experienced pro players.

An Wenyi wasn’t nervous, so why did he ignore Ye Xiu’s warning?

“Does he have other thoughts?” Li Yibo spoke up. Happy’s rookies couldn’t be viewed from common knowledge. Rookies from other teams wouldn’t hesitate to follow what their captain or senior instructed, but it was different for the players on Happy, who didn’t seem to know what nervous meant. Having their own thoughts and ideas during a match shouldn’t be anything strange, no?

More importantly, Ye Xiu’s message wasn’t an order, but a warning. How An Wenyi would respond depended on himself.

The camera switched over to An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was speeding up. The others on Tyranny had noticed this new target and started towards that direction as well. All of them were experienced seniors who had gone through hundreds of battles. This sort of tacit understanding between them was easy. They didn’t need anyone to remind them. After retaining this possibility, they just needed to confirm which target would be more advantageous for them.

Good!

Zhang Jiale felt that things were looking good His Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had entered his predicted range and started moving more carefully. It would be best to look as natural as possible to prevent his opponent from noticing him. Little Cold Hands didn’t make any troublesome movements, which made him feel gratified. Keeping a rookie in the dark about his motives wasn’t anything special. What was more rare was that Ye Xiu didn’t seem to have noticed either.

What a great opportunity! What should I do next? This situation probably could not be maintained for long. Ye Xiu would certainly notice it sooner or later.

Zhang Jiale had started to ponder as he moved. Finally, he took a crucial step towards Little Cold Hands.

But then, Little Cold Hands moved.

Right when Zhang Jiale thought he had succeeded, Little Cold Hands took a step, instantly making it so that Zhang Jiale’s plans fell one step short.

It was just one step. Most people probably hadn’t noticed it, and of the people who had, how many of them understood the implications of this single step?

“An Wenyi finally moved!” Pan Lin shouted. He hadn’t realized that the single step taken by Little Cold Hands was a step away from great danger.

This time, Li Yibo wasn’t caught unprepared because he had been paying close attention to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Tyranny as a whole. Just before Pan Lin cried out those words, he was about to say how Little Cold Hands was about to meet much misfortune. But with that single step, those words were caught in Li Yibo’s throat. What came afterwards was astonishment.

Was it a coincidence?

Or was it intentional?

If it was intentional, An Wenyi’s observational abilities were incredible. And he dared to do it at the final moment. Such confidence and gall was praiseworthy.

Sure enough, Happy’s rookies are all monsters! Even if An Wenyi’s technical skills were poor, he was outstanding in terms of his mental game.

Due to his shock, Li Yibo kep this in his heart. He forgot that he should also make some comments. As a result, the viewers outside didn’t know the significance of that one step. On stage, Zhang Jiale felt it the most.

Coincidence or intentional?

For a moment, Zhang Jiale had the same thoughts as Li Yibo. Next, he needed to test out this question. His Dazzling Hundred Blossoms took another step.

Little Cold Hands retreated another two steps.

It’s intentional! He wants to divert our attention!

The difference in one step was the difference between rational and irrational. If they focused their offensive onto Little Cold Hands, whether it was just himself or the entire team, the outcome would be much worse. It would be better to continue attacking Lord Grim and Dancing Rain.

But even if they continued attacking Lord Grim and Dancing Rain because of their slight adjustments to come here, they had sacrificed a bit of their offense as well.

Not good!

The new step that Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had taken to test Little Cold Hands hadn’t been a wise choice. He had been too eager to know the answer.

It was just a single step, yet because of it, a small opening had appeared in Tyranny’s encirclement on Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng.

Ye Xiu, were you waiting for this opportunity?

Sure enough, Zhang Jiale didn’t see incorrectly. Ye Xiu grasped this opening.

Boom boom boom!

Dancing Rain’s cannonfire came from under the cover of Lord Grim’s umbrella. In an instant, the two seized that tiny opening and rushed out. The only who could block them was Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder. But at this moment, the small screen on the broadcast focusing on Boundless Sea, showed movement. Boundless Sea locked onto Dark Thunder and rushed at him.

Lin Jingyan understood Fang Rui, how could Fang Rui not understand Lin Jingyan? Between them, the only way to deal with the other was to seize a strategic moment. And this time, Fang Rui had succeeded. In the end, he helped Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng escape, thoroughly destroying Tyranny’s encirclement.

The viewers were stunned. Even now, they didn’t know that the single step that An Wenyi had made at the final moment was the reason for all of these changes.

Falling short. Zhang Jiale felt extremely nauseous. He had felt this sort of defeat who knew how many times…

Chapter 1510 - Stubborn People Who Refuse to Change

“Small trick”

Two words popped up in Tyranny’s chat. Before Zhang Xinjie gave any orders, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust rushed out. His target was Little Cold Hands, not Lord Grim or Dancing Rain, who had just escaped.

In the end, Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie had been partners for many years. With this sudden change in circumstances, he reacted the fastest, grasping Zhang Xinjie’s thoughts before the words came out.

The formation shifted towards Little Cold Hands, who had been their back-up choice in case of an accident. Now that an accident had happened, Little Cold Hands was absolutely the better target compared to Lord Grim and Dancing Rain. Those two had broken through their encirclement and convened together with Fang Rui. If An Wenyi supported from the side as well, Happy could contend with Tyranny directly. On the other hand, An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands was separated from the other three.

Desert Dust took a big stride forward. It looked as if he were planning on attacking Little Cold Hands, but at the same time, he cut off contact between An Wenyi and the others on Happy.

Reliable!

He followed Zhang Xinjie’s reliable strategies. If this had been the old Tyranny, he would have chased after Lord Grim and Dancing Rain, fighting until his last breath; Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust would have certainly been at the forefront of the pursuit.

The others on Tyranny saw Zhang Xinjie’s orders and immediately reacted. They were slightly slower than Han Wenqing, but they weren’t too late. They immediately began coordinating with Han Wenqing.

An Wenyi immediately had Little Cold Hands retreat, but when Li Yibo saw this scene, he couldn’t help but sigh.

“What’s wrong, Coach Li?” Pan Lin asked. It was very rare for Li Yibo to express such clear emotions during the playoffs.

“He’s not experienced enough! In the end, An Wenyi is too inexperienced. He could have waited for a bit longer to see if Ye Xiu and the others could open up the situation and convene with him, but by running away, he’s pulling away from Ye Xiu and the others, making it more difficult for them to help him.” Li Yibo explained.

“Right!” Pan Lin thought about it and realized that Li Yibo was correct.

Tyranny’s Han Wenqing was fast, but surrounding Little Cold Hands in a short amount of time was impossible. Their intent was to set up an offensive towards Little Cold Hands, restricting Happy’s movements and seizing the initiative. By having Little Cold Hands immediately run away, An Wenyi was actually helping Tyranny. If they were able to completely separate An Wenyi from the rest of Happy, it wouldn’t just be taking the initiative, but taking the win.

How could Tyranny’s old generals miss such an opportunity?

Burst!

After conserving their energy for an entire season, if they didn’t burst forth facing such a key opportunity, when else would they?

Boom boom boom!

Explosions would always be the loudest sounds on the battlefield. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms went all out, not holding back on any of his attacks. A beautiful symphony of light and shadows was put on display.

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder immediately became more agile. He kept his distance from Lord Grim, Dancing Rain, and Boundless Sea, using Brawler skills like Provoke to harass them. Using a tiger’s mouth to unsheath the blade was a phrase that suited his actions perfectly.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees attacked Little Cold Hands the most directly. However, his offense wasn’t to block him but to urge him to move faster. Tyranny hoped to see Little Cold Hands run faster. The faster the better for Tyranny.

At this point, all of the viewers understood what Li Yibo had been talking about. The important healer had been cut off from the rest of his team and was in danger of being chased down and killed. This situation was far more dangerous than Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu being trapped.

“Why isn’t Ye Xiu reminding An Wenyi!” Pan Lin said anxiously.

“It’s too late!” Li Yibo sighed, “How could Tyranny leave an opening for Happy to rescue him? As soon as An Wenyi took the first misstep, his retreat path was blocked off by Tyranny. In the end, Tyranny’s players are too experienced.”

Experience!

It was the most valuable treasure that old players had, and it constantly shined in Team Tyranny. Their team had the three most experienced players in the Glory Alliance apart from Ye Xiu.

Run!

Right now, Little Cold Hands was just running. No one said anything in the Happy chat to stop him. His Little Cold Hands ran for his life. It was his only choice. However, this was exactly what Tyranny wanted. The faster he ran, the farther he ran, the easier it would be for Tyranny.

Finally, Little Cold Hands ran until Ye Xiu and the others could no longer see him. They weren’t able to maintain the distance between them because Tyranny had been attacking them the entire time. Lord Grim and Dancing Rain weren’t doing too well in terms of health after just narrowly escaping. Tyranny had a healer assisting them too, so there was no way for them to fight too forcefully. What’s more, under Zhang Xinjie’s adjustments, Tyranny didn’t become imbalanced from pursuing Little Cold Hands too excessively. As Little Cold Hands ran, Tyranny put less attention towards him. As Little Cold Hands gradually vanished from Happy’s view, Tyranny also began to stop chasing after him until only Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was the only one left in pursuit.

Han Wenqing versus a rookie healer…

On the other side, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui, who weren’t in the best conditions, had to fight against four players from Tyranny, among them a healer.

It’s over…

Li Yibo really wanted to say these words. If this were the regular season, he would have made the conclusion. However, this was the playoffs. There was mystery all around, and he didn’t dare hastily reach a verdict.

What else could happen?

Li Yibo carefully pondered over this question and thought of Happy’s Luo Ji.

The battle had reached this step already, yet Luo Ji still wasn’t going to make his appearance? He wasn’t sent to the stage just to watch on the sides, could he?

Wait!

A thought flashed through Li Yibo’s mind.

Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust chased after Little Cold Hands to kill him on his own. What if Luo Ji suddenly appeared to rescue Little Cold Hands? A Summoner with a Cleric’s help could easily bully an extremely close-range fighter like a Striker.

Uh… I think?

A question mark jumped out when Li Yibo thought this. Under normal circumstances, the Striker would definitely be the one bullied. However, if the Striker was Han Wenqing, the fierce tiger Han Wenqing… An Wenyi? Luo Ji? These two were still university students and newcomers to the pro scene. Would they be able to hold down a wild tiger?

I’ll just have to wait and see… Li Yibo shifted his gaze.

Even if the two took down Han Wenqing, they would have to go through much effort. What about the other end? Could Ye Xiu and the two others on Happy hold on against a strong offensive from four players on Tyranny? If the trade happened, the ones to lose out would probably be Happy!

As expected, there are no holes! Truly worthy of Zhang Xinjie.

Li Yibo’s final season at Tyranny was the year that Zhang Xinjie joined the Alliance. That season, Tyranny defeated Excellent Era, who was going for their fourth consecutive championship win, stopping their dominance over the Glory League.

Zhang Xinjie had left a deep impression on Li Yibo that season. He felt a bit ashamed though. At that time, the seniors had paid more attention to this junior’s robot-like lifestyle. Zhang Xinjie’s talent at Glory had been overlooked due to his peculiarities. It wasn’t until they won the championships with this healer, who never made mistakes, did they finally realize how incredible of a talent he was.

Separated by many years, Li Yibo looked at Zhang Xinjie again. Zhang Xinjie was more skilled and more experienced, but his style hadn’t changed one bit.

Everyone talked about Han Wenqing’s ten years of perseverance, but in reality, what never changed in Tyranny was Zhang Xinjie, no? It’d be easier to kill him than change his habits…

Two stubborn guys who refused to change had paired with each other despite their incompatibilities, yet they stubbornly persisted for so many years…

They had won a championship, but they didn’t start a new era of dominance. Perhaps this was where the issue lay. They made a few changes, but there were places where they never changed.

And now, one of them had finally made some adjustments. Even though much of it was out of helplessness due to the passing of time, it wasn’t a bad thing. The two core members of Tyranny, their sharpest spear and sturdiest shield, were finally fighting alongside each other together as one for the first time.

Win!

Li Yibo had always been a very very professional commentator. But at this moment, when he saw Tyranny realize the potential that they hadn’t been able to realize for many years, at the final moments of Han Wenqing’s career, he didn’t hesitate to stand by Tyranny. He could only hope that it hadn’t come too late. He hoped to see these two win another championship.

Go Tyranny!

Li Yibo cheered in his heart. He didn’t lose his rationale though. If he expressed such obvious bias during the broadcast, he would probably be laid off.

At this moment, the broadcast had finally cut to Luo Ji’s perspective.

Concealed Light had been moving the entire time. A small screen had followed along for quite some time now. From his position on the map, Li Yibo could confirm Luo Ji’s movements.

Concealed Light wasn’t moving to attack Han Wenqing. Instead, he was rushing over to the side of the battle with more people.

As expected!

Team Happy wasn’t stupid. Having Luo Ji ambush Han Wenqing definitely wasn’t a wise move. However, how much help could he provide to the other side? Tyranny’s side had a healer. Even if it was a 4v4, Happy would still be at a disadvantage. Perhaps Happy was regretting not putting Tang Rou in first? With her energy and drive, no matter if she attacked Desert Dust or joined the other battle, she would have a better chance at turning the situation around.

What could Luo Ji do?

Chapter 1511 - Starting at 13 Minutes 32 Seconds

Happy's Luo Ji had finally appeared on the battlefield after 13 minutes and 32 seconds. All of the viewers watching were having trouble processing it. By this point, most team competitions were at the halfway mark. The faster matches would almost be over. But in this match, one of Happy's players would only just be joining in on the fight at this time...

With one player missing the entire time, how had Happy survived up until now?

When the viewers looked at the time and thought about this question, they were put into a daze. The more attentive viewers couldn't help but think of Happy's first match against Blue Rain in the playoffs. In that team competition, hadn't Happy been hiding one of their players while fighting against Happy? Today's match and that's day's match were looking very similar!

How had Happy won that time?　　

When they searched through their memories to look for an idea, they suddenly remembered. Fuck, what win? Happy lost that team competition, relying on their lead in the group arena to barely win that round.　　

But today, Happy only had a one point lead from the group arena. If they just narrowly lost the team competition like that match, it would end in a draw. Happy's goal for this match couldn't possibly be a draw, right?　

They couldn't think of an answer, so they could only wait and see.

Devil World Flower!

Concealed Light's first summon was incredibly standard. He summoned a Devil World Flower to stabilize the battle.

Then, boom boom boom...

Smoke and fire pervaded the area, burning the Devil World Flower into ashes.

"Hahaha." The crowd burst into laughter. Gunners were the bane of the Devil World Flower. Their long-ranged attacks reached farther than the Devil World Flower could. Since the Devil World Flower couldn't move, it was basically a practice target for Gunners. In addition, the Devil World Flower took additional damage from light and fire elemental attacks. Gunner bullets naturally contained fire elemental properties, making it even easier for them to deal with Devil World Flowers.

As a result, when facing a team with Gunners, the usefulness of Devil World Flowers was very situational. Tyranny had two Gunners, yet Luo Ji's first thought was to summon a Devil World Flower. Before the flower could even bloom, the two Gunners shot it down.

Tyranny fans laughed wildly. This rookie, who had been hiding for 13 minutes and 32 seconds, looked ridiculous.

But soon afterwards, they stopped laughing.

The Devil World Flower wasn't able to display its crowd control, but in that instant, a gap had appeared in the two Gunners' offense.

It wasn't that Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun didn't know about this issue, but they had no choice. The placement of that Devil World Flower had been very tricky. If they hadn't eliminated it instantly, it would have interfered with Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder, creating a gap in Tyranny's offense.

In comparison, a Brawler's ability to control the field was stronger than theirs, which was why the two Gunners didn't hesitate to attack the Devil World Flower to minimize the opening created.

But no matter how small the opening was, there was still an opening. Only a few players could grasp such a small opening, and unfortunately for Tyranny, Ye Xiu happened to be one of them.　

Shining Cut!

A cold light flashed, and Lord Grim instantly covered a length of distance from his original position.　　

Brick!

Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder hurriedly threw a Brick towards the back of Lord Grim's head.　

Pa!

Suddenly, Boundless Sea cut across the field, leaping horizontally into the air, knocking the brick away.

This sort of move required not only precise inputs, but also accurate prediction. There perhaps might be no one but Fang Rui who could have accomplished this.

Boom boom boom!

The sound of cannonfire soon followed. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain fired her cannon as she moved, her target: Immovable Rock.

After Lord Grim used Shining Cut, he borrowed the trees as cover to avoid the gunfire from Tyranny's two Gunners. At this point, his next target was very obvious.

Immovable Rock.

Grasping this small opening, Happy didn't run away. Instead, they launched a fierce counterattack targeting Tyranny's healer.　

But Zhang Xinjie didn't feel pressured.

Happy's end goal was to retreat. By targeting Immovable Rock, they would force Tyranny to retreat to protect him.

But even if he knew what Happy's plans were, there was nothing he could do about it, because if he ignored them, Happy had the capability to kill him in one wave.

In that case, it would become a trade. Happy would kill him, but would suffer heavy damage from the rest of Tyranny. However, whether this trade was worth it, depended on how Han Wenqing handled An Wenyi.

Zhang Xinjie would always choose the most reliable path.　

"?"

A question mark appeared in the Tyranny chat. Zhang Xinjie wanted to know what Han Wenqing's situation was like.

"...."

The reply was a bunch of ellipses. These ellipses meant that Han Wenqing didn't have An Wenyi in his grasps yet.

Zhang Xinjie sighed. He could only give up on this trade. If he couldn't confirm the outcome of Han Wenqing's battle, An Wenyi might be able to rely on his familiarity with the terrain to run a circle around Han Wenqing, convening back with his team. In that case, Happy would have their healer, while Tyranny would have no healer.

Or perhaps... the corner of this map was a support zone. After Happy took him down and suffered heavy injuries as a result, they would sub in with their healthy sixth player and rescue Little Cold Hands. Then, with the help of a healer, facing an alone Han Wenqing...

All sorts of possibilities flew through Zhang Xinjie's mind. He wasn't sure which of these was Happy's true intent, but he knew that if Tyranny didn't make adjustments to protect him, the outcome would not be certain.　　

As a result, a new order came from Zhang Xinjie. His Immovable Rock would retreat, the two Gunners would suppress Lord Grim, while Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder would retreat as well.

As Zhang Xinjie expected, Fang Rui and Su Mucheng immediately went on the offensive, breaking past Lin Jingyan's defensive zone. The battles on both ends began shifting away from each other.

Everything had changed, starting from Luo Ji's Devil World Flower, the Devil World Flower that had been incinerated before it could even be fully summoned.

The changes hadn't stopped yet. Even though Zhang Xinjie pursued stability, he wouldn't just obediently comply with the opponents' intentions. At any moment, he would always look for the possibility of a victory by rushing the opponents.

The retreating Dark Thunder suddenly dashed forward!

Street Riot!

He unexpectedly used a high-level skill. Bricks, bottles, needles, all sorts of low-level Brawler skills began being thrown over.

His target, Lord Grim!

Although he let Fang Rui and Su Mucheng go, Zhang Xinjie wanted Ye Xiu to stay. When he saw that Happy wanted to attack him, he had asked Han Wenqing for his situation. It had taken some time for him to come to a decision.　

If he made the trade, the time used up here wasn't meaningless. But if he didn't make the trade, then Tyranny could take advantage of this time used up.

Because of the delay, Happy had continued their aggression, which meant they would continue moving deeper into the enemy fray to reach him.

The further in the target, the harder it was to retreat.

Fang Rui and Su Mucheng had been let go. But once Tyranny focused on Lord Grim, because he had ventured a bit deeper into their territory, trying to escape now would be much more difficult.

Happy could try to loop around and rescue him, but if they did that, Tyranny would still have the initiative. Ye Xiu, who was trapped, would be their bargaining chip.

You'd better not think of leaving!

Dark Thunder's Street Riot threw out a bunch of CC skills. Ye Xiu could not ignore it.

Shua! The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened. Ye Xiu wanted to use the shield to force his way past it.

Rumble!

A wave of energy split apart the air in front of him. Lord Grim was pushed back.

Implosion Grenade!　　

The instant Zhang Jiale saw Lord Grim open his umbrella, he tossed a grenade. Once the umbrella propped open, a dead angle would appear. Zhang Jiale recognized this point, and tossed the Implosion Grenade where Ye Xiu couldn't see it.

Ye Xiu wasn't able to force his way through. The others on Happy hastily went to his rescue.

An eagle flew past.　　

Concealed Light, who had only appeared on the battlefield after 13 minutes and 32 seconds, only now officially joined the battle. A Thunder Eagle was let out, firing a bold of lightning towards Dark Thunder.　

Bang bang bang bang....

Amidst the gunfire, the Thunder Eagle stuttered. Qin Muyun's Negative Nine Degrees struck the Thunder Eagle, stopping the eagle from moving in the air.

Godlike aim.

It was a stunning display.

Several Tyranny fans began shouting: Gunner King.

The Thunder Eagle had been stopped, but the Four Beast style Concealed Light had more than one summon at his disposal.

Spirit Cat. The nimble Spirit Cat suddenly scurried out from the grass.

Bang!

Floating Bullet. The Spirit Cat was knocked into the air. Then, a Grenade met with the Spirit Cat in the air. The shockwave from the explosion sent the Spirit Cat tumbling back to where it came from.　

The audience began laughing again.

Every move that Luo Ji made looked like a joke. Tyranny dealt with them easily with flashy moves.

But this time, their laughter halted even more abruptly than last time.

Lord Grim had broken through!

Happy's Su Mucheng and Fang Rui didn't even need to act. Just Luo Ji's two summons gave Ye Xiu enough of an opening to break through.

No matter how unskilled the viewers were, at this point, they had realized that Luo Ji wasn't as simple as they thought.

Retreat!

With Lord Grim out, Happy began retreating.　

Chase!

Tyranny went after them. They had no choice but to give chase because Han Wenqing's Desert Dust was chasing after An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands alone. They had to prevent Han Wenqing from getting surrounded by Happy.

"?"

Zhang Xinjie asked for the situation again.

Chapter 1512 - Terrifying Pressure and Precise Calculation

"..."

Ellipses. Han Wenqing's response was more ellipses.　　

He was only facing a Cleric. Against a Cleric without any outside support, if he could get close, killing the Cleric would only be a matter of time. But Han Wenqing's reply was unexpectedly the same as before: ellipses. This meant that even now, he wasn't able to close in on An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands?

Zhang Xinjie felt surprised. Everyone who understood the meaning behind these ellipses felt surprised. The broadcast immediately switched the focus to the battle over there.

Sure enough, Desert Dust was still chasing after Little Cold Hands.

Let alone Tyranny's players and the viewers watching them, even Han Wenqing himself was feeling surprised.　　

Healer classes moved slowly compared to other classes and didn't have any movement skills to help them move faster either. It was true that Strikers needed to get extremely close to their opponents before they could start attacking, but Strikers were naturally fast classes unlike healers. Along with a several movement skills, their movement should be much much faster than Clerics.

But he wasn't able to catch him!　　

Was it because Little Cold Hands was wearing equipment that buffed his movement speed?

Happy had used this sort of strategy before in the Challenger League. A fast Cleric restricted the opponents to a certain extent, but this match, Little Cold Hands was wearing his proper high-crit healing equipment. His movement speed was the same as a normal Cleric, slower than average.

Yet Han Wenqing's Desert Dust was just unable to chase him down. Although Han Wenqing was surprised, he knew the reason why.　　

Because of the terrain.

An Wenyin was extremely familiar with this residential area. In addition, the terrain wasn't flat. There were many buildings on top of the trees, some with two or three floors.　

Little Cold Hands wasn't fast, but he took advantage of the terrain, nimbly moving in and out.

At first, the audience had felt astonished that Han Wenqing wasn't able to catch up to Happy's weak point, their healer. But after the broadcast showed his pursuit of him, everyone felt that it was the opposite. Han Wenqing not being thrown off by An Wenyi and sticking so tightly to him was truly impressive feat!　　

It was indeed impressive.

However, the one who was shocked the most wasn't Han Wenqing, but An Wenyi. He thought that he had studied and practiced this area more than enough. Losing an opponent here shouldn't be hard at all, but it turned out that he was wrong.

Han Wenqing!

Even though An Wenyi admired Zhang Xinjie the most, as a Tyranny fan, how could he not respect Tyranny's captain, Han Wenqing? He had watched Tyranny for many years and was very familiar with the team. But after entering the pro scene, he quickly understood that the might he saw while sitting in front of the TV was very different from personally experiencing it for himself in a match.

The feeling of oppression that he got from Han Wenqing chasing after him made An Wenyi's palms sweat, but he didn't dare take a pause to wipe it away. Under this enormous pressure, the confidence that he had from his familiarity with the terrain was gradually being whittled away. An Wenyi didn't know how much longer he could endure. Han Wenqing had the time to respond to his team with ellipses, but for An Wenyi, the only thing that he had the time for was to keep running for his life. He had no time to do anything else. He didn't even dare to blink at this point. He needed to carefully carefully carefully and quickly quickly quickly make decisions.

To think he hasn't made a mistake yet!

Han Wenqing's astonishment towards An Wenyi gradually shifted from his familiarity with the map to his calmness under heavy pressure.

The public's evaluation wasn't wrong. Even if Happy's rookies didn't have the skill, their spirits were incomparable. A rookie was being chased so closely by him, yet the rookie was still able to keep a clear head, quickly and accurately making the right decision every time.　　

Han Wenqing couldn't help but think of another player, his partner for many years, Zhang Xinjie.

Although the two were partners, when Zhang Xinjie first joined Tyranny in season four, Han Wenqing's outlook towards him was as a senior player towards a new rookie. However, the Zhang Xinjie at that time was similar to this An Wenyi. No matter the situation, there was no sign of panic. Calm and careful were the characteristics of this rookie, becoming the sturdy shield for Team Tyranny.

An Wenyi's technical skills couldn't compare to the rookie Zhang Xinjie of that time, but his mentality and his willpower gave Han Wenqing a feeling of deja vu.

But he wasn't going to let up. Let alone a player similar to Zhang Xinjie, even if Zhang Xinjie had transferred to a different team and were in An Wenyi's position, he would still chase after him with everything he had. To him, that was the greatest respect he could give.

Chase!

Continue chasing!　　

After replying to Zhang Xinjie's inquiry, Han Wenqing wasn't swayed. He didn't feel embarrassed because he couldn't even catch a rookie. He wholeheartedly focused on this one goal. No matter what, he would chase down Little Cold Hands. 　

At this moment, Little Cold Hands suddenly moved horizontally.

Suddenly changing directions was a common method to escape from an opponent, but up until now, An Wenyi had never used such a method.

A sudden turn tested the opponent's reaction speed. If the opponent's reaction speed was fast enough and adjusted prompt enough, it also gave the opponent an opportunity to catch up.

That was why An Wenyi had never used this sort of risky method because he clearly knew his value as a healer in a team competition. No matter how poor his technical skill was or if he was the "weakness" of the team, as long as he was alive, he would be a huge threat.

As a result, An Wenyi had always been exceptionally cautious. But at this moment, he suddenly took a risk that he had never taken before.

Soaring Tiger!

Han Wenqing's Desert Dust immediately used a powerful skill, ferociously pouncing on him. The entire stadium erupted into cheers.

But it missed!

It was just by a bit, but the Soaring Tiger missed its mark. But when Han Wenqing chose this skill, he had thought of what came after. The Soaring Tiger missed, but he hit the tree. He crouched down and borrowed the tree to shoot forward!　

With this, Desert Dust's speed increased sharply, moving like a flying artillery shell. But An Wenyi seemed to have known as Little Cold Hands rolled to the side.

Desert Dust missed again, and this time, he could not immediately turn like before.

Thousand Ton Drop!

Han Wenqing could only use this skill to let Desert Dust fall faster. However, by leaping off the tree and then using this skill to fall, Desert Dust had moved a large distance. When he turned back to find his target, Little Cold Hands had widened the distance between them.

I fell for it!

Han Wenqing continued to give chase, while sighing helplessly.　　

He wasn't a brainy player who was proficient at planning. Although his opponent was a rookie, it looked like he was better at these sorts of schemes than him. An Wenyin once again took advantage of the terrain, calculating what Han Wenqing would do and then courageously took the risk to widen the distance between them. An Wenyi had been a fan of Tyranny before. He was familiar with Han Wenqing. And after becoming a pro player, this familiarity as a fan naturally became an understanding of an opponent. This time, he used what he knew about Han Wenqing to succeed.

The viewers and even Pan Lin and Li Yibo weren't thinking as much. However, compared to Han Wenqing, they knew more clearly why An Wenyi took such a risk. Happy had sent a message in the team chat. Ye Xiu had called for An Wenyi to convene with them.

Would they succeed?

When Ye Xiu sent out the call, everyone had been watching Desert Dust sticking closely to Little Cold Hands and let out a big question mark. But An Wenyi immediately completed a beautiful escape, dispelling their doubts.　　

But, good things don't last!

After having a specific direction to move towards, An Wenyi's escape choices weren't as flexible anymore. He needed to follow a general direction and make a decision.

As for Han Wenqing, he also received a message from Zhang Xinjie, telling Han Wenqing their coordinates and asking Han Wenqing for his coordinates.

With this, Han Wenqing was able to see through An Wenyi's intent.

Now that he knew An Wenyi's aim, he could make predictions. Han Wenqing was no longer chasing after An Wenyi brainlessly like before. Desert Dust's pursuit became more orderly. Sometimes, people felt like he wasn't chasing Little Cold Hands. Instead, it looked like he happened to be following the same route as him. And An Wenyi's attempts at feints gradually lose their effectiveness too.

I've been seen through!

Seeing Desert Dust getting closer step by step, An Wenyi suddenly realized where the issue lay. But at this point, it was too late to regret his previous actions.

Keeping running!

His best choice was to simply run as fast as he could. Tricks would only be a waste of time. Next, it would be a contest of speed. However, since his opponent was a Striker, how could he hope to outspeed him as a Cleric! An Wenyi could only hope that he could meet up with the rest of Happy before his opponent caught up to him.

So he sprinted!

He didn't spare his stamina, using everything he had to sprint as fast as he could. An Wenyi wanted to cover the greatest distance in the shortest amount of time.

But unfortunately, if he could do it, so could Han Wenqing. As long as he caught up to Little Cold Hands, Desert Dust wouldn't need stamina to finish him off.

Sprint, all-out sprint!

Han Wenqing's Desert Dust immediately sprinted after him. The distance between the two characters closed at a visible speed.

"He's caught up!!" Pan Lin shouted.

Launching Kick!

Desert Dust jumped and kicked. It hadn't been easy catching up to Little Cold Hands, so of course he wouldn't use a knockback skill to help push Little Cold Hands away. He used the Striker's knock-up skill. He wanted to send Little Cold Hands into the air and then slowly deal with him.

But...

Boom boom boom!　　

Three rounds of artillery shells exploded between Desert Dust and Little Cold Hands. Little Cold Hands wasn't hurt, but Desert Dust was blown back by the shockwave. A figure stepped out of the forest and then instantly reached Desert Dust's side, cold light flashing.

"When did you ever become so shameful, bullying a little kid like that?" A merciless message from Ye Xiu popped up in the chat.

Chapter 1513 - The Resolve of Both Sides

Team Happy and their healer had convened at an opportune time. The Happy fans let out a cheer, while the Tyranny fans let out a sigh of despair.

But what about after?

Tyranny’s fans quickly regained their composure, because it wasn’t like Happy had the advantage now. Happy had convened with An Wenyi, but Tyranny had convened with Han Wenqing as well. Previously, it had been Han Wenqing chasing down Happy’s healer; in the other battle, it had been Tyranny with a healer suppressing Happy without a healer.

Happy had the disadvantage in both of the battles. Now, they were on an equal playing field with Tyranny. However, with the disadvantage carried over from the previous battles, how would they win on an equal playing field?

Happy didn’t continue fighting. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim rushed out, and with help from his teammates, he sent Desert Dust flying away. Then, Happy immediately turned around to retreat.

Of course, Tyranny wasn’t going to let them go so easily. This was a perfect opportunity. When it came to direct confrontation, Tyranny had no fear.

No more hiding, no more holding back. In an instant, they transformed into the Tyranny that everyone was familiar with, and pounced fiercely onto the retreating Happy.

Happy didn’t fight back.

Trees, grass, houses…

Happy utilized what they could to hide and avoid Tyranny.

A team retreat had its advantages and disadvantages compared to an individual retreat.

The advantage was that they could help each other, opening up more varied options. The disadvantage was that a mistake from a single teammate could affect everyone.

“2, 11!”

A message suddenly appeared in the Tyranny chat. It wasn’t from Zhang Xinjie, but Lin Jingyan!

2, 11 pointed to the hour hand positions on a clock. When the others on Tyranny saw Lin Jingyan’s message, they immediately locked onto those two directions. The characters at the front of the team rushed towards those two directions.

Although Lin Jingyan wasn’t the shotcaller, there had to be a reason for him giving out these instructions.

Desert Dust turned towards the 2 o’clock direction, while Dazzling Hundred Blossoms turned towards the 11 o’clock direction.

The two soon locked onto their next target.

Boundless Sea!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

Lin Jingyan relied on his understanding of his teammate to grasp this opportunity. Han Wenqing and Zhang Jiale didn’t question him and immediately carried out his plan. Boundless Sea was now surrounded by the three of them.

Holy Trinity!

The three attacked without hesitation.

Lin Jingyan was too familiar with Fang Rui’s style. His dirty playstyle wasn’t something that everyone could keep up with, which was why on the team competition stage, Fang Rui would often wander off from the team on his own. Lin Jingyan understood this point and watched for such an occasion to take place. In one move, they surrounded Boundless Sea, and the rest of Happy could not rescue him immediately because he had separated himself from the team.

Rescue him now? Of course they could, but Boundless Sea was already surrounded. If they turned to rescue him, they would have to abandon their original plans to retreat. What’s more, whether they could quickly rescue Fang Rui was another question altogether. This was the danger of a team retreat. If you caught one player, you caught the entire team!

The three generals attacked Boundless Sea decisively.

However, Happy was even more decisive. Tyranny had focused three of their members onto Fang Rui, reducing the overall pressure on Happy. Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock was just a Cleric, his individual threat was limited. Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees was not enough to keep Happy’s other four members there.

As a result, Happy ran away!

They didn’t even stop to pause, decisively abandoning the trapped Fang Rui. They regarded their trapped ally not as a restriction but instead as an opening.

“How determined!” Li Yibo couldn’t help but shout. Happy’s insistence on running away was rather surprising. It wasn’t like abandoning a teammate was never done, but usually, the abandoned teammate would be used to trade for the initiative. Right now, Happy abandoning Fang Rui didn’t yield them any sort of initiative. All they got was an escape from an unfavorable situation. And then? Happy would lose Fang Rui and would still be in an unfavorable situation. If Tyranny simply employed a strategy where they traded blow for blow, Happy would suffer greatly.

After exclaiming in surprise at Happy’s resolve, Li Yibo adopted a critical view of Happy’s decision.

“But at the same time, there wasn’t much else they could do…” Yet after analyzing them, Li Yibo spoke in their defense, “A direct confrontation here would be too disadvantageous for Happy. By sacrificing a player, they gain time to reset the battle and formulate a new plan. If they can take advantage of their familiarity with the map, there will be more opportunities in the future.”

“Is that so?” Pan Lin was still doubtful, because the “more time” that Li Yibo mentioned Happy would gain didn’t seem like it was coming.

Fast!

That was the impression that everyone got.

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was killed incredibly fast. In the blink of an eye, Boundless Sea’s name turned gray.

Their speed came came from their resolve, Tyranny’s resolve!

After Happy abandoned Fang Rui to escape, Zhang Xinjie didn’t hesitate to order the entire team to focus all their efforts onto Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea!

He didn’t care about what Happy would do next, nor did he think about using this situation to make any future set-ups. Quickly kill Boundless Sea! Because a numbers advantage would always be the most reliable and trustworthy advantage on the Glory battlefield. If such an opportunity was presented in front of them, there was no need to hesitate!

A Qi Master wearing Cloth armor had low defense. Under Tyranny’s full focus and the watch of the many experienced players on Tyranny, Boundless Sea wasn’t even able to use defensive skills like Qi Guard that would let him survive just a bit longer. Boundless Sea’s health dropped to zero almost instantly.

Then, Tyranny immediately turned around and chased after the rest of Happy that could still clearly be seen. Pan Lin’s doubt came from this. How much time had Happy gained from Fang Rui’s sacrifice?

Li Yibo was also stunned. He didn’t think that Tyranny’s attacks would be so fierce to the extent that Fang Rui couldn’t even put up a struggle before being killed.

“Happy is in trouble!” Li Yibo immediately determined. At this distance, disappearing from Tyranny’s sights without a trace was impossible. In the end, Happy would not be able to avoid a direct confrontation, except this time, they would have one less player.

“Where is Happy running away towards!” Pan Lin pointed out.

“The support zone.” Li Yibo also saw it.

Starting from when Happy abandoned Fang Rui, their retreat direction had been extremely clear, the support zone. This was because their sixth player would come in from the closest support zone to them. Happy needed to hurry and meet up with their sixth player to maintain a five-member formation before making their next plans.

But now?

“They’ve switched directions!” Pan Lin shouted.

“Hm…” Li Yibo also saw them change directions. After confirming the speed of Tyranny’s pursuit, Happy turned away from the support zone. Tang Rou, who had been automatically loaded in, immediately saw Ye Xiu’s instructions in the team chat, telling her where to go.

“Happy needs to get as far away as possible from the support zone.” Li Yibo said, “They have no way of avoiding a confrontation with Tyranny. The close they are to the support zone, the more advantageous it is for Tyranny.”

“Yeah!” Pan Lin nodded his head. He didn’t need Li Yibo to give any further explanation. When one had a numbers advantage, trades were the most common and most reliable strategy. The closer they were to the support zone, Tyranny, who still had their sixth player, could quickly keep up their numbers advantage when one of their players was traded away. If the team fight took place far away though, then while Tyranny’s sixth player was rushing over, for a period of time, Happy would temporarily be back on equal footing with Tyranny, a 4v4. Statistically speaking, most turning points took place during this period of time in Glory team competitions. The disadvantaged team would often try to turn things around.

Tyranny was an experienced team, but Happy had Ye Xiu, who didn’t lose to them in terms of experience. From this adjustment, it could be seen that Happy hadn’t given up. They were going to put up a fight.

Tyranny was in close pursuit. Happy could not shrug them off, but they managed to convene with Tang Rou’s Soft Mist before the fight began. And the meeting point that they chose wasn’t simply the place as far away as possible from the support zone. Evidently, this was the place that Happy chose as their battlefield. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist didn’t join up with the team directly. Instead, she reached the location first and picked her spot.

Ambush!

Soft Mist was lying in wait for an ambush. The broadcast switched to her view, and it was obvious that was her plan. After seeing Tang Rou’s actions, Li Yibo concluded that Happy wanted to decide the match here.

The broadcast listed the health and mana on both sides. All of the characters had enough mana to last an entire fight. In terms of health, Happy had a clear disadvantage. When their characters lost health, they didn’t have time to replenish it. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had been running away the entire time. He didn’t even have an opportunity to cast an instant heal.

Happy wanted to decide the match here, but could they win?

No one looked at Happy’s chances favorably, even if Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was set up for an ambush. Zhang Xinjie was very cautious. Once he saw that Tang Rou’s Soft Mist wasn’t with the team, he would most likely be on his guard. With the amount of experience that Tyranny had, how effective would Tang Rou’s ambush be? What’s more, Tang Rou wasn’t the type of player who was good at ambushes. She’d probably be more effective standing in front of Tyranny and fighting them alone…

Ye Xiu and the others entered the area. Tyranny hadn’t been left behind. The broadcast focused onto Soft Mist, and the viewers did as well. Her ambush was the one thing that Tyranny was not aware of. Her ambush was probably Happy’s last hope!

Soft Mist slowly raised her spear.

Charge! Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Chapter 1514 - Favorable Terrain

Starting with a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky instead of a Dragon Breaks the Ranks was quite a surprise to the viewers. Those familiar with Tang Rou knew that she loved to initiate with Dragon Breaks the Ranks, and it would have been a very suitable move for her present situation, too.

But in the end, her spear turned into a roaring dragon as it flew towards Tyranny.

She had mixed up her usual starting move, but it was nothing too surprising for Tyranny. Tang Rou had loaded into the map awhile ago, yet there were still no signs of her. From the moment they stepped into this region, the entirety of their surroundings were within their sights.

The magic dragon tore into Tyranny’s formation, but not a single one of them was hit by it.

When using Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, the Battle Mage needed to maintain a certain distance away.

But would that be enough? Due to the long ending lag of the skill, with this skill missing, the counterattack wasn’t something that could be resolved through that bit of distance.

Zhang Xinjie was watching for Tang Rou’s next moves. At this point, the dragon was already dissipating. The Rising Dragon Soars the Sky was unable to show its might before being forcefully cancelled.

A cancel would result in ending lag as well. However, compared to using the skill to completion, the ending lag would be reduced by half.

“Careful!”

Tyranny’s two Gunners had begun firing at Soft Mist. Zhang Xinjie didn’t forget to warn his teammates. For Happy, relying on that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky would have been a bit overconfident. He doubted that Happy had placed their hopes onto that skill landing. The real assault would come during these next moments.

What will they do?

Zhang Xinjie quickly thought up several possibilities, and Soft Mist’s next moves were indeed within his expectations.

Shattering the Lands!

Soft Mist jumped into the air, swinging her spear heroically. Although the Rising Dragon had missed, it had disrupted Tyranny’s formation. In the end, that high-level skill was just a ruse. Her next move would disrupt their formation even further.

Soft Mist fell, and a burst of battle qi erupted.

The Shattering the Lands had been within Zhang Xinjie’s expectations, but Tyranny had no suitable way to deal with this powerful skill. Their only choices were to temporarily retreat or to face it head on!

Reinforced Iron Bones!

The two Fighters on Tyranny trembled. The Shattering the Lands sent out a burst of battle qi, sending branches and leaves flying into the air. When it struck the two Fighters, it made a loud bang. Their health plummeted. The power of a Level 75 skill wasn’t something that a low-level Defense buff like Reinforced Iron Bones could negate.

However, with the Super Armor, while the battle qi still inflicted damage onto them, it couldn’t push them in the slightest. Before the skill had come out, Desert Dust and Dark Thunder had already been charging towards her. The skill was unable to knock them over, and Soft Mist was now stuck in its ending lag. There was no way for her to dodge their pincer attack.

Two streaks of blood flew into the air. The whirlpool of battle qi created by Shattering the Lands instantly dispersed.

Had Soft Mist been struck down? When the audience took a closer look, they were dumbfounded. There were, inside the Shattering the Lands’ area of effect, not three players, but four…

What happened?

The audience felt dazed at the scene in front of them. The more experienced audience members immediately looked towards the big screen. Sure enough, a replay was being shown.

When Desert Dust and Dark Thunder attacked, Soft Mist was still stuck in her ending lag, unable to move. But at the final juncture, Lord Grim suddenly appeared in front of her. His two hands flickered up and down, resulting in two streaks of blood!

Blood from Desert Dust and Dark Thunder…

“Dual Blade Crescent Flow!!” The audience members who knew what was what immediately shouted the skill name out.

Dual Blade Crescent Flow was an Assassin skill that required dual blades. Against opponents who used attacks to parry, this was a perfect counter. For the user, it was a perfect complement to using attacks to parry. Team 301’s captain, Yang Cong, was proficient in this style. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had transformed into two blades, striking down Desert Dust and Dark Thunder simultaneously…

By the time the audience finished reflecting over and appreciating the play, the situation on the battlefield had already changed.

Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan weren’t intimidated by the Dual Blade Crescent Flow, but Lord Grim’s sudden interference had surprised them. And Ye Xiu had appeared at the perfect moment; the two weren’t able to make any adjustments in time. However, they quickly regained their composure and attacked again. Ye Xiu reacted faster, though. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed again, and a streak of black swept towards them.

Shadow Cloak!

Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan immediately saw and recognized the skill. Grabs were still effective against Super Armor.

Their only choice was to dodge.

The two had their characters avoid the Shadow Cloak, and these two experienced players wasted no movement. They dodged just outside of the Shadow Cloak’s range, their movements incomparably precise. Their timing had been perfect as well. Before the Shadow Cloak disappeared, the two were already stepping forward to counterattack.

“Slow down!”

A warning came from Zhang Xinjie, but it was too late…

Shua. The Shadow Cloak suddenly tightened, wrapping the two characters into a bundle. Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan were stunned. Had they misjudged it? No! The two were clear on this point.

Lord Grim took a step back. Although the two were bound by Shadow Cloak, with their Super Armor, he wouldn’t be able to send them away, so he simply retreated. With this retreat, Soft Mist could be seen. Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan suddenly understood.

A Battle Mage was a Mage class, and Shadow Cloak was a low-level skill, so she could learn it too. Lord Grim used the skill first, and then when Soft Mist could move again, she immediately followed suit with a Shadow Cloak of her own. The two Shadow Cloaks overlapped with each other, so how could they have distinguished between them? Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan had overlooked this possibility, and only took into account Lord Grim’s Shadow Cloak. Just when they thought they had avoided it, Soft Mist’s Shadow Cloak took its place.

The two hadn’t seen Soft Mist act, but Zhang Xinjie had noticed it. However, the warning had come too late.

It was just a brief exchange. Lord Grim and Soft Mist immediately retreated. Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun could reach them, but they couldn’t keep the two of them there. What’s more, Happy’s other team members weren’t just sitting there watching. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain stood to the side, providing support for Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

Chase!

Of course Tyranny had to give chase. Desert Dust and Dark Thunder quickly escaped the Shadow Cloak. Lord Grim and Soft Mist weren’t able to make a clean getaway with just that one skill. In the end, Soft Mist’s ambush had given the rest of Happy time to take their positions. But she herself, as well as Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim who had come to rescue her, were still within Tyranny’s attack range.

Tyranny pursued the two of them fiercely. The three others on Happy quickly occupied the high grounds. The houses in the residential area were scattered all over the forest in picturesque disorder.

Zhang Xinjie swept over their positions. The three characters on Happy had moved into the rooms on the trees and were standing by the windows. From the window openings, Dancing Rain was attacking, Little Cold Hands was healing, and Concealed Light was controlling his summons in an attempt to provide cover for Ye Xiu and Tang Rou.

No!

Not providing cover, but assisting them with their offense!

Zhang Xinjie saw their formation and immediately understood. Lord Grim and Soft Mist suddenly stopped. They turned back and rushed towards Desert Dust and Dark Thunder.

In the end, Tyranny had been baited by Happy. However, this couldn’t be considered a trap. Happy occupied a slightly more favorable position, allowing them to establish a more stable offensive formation. Ye Xiu and Tang Rou had timed their counterattack perfectly. With the stickiness of their close-ranged characters, it would probably be riskier for Tyranny to run away than take the fight.

It looks like we’ll be deciding the match here!

Ye Xiu truly wasn’t simple. Happy had been at a disadvantage for the entire period of their pursuit, but by the end of it, he had managed to create a slightly favorable position out of it.

But would that slight advantage be enough?

Happy was at a numbers disadvantage, and because of Tyranny’s pursuit, they weren’t able to stop to take a breather and heal themselves up. How could it be so easy for Happy to catch up to Tyranny’s lead?

Zhang Xinjie saw through Happy’s biggest weak spot and mercilessly set up arrangements to target it.

Attack!

Just attack.

Tyranny’s expertise was in attacking, and the most suitable target at the moment was Lord Grim!

The four focused their fire onto Lord Grim.

“So mean!” Ye Xiu typed into the chat. Lord Grim turned around and ran.

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t surprised. Ye Xiu had no reason to stand his ground here. He could see through Happy’s strategy. Ye Xiu’s and Tang Rou’s main responsibility was to keep Tyranny busy. The main damage dealers were the long-ranged classes on the treetops. This wasn’t a direct fight, but a war of attrition.

Unfortunately, Happy only had two players at the front, Ye Xiu and Tang Rou. If Tang Rou were Fang Rui instead, this situation would be even more favorable for Happy. Fang Rui’s dirty playstyle was exactly what was needed here. With Tang Rou’s playstyle, when she tried to restrict her opponents, she would usually restrict herself as well.

All of these points need to be utilized well!

Zhang Xinjie thought about what methods would be the most reliable and adjusted his plans accordingly. Tyranny suddenly turned their focus towards Soft Mist.

“You guys really think you can do as you please, huh!” Ye Xiu typed into chat as Lord Grim returned back.

“Push towards 1 o’clock!” Zhang Xinjie ordered.

Su Mucheng and the other two on Happy were in an extremely good position, avoiding practically all dead spots. However, even if they individually had no dead spots, they would have a few as a coordinated whole. The 1 o’clock direction was one such hole that Zhang Xinjie had noticed.

The entirety of Tyranny forced their way over. However, Tang Rou’s next moves thwarted Zhang Xinjie’s intentions. She jumped twice, leaping onto what could be considered the second floor in this area.

“Pincer.” Zhang Xinjie was unmoved. How could he overlook the different heights in this terrain. This change was within his expectations. The second floor? There was limited space there. Her options instantly became limited, making it easier to trap her. Tang Rou’s decision exposed her lack of experience. Ye Xiu evidently realized that the situation wasn’t good. Lord Grim hastily went over to rescue her, but with the simplicity of the second floor space, Tyranny was able to quickly complete their encirclement.

“Be careful of the long-ranged classes,” Zhang Xinjie reminded. Dancing Rain’s gunfire could reach her.

The two old generals that had rushed onto the second floor didn’t need his reminder. They could clearly see the circumstances, knowing where Happy’s main attack points were.

Boom boom boom! Under the cover of Dancing Rain’s artillery fire, Tang Rou wanted to escape. Soft Mist, Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Dodge!

This skill had to be avoided. Soft Mist rushed out, striking nothing but a tree.

Zhang Xinjie frowned. Dragon Breaks the Ranks couldn’t be blocked. She could break through from any direction, but the direction she chose seemed too stupid.

But the moment the Dragon Breaks the Ranks struck the tree, an enormous crash could be heard. The second floor on top of the tree suddenly collapsed.

Chapter 1515 - An Unbelievable Collapse

What happened?

Everyone was stunned. Countless people in the crowd stood up, looking around in a panic.

Dust and smoke was scattered all around the stage. The lifelike projections caused many people to misunderstand what had happened. They thought that the actual competition stage had collapsed. It wasn’t until the stadium broadcasted an explanation repeatedly that the panicked crowd came to a realization. When they looked carefully at the stage again, they saw that the stage was intact. What wasn’t intact were the scenes of the match displayed by the projection.

That beautiful fairy-tale like forest had been struck by an apocalypse.

Everything was destroyed. The buildings and walkways built on top of the trees lost their support and collapsed to the ground.

In the group arena, the audience had witnessed the inside of a manor being completely wrecked. However, in comparison to this scene, the level of shock was similar to the difference between an explosion from a grenade and an atomic bomb.

What happened?

Everyone was obviously curious, but soon afterwards, the people with better eyesight could see a figure moving inside this apocalyptic scene.

Who was it?

They couldn’t see the figure clearly. Luckily, the camera zoomed in figure and displayed it on the big screen for everyone to see.

Lord Grim!

Lord Grim was still moving. What else? Flames, the other end had flames! The camera focused on a different area. Dancing Rain, it was Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. Her surroundings were collapsing, but she stood there firmly, firing her gun.

Firing where?

The camera followed the path of her artillery shells and quickly found Tyranny’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. He wasn’t nearly as calm as Dancing Rain. He looked like he had come out from a disaster movie, bitterly seeking to survive. The artillery shells from Dancing Rain landed on him. Zhang Jiale hadn’t noticed the attack. He didn’t have the energy to.

Happy was still attacking!

A Satellite Beam descended from the sky, sweeping over Tyranny.

What else?

Concealed Light!

The audience found Concealed Light. He was the same as Dancing Rain. The collapsing surroundings simply served as a backdrop. It was as if he didn’t even see it. He calmly waved his staff, placing two symbols on the ground, controlling his summons.

Thunder Eagle!

Young Wyvern!

Summons with flight had a huge advantage in these situations. These two summons followed Luo Ji’s commands, unobstructed by the terrain. Their attacks… weren’t towards Tyranny. The fireballs and thunderbolts swept through the forest, exacerbating the collapse.

Could this apocalyptic scene have been created by this rookie, Luo Ji?

After realizing this point, everyone thought of the word, strategy.

Had all of this been a part of Happy’s strategy?

They couldn’t help but examine the outcome of this strategy. How should they examine it? By looking at the health on Tyranny’s characters!

A devastating sight.

Tyranny’s situation was too horrible to describe.

Tyranny originally held the advantage in health, but with one move, the sky and earth had reversed. All five characters on Tyranny had experienced a massive drop in health. What’s worse, it hadn’t ended yet, because Happy was still attacking them amidst this chaos. Happy’s assault was with rhythm and thought. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain led the way. Then, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, and the summons from Luo Ji’s Concealed Light joined in.

As for Tyranny?

Everyone was the same as Zhang Jiale. They had no way of making any decisions in this chaos. Even if they were old generals, none of them had ever experienced the the entire team trapped in a collapsing forest. They couldn’t make any contact with each other. Everyone was trapped in their own predicament. They tried to grasp their opponent’s attacks and counterattack, but the outcome was unsatisfactory. Happy held the initiative, utilizing this unbelievable collapse to thoroughly crush Tyranny.

Who died first didn’t matter. The names of Tyranny’s five characters turned gray one after the other. They had a sixth player, but did it matter? Happy had five and not a single one missing!

“Li… Coach Li…” When Pan Lin saw the fourth name on Tyranny turn gray, he came back to his senses. He and Li Yibo had been completely dumbstruck during this period of time, not uttering a single sound. No one in the broadcast team reminded them. Everyone was staring blankly at the scene in front of them.

“Ah… this… this…” Li Yibo regained his composure, but apart from saying “this”, he didn’t know what else to say.

Tyranny’s sixth player, Bai Yanfei’s Elementalist Rota, had entered the match, rushing towards the battlefield without any second thoughts. No matter the situation, Tyranny’s young heroes wouldn’t back down. But everyone knew that there was nothing he could do. Not even a miracle could save Tyranny at this point.

The match was over. What they needed to do was review this final astonishing scene.

What had happened?

Even though Pan Lin had called for Li Yibo, he ultimately didn’t ask this question. He knew that, let alone Li Yibo, no one in entire world had ever witnessed such a wide-scale collapse in a Glory competition before.

“This… I feel like… Happy had intentionally set it up?” Li Yibo guessed. Even though he didn’t dare believe that it was possible to set up such a frightening scene, seeing how Happy came out of it safe and sound, and then calmly and efficiently wiped out Tyranny, it could be seen that all of this was planned.

“How did they do it?” Pan Lin asked. In the end, he finally asked this question. Those were the only words going through his head right now. Apart from these words, he couldn’t think of anything else.

How did they do it?

Li Yibo laughed dryly. How could he know! But when he turned to look, he suddenly focused on a single character, Concealed Light.

Luo Ji, Concealed Light…

Concealed Light had joined the battle 13 minutes and 32 seconds after it had begun. What had he been doing before then?

Li Yibo realized something and hastily had the director find a replay from Concealed Light’s perspective.

Luo Ji, it really was Luo Ji!

He hadn’t joined the battle until 13 minutes and 32 seconds later. Apart from hiding together with his teammates at first, Concealed Light had been busy in this forest area the entire time. This calamity had been brought about by him.

“It’s Luo Ji…” Li Yibo said. This time, the broadcast displayed a replay of what Luo Ji’s Concealed Light had been busy doing at the beginning. “But don’t ask me how he did it. I don’t know either…”

Luo Ji was just one person. But he was a Summoner, so he could summon many servants to do his bidding. The scene shown in front of everyone seemed to be a busy construction site. All sorts of summons were fiercely attacking the surroundings under the Concealed Light’s orders.

“This… is he breaking apart all the parts supporting the buildings?” Pan Lin said.

“He broke them all? It’s clear that he needs to be able to time when the place collapses,” Li Yibo said.

“This…” Pan Lin wanted to how he did that, but this time, Li Yibo had been prepared. He had preemptively said “Don’t ask me, I don’t know.” In the end, Pan Lin’s “How did he do it?” became a sigh, because this could probably be answered by no one but Luo Ji himself.

“I really want to go to the post-match press conference now,” Li Yibo said.

This question would definitely be the highlight of the post-match press conference. The brilliance of the group arena and the other parts of the team competition had probably been forgotten by now. Everyone’s attention was on this question…

The match officially ended, and Happy won the team competition with a five point lead. When Bai Yanfei’s Rota died, the surroundings hadn’t entirely collapsed yet. There were a few places that were still shuddering. Apart from the astonishment at the turn of events, everyone was also in praise of Glory’s in-game mechanics.

It was over. Happy had won. For Happy’s fans, this was naturally something to be excited about. The Tyranny fans were silent. How could they be happy about such a defeat?

The two teams lined up on stage. After the six players on Tyranny came out from the player booths, they raised their heads to look at the big screen in the stadium because the highlights of the match would always be played during this time. How could they have forgotten about what had just happened? They needed to know the answer!

At the end, when the two teams lined up, the six players on Tyranny were all looking at Luo Ji, who was standing at the end. Ye Xiu? Su Mucheng? Fang Rui? No matter how big of a star, at this moment, they were nothing but air.

Finally, Ye Xiu let out a laugh, taking the initiative to shake Han Wenqing’s hand.

“You were probably scared out of your mind, no?” Ye Xiu said.

“Even you couldn’t have done that,” Han Wenqing said.

“Haha,” Ye Xiu laughed and didn’t explain. He shook Zhang Xinjie’s hand and asked: “You couldn’t figure it out either, right?”

Zhang Xinjie shook his head in honesty. Yes, even he only knew that Luo Ji had been the cause for everything. He didn’t know how he did it, and if someone asked him to do it, he wouldn’t have been able to do it either.

“Sorry for your loss,” Ye Xiu shook Zhang Jiale’s hands.

“Sorry for your loss, my ass,” Zhang Jiale cursed.

“What kind of people are your team members?” When it was his turn, Lin Jingyan spoke up first.

Chapter 1516 - Can Be Casually Accomplished

The match had been decided. But for a playoffs match, the stadium right now was almost too calm. Far too many people hadn’t even recovered from the shock yet. This was Happy’s stadium, Happy instantly reversing the situation to achieve such a massive victory was something that should have made them go wild, but because of this method, they were still processing what had just happened.

It wasn’t until the players of both sides completed the post-match exchange and began acknowledging the crowd that many people were roused from their trance.

They won!

They won. They had indeed won.

Ohhh!

Suddenly, cheers rose up. The passion of the audience had actually come so late.

Sitting in front of a television, Yu Wenzhou received a phone call. It was from Huang Shaotian, but after he picked up, all he heard was noise, clearly coming from the stadium. Huang Shaotian, like the rest of the audience, had been reviewing what had happened and only just now recovered.

“That was incredible!!!” Yu Wenzhou heard Huang Shaotian’s voice yelling from the other end.

“Haha,” Yu Wenzhou chuckled.

“How did they do it, huh?” Huang Shaotian continued to shout.

“Who knows?” Yu Wenzhou said.

Indeed! Who knew the answer to this question?

After greeting the crowd, the players of both teams left the stage and returned to the prep rooms. After a brief rest, they would begin the post-match press conference.

First up was the losing side, Tyranny. Captain Han Wenqing, Vice Captain Zhang Xinjie, and Zhang Jiale were the three representatives. As soon as they arrived, they saw the reporters all eager and anxious to ask their questions. Unsurprisingly, as soon as the conference officially began, the first reporter chosen to speak didn’t even bother with the typical sympathetic words for the losing team, instead directly asking what their views were of this match.

An extremely formulaic question, but for this match, everyone felt that this question was particularly weighty, and went straight to the point.

“Extremely unexpected,” Han Wenqing answered.

Just two words? The reporters were clearly unsatisfied.

“Could you elaborate?” someone requested.

“Happy’s plan in the team round was indeed unprecedented and surpassed all imagination. We had completely neglected this possibility.” An elaboration came from Tyranny’s vice captain Zhang Xinjie.

Even though he was known for his minimal error rate, it was impossible for him to never make an error, and he himself never claimed that title, nor was he ever ashamed to mention his own mistakes. He had categorized this team match as their “negligence,” but even if he defined it this way, most people probably wouldn’t agree with him. That scene shook and shocked the entire Glory world. Tyranny shouldn’t be blamed for failing to anticipate this possibility.

The reporters of course didn’t pursue this point. Immediately afterward, another reporter asked, “This loss, will it affect Tyranny’s upcoming match?”

“I don’t believe so.” Zhang Xinjie’s words were always that precise. “I believe that this kind of large-scale and accurate plan requires a large amount of preparation. Next match is our Tyranny’s home game.”

“Two matches.” This time it was Han Wenqing who added some words from the side.

Zhang Xinjie smiled. Han Wenqing’s “two matches” was equivalent to declaring that next match was Tyranny’s victory. This, of course, was what Zhang Xinjie expected and hoped for as well, but he wouldn’t say these kind of words without confirmation, and besides, he needed to correct Han Wenqing’s statement for the point he wanted to make.

“Next match is Tyranny’s home game, and in the case that we win…”

“Not ‘in the case,’ we’re winning for sure, okay? Next match and next next match, both of them.” This time, Zhang Jiale just mercilessly cut him off.

Zhang Xinjie was helpless, but the reporters were all looking at him, clearly still waiting for him to finish his thought. Zhang Xinjie didn’t bother to emphasize his “in the case,” and instead said, “If we advance to the third match, with the randomly chosen map, Happy still will not be equipped to deploy such a strategy again, so for the upcoming matches, we do not need to worry about facing a situation like today’s.”

To the side, Zhang Jiale curled his lip. Evidently he was still rather dissatisfied by Zhang Xinjie’s usage of “if” in referring to the third match.

Zhang Xinjie’s analysis was rational and rigorous. Based on this kind of analysis, everyone discovered that indeed, even though Happy had produced a frightening scene this round, all they accomplished was this one round’s victory. It had no strategic impact on the upcoming battles. As long as Tyranny adjusted their attitude and didn’t let this loss affect them too much psychologically, they would be fine.

And would this be difficult for Tyranny? They were all war veterans. With Zhang Xinjie’s analysis, this match was just an ordinary away game loss. How could it affect their morale?

Tyranny’s mood was extremely stable. As the background of the frightening events of this battle, they seemed to have completely adjusted their mood by the end of the match. They were already focused on the next match and even the next next match. Whatever Happy had managed to pull off this match, it wouldn’t weigh down their thoughts at all.

The press conference of the losing side didn’t give off the air of being lost or downtrodden at all. This was Tyranny. Nothing could stop them from lifting their chests and advancing forward.

Afterward, the three members who participated in the press conference returned to the prep room. Once everyone gathered their things, they could leave the stadium. The television screen in the prep room, however, was displaying Happy’s press conference. No one purposely tried to avoid it; they would occasionally glance over, wanting to hear what Happy was going to say.

For their press conference, Happy sent out Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, and Luo Ji, three people. It didn’t even need to be said who the star of today’s show was. As soon as the three of them walked out, the cameras flashed nonstop. Eighty percent of them were closeups of Luo Ji, who felt like he was going to go blind – he had certainly never experienced this sort of greeting before.

“Congratulations to Happy on a third straight victory.” Interviews with the winning side were always a bit more cheerful, carefree, and natural. In general, victorious teams were willing to talk a bit more, so reporters weren’t especially impatient.

“Continuing from last round where Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian suffered heavy injuries from cutting down a tree, Happy once again used a similar idea!” Of course the questioning began with this point.

“Haha, that was entirely different. Huang Shaotian did that to himself,” Ye Xiu said.

“Fuck!” Yu Wenzhou, who was watching the television, received more messages from Huang Shaotian, two in a row. First a curse, and then: I’m gonna kill that guy for sure, do you know any assassins you could introduce me to?

Yu Wenzhou smiled and ignored him. The live crowd had burst into laughter, and Yu Wenzhou could understand how embarrassed Huang Shaotian must be.

“So what happened today was something that Happy purposely set up?” a reporter continued to ask.

“Of course,” Ye Xiu said.

“Could you talk about how this was accomplished? You must have made extensive preparations in many aspects, right?” The reporter pulled out the question they cared about the most, and everyone’s gazes focused on Luo Ji.

But unexpectedly, Ye Xiu answered this question first. “It wasn’t necessary. Our player here has an exceptionally sensitive intuition for maps. After just one look, he can instantly figure out how to do it.”

“What?!” All of the reporters were dumbstruck. The press conference actually quieted down completely.

Luo Ji was sweating. Luo Ji was sweating waterfalls. Luo Ji was sweating Iguazu Falls.

They were actually just going to say this?!

A bit unsettled, Luo Ji snuck a glance at Ye Xiu, only to see a completely calm and honest expression.

After just one look he can instantly figure out how to do it? Since when did he have that kind of demonic ability? In order to accurately create this enormous destruction, he had used who knew how many kilograms of draft paper just for his miscellaneous scratch work alone. Guan Rongfei had supplied a large amount of data and calculations on all sorts of aspects of the in-game physics as well. This was a strategy that had been prepared for a very long time. To use it in the regular season would be too wasteful, so they had saved it for the crucial elimination stage of the playoffs, to deliver a hammering blow.

Before they had come to attend the press conference, Ye Xiu exhorted him to say this and that, but he had thought that Ye Xiu was kidding! But now, he saw how, facing the camera lenses of so many reporters, Ye Xiu was so relaxed and composed as he lied.

“You could just do it like that? What kind of power do you have?” When the reporters recovered, they instantly focused on Luo Ji again, and even addressed him with the formal “you.” Hearing this, Luo Ji became even more panicked. Of course, he could only say what he could, if he was wrong he was wrong, so he muddled through a story. “Uh, I was always pretty interested in Glory’s map things, so I guess I have a certain amount of experience, and some intuition, it’s probably just something like that.”

The reporters were too good at observing people. Ye Xiu was very calm, but this Luo Ji, he was still young, and seemed to be a bit panicked. But when they thought again, this was a rookie, suddenly being surrounded as though he were a star. It would be fairly normal for him to be a bit nervous. So this, this… was it the truth?

The reporters were wavering between belief and doubt. Watching the television, though, Yu Wenzhou was already laughing. How could such a thing be possible? As soon as you heard what he said, it was clearly something just to fool them! What kind of idiot would actually believe that?

In the away team prep room, Tyranny hadn’t yet left. When the conference reached this point, the prep room instantly quieted down. Song Qiying hurriedly made his way next to Zhang Xinjie. “Vice Captain, Senior Ye Xiu just said that they hadn’t prepared this beforehand, it was just an on-the-spot plan. Then, even in their away game, they might be able to do it again.”

“Idiot, how could you believe that. That guy Ye Xiu is purposely trying to make this a mystery.” Zhang Jiale immediately came over to teach Song Qiying.

“Is that so?” Song Qiying was at a loss. He continued to watch the television, and heard Luo Ji’s speech.

“Experience and intuition?” Song Qiying muttered, sneaking a glance at Zhang Jiale.

“Look at him, he was clearly taught to say that by Ye Xiu!” Zhang Jiale told Song Qiying.

Song Qiying didn’t say anything, and looked at Zhang Xinjie.

“That kind of experience and intuition, is there such a thing?” Zhang Xinjie was saying.

“Are you an idiot too?” Zhang Jiale was all sorts of speechless.

“We have severely insufficient data in this area. It may be necessary to re-evaluate,” said Zhang Xinjie.

Chapter 1517 - Next Round

The post-match interviews from Happy led to a heated debate. There were people who believed it, but there were many who didn’t. The reporters asked for the logic behind their reasoning, wanting to earnestly understand what they meant by experience and intuition of the terrain.

But Happy pushed all of their questions away, even those from Esport Home’s Chang Xian, who had a very close relationship with them. Happy stated: A great battle is imminent. As Happy’s secret weapon, Luo Ji does not have the leisure to play around. He needs to use his time to continue tempering his “experience and intuition of the terrain”.

“He wasn’t able to display his true strength last round. It was our home game after all. Next round will be the true test.” Ye Xiu told Chang Xian, who had come to him directly to talk.

“Are you serious?” Although Chang Xian had a good relationship with Happy and supported the team, he didn’t believe it personally.

It wasn’t just him. Anyone with a certain understanding of Glory would have their doubts. The ones who immediately gasped in surprise were noobs who didn’t have the skill to see it.

Chang Xian was a professional reporter who followed the Glory scene closely. His own individual skill at Glory might not be anything noteworthy, but his perception of the game could not compare to a normal player. After hearing Ye Xiu’s words, he looked left and right, confirming that there was no one else around. He lowered his voice and asked: “Is this psychological warfare?”

“Haha, yes, it’s psychological warfare,” Ye Xiu nodded his head and laughed.

Chang Xian wanted to cry. Ye Xiu told him yes, but he had said it half-heartedly. Was he supposed to believe it or not?

Sure enough, his miniscule skills were far from enough in front of this God!

“Then, I’ll just have to wait and see,” Chang Xian could only helplessly say some nonsense and leave with a laugh.

“Bye.” Ye Xiu said his goodbyes to Chang Xian before returning to Happy’s practice room. Everyone was there in front of their computers. The atmosphere in the room was quite casual.

The time between games in the playoffs was even more tight than the regular season. The teams had to rush back and forth between venues, which used up a good amount of their time on travel. As a result, a stable practice schedule between games such as in the regular season couldn’t be done in the playoffs. Most of their practice was to maintain their conditions.

If the regular season required consistency, then the playoffs required explosiveness. An explosiveness that used everything you had. The ones who could persist until the end would be the winners. The ones who relaxed would likely be the ones to fall in the playoffs.

Happy had won the first match of the second round. It was something to be happy about, but it was far too early to celebrate. It looked like everyone understood this point. Everyone was using their own methods to reflect on the outcome of the match in preparation for the next match.

“Did he leave?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu. She didn’t lower her voice, afraid of bothering the others. The current atmosphere was their usual daily one. If there was something someone wanted to say, then they could just say it. It wasn’t a practice session, where they needed to focus intensely on their playing.

“He left.”

“How did you say it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Luo Ji is a secret weapon, how can we let them interview him so easily.” Ye Xiu patted Luo Ji’s shoulders as he seaid.

Luo Ji’s body went soft. He turned his head with difficulty: “Isn’t that… not good?”

“Relax, it has nothing to do with you.” Ye Xiu laughed.

Luo Ji wanted to cry. What do you mean it has nothing to do with me? Right now, everyone in Glory was talking about him. Making one’s name after a single battle described this situation exactly. That night, his Four Beast Summon Style was no longer called that. People gave it another name “Building Demolition Style”. It looked like there were countless people who thought he was a demolition specialist who could instantly see through the terrain and destroy it.

Luo Ji obviously understood why Ye Xiu insisted on saying it like that. However, as a rookie, he was completely unprepared for this psychological warfare, which completely distorted the truth. Luo Ji discovered that the world was far scarier than he had imagined.

“It really has nothing to do with you,” Ye Xiu continued, “What comes next is something Tyranny has to worry about.”

“Is that so? Then, next match…”

“Of course you’ll be playing next match. Even if we don’t use the atomic bomb, just having it there is very intimidating.” Ye Xiu said.

Atomic bomb…

Luo Ji felt his body go soft again.

“Do you really think that it’ll scare Tyranny?” Chen Guo spoke up. After a match, she would scour the forums. From what she read, the more persuasive posters were saying that Ye Xiu was just making stuff up. Glory had an enormous playerbase, so there would naturally be many experts in the game. Many people were already pointing out what needed to be done. Chen Guo knew the truth, and felt like Ye Xiu’s psychological warfare was rather naive this time.

“Of course it won’t scare them.” Ye Xiu said,” Nothing can scare Tyranny, but it’ll leave a thorn in their hearts. Even if it’s just a teeny tiny advantage, we still have to take it.”

“Okay…” Chen Guo nodded her head and didn’t say anything more. To do everything they could meant taking those 1%, 0.1%, 0.01% chances. That was what Ye Xiu was saying. Ever since he started in the tenth server, he had always done this.

Team Tyranny.

After the match, they took a flight back to City Q and began preparations for their home game.

Similar to Happy, Tyranny wouldn’t do any strenuous training between playoff games. However, their vice-captain Zhang Xinjie didn’t seem to have a relaxed attitude right now. When Lin Jingyan went over to see what he was doing in the practice room, he saw that Zhang Xinjie was studying the Full Moon Forest map that Happy had chosen last round. His character was looking at the floor that Happy had completely collapsed, leading to Tyranny’s demise.

“Do you really believe him!” Lin Jingyan grabbed a chair and sat besides Zhang Xinjie. He watched him study the area as he asked.

“Not really.” Zhang Xinjie said.

Not really meant that there was some leeway. With Zhang Xinjie’s personality, he wanted to erase that final bit of leeway.

Lin Jingyan knew that he couldn’t stop him. It was just the way Zhang Xinjie was. It had its advantages, but it had its disadvantages. Ye Xiu was poking at this weak spot. His words might not be able to cheat others, but it would work on Zhang Xinjie. It wouldn’t trick Zhang Xinjie, but it would divert his attention away.

There were only three days away until the next match. Would Zhang Xinjie be able to clear away his doubts by then? It wasn’t that Lin Jingyan didn’t trust his teammate, but he really didn’t look favorably on Zhang Xinjie towards this issue. He had seen of the comments related to this topic and agreed with the commentary. Happy collapsing that entire area had nothing to do with experience or skill at Glory, but science…

Science… those words felt so distant to Lin Jingyan. He had worked hard in the pro scene for nine years and understood the scene well. Let alone science, most players of the game weren’t on the high-end of the spectrum in terms of knowledge. The number of competitive players with high educational backgrounds were rather limited. After all, the competitive scene emphasized youth. University graduates would be considered elderly when thrown with new players.

Zhang Xinjie… Zhang Xinjie may be called a Master Tactician with an intelligent mind, but in terms of academics, he was probably at a high school level, no? Last night, he had looked at some very detailed analysis. The poster had included higher-level math like differential equations. Just looking at it gave Lin Jingyan a nightmare.

“This, wouldn’t it be better to give it to the R&D department to look at?” Lin Jingyan advised.

“The R&D department is already looking into it,” Zhang Xinjie was Zhang Xinjie. He had already done what Lin Jingyan had thought of.

“Oh…” Lin Jingyan nodded his head, then… there was no then. The R&D department was already analyzing it, but Zhang Xinjie was still analyzing it himself too. That was it.

Lin Jingyan didn’t say anything more. He turned on the computer nearby.

The two playoffs team that had finished their matches were preparing for the next round. That night, it was the match between Tiny Herb and Samsara, which would be taking place in City B in Tiny Herb’s home stadium.

In the end, Samsara won their away game, beating Tiny Herb 11 to 7. Tiny Herb had lost their home game. It was a rather bad outlook for them. But it wasn’t outside of people’s expectations. The pre-match analysis had Samsara with a higher chance of winning, even if they were against the two-time champions, Tiny Herb. Before the match, the topic of “who would become the next Excellent Era and be the second team to win three championships?” After this round, the answer seemed to have already come.

It was as if this best of three was already over. Then, what about the other best of three?

Happy versus Tyranny. The second match came as scheduled. But looking at the online polls, Happy’s home game win didn’t increase Happy’s winning chances this round. In fact, it actually went down.

Because this match would be Tyranny’s home game. Even if you didn’t like Tyranny, no one thought that Tyranny would stumble because of their loss in the first game. Even if such an unprecedented reversal had happened last round, Tyranny’s heroes wouldn’t fall so easily.

City Q, Tyranny’s home stadium. The two teams lined up under the spotlight.

“How are things going? Have you found a way to win?” Ye Xiu provoked Tyranny.

“What do you think?” Han Wenqing wasn’t as wordy as Ye Xiu, but he never lost out in vigor.

“Little Zhang, good luck!” Ye Xiu called Zhang Xinjie, Little Zhang. There were only a few players in the Glory Alliance that had the qualifications to say that.

Zhang Xinjie chuckled. This sort of psychological attack would do nothing to him.

“You’re really boring.” Zhang Jiale talked back to Ye Xiu soon after.

“Not coming to Happy is actually the biggest mistake you’ve made in your career,” Ye Xiu said to Zhang Jiale.

“Fuck off,” Zhang Jiale cursed. Mistake was ear-piercing enough. There was even an “actually” in front. What did that mean?

Chapter 1518 - Normal People Chasing After the Footsteps of Geniuses

Tyranny’s home fans were unfriendly towards Happy and Ye Xiu in particular. Ye Xiu didn’t care though. After shaking hands with Tyranny’s players, he waved his hands towards the crowd, triggering a flood of boos. A few rather impulsive fans thought of their loss in the last round and immediately started throwing random objects at him. The security quickly put a stop to them and escorted them out.

“Hahaha,” Ye Xiu laughed, not in the least concerned. After greeting each other, the two teams went to their designated seats. But when they looked again, they saw that Ye Xiu hadn’t gone down. He was still standing there on the stage!

What’s the meaning of this?

He would be Happy’s first player for the group arena!

But the problem was that this wasn’t Happy’s home game, it was Tyranny’s, yet he stood there heroically. The Happy fans were quite excited seeing this scene, but the boos from the Tyranny fans quickly drowned them out.

Ye Xiu had come onto the stage, waved his hands to the crowd, and stayed on the stage. The match hadn’t even started yet, and boos had been thrown his way three times already.

“How capable!” Ye Xiu heard someone say from the side. He turned his head to see who it was. Lin Jingyan hadn’t gone down from the stage and stayed as well.

“Haha,” Ye Xiu laughed, “I can hear it. They’re booing you, booing your lack of creativity.”

As soon as he said those words, the boos suddenly turned into applause, turning into the background for Lin Jingyan, who had come over to talk to Ye Xiu. It became even more obvious who the booing was for and who the applause was for.

“Thank you, thank you for the applause,” Ye Xiu turned around and waved his hands enthusiastically to the crowd. Tyranny’s fans suddenly didn’t know what to do. It was really hard to grasp the timing for booing Ye Xiu and applauding Lin Jingyan.

Lin Jingyan didn’t know whether to laugh of cry. He wasn’t capable of doing something like this, but at the same time, he was secretly feeling a bit envious of Ye Xiu’s shamelessness.

In the end, Tyranny’s fans couldn’t endure it any longer. The applause turned into boos again, and Ye Xiu immediately acted like the boos weren’t for him. Lin Jingyan couldn’t help but laugh.

Don’t look at how this was hate not love. The two sides had quite the understanding of each other. When the day came that Ye Xiu no longer stood on the stage, Tyranny’s fans would probably miss these interactions. As for Ye Xiu? Was it because he knew that he would one day have to leave this stage that he teased Tyranny’s fans endlessly?

In reality, he probably wasn’t admiring Ye Xiu’s shamelessness, but his lively interactions with Glory fans.

As for himself?

He had a group of diehard fans rooting for him, but right now, were they looking at him?

Lin Jingyan actually became depressed for some time, up until Ye Xiu came over and called out to him: “So Tyranny sent you to kill yourself?”

“Hahaha,” Lin Jingyan laughed dryly. If Han Wenqing or Zhang Jiale were in his place, they would probably respond with “who knows who’ll be the one to die!” But not Lin Jingyan. From the very beginning, he was different from players like Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing, and Zhang Jiale. Those players were geniuses. It only took one look to know that they were destined to stand at the top of Glory. As for himself? Lin Jinyan knew that he wasn’t a genius of any kind. He was just one among the many who chased after the footsteps of those geniuses. Fortunately, he was able to get very close to these geniuses. Unfortunately, he was left behind despite his efforts, never able to reach the same heights as them.

Nothing could be done… because there was no rule saying that genius couldn’t work hard either. The genius in front of him put in no less effort than he had. Those geniuses never thought of giving others a chance to catch up.

“Being with you guys for so many years has truly been exhausting!” Lin Jingyan suddenly said.

“Hm?” Ye Xiu stared blankly at him. Lin Jingyan’s words had come out of nowhere. For a moment, he didn’t know how to react.

“It’s too bad. I also have goals that I won’t give up on!” Lin Jingyan said.

“Oh? You’re very spirited today!” Ye Xiu said.

“Yes, I’m going to win!” Lin Jingyan said.

“Let’s see you try,” Ye Xiu smiled.

“See you in game.”

“See you in game.”

The two shook hands and went to their respective player booths. The big screen in the stadium displayed the names of the two competitors.

Team Happy – Ye Xiu – Lord Grim.

Team Tyranny – Lin Jingyan – Dark Thunder.

When the time came, the referee confirmed that the players were ready, and the match officially went underway.

It was clear who would be playing first in the group arena. The next question was what type of map would Tyranny choose?

It’s… the Arena?

Everyone was taken aback.

Team Tyranny had unexpectedly chosen the most commonly picked 1v1 map for the all important playoffs stage, the Arena!

This map had the highest pick rate in the game because it was the smallest, simplest, and most direct…

This style fit Tyranny quite well, but maps weren’t chosen for the sake of simplicity. Picking the map was equivalent to giving the home team the initiative. The chosen map was the home team’s first attack towards the away team. It could affect the momentum of the entire match.

However, Tyranny had chosen the Arena. Picking this plain and simple map was the same as giving up their home team advantage. What’s more, Happy’s Ye Xiu liked this map. In the regular season, Happy would often this type of map in the individual competition. For Tyranny to choose this map, had a spy infiltrated the team?

“Coach Li, what’s the meaning behind choosing this map?” Pan Lin asked Li Yibo for his opinion.

“This map couldn’t have been chosen on the spur of the moment, especially with Zhang Xinjie planning Tyranny’s strategies. There must be a reason behind picking this map,” Li Yibo said. This time, Li Yibo wasn’t just trying to get out of saying anything meaningful. These were his actual thoughts. Unfortunately for him, Pan Lin misunderstood, thinking that Li Yibo was just joking around. As a result, he followed up with the usual “Okay, then let’s wait and see”, leaving Li Yibo hanging.

“I…” Li Yibo wanted to say something but hesitated because the match had begun. The Arena was as simple as a map could be. The setting was that there was no setting. As soon as the characters loaded in, there was no time for Li Yibo to make any introductions. The two characters chosen by Happy and Tyranny were already at the center of the map.

Lord Grim, Dark Thunder.

“This map… did you pick it just for me?” Ye Xiu asked in the chat.

Chapter 1519 - Unintelligent Lin Jingyan

“Yeah, I chose it for you,” Lin Jingyan replied. Dark Thunder, charge!

“Lin Jingyan has made the first the move!” Pan Lin immediately called out. He was a bit surprised. Up until now, no one had given any trouble to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim in direct combat. Tyranny choosing such a straightforward map was surprising enough. Lin Jingyan making the first move only added to that surprise.

“Could Tyranny have found a way to counter the Unspecialized Blitz?” Pan Lin continued.

But soon afterwards, Dark Thunder was sent flying away.

“This…” Pan Lin was dumbstruck. That didn’t look like someone who found a way to counter an unspecialized.

Lord Grim gave chase and began his counterattack. Pan Lin continued to commentate passionately, while Li Yibo remained silent.

He carefully watched the fight between Lin Jingyan and Ye Xiu. He was also wondering whether Tyranny had found a way to counter Ye Xiu’s unspecialized. After all, besides Ye Xiu, the most experienced players in the Glory Alliance were the players in Tyranny. The unspecialized playstyle required ample experience to support it. Perhaps the only players who could find a way to break it were the ones in Tyranny.

But in just three moves…

Dark Thunder only had a chance to attack three times before being sent flying by Lord Grim. Li Yibo didn’t see any signs of Lin Jingyan figuring out the unspecialized playstyle. Instead, all he felt from Lin Jingyan was that the fast unspecialized playstyle was rendering him helpless.

But…

When Ye Xiu counterattacked, the defense from Lin Jingyan was as tought as ever.

He didn’t run away or kite him. None of the dirtiness from his days with Fang Rui appeared either. Lin Jingyan looked as if he wanted to beat Ye Xiu in direct combat.

Competing against the opponent’s strength with one’s weakness seemed like he was letting his emotions affect his decisions know matter how it was spun. However, how could someone as experienced as Lin Jingyan make such a low-level mistake?

What is Tyranny planning? Li Yibo searched for an answer. Many people were searching for an answer.

Bang bang bang…

After another intense exchange, the two once again separated.

“So sharp?” Ye Xiu smiled.

“Yeah!” Lin Jingyan replied. Dark Thunder charged forward again!

Lin Jingyan was clearly losing. Dark Thunder had lost more than 20% of his health, while Lord Grim had lost less than 10% of his. However, Lin Jingyan didn’t make any adjustments. He kept doing the same as before and fought him directly even if it looked like there was no chance of him beating Ye Xiu this way.

Lord Grim dodged, turned around, and ran away…

“What!?”

Everyone was dumbfounded.

The way Ye Xiu was playing didn’t seem to have any problems, but right now, he seemed to be… running away!

Ye Xiu was running away from Lin Jingyan. Was Lin Jingyan’s way of fighting really that threatening?

Of course, to the normal players, Lin Jingyan would crush them. But when looking at a competitive match, it had to be looked at in terms of professional play. Even if you said that Lin Jingyan’s attacks were giving Ye Xiu trouble, the amount of trouble it was giving was very limited, no? From their last exchange, it was obvious that Ye Xiu had won that trade.

However, why would someone who had the advantage choose to run away and go on the defensive?

There was no time for everyone to think too much because Lin Jingyan had set his heart on his methods. Dark Thunder turned around and gave chase to Lord Grim, attacking again.

Lord Grim retreated another step, Dark Thunder advanced another step… Then, there was nowhere to run to. Lin Jingyan was an experienced general. He wasn’t going to let Ye Xiu run away as he pleased. He would think of some way to corner his opponent. If the terrain was richer in content, there would be more space and more options to choose from when escaping. But the Arena was a small map without any obstacles. The only way to run was by using one’s own movements. There was limited room to run, too. The Arena was only so big!

After running away twice, Ye Xiu was forced into a corner.

As a result, he counterattacked.

Cold light intertwined with the occasional sounds of clashing weapons. Dark Thunder’s weapon was the most common Brawler weapon, a Claw, which consisted of sharp blades. Blood would fly into the air every time the blades cut. Fast. The two were attacking and defending extremely fast. This was a contest of hand speed and reaction speed. The viewers could only watch the spectacle in awe. They couldn’t see what attacks they were using and whether it was effective. Their only choice was to look at their health bars to determine who was winning.

Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu was winning.

Lin Jingyan’s Brawler wasn’t a match for Ye Xiu’s unspecialized in direct combat. From this point, it seemed like it was obvious who would win the match.

However, Lin Jingyan didn’t retreat or give up. He persisted, insisting on using this sort of method to decide the winner.

Applause!

The crowd applauded.

Brawlers could fight close-range or long-range; they had CC and burst damage; they were an extremely versatile class. Fang Rui was Lin Jingyan’s most important and reliable partner for many years. To synergize with him, he had adjusted his playstyle, and that was during the later parts of his career. Before that, Lin Jingyan was an aggressive player who liked direct combat.

Demon Subduer!

Just hearing his former Brawler’s name, how did that sound like someone who sneaked around and used dirty tricks?

The Lin Jingyan of that time had been chasing after the footsteps of the geniuses. When fighting against them, Lin Jingyan didn’t want to show fear. Even if he lost, he would stand straight until he fell.

Now that he was thinking about it, he had fallen numerous times.

But he had never cowered!

Even when he had adjusted his playstyle to not be as aggressive, he had never cowered. He had ambitions too. For his dream to be the champion, he could give up on everything. To bring back the wild days as Demon Subduer, he could do that too!

Tiger Flips the Mountain!

Double Crescent!

Pain of Scars!

A bright red streak of blood blossomed into the air. As Lord Grim retreated, blood poured out from his right shoulder.

“Oh? Demon Subduer… it’s been a long time,” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you scared?” Lin Jingyan spoke as if he were Ye Xiu. Dark Thunder, charge!

The Demon Subduer here wasn’t referring to the one that Tang Hao was using in Team Wind Howl, but the three-hit Brawler combo that Lin Jingyan often used back in the day. It was precisely because of this three-hit combo that he included the name “three” in the the name Demon Subduer. His team saw this connection, and so the three-hit combo was named Demon Subduer as well.*(See TL note at the end of the chapter)

However, as Glory developed and levels increased, more skills became available. Lin Jingyan’s famous three-hit combo gradually became outdated. Nowadays, it was rarely used and couldn’t be considered a signature move. If his opponent wasn’t Ye Xiu and a younger generation player, they might not have recognized the three-hit combo from Dark Thunder.

“Haha, I was never scared. You know that,” Ye Xiu said. Lord Grim faced him again.

Lin Jingyan’s move had been sudden. Ye Xiu had been caught off guard. But if it was this skill, then even when Lin Jingyan had used it in the past, he indeed had never been afraid of it, let alone now when it had fallen behind the times.

“Take a look at it again!” Lin Jingyan called out.

“You still want to use it?” Ye Xiu disapproved.

“Get ready!” Lin Jingyan wasn’t going to use it again. He already knew that suddenly using this skill to catch him off guard might give him some benefit, but using this secret weapon again would be a joke. The reason it had become outdated was because it had no value anymore. He didn’t mind bluffing though.

“I’m ready. If you use it, I’ll beat you to death!” Ye Xiu said. On the other hand, he wasn’t bluffing. He was threatening him, and it was a real threat too. Nowadays, if Lin Jingyan used it, it would be considered an opening. Taking advantage of an opening to kill the opponent was the duty of a player.

Sure enough, Lin Jingyan didn’t use it again. The two continued to trade blows, and the applause continued. Lin Jingyan’s strategy was somewhat stupid. The current him could definitely play smarter. Perhaps by doing so, he would be able to contend with Ye Xiu to the end.

But this was Tyranny’s home stadium, an the ones supporting him were Tyranny’s fans. Lin Jingyan’s strategy might not be smart, but it was exactly what they wanted to see. People might say that playing smarter would give them a higher chance of winning, but sorry, Tyranny’s people loved to use this sort of brute force method to win. This was what the fans wanted and what they hoped their team could prove.

Team Tyranny was changing, and they couldn’t control it. However, Lin Jingyan’s fighting style right now was something they enjoyed from the bottom of their hearts. It was because of this that they liked Tyranny.

“GO!”

“Beat Ye Xiu!!”

Lin Jingyan didn’t hold the advantage, but Tyranny’s fans didn’t care. From their energy, it seemed as if Lin Jingyan was suppressing Ye Xiu.

“Can you see what Tyranny is trying to do?” Huang Shaotian, who had run to Tyranny’s stadium to watch the game, messaged Yu Wenzhou.

“They’re trying to wear him down,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

Wear down, Huang Shaotian was no stranger to this word. It was a rather painful phrase to him.

That was their strategy in their game against Happy: wear down Ye Xiu in the group arena. But it turned out that Ye Xiu wore down their energy instead.

Team Tyranny was doing the same strategy: wear down Ye Xiu.

It was just that their method was different. They chose the simplest map and simplest method to wear down Tyranny.

Wear him down with brute force.

Chapter 1520 - Unavoidable Exhaustion

Lin Jingyan fought like a hero and fell like a hero.

He had expected this outcome. Having chased after the footsteps of those geniuses for so many years, he knew that these geniuses weren’t like the lazy hare in The Tortoise and The Hare. They wouldn’t leave any room for others to surpass them.

“You can’t let me win once?” Lin Jingyan said jokingly.

“You’ve won before, no?” Ye Xiu replied, “Season four, Round 21.”

Lin Jingyan stared blankly for awhile before saying: “I lose to you even in memory.”

The first round of the group arena ended in 1 minute 48 seconds. Between two players with abundant experience, it could be considered an extremely fast battle. In the end, Ye Xiu won with a huge lead. Lord Grim had 63% of his health left.

When Lin Jingyan left the stage, the crowd didn’t hold back with the applause.

A loss was a loss, but Lin Jingyan’s attitude was what they wanted to see. Even though it might not have been the smart thing to do, Tyranny’s fans liked to see this sort of hot-blooded fervor from their heroes.

‘Go Tyranny!!” It was as if Tyranny was winning. Their fans seemed even more excited than Happy’s. Tyranny’s second player appeared on the big display: Zhang Jiale – Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Another old general from Tyranny.

Amidst the applause, Zhang Jiale walked towards the stage and met Lin Jingyan midway over.

“Nice job,” Zhang Jiale said.

“The rest is up to you,” Lin Jingyan said.

“Watch me take him down,” Zhang Jiale said. The two bumped fists, and Zhang Jiale walked onto the stage.

Soon, the second round began.

“Go die!!”

Zhang Jiale typed into the chat as soon as he loaded into the map. Then, his hundred blossoms bloomed. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms seemed to explode. The shimmering light spread throughout the Arena with him as the center.

Offense, another aggressive offense.

Just like Lin Jingyan, he went for direct attacks without any tricks. The wave of blossoms swept over Lord Grim. With this small Arena, there was practically nowhere to hide. Zhang Jiale’s strategy couldn’t be considered a group arena strategy. In the group arena, no one would be as wasteful as this because your opponent was never just one person. If you only cared about a win over the opponent in front of you, if you lost the group arena, then that win wouldn’t matter.

“Tyranny… are they planning on giving up on the group arena?” Pan Lin couldn’t help but blurt out.

Li Yibo furrowed his brows, unsure what to say.

Exhaustion. He had a grasp of Tyranny’s intentions. He wasn’t certain about it though, so he didn’t say out into the broadcast. But by the looks of it, if their intent was to exhaust Ye Xiu, wouldn’t the price be too large? The Spitfire was a mana-hungry class. With Zhang Jiale not caring about his mana and using everything he had to display his Hundred Blossoms style, even if Ye Xiu lost, how much mana would Dazzling Hundred Blossoms have left to deal with Happy’s next player?

Engulfed by the wave of light, Lord Grim’s figure turned blurry. For Ye Xiu, this was a difficult problem.

He was obviously aware of Tyranny’s intentions to exhaust him, but in this map, the other side didn’t care that Ye Xiu would notice because their arrangements were such that even if he knew, there was nothing he could do to avoid it. Unless Ye Xiu gave up on winning and let Lord Grim stand there for them to kill, in which case, that would be great too. Otherwise, in such a small map facing such experienced players, there was no way for him to kite around and relax.

Last round was like this, and this round would be the same.

Team Tyranny didn’t hide their intent. If you don’t go all out, then you’ll be killed instantly. If you go all out, then you will certainly expend quite a bit of energy. It was true that Tyranny’s side had old players too, but they were taking turns fighting Ye Xiu.

On Happy’s side, after listening to Fang Rui’s and Wei Chen’s analysis, Chen Guo suddenly became worried. But after thinking about it for a bit, she suddenly thought of something.

“In any case, Ye Xiu has taken down Lin Jingyan. We’re already in the lead! He can just do play casually and use up the other side’s mana. We’ll still be winning in that case!” Chen Guo said.

“Oh is that so? Boss, what a good plan,” Fang Rui said.

“Of course,” Chen Guo was delighted. But a second later, she discovered that Fang Rui’s reply had been somewhat sarcastic. The others on Happy didn’t think much of her “good plan”, did they?

“What’s wrong with it?” Chen Guo’s ideas were often demolished by Ye Xiu, so she was very self-conscious.

No one immediately replied. Everyone’s focus was on the match.

Ye Xiu didn’t retreat. Instead, he faced Zhang Jiale boldly just like in his fight with Lin Jingyan.

Everyone’s expression was solemn as they watched the match. Chen Guo didn’t keep asking what was wrong with her “good plan”. It was unlikely that Ye Xiu wouldn’t have thought of her plan, so there must be a reason why he wouldn’t choose to use it.

The battle was as intense as the previous round. Both sides knew each other well, and the intense, fast-paced battle didn’t lack caution either.

The entire stage was a chaotic mess of light. If last round, people couldn’t tell what each player was doing exactly, then this match, with Zhang Jiale’s all-out light blossoms, there was very little left of what they could see.

The only thing they could clearly see were their health bars. Fast. Their health bars were dropping very fast. The difference was that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was dropping steadily. He clearly wasn’t ever able to cleanly escape from the grasps of the Hundred Blossoms style. As for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? His health dropped intermittently. It was just that each drop in health was quite considerable.

Bite him to death!

Happy’s players and Happy’s fans were praying with all their might.

If Lord Grim could stick close to him, he might be able to interrupt Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s fierce assault. Then, in close combat, Spitfires would be at a huge disadvantage. In the regular season, Zhang Jiale had been burst to death this way.

But this time, it clearly wasn’t going to be so easy.

Zhang Jiale, who was going all out, had blocked off everything!

“Too crazy,” Huang Shaotian felt his heart tremble.

“With the way he’s playing, let alone the next player, if Lord Grim had started with over 70% of his health, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms might not even have had enough mana for this round alone,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

Zhang Jiale had let go of everything. His eyes had been set on Lord Grim, who hadn’t even started out with full health. Lord Grim had started with only 63% of his health left. His energy, his decision-making, and his attacks were all concentrated on that 63%.

Only by doing this could he give Ye Xiu the most pressure. It was only by doing this could he make it so that Ye Xiu would not be able to afford to relax.

This round could not be defined as simply as who won or lost. Tyranny’s strategy was being carried out in this forceful way. As for Ye Xiu? Since he couldn’t avoid getting exhausted, then he could only do his best to win as much of a lead as possible for Happy.

As for what the outcome would be, it wasn’t just this round that had to be looked at, but the entire match.

1 minute 24 seconds!

The battle between Ye Xiu and Zhang Jiale had been even faster than the battle with Lin Jingyan. In the end, the first to fall was Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. However, Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossom was useless as this point. He only had 9% of his health and 2% of his mana left.

Ye Xiu wasn’t able to complete a 1v2, but it was very close. When left the player booth, Happy’s fans applauded wildly.

This was Tyranny’s home stadium. Happy’s fans knew of Tyranny’s enmity with Ye Xiu. They had no way of suppressing Tyranny’s fans in their home stadium, so it was only by taking these openings could they show their support to Ye Xiu.

Unexpectedly, boos didn’t come immediately from Tyranny’s fans.

“This despicable guy has his decent moments!” Tyranny’s fans were in a discussion. Ye Xiu fought head-on against the aggression put out from Tyranny. It was what Tyranny’s fans liked to see. As a result, even if Ye Xiu was their mortal enemy, they hesitated.

“His playing today is pretty okay. Let’s boos a bit softer?” Someone suggested.

As a result, the boos still came, but they were light as a feather.

“What’s going on?” Ye Xiu wasn’t used to it. As he walked down from the stage, he saw that Tyranny’s fans weren’t putting in much effort to boo him like usual.

“Now you know what fear is!” Ye Xiu smirked as he said these words to the audience members nearest to him.

“Fuck!” The audience members heard him, and their boos immediately intensified. The reason was soon spread throughout the stadium.

“Fuck, and now he’s proud of himself!” Tyranny’s fan leader and Tyrannical Ambition’s guild leader, Jiang You, felt the urge to flip a table.

“BOO HIM! BOO HIM!” Jiang You roared.

The boos once again echoed loudly throughout the stadium. There were even some “KILL HIM!” shouts mixed in.

Ye Xiu was as calm as ever. Happy’s next player wasn’t affected by these sudden boos from Tyranny’s fans.

Happy’s next player was Mo Fan. He had already become an important chess piece in Happy’s group arena.

“Good luck,” Ye Xiu said as they passed each other.

Mo Fan didn’t stop. He simply nodded his head and kept walking.

Ye Xiu returned to his seat. The others looked at him.

“Almost a 1v2,” Ye Xiu grinned.

Chen Guo immediately noticed the weariness in Ye Xiu’s smile. He couldn’t hide his exhaustion.

Chen Guo had seen this appearance before. It was the same as when he had fought against Wind Howl’s Tang Hao.

And today, Ye Xiu had fought a fierce battle against two players back-to-back. His opponents, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale, were experienced players too. Since they came in with a purpose, they naturally knew how best to wear Ye Xiu down and make sure that Ye Xiu couldn’t avoid it.

The second round of the group arena ended. Ye Xiu left the stage. Tyranny had a practically useless Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, yet Chen Guo felt a bad premonition in her heart.

Chapter 1521 - One Step Away

The third round of the group arena soon began. On Happy’s side was Mo Fan and his Deception. On Tyranny’s side was Zhang Jiale and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. He had sacrificed much to win over Ye Xiu. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had nearly no health or mana left. He had almost no combat capabilities. This fight would end without any suspense.

Even so, Mo Fan played cautiously like he always did. When the round began, he didn’t hurry to approach his opponent.

However, with how small and simple the map was, even if he didn’t hurry over, what else could he do?

Chen Guo had been keeping up with the matches this season from up-close. She also had many Glory experts surrounding her, constantly giving her pointers. Her knowledge had improved day by day. Before the two had even begun fighting, she suddenly realized something.

Picking this map might not be favorable for Tyranny facing Ye Xiu’s unspecialized. However, this map would be used by every player participating in the group arena. Who else did Happy have besides Ye Xiu?

Chen Guo obviously knew what Happy’s lineup was for the group arena. After Mo Fan was Su Mucheng, then Fang Rui, and finally Tang Rou.

Mo Fan’s Fireworks Style required a lot of space to maneuver around in. As for Su Mucheng, the Launcher’s biggest strength was their ultra long range. And for Fang Rui, the more complicated the terrain, the more opportunities he had to display his dirtiness.

But the Arena…

There was nowhere to hide, and the map was small. Happy’s three players would suffer because this map would restrict their playstyles to a certain extent!

This was the complete reason behind Tyranny choosing the Arena. Force Ye Xiu into a an intense fight to exhaust him. And once Ye Xiu was gone, the Arena would become Tyranny’s advantage.

Zhang Jiale wasn’t able to survive for long and quickly left the stage. Tyranny’s third player was Qin Muyun.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees was a Sharpshooter. This map was slightly cramped for Sharpshooters, but Qin Muyun was an expert at picking spots. In a wide open space without any obstructions, movement became crucial for attack and defense. Although Qin Muyun’s class was restricted by this map, his exceptional talent at positioning was perfectly suited for this map.

The others on Happy watched the match with solemn expressions. They had realized this point earlier than Chen Guo had. It was because of this that Chen Guo’s plan wouldn’t work out. Because Happy’s next players would be restricted by this map, Ye Xiu could not afford to hold back. He had to do his utmost to win as big of a lead as possible for Happy to reduce the pressure on them.

Ye Xiu had done an outstanding job. He had faced Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale, two formidable opponents, and nearly completed a 1v2. Happy had a one player lead, but would it be enough to equalize the disadvantage that three of their players would face?

The fight between Mo Fan and Qi Muyun began. Mo Fan didn’t hurry to charge over, but Qin Muyun? Negative Nine Degrees raised his gun and began firing immediately. His attack range could cover the distance between their two spawn points.

The loud sounds of gunfire reverberated throughout the stadium. Mo Fan’s Deception moved nimbly about, trying to use his speed to get into Qin Muyun’s dead angles.

But what happened next gave everyone an even clearer understanding of Qin Muyun’s ability to pick spots.

The Arena was considered unfavorable for long-ranged classes, but nevertheless, Qin Muyun was still able to freely kite around.

Negative Nine Degrees wasn’t just standing there, he was also moving. Every step of his matched Deception’s. The distance between the two would sometimes decrease and sometimes increased, but after a few back and forths, it would always go back to what it was in the beginning.

In an open map like the Arena, it was a pure contest of who had better movement. And in this fight, it was obvious who was superior.

Mo Fan had succeeded many times in escaping from huge chaotic battlefields in the game. He naturally had extraordinary skill in that domain, but there was a huge difference between a huge chaotic battlefield and a 1v1. Mo Fan had been trained in an unorthodox way, while Qin Muyun had trained under standard professional procedures. His ability to pick spots was detailed and meticulous. His every action was backed by clear logical reasoning. Tens years of Glory innovation and improvement had produced this fighting method, and Qin Muyun was executing it perfectly.

Tyranny’s players weren’t just heroes who knew only how to fight fiercely. Qin Muyun, Song Qiying, the two talented rookies that had come from Tyranny, had the mark of their vice-captain, Zhang Xinjie: careful and meticulous.

Mo Fan was clearly losing in this contest of positioning. Compared to Qin Muyun’s precise positioning, Mo Fan’s positioning seemed right but was actually wrong. Oftentimes, he himself wouldn’t know why he took that step. It had come to him instinctively out of habit. This was the biggest flaw of someone who had been trained in an unorthodox way, and it could clearly be seen through Mo Fan.

Mo Fan quickly realized that he had no way of closing in on his opponent purely relying on his own movements. He could only try a few attacks. Ninjas had a few mid-ranged attacked, so when the distance between the two characters pulled a bit closer, Deception attacked.

Shuriken!

A Shuriken was thrown. It was the Ninja’s lowest-level ninja tool. It didn’t deal much damage, but it inflicted a brief stun. As a result, it was very useful for interrupting skills. However, Sharpshooter skills didn’t have cast times, so the Shuriken’s threat was rather limited against them. Mo Fan’s reason for choosing this skill wasn’t at random.

At this distance, even if the Shuriken hit, the brief stun wouldn’t be enough to give Mo Fan any sort of advantage, so it wouldn’t pose a problem for Qin Muyun if he didn’t have his Negative Nine Degrees dodge. Most people would make this judgement and ignore the Shuriken.

However, Glory was a game with very precise mechanics. The effects from a skill would vary depending on where it landed on the opponent. Mo Fan’s Deception threw this Shuriken, seeking this precise effect. His target was Negative Nine Degrees’ right wrist!

During combat, the arms would often be moving, so the chances of hitting the wrist was extremely low. But for Sharpshooters, their arms wouldn’t move nearly as much as Fighter classes who would be throwing out punches left and right. Mo Fan saw an opportunity and had Deception throw a Shuriken.

When a Shuriken hit the wrist, the stun effect wouldn’t affect the entire body, but the stun time would be longer. Sharpshooters used both their hands to fire their guns. A temporary stun on the wrist would be enough to create an opening for an attack.

His reasoning was sound, and even when he threw out the Shuriken, no one had seen through it. Throwing a Shuriken towards the body and throwing a Shuriken towards the wrist looked nearly identical. It was almost impossible to distinguish between the slight difference in angle. If Qin Muyun waited until after the Shuriken before realizing it, it would be too late for him to dodge.

Any ordinary person would not have been able to see through his calculations. When Deception suddenly attacked, Pan Lin got excited. But after shouting out the skill “Shuriken”, his voice suddenly went from loud to quiet. The final “-ken” syllable exposed his disappointment. He clearly recognized that the attack was meaningless. Qin Muyun could completely ignore it and have Negative Nine Degrees continue attacking to punish Deception for his misplay.

But to his surprise, Qin Muyun did not ignore it.

Negative Nine Degrees kept attacking, but he also took a step to dodge the Shuriken.

“Was that necessary?” Pan Lin was in a daze. Even though dodging it didn’t seem to take him much effort, this was a high-level confrontation. A wasted movement that seemed to not matter could be a sign of a deficiency in the details.

“Qin Muyun is being very cautious,” Li Yibo said. He hadn’t noticed the trouble that Shuriken would have caused Negative Nine Degrees either. He was right though. In reality, Qin Muyun hadn’t seen through Mo Fan’s plan either, but he chose to dodge anyways out of caution. Since it didn’t disrupt his tempo, he didn’t care about a possibly wasted movement, so he dodged.

A deficiency in the details?

Being hit by the Shuriken would have been a deficiency in the details! In comparison to getting hit by it, it would be better to take the initiative to react to it.

The Shuriken missed, and the dodge from Qin Muyun had been the right move. He didn’t give Mo Fan an opening.

Since his plan had failed, he could only force his way to Qin Muyun!

Deception moved to the side, ready to rush forward. However, this slight movement to the side drew a reaction from Qin Muyun as well.

Negative Nine Degrees took a step to the side, and from his new viewpoint, he could see Deception’s hands.

Hand seals!

Deception was forming hand seals. He had attempted to hide his intentions by that slight movement to the side. Qin Muyun hadn’t neglected this sort of Ninja trick. He had his Negative Nine Degrees follow along. He noticed the hand seals, but he couldn’t tell what ninjutsu Mo Fan was planning on using. In any case, getting away from his current position would not be wrong.

Negative Nine Degrees continued to move. His aim was to find a new spot, where he could maintain the same type of suppression onto Deception.

Negative Nine Degrees moved back, while Deception moved forward.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Mo Fan had wanted to use this skill to get close, but Qin Muyun had taken precautions. It was Mo Fan’s first time getting this close to his target, but he was off by just one step… just one step was enough for Qin Muyun to set up his wall again.

The fourth round of the group arena ended in Tyranny’s victory.

Chapter 1522 - Snowflake Firing Line

A crushing defeat.

Qin Muyun’s playstyle might not have been as hot-blooded or as tough as Tyranny’s fans would have liked, but winning with such dominance was still something that they enjoyed. Thunderous cheers greeted Mo Fan as he left his booth.

It wasn’t his first time fighting against Qin Muyun. Last time, it had been the group arena too. Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees only had 11% of his health left, yet it took Mo Fan’s Deception nearly half of his health to finish him off. It could be considered a loss for Mo Fan.

This time, the two started the fight at equal health, and in the end, Mo Fan suffered a crushing defeat.

31%.

Deception had only taken out 31% of Negative Nine Degrees’ health when he fell. Putting it nicely, you could call it one third of his health.

It was another loss against Qin Muyun. When he returned to his seat, hints of unhappiness could be seen in his usual poker face.

Su Mucheng, who could be considered as the person closest to him compared to everyone else on the team, patted his shoulders to console him. Mo Fan thought hard for a moment, but when he raised his head to say something, Su Mucheng was already gone.

“It’s my turn,” Su Mucheng called out to everyone before heading over to the stage. She was Happy’s next player in the group arena.

Mo Fan stared blankly. He had just been about to say something, but…

“Have you got any questions?” Mo Fan suddenly heard a voice from beside him. Mo Fan turned to look and saw Ye Xiu looking at him.

Mo Fan turned his head back. He seemed to be struggling whether he should speak or not. Ye Xiu didn’t say anything and simply waited patiently on the side.

“What should I do?’ Mo Fan didn’t turn to look at Ye Xiu, but he spoke up in the end.

“Learn from him,” Ye Xiu replied.

“And then I can beat him if I do that?”

“Don’t limit yourself to just the opponent. You have many opponents. The purpose of learning from him isn’t purely to beat him, but for you to improve, so you can win more,” Ye Xiu said. Qin Muyun could be considered a great wall for Mo Fan. The strengths that Qin Muyun had gained from going through Tyranny’s training camp were things that Mo Fan lacked. If Mo Fan could use what Qin Muyun had for himself, his individual prowess would improve considerably. Just take Qin Muyun’s talent at positioning and movement. If Mo Fan could take those for himself, his Fireworks style would certainly become more threatening.

Ye Xiu hoped that Mo Fan could understand this point, but Mo Fan was giving him the silent treatment again. Ye Xiu waited for a long time, but seeing that Mo Fan didn’t intend on speaking again, he didn’t pursue it.

“Give it a try!” Ye Xiu said before leaving. Mo Fan stared thoughtfully at the new round that was about to start.

The fifth round of the group arena would be Su Mucheng versus Qin Muyun, a battle between Gunners.

The match began with the crisp sounds of gunshots and the loud sounds of cannonfire. As soon as the two entered the map, they began attacking their opponent from afar without needing to move.

Launchers had a longer range than Sharpshooters, but it didn’t matter in the Arena. Sharpshooters had a fast and explosive firing speed, so the gunfire from Negative Nine Degrees seemed denser and more concentrated. Sparks instantly blossomed all around Dancing Rain. As for Negative Nine Degrees? Her first artillery shell had only just exploded. Even though the artillery shell dealt AoE damage, Negative Nine Degrees had already escaped cleanly from it, all while keeping up a continuous stream of attacks.

Unfavorable!

For Happy, this was not a favorable map for Su Mucheng. Negative Nine Degrees moved and attacked without pause. His attack and defense didn’t interfere with each other. Compared to Dancing Rain, his advantages were much more threatening. Qin Muyun even moved his Negative Nine Degrees closer to her. Launchers needed to play from a long range. But Sharpshooters? At close range, they had Gun Fu. Pushing closer to Su Mucheng would put pressure on her. In this map, she didn’t have any ways to pull apart the distance between them. The Sharpshooter’s Gun Fu might not be as sticky as other close ranged classes, but the amount of space it controlled was much greater.

What should she do?

Mo Fan had just been asking himself what he should do, and now he started to worry for Su Mucheng.

On the battlefield, a myriad of changes could happen in an instant. There was no time for her to wait patiently like Ye Xiu did when talking to Mo Fan. She needed to be decisive, and the answer she gave was: burst!

Dancing Rain’s attacks suddenly sped up several notches. The explosions from her bombardment instantly swallowed Negative Nine Degrees. Qin Muyun hastily had Negative Nine Degrees move away, but it was as if he had some sort of blinking target light on him. No matter what he did, Dancing Rain’s attacks followed Negative Nine Degrees closely, refusing to let go.

Firing line?!

Some people could see it. This was the burst from a Launcher’s firing line, but how could she do it at this distance? The firing line’s distance wasn’t limited by the player’s skill, but rather the slow attack speed of Launchers. At too close of a distance, Launcher had no way of linking their attacks together. However, right now, it seemed like Dancing Rain was planning on breaking apart this predetermined limit.

“Why would she do this?” Pan Lin was stunned. Li Yibo felt his head ache. He had a vague feeling that he needed time to think and organize his thoughts, but today, the group arena between Happy and Tyranny was moving at such a fast pace. By the time he finished organizing his thoughts, it would probably be the next round, no?

“Her distance isn’t fixed…” The pro players had more perceptive eyes. On Tyranny’s side, Zhang Xinjie figured out the reason. Some of the more minute details might skip over a normal viewer’s eyes, but not Zhang Xinjie.

“Su Mucheng is using burst skills for her first wave of attacks, borrowing the recoil to retreat. As she pulls away, she chooses skills that can link together to keep up a continuous offense.” As a Gunner, Zhang Jiale was extremely acute towards this area.

“It can be considered a cross-shaped firing line, where the horizontal axis can shift freely!” Lin Jingyan said.

“It’s not just that,” Zhang Jiale said.

“Yes…” Lin Jingyan could see it too, “If it was a cross, it wouldn’t be able to seal off Muyun’s movements…”

“It’s a variation using three overlapping firing lines,” Zhang Jiale said.

“Three overlapping lines… like a snowflake?” Lin Jingyan displayed his imaginative capabilites. (Think of: *)

Snowflake Firing Lline!

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were having a headache. In the meantime, Tyranny had given Su Mucheng’s technique a good name.

“The debate over whether Su Mucheng is a flower vase has reached an end,” Zhang Xinjie expressed. This sort of technique was a masterpiece born from a Laucher’s experience and intuition reaching the apex. It wasn’t something that anyone could use.

“Didn’t that debate come to an end a long time ago?” Zhang Jiale was puzzled. No one in the pro circle thought of Su Mucheng as just a pretty face.

“There has always been debate over it,” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Alright…” Zhang Jiale didn’t argue. He knew that this was Zhang Xinjie’s meticulousness at work. If you had to look at things from his view, it probably wasn’t possible for a debate to ever end.

“But… this match…” Lin Jingyan commented.

The match wouldn’t end just because of this. Su Mucheng’s performance was outstanding, but unfortunately, there was a limit to how far Dancing Rain could retreat. Her attack tempo should be be restricted soon.

“What if she goes again in reverse?” Zhang Jiale said. If Su Mucheng’s changing firing line could retreat, then it could advance. All she needed to do was do things in reverse order. But after seeing their situation, Zhang Jiale found an answer: “Muyun has realized it.”

Yes, Qin Muyun had noticed this possibility. His Negative Nine Degrees was being suppressed by the firing line, but his outstanding positioning negated much of the damage. He had avoided the attacks that would have interrupted his own offense. Qin Muyun was tenaciously continuing his attacks despite the suppression from the Launcher firing line. He kept up his pressure, waiting patiently for an opportunity. He had the same thoughts as the other Tyranny players. He was aware of the problems that Su Mucheng would encounter.

The end… for the Arena, that was the farthest distance away from where Su Mucheng had been at initially.

She’s almost there!

Qin Muyun watched Dancing Rain’s every step. Would she make any changes before then? Qin Muyun didn’t neglect this possibility. He made adjustments to prevent her from taking those options. Dancing Rain’s only choice was to keep retreating.

There!

Dancing Rain made her last step. Her offense stopped there. Next it should be Negative Nine Degrees’ turn to counterattack. Dancing Rain was cornered.

Boom boom boom…

Taking her final step, Dancing Rain gave one last burst. Su Mucheng clearly understood this point. At the last moment, she threw out everything she had.

“It’s her final attack,” Zhang Jiale sighed. Even though Su Mucheng was an opponent, he still felt sad about this one last burst.

“No!” This time, Lin Jingyan felt something was wrong.

“What is it?” Zhang Jiale had already relaxed. He wasn’t as focused, so he hadn’t caught it!

“Negative Nine Degrees doesn’t have enough health,” Han Wenqing, who hadn’t joined in on the discussion, said.

Everyone was stunned, including Qin Muyun.

Everyone had been paying close attention to Su Mucheng, Dancing Rain, her firing line, how many attacks she could make in this short amount of time.

She played beautifully, but the map was too small. The distance was too short. This was the limit of what she could do.

That was what everyone thought, and they couldn’t help but sigh. But everyone had neglected the fact that this limit was enough.

Because Negative Nine Degrees hadn’t been at full health to begin with. He had lost 31% of his health to Deception.

From 69% to 0%, Dancing Rain was able to finish off Negative Nine Degrees with her final wave of attacks.

“We were tricked. The firing line before hadn’t been her limit. She held back, so she could save up for this last final wave,” Lin Jingyan said.

“Don’t forget about her craftiness. She was Ye Xiu’s Best Partner, after all.” Han Wenqing noted.

Chapter 1523 - Two Second Kill

“In the end, Qin Muyun wasn’t able to defend against Su Mucheng’s fierce assault. Negative Nine Degrees has fallen, and the winner of this round is Su Mucheng!!!” Pan Lin announced the winner passionately, not knowing that Qin Muyun was in fact not far from winning.

If only I had realized it just a bit earlier, if only I had been ready for it… Qin Muyun felt upset as he walked down from the stage. Along the way down, he greeted Tyranny’s next player, their captain, Han Wenqing.

“Sorry…” When Qin Muyun was still a few steps away, he stopped to apologize to Han Wenqing.

‘Even we as spectators weren’t aware of Su Mucheng’s intentions. All of us underestimated her,” Han Wenqing said. He wasn’t consoling him, or finding an excuse for him. He was pushing the burden onto the entire team.

“Go back and get ready for the team competition!” Han Wenqing said and then continued onto the stage. Falling was nothing to fear as long as you immediately stood back up. Tyranny’s members needed this sort of backbone.

“Yes!” Qin Muyun nodded his head and returned to the team.

“Tyranny’s fourth player is their captain, Han Wenqing!!” Pan Lin shouted excitedly as the next round of the group arena began.

“How is Han…” Pan Lin wasn’t speaking slowly, but before he could even say four words, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust had rushed forward at an extremely fast speed. His clothing fluttered wildly as the wind flew past him. Desert Dust swung his fist, followed by an enormous explosion. Desert Dust had used his own fists to smash apart Dancing Rain’s artillery shell…

“Ferocious Tiger Flurry!” Pan Lin called out the skill name. Before this, he had wanted to say “How is Han Wenqing planning on facing Su Mucheng” to start the match, but before he could even say four words, Han Wenqing answered his question.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry! He started immediately with a Level 70 skill. Even the normal players knew that this was a very rash and very wrong move choice. But this was the playoffs, the highest stage in competitive Glory, and the “King of Fighting” Desert Dust chose to use such a move to start the match!

Why was it not recommended to use a high-level skill to initiate the fight?

Because even though high-level skills were powerful, if the skill missed, it would leave a huge opening for the opponent to take advantage of. As a result, low-level skills were often necessary as set-up for high-level skills. Players would use their high-level skills when they were certain that it would hit.

As a result, directly using a high-level skill was considered a rash move. However, when Han Wenqing, who had ten years of Glory experienced, used it, no one thought of it in that way.

What they saw a confidence.

Confidence that his skill would definitely hit.

The wind whistled like a tiger’s roar as the punch flew out. Desert Dust rushed straight for Dancing Rain, piercing directly through her artillery shell, and swung his fist. A hit!

Was there too little space in the group arena?

No, no matter how little room there was, it wasn’t to the point where the player could reach the opponent in just one step. Han Wenqing’s unconventional move had been completely outside of Su Mucheng’s expectations. While she was still sending out probing attacks, Han Wenqing bared his fangs and mercilessly pounced onto her.

It had been only two seconds since the start of the round. The King of Fighting, Desert Dust, had closed in on Dancing Rain, and Ferocious Tiger Flurry had landed…

In two seconds, Han Wenqing had killed the match.

“It’s… it’s over…” Pan Lin announced the end of the match, but he didn’t shout out the winner excitedly like he usually did. Instead, he just barely managed to squeeze out these few words.

How much health did Dancing Rain have left? How much mana did Dancing Rain have left? Pan Lin had planned on slowly going over this information, but it turned out that none of it was important. Right now, Dancing Rain’s health had turned to zero. The fight was already over.

Pan Lin didn’t know what to say. The pace of today’s group arena was far outside of his expectations. No fight had lasted more than 2 minutes.

Su Mucheng left the player booth. Her expression wasn’t lighthearted at all.

Ye Xiu had given Happy a nearly one player lead, but Mo Fan’s crushing defeat lost half of that lead. Su Mucheng finished off Qin Muyun quite cleanly, but as soon as Han Wenqing came onto the stage, he thoroughly wiped away Happy’s lead.

Happy and Tyranny both had two players remaining. Although Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust had just fought a round, he had lost a negligible amount of health.

After fulfilling their purpose of exhausting Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing personally pulled the group arena back to the starting line. Moreover, Happy’s next player would be restricted by the map.

Fang Rui. He had no terrain to utilize. Solely relying on technique, his dirty playstyle might have some effect on rookies, but against Han Wenqing…

Han Wenqing may not be as all-around as Ye Xiu, but the hardships he had gone through weren’t any less than Ye Xiu.

“My turn,” Fang Rui said. As he walked onto the stage, he passed by Su Mucheng. The two simply nodded their heads as greetings.

The fast-patched fights in today’s group arena made it so the players were constantly switching in and out. One player came onto the stage, and then before they could be satisfied, the next player came onto the stage.

The seventh round of the group arena, Fang Rui versus Han Wenqing, Qi Master Boundless Sea versus Striker Desert Dust.

It was a confrontation between two Fighters, but the playstyles of the players were complete opposites.

Fang Rui with his dirty tricks versus Han Wenqing with his aggressive attacks.

Tyranny’s fans obviously detested Fang Rui’s playstyle. To them, Fang Rui’s playstyle was heresy. In their eyes, this fight was to annihilate this heretic. The atmosphere in the stadium suddenly turned ablaze.

The match began. It was a simple map, and the characters quickly loaded in. As soon as the match began, Boundless Sea immediately rolled.

This was to prevent Han Wenqing from initiating the same way he did last time. But this time, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust didn’t move. Boundless Sea rolling away made him look like a startled mouse. The crowd burst into laughter. Compared to Desert Dust, who stood there straight as a javelin, Boundless Sea looked too hilarious.

Fang Rui didn’t care though. If Desert Dust wasn’t going to move, then he should continue moving. Boundless Sea spun round and round, rolling several times.

Desert Dust turned around, his gaze fixed onto Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui was feeling annoyed. This stupid map wasn’t suitable for his usual methods of attack, and just relying on his own movements to get into Han Wenqing’s dead angles was simply impossible.

Boundless Sea made a few turns, but not a single opening could be found on Desert Dust. Boundless Sea turned towards another direction. Suddenly, Desert Dust took a step.

The viewers didn’t think much of it, but this one step made Fang Rui feel extremely uncomfortable. The group arena was so small. A single step could change the amount of space a character grasped. Desert Dust’s step had been timed precisely, restricting the amount of space that Boundless Sea could move around in.

No matter how experienced Han Wenqing was, he shouldn’t have been able to find his weak point that fast.

“Old Lin, you sold me out!!!” A message suddenly popped up in the chat.

Everyone was stunned. Then, they realized that Old Lin was probably referring to Lin Jingyan.

Lin Jingyan understood Fang Rui well. Even if Fang Rui had changed classes, the person who understood Fang Rui the most was still Lin Jingyan. And Lin Jingyan’s understanding became Tyranny’s understanding. Right now, he wasn’t Fang Rui’s teammate, but his opponent.

Yes, opponent.

Fang Rui sounded as if he were in the right. It left everyone speechless. What’s more, Lin Jingyan was sitting on the sides. Had he been hoping for Lin Jingyan to reply back?

The crowd laughed heartlessly at Fang Rui, but then, Boundless Sea suddenly acted!

How despicable! How crafty!

Everyone gasped in surprise. Those words were actually just as a distraction. His sudden but reasonable words

Qi Bullet, Flash Burst!

Boundless Sea chained together two skills. The Qi Bullet in the front blocked Desert Dust’s line of sight. The Flash Burst was only the size of a finger, but the condensed qi would pierce through everything.

Desert Dust didn’t dodge. He unexpectedly stepped forward.

The Qi Bullet reached Desert Dust’s face. This skill didn’t deal that much damage, but with Fang Rui shooting it right at his eyes, how many people wouldn’t try to dodge it instinctively?

Han Wenqing didn’t!

Desert Dust didn’t shift in the slightest. He stepped straight forward at the shortest distance and at the fastest speed. The Qi Bullet exploded, and the Flash Burst arrived, but in the blink of an eye, the qi dispersed.

Boundless Sea’s right hand had been grabbed by Desert Dust.

Empty-Handed Blade Block!

Han Wenqing had unexpectedly used a Dismantle skill despite not being able to see and accurately grabbed Boundless Sea’s hand.

For Fighters, their hands were their weapons. Gloves and claws were worn on the hand.

Dismantle, a block and then a grab. It was enforced by the system. If the block succeeded, the grab would be guaranteed as a follow up.

Desert Dust elbowed Boundless Sea’s chest and then followed with a flurry of punches and kicks.

Both were Fighter classes, but Qi Masters couldn’t compare to Strikers at close range.

Boundless Sea covered his head, trying to scurry away. He whirled and spun around, rolling and flipping. The crowd laughed loudly. Just when they were having fun, Desert Dust’s offense suddenly stopped. Boundless Sea had actually escaped from the combo.

This…

Everyone was dumbfounded.

They hadn’t noticed any openings in Desert Dust’s combo, but all of a sudden, Boundless Sea seemed to have pushed him away, interrupting Desert Dust’s combo.

“Being oppressed like that isn’t carefree at all,” Fang Rui typed in the chat.

Carefree? The crowd laughed. That word didn’t seem to have any relationship with someone as dirty as you, no?

Chapter 1524 - Referee Decision

Desert Dust was in the middle of throwing out a punch, when Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea escaped.

Desert Dust retracted his fists and turned around. His unchanging expression had nothing to do with Han Wenqing’s state of mind, although at the moment, Han Wenqing’s expression was as heavy as his character’s…

Many people might not have found any problems with his previous punch, but Han Wenqing knew clearer than anyone else that his punch had been too slow.

This wasn’t a mistake. Han Wenqing knew that his punch needed to chain together faster, but there was nothing he could do. Perhaps if it were five or ten years ago, that punch would have been unavoidable and would have definitely hit his opponent, but now…

Some things couldn’t be accomplished with just effort. For the current him, it was truly difficult to keep up such a fast pace. When he slowed down just a tiny bit, an opening appeared, and Fang Rui immediately grasped it.

What fast reactions…

Han Wenqing sighed. Even if he refused to give up, he couldn’t help but feel how he was past his prime.

He was past his prime, but he didn’t hesitate.

Desert Dust turned around, facing Boundless Sea. Han Wenqing was already preparing for his next wave of attacks.

It hadn’t been easy for Fang Rui to get Boundless Sea to escape. He didn’t dare provoke Han Wenqing so easily anymore. Boundless Sea swayed left and right, drawing in his opponent’s attention, waiting for an opportunity.

But Desert Dust unexpectedly stepped back.

Everyone was shocked.

If Desert Dust had charged forward, even if it was at a bad timing, no one would have been surprised because that was Han Wenqing. Going against the flow, daring to face the dangers, he had done it far too many times.

But he retreated…

Fang Rui hadn’t shown any attempts at an attack, yet he chose to retreat. Perhaps Han Wenqing had realized something. However, retreat had never been a part of Han Wenqing’s toolkit.

But Boundless Sea’s swaying suddenly stopped as well.

What’s going on? Everyone felt like the pace of this match had suddenly turned strange. And the only ones who understood what was going on were the skilled experts.

“To think things would go this way. How boring,” Ye Xiu mumbled.

“What do you mean?” Chen Guo asked. She needed an explanation.

“Fang Rui’s purpose in having Boundless Sea sway left and right was to repeatedly display his intentions to attack. In a high-level confrontation, you have to determine what options are available depending on how the opponent moves. Although Fang Rui’s movements look simple, if they go on for awhile, it’s very exhausting for Han Wenqing,” Ye Xiu explained.

“So you’re saying, Fang Rui was planning on wearing out Han Wenqing?” Chen Guo said.

“Yes,” Ye Xiu nodded his head, “But he probably didn’t think that he could just sway his way to victory. With Han Wenqing’s personality, once Han Wenqing saw through his intentions, he thought that Han Wenqing would try to break through it by force. He was baiting Han Wenqing to continue with his fast-paced offense, but it looks like Han Wenqing simply decided not to take it and retreated.”

“So what if he retreats?” Chen Guo asked.

“By retreating, he widens his vision and opens up more space between them. That way, he can observe Boundless Sea’s movements from a more general perspective, which requires less of his attention,” Ye Xiu said.

“Oh… then why not just have Boundless Sea move forward and keep swaying?” Chen Guo said.

“Then all he needs to do is keep retreating. It’s not like he’ll be forced into a corner. Fang Rui’s move has no value anymore. Insisting on it isn’t stylish at all,” Ye Xiu said, but when he looked back to the stage, “Well, it looks like I underestimated his shamelessness.”

Stylish?

How could the master of playing dirty care about something like style?

Fang Rui didn’t hesitate to do something unstylish. It was just like Chen Guo said. Boundless Sea pressed forward and continued to sway left and right, baring his claws like a crab.

Just as Ye Xiu said, Han Wenqing simply continued to retreat.

The viewers who understood what was going on looked at Fang Rui disdainfully for being so boring. The viewers who didn’t understand were confused. Could Boundless Sea’s swaying be the start of some sort of trump card? Something threatening enough to force Han Wenqing to retreat?

One side advanced, while the other side retreated. Desert Dust moved along an arc to make sure that he wouldn’t be pushed to the edges of the map. The two continued like this, and not long afterwards, they had went around half the map.

“He’s really become patient!” Ye Xiu sighed. If this was the Han Wenqing of the past, Desert Dust would have certainly charged over to punch his opponent by now.

“What’s going to happen if they keep going round and round in circles?” Chen Guo asked.

“The referee will intervene,” Ye Xiu said.

“Fang Rui’s not planning on continuing until the referee makes his move, is he?” Chen Guo said speechlessly. She understood why a player like Fang Rui wasn’t suited to be the core of a team. This was too shameless!

“He’s testing Han Wenqing’s patience,” Wei Chen spoke up.

Ye Xiu nodded his head. Fang Rui knew that Han Wenqing was dealing with his threats with ease, but if he insisted on continuing with his threats, then that was probably his plan. Fang Rui was using his shamelessness to tear down Han Wenqing! Pressing forward like this was boring and unstylish, but if Han Wenqing followed along and kept retreating, he didn’t look any better. Seventy percent of the shamelessness was coming from Fang Rui, but the other thirty percent was from Han Wenqing cooperating with him. Han Wenqing probably disdained doing something like this, so Fang Rui refusing to give up was intentionally provoking Han Wenqing to act.

However, it looked like Han Wenqing was quite tyrannical in terms of his bottom line. They had went around half the map, but Desert Dust’s footsteps were as steady as ever. It seemed like he had no intentions of breaking this stalemate. Had he really decided that he would bring down this fight to the lowest point with Fang Rui?

Those who understood the fight had mixed feeling about Han Wenqing. The Alliance’s symbol of a hot-blooded hero was also going to stoop this low?

After half a circle, they went around another half a circle. The two had now circled around the entire Arena. The pace for a two minute match had finally been broken, but no one would have expected it to be done in such a shameless method with Han Wenqing joining in on it.

After going around an entire circle, Fang Rui had no trouble keeping up the shamelessness. Boundless Sea continued to sway freely left and right. It looked like he would have no issue going for another hundred circles. As for Han Wenqing? If he really did go around a hundred circles with Fang Rui, the image that he had upheld for ten years would be completely destroyed. That was what the people who understood what they were watching thought.

What would happen next? Everyone had mixed feelings. Finally, when the two started their second circle around, the envoy of justice, the referee, couldn’t endure it any longer.

“Please display a proper competitive attitude.” A system notification appeared.

“Haha,” Fang Rui laughed as a reply to the referee. Boundless Sea immediately paused, followed by a punch from Desert Dust.

“Fuck, how despicable!!” Boundless Sea went flying. Fang Rui typed furiously. A yellow card lit up, along with with punches and kicks.

Everyone was wide-eyed.

Fang Rui very rarely had the opportunity to call others despicable. Usually, he was the one being despicable. But this time, honestly speaking, Fang Rui was right…

He unexpectedly seized the moment Fang Rui was responding to the referee’s call to attack.

The Glory competitive rules never stated that the two sides needed to immediately stop when the referee made a decision, but the referee decision would definitely influence the fight in some way. During this time, the players would make certain adjustments.

Han Wenqing decisively launched his fiercest attacks, strike Fang Rui while he was responding to the referee with a “Haha”

This was most definitely a dirty move. Fang Rui had even used it at the start of the round. He had sent a message to Lin Jingyan, who wasn’t even playing, in an attempt to distract his opponent and use that as an opportunity to attack.

And now, Han Wenqing had used the referee’s decision instead.

“Han Wenqing… um…” Pan Lin didn’t know what to say.

“What rich experience! He anticipated that the referee would intervene. The moment the referee intervened, there would be a change in tempo, and he used this opportunity to attack,” Li Yibo didn’t hesitate, immediately explaining the situation to Pan Lin. He made it sound like the move from Han Wenqing wasn’t a dirty sneak attack.

Li Yibo used to be from Tyranny, after all. Han Wenqing had been his captain. This time, Li Yibo clearly showed his bias in defending him.

“Ah… yeah, what rich experience, to anticipate even something like this…” Pan Lin instinctively agreed with Li Yibo.

“In the end, Han Wenqing won the battle of patience. Fang Rui wasn’t focused enough, even responding to the referee with a “haha”. This superfluous act led to him losing the initiative,” Li Yibo was playing favorites today. After praising Han Wenqing, he criticized Fang Rui. His words were correct though. It was just that he intentionally overlooked how dirty such a move was.

“He should… be able to win…” Pan Lin said.

Strikers were exceptional at close combat. It was common for them to kill their opponents in one go after getting close to them. Fang Rui had been able to escape from Han Wenqing previously, and this time? By launching a sneak attack when Fang Rui’s attention was elsewhere, he put himself in a very favorable position. Fang Rui, who had been baiting Han Wenqing, had been mentally prepared initially, but when the referee decision came, he indeed got careless. Because of the referee announcement, his previous plan stopped there. He hadn’t thought that Han Wenqing would actually take advantage of the referee to launch his offense that he had been waiting to do…

Whether or not a move was dirty had never been something Fang Rui was concerned with. When he cursed at Han Wenqing’s despicableness, Fang Rui had been upset with himself. To think he would overlook the possibility of launching a sneak attack when the referee came to a decision. His own dirty playstyle wasn’t dirty enough!

Chapter 1525 - A Historic Clash

I lost…

Fang Rui shook his head as he walked down from the stage. His greatest strength was his dirtiness, yet he actually lost because of a dirty move from his opponent. Like a swimmer drowning, it was too disgraceful.

“Fuck, Han Wenqing!”

When he returned back to the player bench, he took the towel that his teammates handed over, but he didn’t wipe his hands. Instead, he threw the towel hard against the seats as if Han Wenqing was sitting there.

“If you were my opponent, I definitely wouldn’t have fallen for that,” Fang Rui said honestly to Ye Xiu.

“Nah, you definitely would have,” Ye Xiu replied back honestly.

“Definitely wouldn’t have.”

“Definitely would have.”

Chen Guo felt a bit confused, but after thinking about it for a bit, she understood.

Fang Rui meant that he had been careless because Han Wenqing wasn’t the type to play dirty. If he had been against Ye Xiu, he definitely wouldn’t have been so careless because Ye Xiu was someone who did play dirty, but Ye Xiu was denying it.

“Pay attention to the match! Stop arguing!” Chen Guo scolded the two.

“Little Tang, good luck! Destroy him!” Fang Rui immediately turned around and called out to Tang Rou. But because of how loud the audience was, his voice could no longer reach her.

Chen Guo felt deeply worried. Ye Xiu had won a lead at the cost of his energy, but not only had they lost their lead, they had fallen behind.

Han Wenqing had beaten two of Happy’s players. He lost almost no health against Su Mucheng, and although his fight with Fang Rui had taken a long time, half of the time, they were just running around. The other half of the time he had the initiative. Fang Rui hadn’t been able to land any effective combos. He had only been able to trade a few blows while he was defending against Han Wenqing. In the end, Desert Dust won with 59% of his health left, and much of this was because Han Wenqing had often taken blows that he could have avoided in order to keep up his offense.

1v3!

Tyranny’s home crowd had already begun shouting for a 1v3. Considering he had beaten two players and still had over half of his health left, it was a very reasonable expectation.

On stage.

Han Wenqing, Tang Rou.

Desert Dust, Soft Mist.

Striker, Battle Mage.

Ten years ago, it was these two classes that began the longest rivalry in the Glory Alliance.

The two weren’t teammates, but Han Wenqing was incomparably familiar with this class and was very proficient against them. Facing Battle Mages not named Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing had an astonishingly high win rate. Apart from a few rather extreme situations in the group arena, in a fair 1v1, Han Wenqing had never lost against a Battle Mage.

At the Season 8 All Stars, One Autumn Leaf’s successor, Sun Xiang, who was the most skilled Battle Mage of the new generation, had fought against a Han Wenqing past his prime. In the end, Han Wenqing still came out on top.

Now, he was facing Tang Rou, this season’s Best Rookie and a Battle Mage.

But no matter the Battle Mage, there was always a shadow of Ye Xiu. Even the proud Sun Xiang had practiced hard to learn Ye Xiu’s Dragon Raises Its Head. As for Tang Rou, she had been taught by Ye Xiu, and there was no escaping his legacy.

However, Han Wenqing discovered that not only were there shadows of Ye Xiu in Tang Rou, there were also shadows of himself.

This girl also liked to be fierce and aggressive, wanting to use force to destroy everything, just like him. Attack, attack, and attack, never retreating, always attacking. It didn’t matter how much health was lost, as long as the opponent was injured more.

This was their style, and Han Wenqing couldn’t be any more familiar with it.

A familiar opponent and familiar self. The shadows of these two rivals had overlapped in her.

How difficult would it be to face this sort of opponent?

Han Wenqing sucked in a deep breath and focused.

The match began.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Without any hesitation, the moment Tang Rou loaded into the map, Soft Mist launched an attack. In this small map, for these two players, the start of the match was like a gunshot signalling the start of a 100m dash.

Who would be faster?

Tang Rou!

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was faster because Han Wenqing chose to run away as soon as the match began.

A decision that he would have never done in the past had once again appeared another fight today.

This time? Because he was familiar with himself and his opponent’s playstyle, he chose not to make this a contest of speed. In the past, he would often like to win this way, seeing who was faster, who was fiercer.

But now, Han Wenqing was very clear about how his hand speed and reaction speed had slowed down. He couldn’t compare with his past self.

So he used what reaction and hand speed he had to dodge.

Boom…

The dash from Dragon Breaks the Ranks seemed to explode as it swept past Desert Dust. It failed to hit, but just the surging magic energy from it shook Desert Dust. However, this was all within Han Wenqing’s expectations. Desert Dust borrowed this force to spin his body, using a Whirlwind Kick to strike Soft Mist’s back.

Peng!

The sound of a collision sounded.

The instant Tang Rou realized that the Dragon Breaks the Ranks would miss, she cancelled the skill. Dragon Breaks the Ranks was a high-level skill with little starting or ending lag. It could be considered an abnormality among high-level skills. Soft Mist turned around. Before her Dragon Breaks the Ranks had completely dissipated, she used a Sky Strike, blocking the Whirlwind Kick from Desert Dust.

The two characters ricocheted back. They readjusted themselves and charged forward again!

When two players of this playstyle met, the result was going to be an intense battle. However, from their first exchange, it could be seen that the two relied on different things. Han Wenqing relied more on his experienced and his understanding of Battle Mages and Tang Rou, guessing what his opponent would do next. As for Tang Rou? She relied on her fast reaction and hand speed. It was always Han Wenqing’s Desert dust making the first move and then her reacting, catching up and not losing out.

The two were locked in combat. Their healths plummeted. In this sort of confrontation, how could there not be fierce trades?

It was just that even though Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was losing in terms of health, he had other players behind him. As for Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, even though she came in with full health, after this even fight with Han Wenqing, even if she won, she would be facing the next opponent heavily injured.

This was why players like Han Wenqing and Tang Rou weren’t suited for the group arena, especially with five players rotating. Their brave advances often led to trades, health for health. If they could completely suppress their opponents, it worked out well. But in today’s match, force against force, it was unlikely that either side would be winning without losing much health.

If this continued, Happy would win this round, but their hopes for the group arena as a whole weren’t optimistic.

“Sigh… Little Tang…” Even Chen Guo felt that it wouldn’t be good if this continued.

“What’s wrong? I think she’s playing very well!” Ye Xiu said.

“Tyranny still has another player!” Chen Guo reminded Ye Xiu. Did he count wrong?

“If she doesn’t play like this, she probably won’t even be able to see the next player,” Ye Xiu said.

“Ah?”

“Do you think Little Tang has a better chance at winning against Han Wenqing meeting force with force, or by slowly playing it out in a contest of experience, decision-making, and technique?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo was stumped.

Experience, decision-making, technique… a contest with Han Wenqing?

Chen Guo already knew the answer.

“Through a spurt of energy, she still has a chance. But if she slows down the pace, it’ll be much more difficult,” Ye Xiu said.

The fight was like a whirlwind, decided in less than a minute. Tang Rou, but she sacrificed much of her health in doing so. Soft Mist only had 50% of her health left, exactly half of it. The two traded blow for blow, with neither side able to gain an advantage over the other. In the end, it could only be a draw.

Tyranny’s fans were feeling quite regretful about this outcome! They had hoped to see a 1v3 from their captain on this playoffs stage. It would truly be too amazing of a comeback.

However, doing this much was already an outstanding performance. When Han Wenqing walked down from the stage, the applause was thunderous. Apart from that, Tyranny’s fans also felt that Tang Rou was quite admirable, daring to face their captain so bravely. Of course, if she had been a different class, it would have been even more admirable. They had a subconscious hate for Battle Mages.

The group arena was at the final match point. Tyranny’s fifth player appeared on the big screen.

Song Qiying, Striker, River Sunset.

A new generation Battle Mage against a new generation Striker. The two would be facing each other on the stage. However, they didn’t have the personalities of their seniors.

Although Tang Rou’s Battle Mage had absorbed much of Ye Xiu’s techniques, her style was a complete opposite of Ye Xiu’s.

As for Song Qiying? He was rumored to be Han Wenqing’s successor, but his playstyle was more similar to his vice-captain’s. It was the complete opposite of Han Wenqing’s.

But no matter how much their styles had changed, the subject of this confrontation would never change.

Victory! Only victory mattered!

As soon as the match began, Soft Mist rushed forward. She didn’t use Dragon Breaks the Ranks, instead running to start her offense. With only 50% of her health left, she needed to gain the upper hand. And Tang Rou? She was most proficient at establishing advantages through aggression. And in this simple map, there was no better method.

Song Qiying was very calm. Although he wasn’t as experienced as Han Wenqing, he knew what Tang Rou needed. He calmly avoided her rush.

Then, he didn’t immediately counterattack like Han Wenqing did. Such a forceful counterattack would quickly result in the two sticking together. Even though trading blows would be an effective strategy for him since he had the health lead, it wasn’t his style, so he didn’t do it.

Perhaps this was Tyranny’s true style: it wasn’t just pressing onward relentlessly, but tenaciously persevering with one’s own path.

Chapter 1526 - A Match Decided by Force

The pace of the group arena had slowed for a second time after the match between Fang Rui and Han Wenqing.

This definitely wasn’t the pace that Tang Rou was hoping for. Under these circumstances, it wasn’t hard to figure out who held the advantage.

Song Qiying.

He was a rookie too. Compared to Tang Rou, he had started playing Glory much earlier. He had also gone through the same training camp as Qin Muyun and had a solid foundation.

He controlled the pace of the fight extremely well, ruining Tang Rou’s plans. She wasn’t able to break open this 1v1 situation. The pro players watching were discussing the battle. This was a battle between a spear and shield, and right now, the sturdy shield was blocking the sharp spear.

If the sturdy shield couldn’t be broken, it would rebound back. As a result, in this confrontation between attack and defense, it would end up as a trade. Song Qiying’s strategy was to trade using a dense defense. Compared to Team Blue Rain, who could launch an explosive counterattack at any moment while defending, Song Qiying’s defense was more simple and pure.

To think a player like this could come out of Tyranny. Countless people were clicking their tongues in wonder.

Tang Rou obviously wasn’t thinking the same. It was depressing. Song Qiying’s control over the pace of the match felt oppressive. It wasn’t that she wasn’t thinking of a solution, but no matter what she did, her opponent would quickly figure it out and then eliminate it.

It looked like Soft Mist was attacking, while River Sunset was defending, but for Tang Rou, it didn’t feel like she was attacking. She felt like she was hitting against a wall. She would hit it again and again, and every time, she would bounce back. So far, she had lost 30% of her health. As for her opponent? He had only lost 15% of his health. It was an exact two to one trade as if everything was precisely calculated.

If this continued, when her opponent lost 10% more health, wouldn’t it be the end for her?

Tang Rou was unwilling to lose. Being unable to win would always be something she would be unhappy about.

Soft Mist’s attacks suddenly stopped, and she retreated several steps back.

“Oh…” Many people sighed emotionally.

“She should have stopped a long time ago. Being reckless isn’t a solution,” Pan Lin also said.

“It looked as if she had the initiative, but in reality, she was being led around the nose by Song Qiying. She should have taken a pause and looked carefully for an opening,” Li Yibo said. He had gone back to his fair and unbiased commentary, earnestly giving advice to Tang Rou.

“But what if she isn’t able to find any openings?” Pan Lin asked.

“Then… it’s impossible to win,” Li Yibo said.

Yes, if you couldn’t find any openings and you couldn’t beat the opponent, then you would be the one who lost. It was very simple reasoning.

What will Tang Rou do?

She had always given them an impression of having a fierce offense, but in front of this unbreakable wall, how would she make adjustments?

Soft Mist had stopped attacking for five seconds already. Song Qiying’s River Sunset didn’t hurry to counterattack, but he was also pressing forward step by step. He obviously wasn’t someone who only knew how to defend and didn’t know how to attack. It was just that he attacked just as carefully as he defended.

“Uh, is Tang Rou planning on giving the initiative to Song Qiying and then searching for an opening in his offense?” Li Yibo had a few ideas, “That is a decent solution, considering that she isn’t able to get past her opponent’s defense. But… Song Qiying’s cautious style will make it hard for Tang Rou to find an opening. What’s more…”

Before Li Yibo could finish speaking, a figure rushed forward.

Soft Mist.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

After a five to six second pause, Tang Rou started attacking again. Giving the initiative to Song Qiying? The idea was proven wrong before Li Yibo could even finish up his commentary.

The distance was very close, and Dragon Breaks the Ranks wasn’t an easy-to-dodge attack. However, Song Qiying’s caution was such that he would always be ready for any attack.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks?

The moment Soft Mist raised her spear, River Sunset had already begun rolling to the side.

Magic energy and wind collided, creating a loud boom. Dragon Breaks the Ranks rushed forward, but River Sunset was already moving away. However, to his surprise, Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames was turned slightly towards where River Sunset would dodge to.

Those who weren’t perceptive enough wouldn’t be able to notice this small detail.

Song Qiying had noticed it though. He was the same as Zhang Xinjie, someone who carefully observed the opponent and paid attention to the details. He had even determined correctly that this slight turn had happened after River Sunset had started dodging.

In other words, Tang Rou hadn’t predicted where he would move to, she had reacted to his movements.

It had only been a slight shift to the side, but at this close of a distance and the speed of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, being able to make this adjustment showed how astonishing her reaction speed and hand speed was.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks wasn’t a single target attack. The collision between magic and wind dealt AoE damage.

The area that the attack covered deviated slightly from where it was before, but luckily for Song Qiying, he was still able to dodge it.

Song Qiying could see it clearly. Even with this adjustment, the Dragon Breaks the Ranks wouldn’t be able to hit him. If Soft Mist had been a bit further, if the adjustment had been slightly bigger, the outcome might have been different.

Song Qiying was still thinking about this, when suddenly saw a flash of red light before him.

How!

He was shocked. He instinctively dodged, evading this sudden attack.

It missed and then… there was nothing afterwards.

That sudden attack wasn’t from Dragon Breaks the Ranks. If it had been, he wouldn’t have been able to dodge the AoE. Song Qiying saw Soft Mist retract her red spear. It looked like she wasn’t done with her assault.

River Sunset and Soft Mist had been about 4.5 steps away previously.

With only a distance of 4.5 steps, she was able to use Dragon Breaks the Ranks, adjust it, cancel it, and then follow up with another attack to make up for what her Dragon Breaks the Ranks couldn’t cover.

Even though it ultimately didn’t work, Song Qiying felt his body go cold. What was more terrifying was that it wasn’t over yet. The red light quickly returned. Shua shua, two thrusts in quick succession, Double Stab!

River Sunset didn’t dodge because Song Qiying knew that if he only dodged, he would lose control over the tempo. He would lose control over the fight.

The pause from Tang Rou was to give Song Qiying a chance to attack? The people who thought that were gravely mistaken. The pause looked to be a short mid-fight break. What came after was an even fiercer and more explosive assault. When she attacked, she didn’t make any probes, nor did she hold back. She went all out with her attacks. More importantly, whenever Song Qiying made any changes, she would immediately react to it. She was accelerating the tempo to her maximum speed, biting tightly onto her opponent.

It was dangerous for the enemy and for herself. It was obviously very difficult to maintain such a tempo. It would be easier for her to make a mistake, and for Tang Rou, a single mistake could mean the end for her.

Pu pu!

Two streaks of blood from River Sunset flew into the air. Song Qiying didn’t dodge the skill, tanking the damage. River Sunset stepped forward and let out a punch. He needed to respond with a few attacks so he could keep the tempo of the fight under his control.

He punched, but he missed. Soft Mist looked as if she didn’t even dodge. However, the punch had missed by just a hair.

When Han Wenqing saw this scene, he couldn’t help but feel emotional. The spear was long, while the fist was short. A stab was the spear attack with the longest reach. If the Striker wanted to attack after taking the hit, he would need to get close to her first. He had encountered this challenge repeatedly when he had fought with Ye Xiu in the past. Ye Xiu would always take advantage of these sort of situations.

The punch missed, but Soft Mist’s counterattack arrived. Song Qiying was able to found an opening to use Reinforced Iron Bones and had River Sunset take the hit again to continue his attacks!

He needed to control the tempo, and he could no longer rely on just defense to do so. Song Qiying focused on his offense.

But Tang Rou didn’t retreat. She also knew where they key to her victory lay in. She couldn’t stop. If she stopped, she would lose without a doubt.

The pace of the fight soared, quickly following the style of today’s group arena again. Fist and spear clashed, making everyone think of the former rivalry between Han Wenqing and Ye Xiu. What made many Tyranny fans annoyed was that the Battle Mage played the way they liked. Fortunately, Song Qiying wasn’t bad either. Facing this fierce opponent, he didn’t cower.

Who won today’s group arena would be decided through a contest of force.

Who would win?

For a moment, no one could tell. Soft Mist had less health, but she held the advantage. River Sunset’s health was dropping faster. And at this tempo, it was very easy for a mistake to happen. It was possible for a last second comeback.

Everyone quieted down, focusing on the match. Even Pan Lin and Li Yibo had stopped talking. With the speed they were going, how were they supposed to commentate? They might as well wait for the outcome and then analyzing it from there!

Bang!

In the end, with one final collision, the winner was decided.

Song Qiying, River Sunset. In the end, he stood until the end. Tyranny had won the group arena.

Although Tang Rou had lost, she had used 20% of her health to take down 60% of River Sunset’s health. Her performance had been astonishing.

The group arena ended. The two players walked out from their booths amidst thunderous applause. The applause was for Song Qiying’s win as well as Tang Rou’s performance. Even though Tang Rou wasn’t well liked by the public and used Tyranny’s most hated class, the Battle Mage, Tyranny fans loved the way she played!

Since they liked it, they happily applauded. This was just how Tyranny’s fans were.

Chapter 1527 - Sunset Dunes

“You should have done that earlier!” Ye Xiu told Tang Rou as she came down from the stage and received applause from her teammates.

“Okay, next time,” Tang Rou replied with a smile. She knew that Ye Xiu’s words were probably a form of encouragement for her outstanding performance in the latter half of the fight.

The current Tang Rou was no longer the noob who challenged Ye Xiu and got crushed dozens of times. She could see the difference in skill between two players now and wouldn’t be so foolishly confident like before. She knew what sort of tempo she played best at. The higher she raised the tempo, the more likely it was for her to make a mistake. It was similar to how in basketball, the farther away you are from the hoop, the less likely it is to make it in. Although half-court three point shots sometimes made it in, who would count on those to be their main method of attack?

Tang Rou’s final burst was like a half-court three point shot. If she hadn’t been forced to do so, why would she have made such a choice?

Ye Xiu smiled as well. He was very pleased with Tang Rou’s spirit.

“In the playoffs, when it’s time to go all out, don’t hesitate,” Ye Xiu added.

“Of course,” Tang Rou said.

“Pay attention to the timing,” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay…” Tang Rou nodded her head pensively. In that previous fight, her Soft Mist had used 20% of her health to wipe out 60% of her opponent’s health after her explosive burst. What if she had done it earlier? If she had started with that burst and kept it going until the very end, Happy might have won.

It looks like I’m still not fast enough at making these types of decisions! Tang Rou sighed.

“Then, let’s take back the point we lost in the group arena in the team competition!” Ye Xiu said to the team.

Although Happy had lost a point in the group arena, since they had won the previous game, they didn’t feel too nervous about the loss. The entire team was still in high spirits.

On Tyranny’s side, despite winning the group arena, the atmosphere wasn’t as lively as Happy’s. Their team was huddled together, anxiously preparing for the following team competition. As the home team, their plans could be more targeted.

The mid-match break quickly passed, and the referee called for the two sides to come onto the stage. The lineup for the two teams were displayed onto the screen. On Happy’s side, there was a player not on the main roster, who was being followed closely, Luo Ji. In the previous game, Luo Ji had demolished the map, leading to Tyranny’s loss. He had been proclaimed as someone who had exceptional talent in this area. Would he continue playing in today’s match?

The names lit up on the screen one at a time.

Happy – Ye Xiu. Tyranny – Han Wenqing.

Happy – Su Mucheng. Tyranny – Zhang Jiale.

Happy – Fang Rui. Tyranny – Bai Yanfei.

Happy – Tang Rou. Tyranny – Qin Muyun.

Happy – An Wenyi. Tyranny – Zhang Xinjie.

Happy – Bao Rongxing. Tyranny – Lin Jingyan.

No Luo Ji.

A commotion began going among the crowd. When they saw that Luo Ji wasn’t being put in, they felt like the claim that Luo Ji could destroy the map whenever he pleased turned out to be a bluff. Happy didn’t dare choose Luo Ji in their away game.

On the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t immediately start analyzing the two team’s lineups. They first discussed why Luo Ji wasn’t put in, before commenting on the differences between their lineups compared to the previous game.

On Happy’s side, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, and An Wenyi had the most stable positions in the team competition. This time, Tang Rou was put in as a starter. Steamed Bun replaced Luo Ji, but he was designated as Happy’s sixth player.

Tyranny’s lineup was the same as before. The only difference was that their Elementalist, Bai Yanfei, had swapped positions with Lin Jingyan. Bai Yanfei would be in the starting lineup, while Lin Jingyan would be their sixth player.

“Both sides have made slight adjustments to their lineup! But the home team usually has a clear strategy in mind. Tyranny specifically placed Bai Yanfei in a starting position. Coach Li, do you think there’s a reason for this?” Pan Lin asked.

“Bai Yanfei, Zhang Jiale, Qin Muyun. Tyranny has three long-ranged classes in their starting lineup. Bai Yanfei’s Elementalist is nicknamed the “Gun Turret” and is proficient at AoE spells. By coordinating with Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, the two can cover an extremely large area. My guess is that Tyranny has chosen a relatively large map to play in.”

“Oh oh, we’ll see. The players have entered their booths. The match is about to begin,” Pan Lin then confirmed that these ten players would be starting in the team competition.

The map began loading. The answer to the question that everyone had been wondering about was on verge of appearing.

“Ah, it’s Sunset Dunes!” Pan Lin called out. He immediately followed up with praise for Li Yibo: “Coach Li, you guessed right. As you said, Tyranny has chosen a large map. As expected of someone who came from Tyranny!”

“Hahaha,” Li Yibo laughed. After laughing, he felt like something wasn’t quite right. “As expected of someone who came from Tyranny?” Wasn’t that implying that he couldn’t make accurate predictions for teams that weren’t Tyranny? Li Yibo’s confidence had been wavering recently. He couldn’t help but overthink it. Pan Lin hadn’t meant to imply that and wasn’t aware of the issue. He continued by introducing the map to everyone.

Sunset Dunes was a desert under the light of the setting sun. The main features of this map were the sand dunes and the oasis at the center of the map. The map was indeed quite large.

“Happy’s decision not to field Luo Ji was the correct decision,” Pan Lin said half-jokingly. Who would have thought that as soon as the match started, Ye Xiu would type into the chat: “Just as I thought! Not putting in Luo Ji today was so smart of me.”

There were no buildings in this map. The sand dunes were the only parts of the map that weren’t flat. The oasis at the center was really just a small puddle. The lonely tree near the oasis and the cacti scattered throughout the desert were the only objects in this map.

Luo Ji’s “Demolition Style” would be useless here.

The two teams spawned at the north and south ends of the map. Tyranny was more proactive, immediately pushing forward as soon as they spawned. As for Happy, they were a bit slower than Tyranny, but they quickly set out as well.

The two teams didn’t take a roundabout route, heading straight for the center. Tyranny didn’t stop after moving past a sand dune. As for Happy, they paused slightly. The five characters were looking left and right, observing their surroundings.

The sand dunes weren’t mountains and weren’t that tall. Just standing on the slope gave them a fairly good view. Not only could they see all around them, they could see several hazy figures in the distance to the north.

“There doesn’t seem too many good places to set up ambushes in this map…” Happy’s team members began discussing their next moves. Fang Rui started with his opinion.

“There are some good spots for me to attack from,” Su Mucheng remarked.

“The sand has a certain level of impact on our movements,” An Wenyi’s gaze was fixed at his feet. Their feet sunk into the sand, leaving behind deep footprints.

“They’re rushing straight for us,” Tang Rou mainly observed their opponent’s movements.

“Let’s go somewhere high enough where we can see them more clearly before making any further plans!” Ye Xiu said, giving them an opening of sorts in this team competition. As a result, Happy didn’t go down from this sand dune. Ye Xiu led the way as they climbed it. After Tyranny’s five players ran across the sand dune, they could be seen more clearly. Tyranny also noticed Happy. They turned and rushed towards them.

“It looks like they want to attack us directly,” Fang Rui said.

Happy didn’t like direct fights. As a new team, they were slightly inferior to Tyranny’s old team in a direct fight in many aspects. What’s more, the terrain was special. An Wenyi noted that the sand would affect their movements. It wasn’t just movement speed; their jumps, rolls, and other movements that required leverage would be affected. It would affect their attacks as well. Tyranny chose this as their map and was used to these effects. But Happy? Ye Xiu would be better. He had played in countless matches and would adapt quickly to this sort of terrain. Su Mucheng and Fang Rui had experience as well. However, Tang Rou, An Wenyi, and Steamed Bun were rookies. Their playing would definitely be impacted to a greater degree.

“Does the wind do anything?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked.

“It does, but the direction of the wind is constantly changing and it isn’t easy to grasp,” Fang Rui replied. His Qi Master’s qi attacks would be affected if the speed of the wind was high enough.

Happy examined their surroundings carefully. Tyranny was obviously familiar with these characteristics, and they clearly wanted to use this map to restrict Happy.

The sunshine… couldn’t be used either.

Ye Xiu took a look at the sun. The setting sun was just about to go under the horizon. The sun rays were dim enough for him to look at the sun directly. There wasn’t much of a difference between having their backs against the sun or facing the sun.

“You guys stand here,” Ye Xiu called out to the others. He used his umbrella to point to a spot.

The four gathered there.

“Stand in a line,” Ye Xiu said.

“Are we taking a group photo? I don’t think that’s a good idea. It’s the playoffs, let’s be more serious,” Fang Rui said as his Boundless Sea posed for the camera.

“Stand up straight,” Ye Xiu said, while his Lord Grim retreated.

Happy’s four players lined up. As for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, after moving away a certain distance, he turned back to look at them.

The opening period was a bit dull since the fighting hadn’t started yet. It was just the commentators guessing what the two team’s intentions were.

Tyranny was pushing forward. Their intentions were rather obvious.

As for Happy? They were just moving on top of a sand dune, but because the team was discussing the map in the chat, it wasn’t too boring. Ye Xiu suddenly ordered everyone to do this and that, so the viewers were obviously curious about what he was planning. The broadcast nimbly cut to Lord Grim’s perspective.

Under the backdrop of the setting sun, Happy’s four characters were standing directly in the center of the sun. It looked rather imposing.

Were they… really taking a group photo? Everyone was puzzled.

Chapter 1528 - Flowing Sand Dunes

“What?” Not just the spectators, but Happy’s teammates were having trouble understanding what Ye Xiu was doing. Fang Rui had his Boundless Sea posing for a camera, but he obviously didn’t actually think that Ye Xiu was lining them up for a picture.

“If you’re standing in the sunlight, it’s hard to differentiate between you guys at a glance,” Ye Xiu said.

The others on Happy immediately understood what he was getting at. If Ye Xiu couldn’t differentiate between them, then their opponents wouldn’t be able to either. This meant that it would be hard for Tyranny to determine what attacks they were planning on using. It was a characteristic of the map that could be taken advantage of.

The viewers could see Happy’s chat, so they quickly caught on as well. Everyone loved to see the players communicate their goals in the chat. Teams with too much synergy wouldn’t speak much, often leaving the viewers puzzled.

“Let me see,” Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain walked over to Lord Grim’s spot and turned to look at the setting sun. Amidst the warm red sunlight, only the silhouettes of the characters could be seen. Under these circumstances, it was indeed very difficult to tell what attack or move was being used.

“Yes yes yes…” Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea walked over to take a look and expressed his approval.

“Maybe we can set something up over here to take advantage of it?” Fang Rui suggested as he watched Tyranny come closer and closer.

“I doubt Tyranny would overlook this possibility. We just need to be on guard against them taking advantage it. Apart from that, if a chance arrives, we can try taking advantage of it too,” Ye Xiu said.

The countless viewers looking at Happy’s chat felt somewhat ashamed. They had thought that Happy could set something up using this discovery, but when they saw Ye Xiu’s words, they realized that they had looked down on Tyranny too much. To think they would feel as if Tyranny would overlook an important detail in the map that they had chosen themselves.

“How are we going to fight them?” Fang Rui asked. They had made several insights into the map, but in the end, they hadn’t come up with a plan.

Ye Xiu finally issued out orders telling them where to stand.

No one questioned him. The rest of Happy immediately went into position according to Ye Xiu’s instructions. Tyranny was about to reach the bottom of their sand dune, but when they saw Happy’s arrangements, they immediately changed directions.

Fang Rui looked behind him and saw the setting sun. From Tyranny’s actions, it looked like Tyranny knew about the effects of the sun on the map. Ye Xiu’s arrangements had been to take advantage of the sunlight, but Tyranny noticed it and immediately made adjustments. Tyranny no longer faced the sun, instead choosing to rush in from the side.

“Let’s go!” Ye Xiu led the team forward. Tyranny stopped. Happy stopped. This time, the others on Happy didn’t need Ye Xiu to instruct them. They understood what he wanted to do and carried it out themselves. Ye Xiu wanted to take advantage of the sun behind them, using it to stop Tyranny from approaching.

This time, Tyranny didn’t give chase. They simply waited at the bottom of the sand dune. There was no communication in the chat, so the viewers didn’t know what they were thinking.

“Coach Li?” Pan Lin was starting to make Li Yibo feel sick.

Li Yibo felt his head hurt. He had a certain understanding of Tyranny, but right now, he couldn’t see through their thoughts. Under Zhang Xinjie’s lead, Tyranny should be taking the more reliable approach. In this case, the reliable approach was to circle around a bit farther. Eventually, they would be able to escape from the influence of the sun. Instead, Tyranny had stopped. What were they thinking? There was nothing in their chat either. It seemed like everyone already knew what to do.

“They’re probably waiting for the right opportunity,” In the end, Li Yibo had to say something. He had to resort to using a word like “probably” implying that he wasn’t sure.

“What will this opportunity be? Let’s wait and see,” Pan Lin spoke tactfully. When he heard Li Yibo’s uncertainty, he immediately knew that he shouldn’t continue pursuing this topic.

Tyranny stood still at the bottom of the dune. Happy stood still at the top of the dune. Tyranny wasn’t communicating, but Happy was.

“Let’s see what they’re planning,” Ye Xiu said calmly.

“Should I send out a probing attack?” Su Mucheng asked.

“Sure,” Ye Xiu agreed.

In terms of distance, Tyranny was within Dancing Rain’s range. But because Dancing Rain held the high point, she had to take in account the height difference. She could reach them if she calculated the angle well enough, but this sort of max-ranged attack wasn’t any sort of threat to them.

Even so, as soon as Dancing Rain raised her cannon, Tyranny collectively retreated back a few steps.

“I can’t hit them…” Su Mucheng felt that it was a pity. Dancing Rain lowered her cannon.

“How careful,” Ye Xiu sighed. Zhang Xinjie wasn’t even willing to give them the slightest of opportunities.

Ye Xiu suddenly noticed that his vision had become somewhat hazy. Just when he was wondering what it could be, there was finally some signs of movement.

The movement was the wind, blowing from the north to the south. The sand seemed to be like a wave as the wind swept it up, slowly gathering beneath the sand dune.

Tyranny wanted to use the wind to start the fight!

Although Ye Xiu didn’t have a deep understanding of the map, he had much experience! He had guessed what sort of medicine Tyranny was brewing.

Bang bang bang bang, the sound of gunfire could be heard. Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun, the two Gunners, open fired at the sand. The sand lifted up from their attacks was swept up by the wind, adding to the growing whirlwind of sand.

How big could it get? Big enough to completely cover an entire team?

Ye Xiu wasn’t sure, but more and more sand was building up, and the whirlwind was getting denser and denser. More importantly, the wind was picking up as well. This was Tyranny’s biggest assurance for their plan.

It’s coming!

The sand that had gathered reduced the visibility to only a few steps distance, which was more than enough to cover up Tyranny’s movements. Happy could no longer see Tyranny as the whirlwind of sand quickly approached them…

That was what Happy thought at least. However, the viewers could see that Tyranny wasn’t in a hurry. They weren’t in a hurry to use this sandstorm to approach Happy. Although their movements were already covered, they controlled their pace as if they were waiting for something.

What are they waiting for?

No one knew. The viewers only knew that Happy had started moving. The sandstorm passed over the sand dune, swallowing them up.

Right when Lord Grim stepped to the side, he immediately realized that something wasn’t right.

“Be careful beneath you” He quickly warned, but the others on Happy had taken the step already and lost their balance.

The sand was moving down from the sand dune. The ground beneath them wasn’t stable. The movement of the sand wasn’t slow either, and it couldn’t be seen from the surface.

To think they hid such a move!

Ye Xiu knew that they wouldn’t be able to escape from Tyranny. Sand filled the skies and silently flowed beneath them. The entire sand dune seemed to be collapsing.

Everyone on Happy wass struggling to keep their balance. This wasn’t a situation that could be kept under control through normal movements.

Rotor Wings!

Ye Xiu realized it the earliest and reacted the fastest. Lord Grim flew into the air, dispelling the effects of the sand.

Boom boom boom!

The sound of cannonfire rang. Su Mucheng used Aerial Cannon, and Dancing Rain seemed to hop across the sand like a dragonfly touching water. Not far from her, Little Cold Hands floated into the air, using Angel Wings to rise.

Fang Rui and Tang Rou used skills to deal with the sand. However, since they didn’t have any way to directly avoid it, they could only forcefully blow away the sand around them to disrupt the flow of sand and give them an opportunity to adjust themselves.

Happy’s five players each used their own methods to resist the sand and looked to be doing it skillfully. However, Ye Xiu knew that this wouldn’t last long. For example, the skills that Lord Grim and Little Cold Hands used had a time duration. They couldn’t keep using it forever, and the movement of the sand couldn’t be seen from the surface. They knew didn’t know where to land. What’s worse, it was about time for Tyranny to start their attacks.

Sure enough, Ye Xiu’s judgement was correct. Gunfire! Tyranny’s two gunners had started firing at them. Even if Ye Xiu had predicted it and warned everyone to be careful, what could they do?

Bang bang bang bang…

The wings on An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands was instantly riddled with holes. When he fell, he was immediately swept up by the sand, and An Wenyi didn’t have any other methods to escape from it.

He was their healer though, and he had to be saved. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately headed towards him. Tyranny wasn’t in a hurry to strike Little Cold Hands, firing towards Lord Grim instead.

Ye Xiu cancelled Rotor Wings in midair and plummeted down.

He had determined the direction of the bullets and figured out Tyranny’s location. Perhaps the ground over there was more stable.

“Follow me!” Ye Xiu didn’t forget to call out to everyone. Right now, even if he didn’t want clash with them, he had no choice but to.

Falling Light Blade!

Lord Grim used a skill in midair, following the slope of the sand dune. With this, he dropped down very far and looked to be having an easy time. But when he saw Tyranny, he could only grumble bitterly. They had been waiting for him!

Soaring Tiger!

Han Wenqing wasn’t polite. He locked onto the Falling Light Blade. Desert Dust jumped towards him and kicked.

But as soon as Ye Xiu saw Tyranny waiting for him, he knew the situation wasn’t good. How could he just keep going? He cancelled Falling Light Blade, but intentionally let himself continue falling towards them to keep Tyranny’s attention onto him. When he saw Desert Dust approach, he immediately had Lord Grim finish the hand seals.

The shadow clone left behind poofed into smoke when Desert Dust struck. Ye Xiu was quite bold. Lord Grim had teleported directly into the center of Tyranny’s formation.

Desert Dust wasn’t there though. There were only long-ranged attackers there.

Chapter 1529 - Being Familiar Only Makes It More Troublesome

Shining Cut! Charge! Colliding Stab!

Lord Grim used three movement skills back to back, attacking the three characters in a triangular formation.

All three players dodged. Not a single hit landed on any of them, but his attacks carved out a triangle deep into the sand.

Son of a bitch!

Tyranny felt astonished seeing the grooves in the sand. They hadn’t expected Ye Xiu to be able to find the key point to this map.

The sand dune was crumbling, and the sand was sliding downwards. However, Tyranny was also situated on the sand dune, yet their area was safe.

Why? How did he do it?

Ye Xiu didn’t know the details, but he clearly remembered that Tyranny’s two Gunners had started their assault with attacks towards the sand. In the beginning, he thought that their aim had been to lift the sand up to cover their movements, but now that he looked at it again, their attacks hadn’t been just to lift the sand up but to start the crumbling of the sand dune as well.

They used their attacks to create a hole in the surface of the sand to initiate the sinking of the sand. That was the idea that Ye Xiu was able to come up with at the moment, which was why he carved out that triangle.

In the blink of an eye, the triangle was erased by the sand. Ye Xiu could feel the movement of the sand underneath Lord Grim’s feet and confirmed his theory.

With the movement of the sand beginning to spread, Tyranny’s small safe harbor would soon be wiped away.

Tyranny knew that they couldn’t stay here much longer and began to retreat. However, at this moment, Bai Yanfei was startled by a realization.

His retreat path had been blocked by Lord Grim. In such a short amount of time, how many moves ahead had he planned? Cancelling Falling Light Blade to dodge Desert Dust’s attack, separating the three long-ranged Tyranny players while simultaneously destroying their safe zone, and also positioning himself such that he blocked off Bai Yanfei’s Rota.

Fortunately, Bai Yanfei wasn’t the only one who made the realization. Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie, the strategist who refused to overlook even the smallest of details, caught on to Ye Xiu’s intentions.

Pray, Sacred Fire!

Bai Yanfei immediately understood, and Rota began to move.

Lord Grim moved forward to block him, when a burst of white flame leapt in front of his path.

Ye Xiu immediately had Lord Grim stop, but in this short instant, Rota was able to Teleport past Lord Grim.

Bang bang bang bang.

The ones who were able to escape first, Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun, counterattacked, retreating while firing. However, the biggest threat came from behind.

Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust rushed straight for Lord Grim once again. Because he was moving with the sand, his speed was faster than before. As expected, since Tyranny had chosen this map, Tyranny seemed to be far more comfortable with the sand than Happy.

Boom boom boom!

But this time, before Desert Dust could reach Lord Grim, he heard an explosion. The sand in front of him had been blasted into the air, covering the sky. Even though it wouldn’t be able to stop him, it blocked his vision to a certain extent. No matter how brave Han Wenqing was, he didn’t dare get close to someone as crafty as Ye Xiu while blind.

Change directions!

Han Wenqing didn’t even try to approach the wave of sand to prevent Ye Xiu for using any underhanded tricks. When he turned around, he looked behind him and saw Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain sliding down from the sand dune. The cover from the sandstorm didn’t differentiate between friend or foe. Once Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain entered the sandstorm, Tyranny had lost her location as well. When she suddenly showed up in Han Wenqing’s view, she was already half way down from the sand dune.

No, it wasn’t just Su Mucheng.

Boundless Sea and Soft Mist. Fang Rui and Tang Rou were there as well.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks! Soft Mist raised her spear and charged forward. The sand swirled around the dragon as it flew towards Desert Dust. Not only had the sand not provided any resistance to the surging momentum of Dragon Breaks the Ranks, it had strengthened it.

On one end was Ye Xiu, who was hiding who knew what tricks behind the cover of the sand. On the other end was the powerful Dragon Breaks the Ranks. The two threats formed a pincer attack. Lord Grim’s position wasn’t just to seal off Rota’s retreat path. More importantly, he maintained a constant threat to Desert Dust. While the rest of Tyranny’s attention was on rescuing Bai Yanfei, Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu coordinated together to trap Han Wenqing.

Ye Xiu had simply picked a spot, yet it hid so many hidden motives. This was what it meant to be a top player!

But Han Wenqing was also a top player.

If there was no opening, then he simply had to make one. This sort of brute force method was his specialty.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

He moved while activating Reinforced Iron Bones. Desert Dust moved past the wall of sand, dodging Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks. But what did Lord Grim have in store for him?

Two hands stretched into the sand. In these hands was a dismantled Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, the Tonfa form.

Grab!

Han Wenqing was able to determine what it was immediately.

As expected, Ye Xiu had expected him to brute force his way out. He had also predicted correctly that he would use Reinforced Iron Bones to give himself Super Armor.

Grab skills ignored Super Armor.

Ye Xiu had predicted what Han Wenqing would do, but Han Wenqing had also predicted what Ye Xiu would do.

Stomach Kick!

Desert Dust kicked so fast that it was all just a blur to the audience. Then, they heard a “pa”. The Stomach Kick was fast enough to produce a sonic boom.

He had attacked later, but it was fast enough to arrive first.

However, it didn’t hit!

To be able to dodge such a fast kick, Ye Xiu must have predicted it.

Han Wenqing didn’t delay. The instant his Stomach Kick retracted, he kicked again.

Whirlwind Kick!

As he spun, he kicked up a bunch of sand.

His body had turned, but his head was still locked in the same direction. Han Wenqing was adjusting his line of sight as he used the move.

The Whirlwind Kick could be dodged, but the sand couldn’t be.

Crash…

Sand rained down smashing into Lord Grim, allowing Han Wenqing to see Lord Grim’s outline.

The Whirlwind Kick fell, and then another kick chased after that outline. The purpose of the Whirlwind Kick hadn’t been to attack the opponent, but to sweep up the sand.

Pa!

So many exchanges had happened in an instant. The kick should hit, but Han Wenqing immediately noticed that his kick had struck Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shield.

Nothing could be done. Ye Xiu was too familiar with him. Ye Xiu knew that he would use the kicked-up sand to attack. The attack had been too quick for him to dodge, but using his umbrella shield to block it wasn’t a problem.

Jump off the umbrella and then Eagle Stamp.

Han Wenqing instinctively wanted to use this move, but a thought suddenly flashed into his mind.

Wasn’t Ye Xiu able to predict what he would do because of his instinctive habits? Facing an opponent who knew him this well, it was only by doing something unexpected would he be able to give him a surprise.

But with this slight hesitation, Han Wenqing immediately noticed that the moment Desert Dust missed, Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had retracted.

A cold light flashed as a sword swung towards him.

It was only then did Han Wenqing realize that his Desert Dust was in a situation no different from being knocked up into the air.

It had only been an instant, yet in this instant, Han Wenqing had lost the initiative. He didn’t panic though. His Desert Dust straightened up in the air, Thousand Ton Drop!

His Reinforced Iron Bones was still active. With Thousand Ton Drop, no matter how powerful the attack, it wouldn’t be able to make his Desert Dust budge. Han Wenqing was prepared to take the sword slash. But when he saw the sword light spinning, Han Wenqing suddenly realized that something wasn’t right.

It didn’t deal much damage, but wherever the sword light passed, space itself seemed to warp, giving it a different type of strength. Because of the yellow sand, it wasn’t until it got close that Han Wenqing was able to recognize it. But it was already too late to react.

Spellblade skill, Wave Wheel Slasher!

Sword light cut apart the void. The spell waves formed a seal, locking the target in place. For Swordsman classes, whether or not you were a Spellblade, it was a must-learn skill to deal with Super Armor.

Facing a Swordsman, Han Wenqing would have been 100% on guard against it.

But because he was facing Ye Xiu, an unspecialized, in such a fast-paced fight, Han Wenqing had overlooked this possibility.

The difficulties of the unspecialized lay here. No matter how familiar he was with Ye Xiu, he wasn’t familiar with this class because of its uniqueness. The more experienced the player, the more the player relied on what possible options their opponent’s class had in a given situation. However, these sort of intuition didn’t work facing an unspecialized.

And Han Wenqing was an old rival of Ye Xiu and understood him incomparably well. However, he would instinctively think of him as a Battle Mage. He had to force himself to unlearn his habits against him because he wasn’t facing One Autumn Leaf. After that, he had to comb through what possible options an unspecialized had. But because each form of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could have a bonus skill added to it, in theory, it meant that apart from class advance skills, Ye Xiu had access to any skill in Glory. Han Wenqing wasn’t a robot. No matter how big-brained he was, how could he sort through so many options in an instant?

The unspecialized was indecipherable.

You had no experience against the class. Your intuition would fail you. The transformations that Lord Grim’s weapon had access to broke through the limits of what a player could think up. And because of the extremely fast-paced combat, there was simply no way to predict what skills an unspecialized might use. Even if he understood Ye Xiu’s style and his habits, he couldn’t pick out what Ye Xiu would do next. There were simply too many options to consider.

This familiarity became a burden. His familiarity made him instinctively react a certain way, which gave out an opening.

Han Wenqing had been trying hard to remind himself that he was no longer facing a Battle Mage.

But just telling himself that couldn’t stop the battle habits and intuition he had built up through eight years of rivalry. In a crisis, his instincts had been polished through many years of experience, and that made his skills incomprehensive.

“How difficult!” His evaluation from ten years before never felt closer today.

Chapter 1530 - Response, Negligence

Dancing Rain, Boundless Sea, and Soft Mist rushed forward together. Desert Dust, who was trapped by Wave Wheel Slasher, looked to be in a dire situation. However, no one forgot that this was a team competition. The broadcast no longer focused on Desert Dust and switched over to the others on Tyranny.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Negative Nine Degrees, and Rota. Sure enough, the three long-ranged attackers had already set out. They moved like the wind, focusing their long-ranged attacks on Happy’s healer, Little Cold Hands, who was standing far away at the back; he hadn’t rushed over to attack Han Wenqing like the others on Happy.

Sacrifice Han Wenqing for a trade?

Tyranny’s choice was truly brave, decisively abandoning their captain and their core player. As for Little Cold Hands? When he had been using Angel Wings, he had already been the main target for Tyranny’s long-ranged attackers. Later, the sudden death charge directly into their formation from Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had destroyed their little safe zone, leading to a slight strategic shift from Tyranny.

As soon as they regained their footing, they continued to bite at Little Cold Hands. It was as if they didn’t even see Desert Dust’s predicament.

What to do?

Tyranny had been decisive. Now, it was Happy’s turn to be troubled. With this trade, even though Happy would be able to eliminate Tyranny’s captain, it would be at the sacrifice of their healer. In a one to one trade, the healer had to be prioritized. In the team competition, this was practically an established rule.

Understanding this rule, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain shift targets.

Boom boom boom.

Her explosions lifted a cloud of sand into the air, reducing the visibility that Tyranny’s long-ranged attackers would have. But after those artillery shells exploded, it also led to a sudden change in the flow of the sand. Little Cold Hands, who had been standing there, felt the ground beneath him slip, and he fell onto his butt…

The Launcher’s heavy firepower was far more destructive than the likes of a Sharpshooter or Spitfire. On the other hand, Elementalists dealt magic damage. Their destructive abilities couldn’t compare to physical attacks.

Dancing Rain had created a wall of sand, obstructing the long-ranged attacks from Tyranny, just like she had intended. However, by blowing up a hole in the sand dune, the flow of sand suddenly accelerated.

“Careless!!” When Pan Lin saw Little Cold Hands slip and fall onto his butt, he criticized Su Mucheng.

But that wasn’t what Tyranny thought.

Don’t underestimate Su Mucheng’s cunning. This was the lesson that they had just learned in the group arena.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had switched directions. And Little Cold Hands, who was sitting on the sand dune, was now sliding down the sand dune.

Anyone with an eye for tactics should be able to understand.

By accelerating the downward flow of the sand, Little Cold Hands would be able to get under the protection of his teammates faster. Blowing a hole into the sand dune and accelerating the flow of the sand definitely wasn’t out of carelessness. It had been intentional. As for Little Cold Hands slipping and falling onto his butt, that had been intentional from An Wenyi as well. He wasn’t as technically skilled as Ye Xiu and the others on Happy. Trying to control his character in the moving sand was very difficult for him. He understood Su Mucheng’s intentions, but he wasn’t confident in being able to adjust to the sudden increase in speed.

As a result, he didn’t force himself to. Instead, he fell down, letting the sand carry him.

It was quite clever, and in a match, cleverness and decisiveness were often needed.

Soft Mist suddenly charged at Tyranny’s long-ranged attackers, interfering with their attacks towards Little Cold Hands. Lord Grim and Boundless Sea teamed up on Desert Dust, with Dancing Rain supporting them.

Happy had no intentions of letting Desert Dust go, and at the same time, they wanted to save Little Cold Hands.

It was a brilliant response. Those who saw through Happy’s solution praised them. Unfortunately, it stopped there.

Happy’s brilliant response wasn’t able to be carried out to completion because they had overlooked a certain someone.

Han Wenqing.

Han Wenqing was being attacked from all sides, and it looked as if Happy wouldn’t have any trouble dealing with Desert Dust, which was why everyone had focused on An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands instead.

Dancing Rain turned fire, Soft Mist switched directions. In that instant, Su Mucheng and Tang Rou indeed hadn’t been worried about Han Wenqing. After all, both Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were there.

But…

Thousand Ton Drop!

Desert Dust crashed to the ground, pressing on the loose sand with a thousand tons of force. His two legs sunk deep into the sand. Following afterwards, a whirlpool seemed to be created. The surrounding flow of sand above it all changed directions towards the deep pit smashed out by Desert Dust’s Thousand Ton Drop.

Of the four surrounding him, only Lord Grim who was below him had firm footing. The three above him, including Soft Mist who had switched directions, instantly lost their balance.

Thousand Ton Drop ignored Grab skills. Even if Ye Xiu had used a Toss or a Back Throw, Desert Dust wouldn’t have budged.

Only a move like Wave Wheel Slasher, which used magic to create its own space, could seal Desert Dust’s movements. However, Wave Wheel Slasher only lasted for so long, and it didn’t interrupt Thousand Ton Drop.

As a result, when Wave Wheel Slasher ended, Thousand Ton Drop continued.

Happy’s brilliant response was disrupted just like this by the trapped Desert Dust.

Ye Xiu immediately had Lord Grim attack. With Desert Dust’s legs stuck in the sand, he wasn’t going anywhere. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear. A Circle Swing was just about to nab Desert Dust, when he twisted around…

Not good!

Ye Xiu’s instincts were telling him to retreat.

Cancel and jump back!

Ye Xiu reacted extremely fast. The Circle Swing was cancelled, and Lord Grim jumped as far back as possible. However, the other three on Happy who were still regaining their balance couldn’t react in time. Desert Dust finished turning around, and all three characters were pulled into his grasp.

Spiralling Whirlwind!

A Level 70 Grappler skill. Han Wenqing had chosen this skill to put on his Desert Dust’s Silver weapon, Flame Fist!

Hua!

Yellow sand burst into the sky.

Desert Dust shot out of the ground. The spinning force produced by his two arms held tightly onto the three from Happy. They rose into the air along with Desert Dust, flipped upside down, and then crashed to the ground…

Pu pu pu…

Grab skills could not be Quick Recovered. The three slammed into the ground, creating three craters in the sand dunes and three waves of sand.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was in this area, but he didn’t go and rescue his teammates. Instead, Lord Grim ran towards a different direction. It looked like he was in a hurry, yet he didn’t use any movement skills.

It wasn’t that Ye Xiu didn’t want to, he couldn’t.

He could not save Su Mucheng and the others, and he could not increase his speed with a skill like Shining Cut.

Because the moment he dodged that Spiralling Whirlwind, he stepped onto a Sacred Fire…

Zhang Xinjie, Immovable Rock.

Han Wenqing’s most trusted partner had his back.

Ye Xiu’s choice was out of helplessness. Unable to use any skills, he didn’t dare fearlessly charge towards the enemy Cleric. If he moved any closer to Desert Dust, Han Wenqing would probably give him ten years worth of revenge.

The tides instantly shifted.

The three on Happy had been thrown into the sand, while Desert Dust calmly landed. Trapping and suppressing him wasn’t going to be possible anymore.

However, the one in the most danger was An Wenyi.

Happy’s response had been crushed instantly. Little Cold Hands was now sliding down into the mouth of the tiger. An Wenyi needed to get up and run away. This time, An Wenyi being called Happy’s weakness were no longer empty words. He tried his hardest to move his character in the river of sand. In the end, it looked like he was trying to doggy-paddle his way up.

The crowd laughed loudly seeing this scene, but not Tyranny.

An Wenyi looked to be in a sorry state. Little Cold Hands wasn’t moving gracefully at all, but his judgement was correct. The direction he chose to run away to was the worst possible direction for Tyranny. He had chosen to move towards the Lord Grim and Immovable Rock.

But Tyranny wasn’t worried at all.

Previously, Happy had neglected the trapped Han Wenqing. This time, they had neglected Zhang Xinjie. Tyranny’s two core had actually been overlooked…

All three long-ranged attackers fired at Little Cold Hands.

Multiple people targeting with a flustered rookie was much more efficient than Ye Xiu targeting an experienced Zhang Xinjie.

Tyranny’s reasoning was that simple. They had confidence in themselves and in Zhang Xinjie. An Wenyi had picked the best possible option, but it wasn’t enough to shake Tyranny.

Happy’s other three players had gotten up. When they saw the situation, they knew that they had to save Little Cold Hands. However, an imposing figure stood in their way.

Han Wenqing, Desert Dust.

One person, ready for a 1v3!

The crowd erupted!

This was their captain. When they needed him the most, 1v2, 1v3, 1v4, he wouldn’t retreat.

This bravery had never faltered no matter how much time had passed. Even if he was beginning to play more flexibly, when brute force was needed, he would proudly stand at the front.

Ten years, just like the past.

Chapter 1531 - Dependable Scheme

Wind continued to blow, and sand continued to fill the sky.

Han Wenqing’s 1v3 wasn’t simply out of bravery. Tyranny had chosen this map specifically, and he was taking advantage of it perfectly. Desert Dust moved effortlessly and nimbly compared to his three opponents. From time to time, his attacks would strike the sand, producing a change in the flow of sand. For Happy, it was an enormous hindrance.

Fang Rui and Su Mucheng could rely on their experienced to adapt to the flow of sand. However, with Han Wenqing constantly changing the flow, they had to focus much of their efforts onto adapting to the sand beneath them. As for Tang Rou, she was having an even more difficult time. Her experience in Glory was lacking, and had to rely on her reaction speed and hand speed to deal with the sand. The amount of effort she had to put in just to move around was frightening.

As such, Han Wenqing was able to hold them off despite it being a 1v3.

He didn’t need to win over his opponents. He just needed to keep them here until his teammates took care of Happy’s Little Cold Hands.

Happy obviously understood what Tyranny intended to do. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim continued to pursue Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock. He trusted his teammates. If they could get past Han Wenqing and get to An Wenyi, forming a defensive wall for him, An Wenyi could start putting his healing to use. It would become a 4v4 with Happy having the upper hand. Happy would have a healer, while Tyranny would not. What’s more, Tyranny’s healer would be in a 1v1 against Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu’s decision to pursue Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock seemed like it had been out of helplessness due to the Sacred Fire. But now, it had become a key chess piece on the board. However, for this chess piece to shine, it needed Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, and Tang Rou to break open the situation.

3v1, break through…

The task given to them didn’t seem hard at all. Those who understood Happy’s strategy felt amazed at Ye Xiu’s decision to target Immovable Rock. To them, it was a godlike play that would turn the tides of the match.

But no one would have expected that the three on Happy would be unable to get past Han Wenqing!

You couldn’t blame the three for not trying. Neither of them were playing poorly. The pro players watching the match put themselves in their shoes. Facing Han Wenqing’s attacks, none of them felt like they would be able to break out of his blockade easily.

It takes time to adapt to the sand.

They looked at the flow of the sand and how Desert Dust was constantly changing the direction of the flow. They thought to themselves: how would they break through this situation?

It was a habit that pro players had to improve themselves. It was only these types of difficult situations would would lead to this kind of serious thinking.

Time passed.

Dancing Rain would send out a few long-ranged attacks from time to time, but it wasn’t enough to affect the assault onto Little Cold Hands by Tyranny’s three long-ranged attackers. Happy’s three players weren’t taking much damage, but An Wenyi was having a rough time. He was being bombarded with spells and bullets from an Elementalist and two Gunners. What’s worse, two of these attackers specialized in AoE attacks, making it feel like he had nowhere to run to.

“I don’t believe it!!” A message from Fang Rui jumped out. Boundless Sea suddenly took a large step forward. Su Mucheng saw this and had Dancing Ran retreat.

Yes yes yes…

The pro players watching the match nodded their heads. They were taking advantage of the fact that Strikers had very low range. Their weakness was that the area under their control was small. Retreat and go around. It might take more time than going in a straight line, but it was definitely one way to get past him.

Boundless Sea and Dancing Rain didn’t only retreat. One went left, while the other went right, so Han Wenqing could only deal with one of them.

But Han Wenqing wasn’t troubled at all. He didn’t even glance at the two of them. It seemed like he knew how they would respond. His Desert Dust focused solely on Tang Rou’s Soft Mist.

The two had previously fought in the group arena. It had been an intense fight. In the end, Tang Rou relied on her health advantage to win over Han Wenqing.

However, in the team competition, this time, Tang Rou was losing.

The map affected her too much. In this environment, Tang Rou had no way to only concentrate on attacking. After a few exchanges, Desert Dust used an Emperor’s Fist, pushing Soft Mist ten steps back.

Turn around, sprint!

Desert Dust was ahead of Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea, and he headed straight for Little Cold Hands.

Kill!

His intentions were obvious.

Boundless Sea and Dancing Rain gave chase. Suddenly, a storm of fire rained down on them.

A swap!

Tyranny had made a swap. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust attacked Little Cold Hands, while the three long-ranged attackers targeted Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea.

Blossoms of light and magic explosions swallowed the two of them. Even though Boundless Sea activated Qi Wave Shield as a defensive option, he couldn’t completely protect both of them with it. Dancing Rain didn’t have any defensive skills.

Breaking out forcefully would be unwise. Su Mucheng could only have Dancing Rain return fire to see if she could create an opening.

“This isn’t too bad for Happy,” Li Yibo analyzed the recent changes in the fight.

“If this continues, both healers will be in a 1v1, and it’ll likely end in a trade: healer for healer,” Li Yibo continued.

“I see…” Pan Lin nodded. The broadcast switched over to the fight between Ye Xiu and Zhang Xinjie.

The king of 1v1s against a squishy Cleric. It was obvious who would win. It was simply a matter of time.

The Sacred Fire on Lord Grim had worn off a long time ago. He quickly used several movement skills to close in on Immovable Rock. The two were rather far from the rest of the battle. They were no longer on the sand dune.

Ye Xiu didn’t show any mercy, while Zhang Xinjie did his best to survive.

The two Master Tacticians knew where the key to this battle was. It could even be said that this key had been formed because of their clash in tactics.

However, neither of them spared a moment to take a look at the situation over there.

Even against a Cleric, Ye Xiu didn’t relax. Because from Immovable Rock’s direction of escape, he could see Zhang Xinjie’s intention.

Not far ahead was the support zone!

The switching of players was protected by the system. No attacks could interrupt it. If Zhang Xinjie reached there, he could swap with Tyranny’s sixth player, Lin Jingyan.

Of course, there was a time restriction on switching players. Players couldn’t just keep switching back and forth however they liked. However, just one switch was enough. Tyranny would be able to protect their important healer. As for the other end, Tyranny held the initiative. If Happy couldn’t save their healer, and Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock was able to escape, it would be disastrous for Happy.

Even if Little Cold Hands was rescued in the end, it wouldn’t be a problem for Tyranny. They would certainly retreat back ahead of time and rescue Zhang Xinjie.

Tyranny would not lose out either way. Zhang Xinjie liked safe and reliable plans.

Ye Xiu obviously wasn’t going to let him have his way. Lord Grim held onto Immovable Rock tightly, not giving him a chance to run.

Zhang Xinjie obviously couldn’t pray that Ye Xiu would make a mistake. He never believed in placing his hopes on luck. He persevered and waited. He was waiting for an opportunity, waiting for an opening when Ye Xiu attacked.

It’s here!

Zhang Xinjie was calm and cautious. This sort of personality made it easy for people to mistake him for having low hand speed. However, ever since he had joined the Alliance, he had never fallen out of the top ten in hand speed!

Glory’s number one healer was top-tier in reaction speed and hand speed even among pro players.

Charge!

The robed Cleric suddenly used this bold Knight skill.

For spectators familiar with the Glory competitive scene, it wasn’t anything novel. Pro characters were meant solely for PvP. As a result, many of their skill choices were different than those who needed to do dungeon quests.

For healers focused on PvP, learning a low-level skill from a Priest class like a Knight was nothing strange. When the opponent closed in, this sort of movement skill was very useful.

Immovable Rock had used Charge when he first tried to escape, but in the end, his movement capabilities couldn’t compare to an unspecialized. He was quickly caught. Zhang Xinjie didn’t hastily use Charge as soon as he could. He couldn’t underestimate Ye Xiu.

Even if it was an instant cast skill, it required the right timing.

He finally found an opportunity. He instantly Charged out like a warrior.

Hua!

As soon as he used Charge, his vision was blocked.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened in its shield form. Ye Xiu had reacted in the end. The shield was big, and the edges of the shield were able to block the Charge.

Clerics looked amazing when they used Charge. Their weapon was oftentimes a cross. When they used Charge, their cross would float in front of them, radiating with a holy light as if it were guiding the Cleric. Unfortunately, this holy light encountered a shield.

Charge couldn’t be completely nulled with a shield. What’s more, because of how big the umbrella shield was, it was rather light. In terms of priority, it was considered a weak shield. Even though a Cleric’s Charge couldn’t compare to a Knight’s, it couldn’t be completely blocked.

Immovable Rock’s Silver weapon, Backlight Cross, shined with white light, pulling Immovable Rock forward.

Lord Grim twisted his body, forcing his center of mass down to stop himself from sliding back.

The distance that Lord Grim slid back was rather unexpected. The terrain was the reason. The two were situated on loose sand. With a push, the sand gave way. The friction from sand couldn’t compare to that of solid ground. By the time, Lord Grim’s feet had sunk far enough into the sand to create enough resistance to stop the Charge, the skill duration was almost over.

Immovable Rock had pushed farther than expected, but it still wasn’t enough to reach the support zone. Suddenly, light burst out from Immovable Rock’s Backlight Cross, creating a circle of light. It looked astonishing, but the surface of the sand didn’t seem to be affected by it. However, Lord Grim, who was still holding up the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, was directly pushed back several steps by this light.

Paladin skill: Angel’s Might!

Chapter 1532 - Post Match What-Ifs

Paladin skill: Angel’s Might.

The skill forced the target back. It ignored Super Armor and resistance from shields.

After the Blue Rain home game against Happy, many analysts had mentioned that if Blue Rain’s healer, Xu Jingxi, had used an Angel’s Might against Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion, the outcome of that match would have been very different.

There were always all sorts of what-ifs after a match. And in this match between Happy and Tyranny, there were what-ifs as well, and Angel’s Might had once again become a hot topic.

Happy had lost.

The Angel’s Might from Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock hadn’t been the only turning point, but it was the most important one in the team competition. Angel’s Might forced Lord Grim back, and Zhang Xinjie was able to take advantage of that opportunity to reach the support zone. By the time Lord Grim was able to recover, his opponent had become Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder.

Post-match analysis had pointed out that Lord Grim could have theoretically intercepted Immovable Rock before he reached the support zone. But in the end, he was one step too slow.

One reason was that Zhang Xinjie’s reaction speed and hand speed weren’t slow. Another reason was that perhaps Ye Xiu had gotten old, or perhaps it was because the exhaustion that Tyranny had built up onto Ye Xiu had finally taken effect.

He had been just a hair off. No one could pinpoint the exact reason, not even Ye Xiu himself.

Happy needed to face the reality of it. The outcome of the second round between Happy and Tyranny ended in Happy’s defeat.

The two teams had returned back to the starting point. This set would be decided in the third game, and because Tyranny had placed higher than Happy in the regular season, the game would be held in Tyranny’s home stadium. However, the home stadium advantage was only limited to additional morale from the home team’s fans and income from ticket sales. Neither team had the advantage of choosing the maps in the deciding match. The maps would be chosen randomly, and they would be maps that no Glory player had ever seen before. The Glory game company had created maps specifically for the playoffs. Before these maps were used, no team would have information on them. The maps would be randomly picked from this collection of playoff maps on the day of the match.

It seemed as if neither side had the map advantage. However, Tyranny consisted of experienced old generals. Their ability to adapt to maps was absolutely higher than Happy’s rookies.

With the match taking place in Tyranny’s home stadium, even though they wouldn’t be choosing the maps, the support from the crowd would certainly have a positive effect on their morale.

The break between game two and game three was two days. It would be unwise for Happy to fly to City H and then fly back. As a result, during these two days, Tyranny could adjust their mindsets to face this final deciding game in the environment that they were most familiar with. As for Happy? Their only choice was to slowly digest their recent defeat in this unfamiliar environment.

The night that match ended, in this unfamiliar city and unfamiliar hotel, there were few people on Happy who were able to sleep soundly.

Chen Guo was someone who always worried, and sure enough, she wasn’t able to sleep. She rolled around in her bed, wanting to find someone to chat with, but at the same time, she didn’t want to bother anyone else. Unable to calm down, she browsed the Internet for three or four hours. Half the time, she was simply staring at a blank page.

There was still one more game left. It could be said that the battle had only just begun. Why did she need to be so nervous?

Chen Guo consoled herself, and then took a look at the page she had just opened. What a coincidence, it was a poll showing their chances in the next game.

Tyranny – 87.3%

Happy – 12.7%

“Fuck!” Chen Guo couldn’t help but curse. The poll was too lopsided! The first game had been Happy’s home game against Tyranny. At that time, people had favored Tyranny, but in the end, Happy had won. As a result, in Happy’s away game against Tyranny, although people still favored Tyranny, the support for Happy had been considerably higher. Why did it suddenly become this lopsided for the third game?

Chen Guo was irritated, thinking that it was unfair. But in her heart, she knew that her uneasiness and worry was because she might be unconsciously thinking the same thing…

Even though half of those three or four hours were her staring blankly at the computer, she had still looked over quite a few comments on their prospects.

Chen Guo had a certain level of ability now. She was no longer the same as before, where she simply believed anything that seemed somewhat reasonable. When she read commentaries online, even when it was by a well-known analyst, she wouldn’t blindly believe it. She would think on her own and come up with her own opinion. But the more she looked, the more nervous she became because she agreed with many of these opinions. She couldn’t come up with anything to refute them.

Such as the advantage that Tyranny had with the random maps.

Such as Happy having trouble adjusting in an unfamiliar environment.

Such as the blow to Happy’s morale after their recent defeat.

These were all valid points. No matter how much Chen Guo didn’t want to think about them, they would still be there.

Especially the part about morale. Chen Guo had personally seen the disappointment and listlessness from Happy after the loss.

Everyone in Happy is strong! After a night’s rest, they’ll be back to normal! Chen Guo kept telling herself this, but she herself couldn’t fall asleep.

After browsing the Internet for those three or four hours, she still couldn’t sleep. After seeing how big the gap was between the two teams in the poll, she definitely couldn’t sleep.

Chen Guo furiously gave a vote for Happy. Nothing changed. The disparity continued to stare back at her.

At this moment, her QQ flashed. Chen Guo checked. It was Ye Xiu.

“You’re not going to sleep?” Ye Xiu asked.

“You’re not sleeping either.” Chen Guo saw that, like herself, Ye Xiu hadn’t slept. She wasn’t happy at all about it, though – it only made her feel more depressed. In her eyes, Ye Xiu was Happy’s unshakeable pillar. No matter what situation they were in, he would never waver. But it looked like even he couldn’t sleep. It seemed like the problem was far more grave than she had imagine.

“Oh, I got up to steal veggies,” Ye Xiu said**.

“…..” Chen Guo was speechless. She had been with the guy for two years. When had he ever cared about veggies?

“Why can’t I steal your veggies?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chen Guo was furious. She hadn’t taken care of her farm for many years and hadn’t harvested her veggies in a long time. Once someone stole your veggies, you wouldn’t have any veggies left for anyone else to steal. These were the basics. Did he really think he could trick her, saying that he got up to steal her veggies?

“Go to bed. Everything will be fine,” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo really wanted to ask what he meant by “fine,” but in the end, she simply typed out an “Okay.”

**(TLN: The author is talking about Happy Farm, which was a very popular farming social network game in China that came out in 2008. You can steal other people’s veggies in this game. The most notable clone/rip-off of Happy Farm is FarmVille (released in 2009).

She turned off her computer and went to bed. Chen Guo tossed and turned restlessly. She would go to sleep for a bit and then wake up. Who knew how many times she had woken up during the night? When she got up to take a look at herself in the morning, she had two dark bags under her eyes.

Ah, our morale! Chen Guo thought to herself. How was she supposed to see everyone? Her nervousness and uneasiness were obvious. It might infect the others.

Chen Guo was still feeling gloomy when she heard a knock from the door.

“Who is it?” Chen Guo asked.

“Are you up, Guo Guo?” Tang Rou answered.

Chen Guo opened the door. Tang Rou was standing outside in her pajamas. When Tang Rou saw Chen Guo, she immediately let out a laugh.

“Looks like you didn’t sleep well again,” Tang Rou said.

“Why do you mean again…” Chen Guo mumbled unhappily. It was true, though. Ever since Team Happy had become official, Chen Guo had often lost a lot of sleep. Every night before a match, she would toss and turn, unable to sleep. Whenever Happy won a match, she wouldn’t be able to sleep because she was too excited. Whenever Happy lost a match, she wouldn’t be able to sleep because she was too depressed. Back when she was an Excellent Era fan, it would only happen occasionally. Now that she was completely invested into Happy, from the Challenger League to the playoffs, Chen Guo had countless sleepless nights.

“Hurry up and get ready. Let’s get breakfast!” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo went to wash her face and asked, “What about everyone else?”

“Ye Xiu told everyone that was up to go to the practice room,” Tang Rou said.

“Why wasn’t I told?” Chen Guo was puzzled.

Tang Rou bent down and picked up a slip of paper from under Chen Guo’s door. She handed it over to Chen Guo for her to take a look.

“A slip of paper? How crude!” Chen Guo looked down on it in disdain.

“He was afraid of disturbing the others!” Tang Rou said.

Chen Guo stared blankly. It was a good method to communicate with them without disturbing anyone. There was no set time either. It was simply whenever you got up.

Chen Guo wasn’t in the mood to try go back to bed. She quickly tidied herself up. She didn’t bother putting on any makeup to hide the bags under her eyes and dragged Tang Rou out the door with her. She wasn’t in the mood to eat breakfast, but since Tang Rou wanted to, she couldn’t just let her starve.

After eating breakfast, the two went to the practice room.

In away games, the home team would provide them practice rooms. The big teams would have practice rooms specifically for away teams. In the early days, when teams seeked victory by fair means or foul, teams used to intentionally make the away team practice rooms worse to affect the away team’s practice and mood. Later, the Alliance took charge and eliminated this sort of underhanded move by investigating the practice rooms given to away teams ahead of time. Nowadays, no team would suffer from this sort of practice.

Happy had used Tyranny’s away-team practice room before in the regular season and the previous game. The room was quite nice. With Tyranny’s personality, they would never fall so low as to engage in these types of dirty practices.

When the two arrived at the practice room, Ye Xiu was already there. There was also Su Mucheng, Qiao Yifan, Luo Ji, and An Wenyi. The others weren’t there.

Chen Guo looked around. She couldn’t tell how they were doing from their expressions, but at the very least, no one had dark circles under their eyes like her.

She casually gave them a greeting. Chen Guo and Tang Rou went to find their seats. No one said anything. Only the sound of keyboard tapping and mouse clicking could be heard. Ye Xiu got up and waved to Tang Rou. “Here’s a video I want you to take a look at.”

“Sure,” Tang Rou nodded her head and opened the video that Ye Xiu sent her. It was a video of Soft Mist showing clips from last night’s match. Soon afterwards, Ye Xiu got up from his seat and headed over towards her.

Chapter 1533 - Everyone With Their Own Video

Chen Guo’s attention immediately shifted to Tang Rou’s computer screen. Ye Xiu must have compiled the video last night to help Tang Rou improve.

“How is it?” Ye Xiu went behind Tang Rou and watched the video together with her.

Tang Rou didn’t answer back, watching the video carefully. Chen Guo was also thinking, but… even at her skill level, she could tell that the video didn’t quite look like the usual analysis clips that Ye Xiu gathered after a match. The angle, distance, and rhythm didn’t look right.

Tang Rou’s brows were beginning to furrow. It seemed like she was also having trouble understanding what she was watching.

“You’re not going to listen to the sound? It’ll be better that way!” Ye Xiu advised.

Oh! He recorded his own voice? So that’s the case! Ye Xiu had never done that before! Chen Guo suddenly understood. Even though she was curious, she didn’t fight over the headphones. She watched as Tang Rou take the headphones and put them on. Her expression became even more puzzled. Then, she stopped looking at the clip and turned her head to look at Ye Xiu.

“How was my music choice? You play music. What do you think?” Ye Xiu was in high spirits.

“Pretty good…”

“Music choice?” Chen Guo was starting to feel puzzled again. Tang Rou removed her headphones and handed them over to Chen Guo. Chen Guo immediately put them on. Hype music started playing as she watched the video…

The video became more fun to watch, but at the same time, it also indicated that this wasn’t a video reviewing her mistakes in last night’s match. It was a compilation of highlights showing off her skill.

“It’s pretty good, right?” Ye Xiu asked Chen Guo for her opinion.

“This was what you were working on all of last night?” Chen Guo asked.

“Yup!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

“…”

“Amazing, right?”

“Yeah… amazing…” Chen Guo struggled to nod her head. She had hoped that Ye Xiu would give her an explanation, but…”

“Haha,” Ye Xiu laughed and then left.

“Hey hey hey!” Chen Guo couldn’t bear it anymore and caught up to him.

“Hm?”

Ye Xiu dragged Ye Xiu to a corner and lowered her voice: “You spent all of last night making this type of video? What are you planning?”

“I’m planning on showing it to everyone!” Ye Xiu said.

“What’s the point?” Chen Guo asked.

“For them to watch?” Ye Xiu was starting to get confused, seeing Chen Guo’s expression.

“Just to watch, nothing else?”

Ye Xiu thought about it: “Well, there’s music to accompany it, so they can listen too…”

“You… want everyone to watch these videos to raise the team’s morale!” Chen Guo said.

“It’s better than looking at those post-match reviews, no? Weren’t you reading through those all night yesterday?” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo wanted to refute it, but she couldn’t. Everyone knew about her habits. There was no point hiding it!

“It’ll liven up the mood!” Ye Xiu said to her.

“…” Chen Guo was speechless.

“Every match brings new possibilities. Whether it’s a win or a loss, the past doesn’t mean anything. During these two days, it wouldn’t be good to try to force anything. In fact, it would probably mess up our original rhythm. Rather than having that happen, it’d be better to give everyone some confidence. We can only keep moving forward,” Ye Xiu began speaking more seriously.

“Why didn’t you just say this to them?” Chen Guo said.

“Because…” Ye Xiu turned his head back,” Not everyone’s up yet.”

“You’re so annoying,” Chen Guo walked away furiously, ignoring Ye Xiu. She returned to her seat and looked at Tang Rou. She had put on her headphones and was watching the video again.

“What do you think?” Chen Guo asked.

“It feels pretty good watching it,” Tang Rou smiled.

The others on Happy arrived at the practice room one after the other. Each of them received their own highlight video. The ones who played last night had clips from last night. Those who hadn’t played last night had clips from past matches. The contents of those videos were all highlight clips showing off their skill.

“Wow! Wow! Wow!” Fang Rui watched his highlight video and made a lot of noise, “What a high quality video! I didn’t know you had talent in this area.”

“I’m only so-so,” Ye Xiu replied modestly.

“I’m going to upload it,” Fang Rui said. Shortly afterwards, Chen Guo discovered that Fang Rui really had uploaded his highlight video to Glory’s most popular video-sharing site. Most of those videos were players trying to show off. A God wanted to squeeze in there too and fight them for the top spot?

The outcome was obvious.

“The Golden Right Hand – The Greatest – The Matchless – The Magnificent Qi Master – Boundless Sea.” Such a ridiculous title was eye-catching enough. When people clicked on it, they saw that it was indeed Boundless Sea. It wasn’t anything new, though. It consisted of clips from last night’s match, and anyone could make this sort of clip. But when everyone saw who had posted the video, they exploded. The uploader was Fang Rui himself. The account had been verified by the site. It was Fang Rui without a doubt!

As a result, it no longer mattered what the contents of the video were. Fang Rui’s name alone was enough to make the video trending.

Not long afterwards, it was no longer just that site. The video was uploaded everywhere to all the major video-sharing sites. In some places, there were even news articles that had been published. The widespread opinion was criticism of Fang Rui not using this time to review last night’s match, instead using the time to make a highlight video of himself and uploaded it to the Internet to show off. What sort of mentality was that?

What mentality?

Chen Guo didn’t know either!

But Wei Chen couldn’t endure it anymore, seeing Fang Rui’s smug look. He also uploaded his. However, he hadn’t played last night. Most of the clips were from past matches, and he also wasn’t as popular as Fang Rui, so the video wasn’t as popular either. Although his video also caused quite a bit of commotion, it couldn’t compare to Fang Rui’s.

What is Happy doing?

Even though Wei Chen’s video showed off past clips, his video had been uploaded shortly after Fang Rui’s. It was a very subtle detail that many people caught onto.

And how could Steamed Bun not join in? Wei Chen called out to him, and Steamed Bun also uploaded his video.

Steamed Bun had been the sixth player in yesterday’s team competition. By the time he came out, the match was already over. He didn’t make any crazy plays, but even so, he had enough moments to make a beautiful video.

“Another one, another one…”

The Glory community was astonished. They felt like they had grasped Happy’s thoughts. Who on Happy would be next?

But the others on Happy weren’t the type to blindly join in. They had some fun observing what all the commotion was about, but that was it. Then, they took their own videos and carefully hid them away. Because of their understanding of their teammates, even if they didn’t upload them, they couldn’t rule out the possibility of those three from doing it for them.

Unfortunately for Luo Ji, by the time he realized it, it was too late.

“Let me help you!” Steamed Bun’s devotion to righteousness inspired reverence. He took Luo Ji’s video and uploaded it.

“NO!” Luo Ji hastily tried to stop him.

But it was futile to think that Luo Ji could overpower Steamed Bun in real life.

“There’s no need to be polite,” Steamed Bun blocked Luo Ji with one hand, while uploading Luo Ji’s video with the other.

“Sure enough!”

The Glory community had been waiting for Happy’s fourth video.

“It’s from Bao Rongxing again?” Everyone was slightly surprised, but when they saw the video, they saw that it was Luo Ji’s Concealed Light.

Luo Ji hadn’t played last night, but he had been the star of the first game with Tyranny. It had given the Alliance quite a bit of trouble. They weren’t sure if they should give him MVP of the match in the team competition.

They could give it to him, but he didn’t actually have any eye-catching moments in combat. They could choose not to, but that match had been decided by him single-handedly. In the end, the MVP title for the team competition was given to Luo Ji. Without him, Happy would not have won so decisively. This was the reasoning given by the broadcast.

The video showed Luo Ji creating that decisive play in the team competition.

In the lonely depths of the forest, Concealed Light wandered around, ordering his summons around. The bustling scene all around, along with the accompanying music, made for a fun watch.

“Amazing!” Players typed out in the comments below. It had undoubtedly been a brilliant play. There was not a single mistake. The work done by the summons was like a symphony.

The people wanted more. The video-sharing site received a spike in users. Countless people were refreshing for Happy’s next video.

But there was none.

The others had hidden away their videos, refusing to let Fang Rui, Wei Chen, or Steamed Bun do as they pleased with them. The video uploads stopped there.

After a night of hard work, this was what he came up with? Seeing Fang Rui and the others pester Qiao Yifan and An Wenyi to upload their videos, Chen Guo continued to be speechless.

But she could at least feel that the team was in a much better mood compared to last night. Everyone was in high spirits as they watched these videos.

Afterwards, now that everyone was up, Ye Xiu said the words that Chen Guo was wondering why he didn’t say it. He added another sentence after “We can only keep moving forward.”

“Let’s watch today’s match tonight.”

Tonight’s match was Samsara versus Tiny Herb. The winner would move onto the finals. But seeing where they would be watching it, Chen Guo was surprised. Ye Xiu said that they were going to watch the match, but he had never mentioned that they would be watching it with Tyranny…

They would soon be going into a fight to the death. Wouldn’t it be awkward gathering together now?

Chen Guo felt somewhat uncomfortable and talked very carefully. When she looked at the others on Happy, she saw that the rookies looked somewhat uncomfortable too. It was only Ye Xiu and the other experienced players who were at ease, especially Fang Rui. He was having a good time chatting with his old friend, Lin Jingyan.

Why’d we need to watch it with Tyranny? Chen Guo tried to understand. She felt like there was some purpose to it, but it wasn’t convenient to ask Ye Xiu right now.

The match began.

“I’m betting on Samsara winning. Does anyone on Tyranny dare to bet against me?” Wei Chen asked arrogantly.

“We favor Samsara too,” Zhang Xinjie replied.

Chapter 1534 - A Change in Eras

Samsara, Tiny Herb. These two teams were currently the only two teams in the Alliance with two championships. However, Samsara’s two championships were consecutive, more impressive than Tiny Herb’s, which were interrupted in between. In addition, they were also on their way to their third consecutive championship, but Tiny Herb? They had already gone two years without anything.

The majority of the current Tiny Herb was no longer the Tiny Herb that had obtained two championships. Their God of Healing, Fang Shiqian, their unassuming yet diligent and reliable Knight, Deng Fusheng, had already left Tiny Herb and Glory.

After Tiny Herb’s two championship wins, they went through a reconstruction. People could see that now, Tiny Herb’s most important player, Magician Wang Jiexi, had began the countdown on his time at Tiny Herb. Many players who debuted in the third season had already retired, and though team aces would usually retire later than normal players, of the Season 3 debuts, Seaside’s All-Star level ace Zhao Yang had already retired last year and 301 Degrees’ captain Yang Cong had also abdicated from this position as the core of the team after Bai Shu joined. He was clearly getting ready to leave things to his juniors as well.

Wang Jiexi was still a member of Tiny Herb’s main roster, an irreplaceable ace player. The most irreplaceable player.

How much longer would Tiny Herb spend depending on Wang Jiexi? Everyone who cared about Tiny Herb cared about this question. Just from onstage performance, it didn’t seem like Wang Jiexi had declined in any way, but he was still getting old. There was only one explanation for his stable performance despite the erosion of age: he was over-exerting himself.

Yang Cong, having abdicated from his position of ace, might slowly only play in rotation and become a substitute player if he continued to lower the standards to which he held his own performance. With this pace, he’d still be able to play at decently high level for a good two, maybe even three years.

What about Wang Jiexi?

If he continued the way he was, leading Tiny Herb on this charge to the finish, how long would he be able to last?

Everyone was worried, but they couldn’t help but admire him for his spirit and willingness to sacrifice himself for his team. If he was willing to persist, then they were willing to bear witness to what he had left to give and hope this kind of sacrifice could earn him something in return.

However, the obstacle in Wang Jiexi’s way, in Tiny Herb’s way, was Samsara. The mighty Samsara.

Compared to Tiny Herb, Samsara was a team currently in its prime. Their players had mostly joined in Season 5 and 6, and they were all at the peak age of their pro careers. Even the younger ones, like Sun Xiang, for example, had debuted in Season 7 with experience in weaker teams and powerhouse teams and even the Challenger League before coming to Samsara. Sun Xiang’s four years in the pro Glory scene had been even more comprehensive than many veterans.

In Season 8, Samsara beat Blue Rain in the finals.

In Season 9, Samsara struck down Tyranny in the finals.

This season, they met Tiny Herb in the semi-finals.

Samsara was going through these former championship teams one after the other. It seemed like they were using this method to announce to the people of Glory that a new chapter had begun in the Alliance, and Samsara was the author of this new chapter. Though many people were unwilling to accept this, they couldn’t deny that Samsara was a strong team.

Take the two teams currently watching this match together.

Tyranny was an old team with old players who refused to leave the stage. They felt an even deeper desire. As for Happy? As a new team with newcomers, they should’ve been a team of an even newer era than Samsara, but this team just had to have Ye Xiu in it, and Wei Chen, and Su Mucheng from the Golden Generation, as well as Fang Rui who was from the same generation as Samsara’s Zhou Zekai. It was complicated and hard to say what sort of attitude Happy would have for Samsara.

However, for this match between Tiny Herb and Samsara, the two teams didn’t hesitate to place their bets on a Samsara victory.

The home team Samsara didn’t choose any map with particular strategic value, just something the were more familiar with, and then faced Tiny herb head on.

Five to three.

Zhou Zekai, the fourth player on Samsara’s side, closed the curtains on the group area.

In the following team competition, Samsara used their map advantage, not underestimating their opponent in the slightest.

Zhang Xinjie generally never gave uncertain answers, and therefore very rarely made predictions of matches. However, this time, he gave a very clear cut answer, “Samsara will win.”

Yes, Samsara will win.

The situation was already clear enough.

“Any opinions on Samsara? Feel free to tell us; it’s not like you’ll need it.” Ye Xiu smiled.

There was no way that Zhang Xinjie wouldn’t get what Ye Xiu was after. He smiled and ignored the question. Behind him, Zhang Jiale leaned over, rebutting Ye Xiu. “How about you talk about your opinion on Samsara.”

“They’re really good,” Ye Xiu said.

“No shit,” Zhang Jiale replied.

“Even better than last year,” Ye Xiu then added.

Silence.

Last year, Tyranny had fallen to Samsara in the finals. Tyranny’s players had been unable to keep up the fight against time. This time? Their abilities had been eroded by yet another year, while Samsara had only grown stronger.

It really was time for a new era to begin.

Even if one of them managed to snipe Samsara this year, no matter if it was Ye Xiu or Tyranny’s veterans, they didn’t have the power to compete with Samsara further.

Samsara would start anew next year, but what about them? Their era had was one to be left behind.

“Even if we’re just a rock they stumble over, we’ll make them fall as harshly as we can,” Han Wenqing said.

Everyone understood what he meant. They could only make their trip and delay them, but they wouldn’t be able to trap them. Today, they could only be that small rock in their way. No matter how stubborn Han Wenqing was, he still had to accept the inevitable.

“Then we’ll crush them under our feet.” Unexpectedly, someone spoke up from behind Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu turned his head and saw Tang Rou, as well as Steamed Bun, Qiao Yifan, Mo Fan, An Wenyi, Luo Ji…

They weren’t from the same era as the veterans. The veterans might be worn-away pebbles, but they weren’t. For Ye Xiu and co, this was an ending, but for them, it was only the beginning.

“You’re right,” Ye Xiu chuckled. “Then, let’s lay the best path possible for you!”

“Crush Samsara!” Zhang Jiale added.

“What are you spazzing out about? Your destiny is to be crushed by us,” Ye Xiu mocked.

“Fuck!” Zhang Jiale bristled. He got too into it, forgetting for a moment that these guys were fighting to the death with them next.

“Let’s go. You guys should go and prepare for your defeat as well!” Ye Xiu said, getting up.

The match wasn’t over, but even Zhang Xinjie dared to say the result. There was no more suspense to the match. It had been over for a while now. Ye Xiu led Happy’s players out first.

“Is it really okay to let those guys walk off all smug like that?” Zhang Jiale raged. He was very much displeased with the lack of response to Ye Xiu’s trash talk.

“If there was any use in trash talking, then why even bother competing with matches?” Han Wenqing said.

“Actually it’s because we can’t win in trash talk, no?” Lin Jingyan said honestly.

There was a moment of silence.

“Fuck.” Shockingly enough, Han Wenqing cursed, unable to say anything against that.

“Hey!” That was when Song Qiying, attention still on the match, suddenly gave a cry of surprise.

Everyone looked over.

The match that they had thought was set in stone had suddenly rippled. Though in the end it didn’t manage to change the final result, but…

“I made too hasty a judgement,” Zhang Xinjie decided. That meant that while those ripples made by Tiny Herb’s new generation players Liu Xiaobie, Gao Yingjie, and the others didn’t manage to turn the tables, it did create the hope of a comeback.

Samsara won, one step closer to their goal of three consecutive championships. Tiny Herb lost, but people unexpectedly saw in this match that Tiny Herb had a future that wasn’t as simple as it seemed at first glance. Perhaps it wasn’t as people had feared, that Tiny Herb would crumble with Wang Jiexi’s departure.

Tomorrow. Everyone had a tomorrow.

For Happy, tomorrow was the last day off before the deciding match of the quarterfinals.

“Well, what must be said must be said.” Happy’s members gathered in the practice room once again in the morning, with Ye Xiu making a speech.

“Never mind all of you, even I’ve never played in the third game of a set before,” Ye Xiu said.

“Neither have I,” Wei Chen added.

“You haven’t even done this for as long as I have!” Fang Rui retorted.

“Shut up, all of you!” Chen Guo yelled.

Silence fell.

“Continue,” Chen Guo directed at Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu let out the breath he had held in, as he was used to thinking that the “shut up” was also directed at him.

“We don’t know the map beforehand, so there’s no way of making arrangements for it. Even the lineup will be decided last minute. So we all have to prepare to be called up at any moment. I want you all to keep that in mind,” Ye Xiu continued.

“Understood.” Everyone nodded.

“We won’t make arrangements today. You should all take time to prepare yourselves however you want. Either way, we need to be in top shape for tomorrow’s match. You heard what we said last night. Since Tyranny’s Han Wenqing has casted Tyranny as a pebble, then we have no choice but to adhere to that and kick them aside,” Ye Xiu said.

Everyone laughed. They had all heard Han Wenqing’s words, but they all knew that this wasn’t a role he had casted Tyranny for, just musing over things from the perspective of a veteran. Ye Xiu had obviously been included as part of the pebble metaphor, but now Ye Xiu had decided to go off from that. It was obviously a joke!

“Kick them aside!!” Steamed Bun cheered.

Happy’s members facepalmed. Okay, so it wasn’t that obvious to some people.

“Our target is the championship. Did anyone take a look at what happened last night after we left?” Ye Xiu asked.

“I saw some comments online and went to finish watching the match,” An Wenyi said. “Tiny Herb almost made a comeback.”

“Oh?” Many of them made noises of surprise. As expected, most of them hadn’t bothered to pay the match any attention after leaving.

“See that? That’s competition. Nothing is certain until the very last moment. Even like last night when we were all certain of a steady victory on Samsara’s side, miracles can still happen,” Ye Xiu said.

“To most people, our victory in the Challenger League was a miracle, and winning the championship will be even more of a miracle. Since they like miracles so much, then we have no choice but to create another miracle for them to witness,” Ye Xiu said.

They all laughed again. Miracles were miracles. He was joking again.

“Let’s create our miracle!” However, this joke gained everyone’s support. Whether out loud, or silently to themselves, they all cheered.

Chapter 1535 - Settling the Ten Year Rivalry

The day of the decisive battle between Happy and Tyranny finally arrived, and this showdown was drawing a great deal of attention. The other semifinals match between Samsara and Tiny Herb had already been decided, with Samsara entering the finals. The victor of today’s match would be the the team competing against Samsara for this year’s championship.

Tyranny was the team that had met Samsara in last season’s finals. This season, many people thought that they weren’t doing well, but unexpectedly, having curbed their domineering attitude, they were able to quietly kill their way to this level. The other team, Happy, a new team, a new team that had killed its way here from the Challenger League, was already standing at the doorstep of the finals. Even if their path ended here, this was a sight that had never been witnessed before in Glory history.

Ye Xiu, this name with which everyone was both familiar and not. He had left this stage, but he had not vanished, and now, he led this new team to stand once again before the world’s eyes.

I’m back!

Just like he had said after winning the Challenger League, he had indeed returned here, his sword pointing toward the highest stage. But now, he first needed to conquer this city.

The final match, Tyranny’s home game. There was not an empty seat in sight.

The two teams had only just entered the stadium when the audience rose up in a surging roar, as though this was already the highlight. Tyranny’s fans made use of their numbers advantage, rallying and cheering on their team with vigor. The small bit of noise from Happy’s fans in the away team section was completely smothered.

Even though this was a life-or-death match, the pre-match customs were still the same. The two teams entered, acknowledged the crowd, and then headed toward their respective player areas.

But those who watched these matches often all knew that one person would stay behind at this time.

Ye Xiu!

Regular season, playoffs, he was always Happy’s first player. After the necessary greetings before the match’s start, he usually just stayed onstage, directly going to compete in the first battle.

This time was no different. Ye Xiu once again remained onstage. In that short moment, Happy’s fans proudly burst forth with especially loud cheers.

Ye Xiu, first to battle, the invincible symbol. From the regular season to the playoffs, not a single person had yet managed to refute that.

But just a moment later, the proud cheers of the Happy fans were once again drowned out by the roars of the Tyranny fans. Because this time, Team Tyranny made a tit-for-tat response.

They, too, had a player remaining onstage.

Their captain, Han Wenqing. After avoiding Ye Xiu in the group arena for two matches of this season’s playoffs, this time, he avoided no longer, heading straight forward to stand before Ye Xiu.

“Hehe,” Ye Xiu chuckled. “If you backed down from this again, that really wouldn’t be like you at all.”

“Stop talking nonsense,” Han Wenqing said.

The two of them turned around, heading in opposite directions. It seemed as though they were walking away from each other, but in reality, they were both stepping toward that battlefield. That battlefield where one of them would have to die.

First match of the group arena: Happy, Ye Xiu, Lord Grim; Tyranny, Han Wenqing, Desert Dust.

The judge was taken aback.

The roster for this third match was decided on the spot, and after deciding, they were supposed to notify this judge.

Now, seeing the actions of Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing, they were undoubtedly the first players of the two teams, but the problem was, neither of them had reported to the judge!

If this process wasn’t followed, then strictly speaking, this match between Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing would be invalid.

But these two people were walking so steadfastly toward their own competitor booths, without the slightest sign of turning around.

And the atmosphere of the stadium had truly been ignited.

These ten year opponents, in this match where the fates of their respective teams would be decided, completely and violently collided together at last. To settle these ten years, there was perhaps no scene more perfect than this. So perfect, that even the judge couldn’t bring himself to break the atmosphere over a technicality.

Just let it be…

The judge compromised, skipping past this step and treating it as though the two players had already reported to him.

Only now did the giant display screen light up with the names of the first group arena combatants.

Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing!

Even though they had already seen the answer, when these two names were displayed, the crowd couldn’t help but become excited once again, especially those old fans who had been following Glory for many years now. For them, there was simply so much weight behind a showdown between these two names.

“Captain! Destroy him!!” Even though that was the case, the manly men of Tyranny were resolute and determined. They weren’t hoping for this ten year culminating battle to be interesting enough to live up to the two players’ fame or anything. They were most looking forward to seeing their captain’s Desert Dust knock Ye Xiu’s character to the ground in one punch.

Bang bang bang! Bang bang bang!

A number of Tyranny’s fans had brought props to cheer their team on, and they now began drumming them. All sorts of bright sounds mixed together into a cacophony in the stadium. But it didn’t matter what it sounded like, it was all to cheer Han Wenqing on.

The countdown to the battle began, and the system began to randomly select the map. The large question mark, representing the random selection, rotated around and around.

Selected.

Group arena map: Lava Arena.

Because it was a map specially designed by the Glory developers for the playoffs, it didn’t exist in the Glory map. Just from the name, no one was sure what kind of map this was. Now that the map was announced, they had to give some introduction and description of this map. The large display and the projection in the stadium, as well as the broadcast, quickly gave everyone an overview and described some of the map’s features.

The map as a whole was very easy to describe. It was shaped like a tic-tac-toe grid surrounded by a ring, and everywhere else was covered with hot lava. Clearly, this was a map with status effects. Characters that fell into the lava would certainly suffer damage from burns.

The structure could be understood at a glance, the effects could be understood at a glance. There wasn’t much new or strange that could be discussed about this map.

When the characters loaded onto the map, the battle officially began. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim spawned in the south, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust in the north. As soon as they entered the map, these two most experienced players in the pro circle looked around, and as soon as they saw the roiling and bubbling lava, they basically understood what this map was about.

The two of them both moved very quickly, but their camera views were in constant motion, observing everything that they passed by. The map seemed as though it could be understood in a glance, but when it came to the details, the length and width of each section of the map could impact any battles that occurred there. The two players were both rapidly gathering all the information that they noticed.

Very soon, the two of them appeared in each other’s sights. There wasn’t much that could serve as an obstacle on this map, so the players’ views were quite unobstructed.

Bang.

Ye Xiu made the first greeting with a gunshot, but at this distance, there was of course no threat. Desert Dust was in fact still outside of Lord Grim’s attack range. But in the same moment, Lord Grim was already charging toward where Desert Dust stood.

How could Han Wenqing back down?

He came forth first in the group arena, meeting Ye Xiu head on. Having reached this point, he of course would not retreat.

“I’ll use you to test the power of this lava!” Ye Xiu shouted in the chat. Lord Grim opened fire again, and this time, Desert Dust was already within his attack range. But the two characters were separated by lava. A simple jump wasn’t enough to cross over. Desert Dust was forced to walk a small semicircle along the path.

It looked like Ye Xiu had controlled Lord Grim thoughtlessly to charge over here, but his final attacking position caused Han Wenqing a great deal of trouble.

Just in this moment, the audience discovered that this map was relatively disadvantageous toward Desert Dust.

Attack range was one part of it, but more important was that the structure of this map, understandable in a glance, allowed Ye Xiu to easily anticipate Han Wenqing’s movements. If he wanted to attack Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, there was only that one path he could choose to take. Taking any other paths would be like circling around the other side of the planet to reach his destination.

And in this kind of high-level confrontation, if your movements were seen through, then you would be suppressed.

So as Desert Dust took this roundabout path, he was stung again and again by Lord Grim’s long ranged attacks. Even worse, even if Desert Dust managed to make his way through the attacks along this road, Lord Grim certainly wouldn’t wait around for him to close in.

But Han Wenqing wouldn’t back down just like that, nor would Tyranny’s fans waver at seeing this kind of difficulty.

The cheers became louder, Desert Dust’s movement became faster!

It was the final match between them, did he have anything to hold back? No! After saving strength for an entire season, if he didn’t let it out now, he would have no more chance.

Lord Grim’s long ranged attacks came from the Gunner and Mage classes – gunshots, flashes. But ultimately, they were unable to stop Desert Dust’s advance.

As expected, Ye Xiu didn’t stand around waiting for Han Wenqing. Seeing Desert Dust approach one step after another, Lord Grim began to back away.

Attack and retreat, using the map, Ye Xiu began kiting Han Wenqing.

Han Wenqing still did not retreat. He focused everything on Lord Grim’s attacks, dodged, and then advanced.

One step, two steps…

He was closing in.

Whoosh!

Lord Grim suddenly pulled a flash of light, Shining Cut! He used this Assassin skill to swiftly move, instantly pulling apart the distance between their characters again.

Those who were keeping track of the distance instantly felt their hearts shatter. And then they thought about how many such skills Lord Grim had, and they thought about how the cooldowns for these skills weren’t very long, enough to be used nonstop, and their shattered hearts felt like shattering once again.

But Han Wenqing didn’t care. It was as though he didn’t understand this principle. He stubbornly, persistently, continued to chase.

Ordinary movement, with the occasional Swift Run. Aside from this, there was the Reinforced Iron Bones that could allow him to withstand attacks, but he did not use it. There were the skills that could give him similar bursts of speed like Soaring Tiger, but he did not use those.

Han Wenqing was chasing him tightly, but at the same time, he was saving up, and also at the same time, he didn’t forget to study his surroundings.

The general setting was just this. Now, it was the details of the map that would decide many things.

This was a chase that was extremely disadvantageous for him, but Ye Xiu didn’t have it easy, either. In this life-or-death match, both of them understood very clearly the consequences of a single misstep.

Chapter 1536 - An Opportunity Not Seized

The roiling heat from the lava caused the outlines of the two characters to appear hazy.

“Han Wenqing’s in a shaky situation!” Commentator Pan Lin exclaimed, after seeing Desert Dust repeatedly close in, only for Lord Grim to use a movement skill to pull away again.

“But he hasn’t been shaken off,” Li Yibo said calmly from the side.

This thrilling fight had put Pan Lin in an excited state, commentating almost nonstop. But Li Yibo, during this intense match, was in fact uncommonly calm.

This match, for him, was also filled with many memories!

As first-generation players, Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing’s rivalry was a symbol of their time. In that era, the Alliance had just begun, and many technical and tactical aspects of Glory were still in their formative stages. In that setting, individual strength would become the deciding factor of a match. And Li Yibo, as a member of Team Tyranny, could be said to have completely experienced this symbol of that era. To this day, he still remembered when Excellent Era had won their third consecutive championship, the helplessness and despair that Ye Xiu’s domination had brought upon them.

Everyone in the team had felt discouraged and frustrated. But their captain Han Wenqing had never bowed down. Even if he only had a sliver of health remaining, he was the kind of person who would fight relentlessly until the very end.

Scene after scene from those old seasons played through Li Yibo’s mind. In comparison, he truly didn’t feel that Desert Dust closing in or widening the gap was any problem. Han Wenqing had faced far more despairing situations in the past without wavering.

It was just as Li Yibo had calmly said to Pan Lin: He still hadn’t been shaken off!

“Ah, chance!” Pan Lin suddenly shouted.

The expanse of lava to the right of these two characters came to an end and suddenly narrowed. Lord Grim was sticking to the side, looking like he wanted to turn right, but at this moment if Desert Dust suddenly used a jumping skill, it should be strong enough for him to directly leap across the lava to arrive in front of Lord Grim.

It was indeed a chance! Li Yibo’s eyes lit up.

But to everyone’s surprise, although Lord Grim looked like he was about to turn right, after taking one step, he suddenly began to Swift Run left.

“Ah!” Pan Lin already let out a shout of surprise. If Desert Dust had leapt like he thought he would, never mind catching Lord Grim, he would simply be a thousand miles off.

But Desert Dust hadn’t moved, as though Han Wenqing hadn’t detected that chance at all.

“Hehe, it was a feint, but unfortunately he didn’t fool Han Wenqing,” Li Yibo said, as though nothing had happened. With regard to this match, his position couldn’t be clearer. He resolutely supported Tyranny’s Han Wenqing! But he couldn’t let it show too obviously, so he pretended to be very calm.

“Right now, Lord Grim is heading left, Desert Dust continues to chase him. But Coach Li! If Han Wenqing had seen through Ye Xiu’s feint, then he should have also seen that Ye Xiu was preparing to control Lord Grim to move left, right? Then why didn’t he make any anticipating movements? If he had, then he’d be able to catch him, right?” Pan Lin asked.

Li Yibo hesitated.

That was right, why hadn’t he? Desert Dust also had a few explosive instant-movement skills, and Han Wenqing had been saving them all this time. But just now had been a pretty good opportunity. Why hadn’t he used them?

“There was a chance, but it still wasn’t good enough…” At this time, Yu Wenzhou was also responding to Huang Shaotian’s message.

“This still wasn’t good enough? I’d say it was pretty perfect!” But this time, Huang Shaotian disagreed with Yu Wenzhou’s analysis. His earlier message had been just like what Pan Lin had said, about how Han Wenqing could have made a predictive movement in that moment.

“To you, maybe it was enough, but for him it may not have been enough.” This was what Yu Wenzhou replied.

Huang Shaotian paused, understanding Yu Wenzhou’s meaning.

Huang Shaotian hadn’t had a firm grasp of that opportunity either, but a 50% chance of success was good enough for him to take action. In desperate times, 10% was good enough too.

But for Han Wenqing? He was no longer at peak performance, and judging from his attitude and choices over the course of this season, he was very aware of this fact as well. A few years ago, if faced with that opportunity, Han Wenqing probably would have controlled Desert Dust forward without a second thought. He might have even been fooled by Ye Xiu’s feint. But now, a false action, or an opportunity with a lower chance of success, wouldn’t spur him into action lightly.

He had changed, but in reality he wasn’t actually beginning to retreat or anything. He was just valuing his own drive and vigor, because he knew that he no longer had the ability to repeatedly enter a high-intensity explosive state.

While Yu Wenzhou and Huang Shaotian discussed Han Wenqing’s choice from the perspective of opportunity, a discussion amongst the players of another team took it a step further.

“He didn’t seize that chance, but he established a stronger suppressive atmosphere,” said Jiang Botao of Samsara.

Samsara had already entered the finals. The outcome of this match would tell them their opponent. Everyone on the team was curious about the result, and they were now gathered in front of the television to watch this match.

“From the performance, it looks like Ye Xiu has the advantage, but in reality he doesn’t have the initiative, hm?” Jiang Botao said, consulting the teammate next to him.

“Mm.” Zhou Zekai nodded.

“If it continues like this…” Because he also didn’t fully understand the map, Sun Xiang couldn’t make any particularly insightful predictions either.

“Who do you think will win?” Jiang Botao, smiling, suddenly asked Sun Xiang.

Sun Xiang was silent for a while, before opening his mouth. “I hope Ye Xiu wins.”

“Understood.” Jiang Botao continued to smile. After a year on the same team, he of course understood Sun Xiang’s personality. He hoped that Ye Xiu would win, and he hoped that Happy would win, but it definitely wasn’t because of any feelings of attachment toward Excellent Era or One Autumn Leaf. He hoped for this only because of last year’s failure in the Challenger League.

He received One Autumn Leaf from Ye Xiu, only for Ye Xiu to turn around with a new character, pull together a new team, and ferociously defeat him. Never mind an arrogant and proud youth like him, anyone in his place would feel incomparably depressed.

Even though Samsara had won twice against Happy during the regular season, those matches didn’t have the decisive finality that the Challenger League finals or the League playoffs did. Sun Xiang’s frustration and depression couldn’t be soothed by those two victories. He needed a more decisive stage.

The playoffs!

Seeing that Happy had the chance to make it to the playoffs, Sun Xiang was genuinely happy. The reason for this was, naturally, that he wanted to meet them on this stage. And then, when the final rankings and the playoffs bracket came out, it was revealed that there was only one chance for the two teams to meet – in the finals.

For Sun Xiang, this stage couldn’t be more perfect. It was a hundred times more decisive than the Challenger League stage had been. But Sun Xiang was still a bit worried for Happy, fearing that that they wouldn’t be able to enter the finals.

But now, Happy, Tyranny, this last match’s outcome would determine who would meet Samsara in the playoffs. Out of all of Samsara, Sun Xiang was the most concerned about this. Half an hour before the match began, he was already waiting in front of the television.

“Turn around and face him! What are you running for!” Sun Xiang was much more immersed in the battle than anyone else.

But Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim still didn’t turn around.

The chase continued for another round, and a fork appeared up ahead once again. This was already the end of the map. Straight ahead was lava, so there was no way to continue forward. Only left, or right.

All this time, it had looked like Desert Dust was Ye Xiu’s kite, only responding to his attacks. But at this moment, he suddenly made a movement before any attack came.

Desert Dust suddenly headed left.

Just as everyone was wondering whether it was intentional, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was already moving right.

A mistake in prediction?

Even as everyone wondered this, Desert Dust was already nimbly switching directions to head right. But it looked like the path he took wasn’t headed directly for Lord Grim. It seemed to be slanted, leaving him some space.

Positioning himself to force Lord Grim toward the right!

The experts all saw through it.

Slanting leftward was a predictive move against the scenario that the opponent would go left. Ye Xiu of course could very easily not go left. And Han Wenqing didn’t care that his prediction wasn’t correct, because his goal was simply to force Ye Xiu to go right.

What was the point of going right?

Turning right here meant sticking to the very south of this map. Not far from here was the position where Desert Dust had spawned. That was to say, that area was the area that Han Wenqing had studied at the very start of the match, before the two sides had met. And to Ye Xiu, that area was a foreign area he had just stumbled into.

The difference was between having glanced at it once before, and only beginning to glance at it now.

Would victory be determined by such a small difference?

Everyone watched as Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim headed toward the area that Han Wenqing had seen before. But then, he suddenly moved horizontally to the right, straight toward the lava!

What was he doing?

Everyone was only wondering, but Han Wenqing’s actions were even faster than their questions.

Desert Dust also immediately cut toward the lava.

Lord Grim jumped up…

Suicide? Of course not. In midair, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened, the spokes of the umbrella unfolded, Rotor Wing!

Lord Grim directly flew across the lava, heading toward the path that he had taken here.

What about Han Wenqing? He could turn right and see the path he had taken, but this lava in the middle wasn’t something he could cross just with a jump. Ye Xiu had clearly waited for him to reach this position before taking that action.

What was more awkward was that Han Wenqing couldn’t control Desert Dust to immediately turn and run after him. Ye Xiu had full control over his flight path with the Rotor Wing, so if Han Wenqing tried to seize a position, Ye Xiu could simply turn around in midair. Lord Grim jumped first, then activated the skill, giving him many possible positions to choose and leaving himself this room to breathe.

Just a bit of maneuvering, with so much hidden within. The audience couldn’t grasp any of this in this moment, but all of the experts understood the difficult situation Han Wenqing was currently in.

But the more difficult the situation, the faster Han Wenqing made his decision. Desert Dust resolutely rushed forward.

Had he judged where Lord Grim would fly? But after seeing him move like this, Ye Xiu could simply control Lord Grim to fly back! But just at that moment, Desert Dust’s legs left the ground. He had actually jumped…

Was he crazy?

Everyone was shocked. It seemed as though Han Wenqing wanted to directly attack Lord Grim in midair, but no matter what, a Striker couldn’t jump that kind of distance, right?

And this jump, wasn’t it a bit short? It definitely wasn’t at the limit…

Wait a second. That thing sticking out of the bubbling lava, what was that?

Chapter 1537 - Achilles’ Heel

The audience didn't have time to check closely what the thing floating in the lava was when Desert Dust dropped down. The lava splashed like water where his foot landed. It was only then did they notice that he had stepped onto that thing.

His character didn't sink. This time, everyone could see clearly that the thing floating in the lava was a small rock, which could be used as a foothold.

With how fast the lava and hot air flowed, it was a wonder how Han Wenqing had discovered this hidden foothold. Nevertheless, they knew that once he landed on the foothold, he would be able to act again.

Soaring Tiger!

The force from the kick pushed the lava aside as Desert Dust flew into the air.　

Soaring Tiger didn't allow him to fly, but it was still a powerful jump. Han Wenqing adjusted his jumping angle well. Desert Dust was like an artillery shell as he headed straight for Lord Grim, who had activated Rotor Wings. After they crashed into each other, where would they land? Perhaps even Han Wenqing didn't know. He was only certain of one thing. Whether he fell into the lava or the water, he would definitely be able to drag Lord Grim together with him.

Not good!

Ye Xiu felt a bad premonition when he saw Desert Dust leap towards the lava. He didn't think the old rival of his was discouraged to the point of wanting to kill himself.

During Han Wenqing's first jump, Ye Xiu had anticipated where he would land. Even though he wasn't able to see the landing spot, Ye Xiu was certain that Han Wenqing had found a place for him to jump again from.

Soaring Tiger!

Ye Xiu had made the prediction the moment Han Wenqing acted. By the time he realized that Han Wenqing would use this skill, Desert Dust had already landed on that small rock and used Soaring Tiger to rocket towards Lord Grim.

However, this prediction was enough for Ye Xiu to react. Life and death in a match depended on these small moments.

Lord Grim dropped down.　

An unexpected response. Forward, backwards, left, right, up, the audience had helped imagine the different scenarios for Ye Xiu. However, no one had expected him to go down. From everyone's perspective, by moving down, Lord Grim would be exactly where Han Wenqing wanted him to be.

Maybe it was precisely this reason that Han Wenqing would be caught off guard? Some people thought of themselves as clever coming up with this reasoning. For example, Pan Lin. He was just about to say his thoughts, but the changes in the battle were too fast. There was no time for him to interject.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions suddenly sounded from in the air.

Lord Grim had retracted his Rotor Wings. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was held in front of him, sending Anti-Tank Missiles towards the incoming Desert Dust.

Desert Dust had no way to dodge these missiles from in the air. Soaring Tiger was still being used though, so his character wouldn't be knocked back by the explosions.

Desert Dust might not be knocked back, but Lord Grim would.

Using the recoil from the Anti-Tank Missiles, Lord Grim dropped even faster diagonally downwards.

The lava was still beneath him. However, Lord Grim had plenty of skills in his arsenal. He had methods to move around in the air and get himself to shore.

As for Desert Dust? Soaring Tiger had missed, and he had no way to move around in the air. It seemed like Han Wenqing could only watch as his Desert Dust fell into the lava.

Han Wenqing's play hd been too risky!

Countless people sighed. However, the two players on stage didn't think it was over.

Han Wenqing hadn't given up, and Ye Xiu didn't think that he was safe yet.

Amidst the smoke and fire from the explosions, Desert Dust dropped down at a speed far faster than Lord Grim.

Thousand Ton Drop!

Han Wenqing had unexpectedly used this skill, and what he wanted was to fall down faster. When he reached Lord Grim's height, he cancelled Thousand Ton Drop.

Launching Kick!

Desert Dust moved sideways in the air, his legs kicking out. 　　

He was falling directly downwards, while Lord Grim was falling down diagonally. There was quite a bit of distance between them. However, Han Wenqing reacted extremely fast. The moment the Anti-Tank Missiles were fired, he had predicted that Lord Grim would fall down diagonally. It was at that moment he used Thousand Ton Drop.

One was moving diagonally downwards, while the other was moving straight downwards. The two characters had begun moving at slightly different times. However, Thousand Ton Drop was faster. In the blink of an eye, Han Wenqing had caught up, and Lord Grim was within Launching Kick's range. Even if unspecialized characters had plenty of ways to move around in the air, Han Wenqing's response had been too fast. Ye Xiu had no time to use another skill!

In that instant, Ye Xiu could only have Lord Grim raise his umbrella above him. He had to at least try to parry it. By parrying it, he could keep control of his character. If he was directly hit by Desert Dust's Launching Kick, Lord Grim would be sent flying towards wherever Han Wenqing wanted.

Their attacks met in the air.

Ye Xiu watched the approaching attack carefully. Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was held at a certain angle, ready to use the force from the kick to move where he wanted to.

But Desert Dust had the same idea too. When his Launching Kick landed on the umbrella, Lord Grim used the force to fall down even faster, while Desert Dust twisted his body in the air, using his other leg to kick. Whirlwind Kick!

Combo!

Despite being in the air, Han Wenqing was able to complete a two-hit combo. His Launching Kick landed on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella followed by a Whirlwind Kick. He was still falling down too, and he was even able to move horizontally again in the air...

Everyone was struck dumb. How many inputs had been needed for him to borrow the force from Launching Kick to position his Whirlwind Kick?

Pa!

This time, the sound of a kick hitting flesh could be heard.

It hit?

Tyranny's fans were feeling excited, but when they took another look...　

No!

Lord Grim had suddenly swung his arm. In his hand was part of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. He had actually been able to parry Desert Dust's Whirlwind Kick.　　

This is?

The spectators weren't able to tell what skill Lord Grim had used. It wasn't possible for the parry to be from a normal attack. Whirlwind Kick had a higher priority than normal attacks, and Lord Grim would have certainly been sent flying.

Pa pa pa pa pa...

The audience kept hearing the sound of punches and kicks hitting flesh again and again.

Desert Dust had the upper hand?　　

No!　

It wasn't only Desert Dust punching and kicking. Lord Grim's unspecialized was also using Fighter skills to contend with Desert Dust at this close distance.

It was close combat at a distance that couldn't get any closer.

There was almost zero distance between them. Let alone a sword, even a dagger would be too long. Only punches and kicks could be used at this distance.

Tyranny's fans felt exhilarated.

If they fought like this, how could their captain not have the advantage? It was true that unspecialized characters had Fighter skills, but how could they compared to a true Striker? What's more, Han Wenqing had immersed himself with this class for ten years. At close combat, if he said he was second, who dared to say they were first?

Not even Ye Xiu dared to!

This time, they were right. Ye Xiu was proficient at all classes, but even so, his skill in this area couldn't compare to Han Wenqing, who had been perfecting it for ten years. In addition, there was a difference in their classes. Strikers were specialized in close combat. Desert Dust was outfitted in equipment specifically to buff his close combat capabilities. As for Lord Grim? Even though he had a full set of Silver equipment, it was more all-rounded.

So that's the case!

The eyes of the various pro players watching the match suddenly lit up.

Ye Xiu was very well-rounded. When he came out of retirement with his unspecialized, Lord Grim, he was displaying his knowledge as the Glory Textbook to the limit. Everyone felt their heads hurt facing him because no one could keep up with the constantly changing unspecialized. As a result, they would often be on the defensive.

However, Han Wenqing, Ye Xiu's rival of ten years, was now forcefully suppressing Ye Xiu because he wasn't competing with Ye Xiu all-around, or trying to figure out the constantly changing unspecialized. He was pulling Ye Xiu into his domain.

By limiting the fight to close combat, even if Ye Xiu was proficient in all areas, many of his unspecialized skills couldn't be used in these conditions. He could only use the same method of fighting as Han Wenqing to compete. His fundamentals at close combat may be exceptional, but it couldn't compare to Han Wenqing's.

The pro players watching immediately thought of ways to pull Ye Xiu into their area of expertise, but as they thought about it, most of the players immediately felt grieved.

Even if they fought with Ye Xiu in their own domain, it wouldn't be enough to give them an overwhelming advantage against him. It seemed like only a God like Han Wenqing with ten years of experience in one area would be able to have this effect.

The viewers all had their own thoughts, but the match continued.

Everyone felt like Han Wenqing would be able to hold the upper hand with this way of fighting, but they forgot that this situation couldn't continue forever because the two were in the air.

Lord Grim's previous escape route had been cut off by Desert Dust. The two fought as they dropped towards the lava.

Han Wenqing didn't seem to notice. He was completely unconcerned. Desert Dust's offense didn't expose any openings, so Ye Xiu was helpless. He wanted to try get away, but at this close of a distance, he could only fight. Skills from other classes? There was no point thinking about them. If those skills were used, Han Wenqing would mercilessly interrupt them because they were too slow.

The instant the two characters were about to fall into the lava, Desert Dust suddenly trembled.　

Reinforced Iron Bones!

He had unexpectedly activated this skill at such a crucial moment. Was he planning on using his increased defense and Super Armor to find an opportunity after they fell into the lava?

Everyone thought those were his intentions, when Desert Dust suddenly used High Kick!

High Kick had a knock-up effect. Han Wenqing hadn't used the skill before. He knew that Ye Xiu would definitely tank a movement displacement skill like High Kick and use the opportunity to escape, but even so, he decided to use it at this moment.

Why?

Even Ye Xiu hesitated. If that kick had come earlier, he definitely would have took the hit. But using it at this moment? No matter how he looked at it, it must be some sort of trap.

Block!

Ye Xiu reacted based on his understanding of Han Wenqing. He didn't tank this very suspicious kick. He put up his arms to block it, but the kick suddenly changed direction and missed. Then, his legs suddenly swung down. Desert Dust's upper body seemed to want to rise up as a result.

This is... Eagle Stamp!

This strange way of using the skill made Ye Xiu hesitate again. He could only hastily try to block the attack.

Pa!

The kick struck Lord Grim's arms. Desert Dust used the momentum to leap into the air, while Lord Grim dropped down into the lava.

Flames immediately enveloped Lord Grim. The lava constantly dealt damage to Lord Grim.

And at the same time, pa pa pa pa...

At max level, Eagle Stamp could be used five times. Desert Dust had only used one previously, so he followed again another four times.

"Han Wenqing, this isn't right!!!" At this moment of life and death, Ye Xiu still had the time to trash talk. Lord Grim was half immersed in the lava, the fire damage eating away at his health. As for Desert Dust? He was stepping on Lord Grim again, pogo-sticking off his head!

By using Eagle Stamp, would Desert Dust be able to get back to land? No! But by doing this, he would fall into the lava later, and Lord Grim would take more damage from the lava. As a result, Desert Dust would have a health lead. The brave Han Wenqing only had victory on his mind against Ye Xiu, and he would take these little selfish schemes too.

Chapter 1538 - The Boiling Rock

Desert Dust looked like an eagle spreading his wings as he used Eagle Stamp. The stadium erupted with applause. They might not understand Han Wenqing’s true intentions, but the scene in front of them was showing Desert Dust repeatedly stepping on Lord Grim, forcing him into the lava. So what if Desert Dust would soon fall into the lava too! It was more than enough to make the Tyranny fans feel like they had the upper hand.

“It’s not going to be so easy!” The more perceptive viewers had already noticed that there were movements coming from Lord Grim. How could Ye Xiu be so easy to deal with? Of course not, just a second ago, he had the time to type out some trash talk!

Hand seals!

Hidden by the waves of lava from the fall, Lord Grim’s two hands moved in a blur. A Ninjutsu seal was instantly completed.

Even though Lord Grim would certainly fall into the lava, he had been able to escape from Desert Dust’s range, allowing him to use other skills.

Poof!

With a gentle poof, Lord Grim turned into a cloud of smoke. The shadow clone had been instantly destroyed by the heat from the lava.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Lord Grim had used the Ninja skill commonly used for movement.

Where was his real body?

Pa! Splash!

Two sounds one after the other. Lord Grim appeared where the shadow clone had just disappeared from…

What’s going on? Everyone was confused.

That obviously couldn’t have been where Ye Xiu had planned on moving to. There was only explanation, his Shadow Clone Technique had somehow been interrupted.

A replay. A replay was needed. No one understood what had happened in that instant.

Only the two players on stage knew.

Eagle Stamp… number six!

After the five kicks from Eagle Stamp, Ye Xiu immediately used a Shadow Clone Technique. However, he hadn’t expected a sixth kick to follow, and this sixth kick had interrupted his Shadow Clone Technique. The shadow clone destroyed by the lava had been a failed clone. The real body hadn’t been able to escape and was stepped on again.

A sixth kick from Eagle Stamp had indeed been outside of Ye Xiu’s expectations, but he didn’t think it was impossible.

Eagle Stamp’s limit was five kicks. After the Level 75 level cap increase, the max level for Eagle Stamp had increased as well. The number of times it could be used was still five, but this max level increase was only the max level that could be added using skill points. Equipment that increased skill levels could break through this max level limit and continue raising it.

Evidently, Desert Dust had equipment that raised Eagle Stamp’s level, and it looked like it raised it high enough for him to use six kicks.

Unless you saw it in action, there was no way to know. Silver equipment stats were hidden. After ten years, the current Desert Dust had no Orange equipment.

The viewers still didn’t know what had happened, but they did see that the Shadow Clone Technique had been interrupted. In any case, applause first!

Amidst the applause, Lord Grim swung his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella out of the lava like a dragon flying out from the sea. The lava slid down from it, creating a rain of fire.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was in its original form as it swung towards Desert Dust.

The original umbrella form was considered a Priest weapon. As a result, some people were able to determine what skill Lord Grim had suddenly used.

Knight skill: Heroic Leap!

There was nothing Han Wenqing could do! Nothing. He could predict the Shadow Clone Technique because it was a sub-Level 20 skill. It was a skill that was a part of an unspecialized’s toolkit. Shadow Clone Technique was extremely useful in his situation, which was why he had paused after five kicks from Eagle Stamp. He had left an opening for Ye Xiu. When he saw Lord Grim form the seals, he had Desert Dust kick a sixth time, interrupting the Ninjutsu art.

But a Heroic Leap…

If it was Level 20+ skill, it meant that it was a bonus skill added onto the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s Priest form. Apart from class advancement and class awakening skills, any mid or high level skill of the same class could be added to a weapon. Teams frequently took advantage of this point. They made changes to the skills attached to their weapons to give a surprise to their opponents. However, there had never been a weapon like the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella before. It had 12 different forms, which meant 12 different high-level skills encompassing all six superclasses. The surprise was too big and couldn’t be eliminated.

Han Wenqing could predict the Shadow Clone Technique, but there was no way he could have predicted a Heroic Leap.

Han Wenqing had made some precautions though.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Before Desert Dust had used Eagle Stamp, he had activated Reinforced Iron Bones. The buff was still active on him. Han Wenqing had the Super Armor active in case that Ye Xiu did something outside of his predictions. He hadn’t thought that he could truly completely suppress Ye Xiu. If not, the legendary dynasty established in the early years of the Alliance wouldn’t have been by Excellent Era, but Tyranny.

Lord Grim jumped high out of the lava with a Heroic Leap. The strike from his umbrella looked extremely imposing too. But Han Wenqing knew that the strike was flashy but not threatening. The attack priority from Heroic Leap didn’t come until the user landed on the ground. No matter how fearsome Lord Grim may look, just one punch from his Desert Dust would be enough to send him flying.

But Han Wenqing didn’t want to do this.

Send him flying away? Ye Xiu could take the opportunity to get back onto the land. And then with Desert Dust in the lava, wouldn’t that just be suicide?

The plan stays the same!

He wasn’t afraid of falling into the lava, but no matter what, he needed to drag Lord Grim with him.

Desert Dust readied himself. Han Wenqing stared closely at the path of Lord Grim’s weapon.

Shua!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella changed forms!

As expected!

Han Wenqing hadn’t been surprised at all. He had guessed that Ye Xiu wouldn’t actually use Heroic Leap to attack him. The attack wouldn’t even be able to break Desert Dust’s Super Armor.

Ye Xiu will definitely use a different attack.

Han Wenqing had guessed right. His line of sight never left the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

As the umbrella quickly changed forms, it swung towards Desert Dust.

I’ve been waiting!

Desert Dust’s two hands clapped together, Empty-Handed Blade Block!

Locked in place!

He locked the umbrella in place firmly. A Dismantle skill. A block and then a throw.

Go down!

Desert Dust wanted to use the umbrella to throw Lord Grim back into the lava, but to his surprise, his throw failed.

How?

In all his years as a Striker, he had never seen Empty-Handed Blade Block miss after blocking an attack. A Dismantle skill had two parts, a block and a throw. Although it consisted of two parts, they were linked together. After the block, it shouldn’t be possible to avoid the throw.

At this moment, although the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been blocked, it hadn’t finished transforming. The umbrella pulled open, and the ribs of the umbrella squeezed together in the form of an arc. It hung there as if it would fall off at any moment.

This form is… a scythe!

From Knight sword into scythe. A scythe was a Priest weapon, so it wouldn’t affect the Heroic Leap because it was Priest skill too.

Priest skills…

Lord Grim pulled back on the umbrella. The form changed again, and the umbrella split into two halves, which flew back to Lord Grim’s hands as if they had grown wings.

Fly back…

Han Wenqing realized what had happened.

Spirit Guidance!

Exorcist skill, Spirit Guidance. It was an attack, where the weapon flew towards the target. In other words, when the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed from Knight sword to Priest scythe, it was considered as a flying weapon and not in Lord Grim’s hands.

Dismantle skills worked on flying weapons, but in that case it could only block, not throw. The other person was more than ten steps away from you, how were you supposed to throw him?

Although Lord Grim was extremely close to Desert Dust, that was how the system judged it. Empty-Handed Blade Block had blocked a flying weapon, so the block hadn’t locked Lord Grim in place. As a result, Lord Grim could dodge the throw.

After dealing with Desert Dust’s attack, the umbrella split into tonfas. A cold light glinted.

Brawler skill, Poison Needle!

Another skill attached to a weapon. At this close of a distance, there was nowhere to run.

The Poison Needle hit. The damage wasn’t high, nor was the DoT threatening. However, Poison Needle broke Super Armor!

Lord Grim’s Poison Needle was only level one, even so, it removed Super Armor for up to five seconds. For the current situation, it was more than enough. Five seconds was enough for the two to fall into the lava eight times.

The moment Poison Needle came out, Lord Grim took a step forward.

There was nowhere to run to in the air, and with his Super Armor broken, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust could only try to parry the blows.

Pa pa pa… splash… pa pa…

Eagle Stamp!

Lord Grim also used an Eagle Stamp. It didn’t matter if it dealt damage or if Han Wenqing parried it. With three Eagle Stamps, Desert Dust fell into the lava. Lord Grim finished it with two more stamps.

The applause was still going…

Tyranny’s fans obviously didn’t want to give Ye Xiu applause. Happy’s fans were in Tyranny’s home stadium and weren’t able to make such loud noises. The applause had been for Desert Dust breaking Lord Grim’s Shadow Clone Technique, sending him into the lava again.

But the reversal had happened too quickly. While the crowd was still clapping, Lord Grim used Heroic Leap, Soul Guidance to cheat Desert Dust’s Empty-Handed Block, Poison Needle to break the Super Armor, and then Eagle Stamp to send Desert Dust into the lava!

This was how fast top pro players played. Using seconds to count was too slow. Tyranny’s fans hadn’t been able to stop their applause when Ye Xiu finished his series of inputs. Their captain was now the one in the lava.

Words couldn’t describe how fast the reversal had been. How long could characters stay in the air? Even in this short amount of time, several back-and-forths had occurred.

In the end, Desert Dust had fallen into the lava. Lord Grim used Eagle Stamp to get into the air, and then with the skills available to him, who knew if he would be able to get back to land.

There was nothing Han Wenqing could do. However, he knew that if he let Lord Grim get back to land, the fight would be over!

He had to drag him down no matter what!

Desert Dust flickered in the lava, Cloud Body! His hand moved in a blur to grab Lord Grim’s retracting foot at a tricky angle.

Just a bit off!!!

Desert Dust hadn’t fallen to the bottom yet. His body was still sinking. Although he could stretch his hands out, the sinking made him miss just by a bit.

Suddenly, Lord Grim dropped down into Desert Dust’s hands.

How?

The more vigilant spectators thought that this was some sort of trap from Ye Xiu, but the experts could immediately tell that Ye Xiu hadn’t intended for this to happen. Ye Xiu couldn’t have done anything about it. The grab from Desert Dust hadn’t been a normal grab.

Grappler skill: Overhead Toss!

In today’s life and death match, Han Wenqing had given Desert Dust this skill.

Overhead Toss. It was a grab with extremely high priority against those in the air. It was through this high priority that he was able to reach his target.

Toss!

Lava splashed everywhere.

This time, Lord Grim didn’t just drop into it. After being tossed by Desert Dust, Lord Grim split apart the lava. The lava fell back and swallowed Lord Grim whole.

Everyone was dumbstruck. They didn’t know what happened when the lava swallowed someone completely. From their intuition, shouldn’t the person be burned into nothing but bones?

Han Wenqing didn’t dare relax though. He stepped forward, relying on his intuition to continue attacking Lord Grim. But before he could take a second step, a figure suddenly appeared from behind Desert Dust. It was as if a mass of flames had crashed into Desert Dust.

Ninjutsu – Underground Tunneling Technique!

Chapter 1539 - Beneath the Lava

Underground Tunneling Technique!

The crowd gaped at the sight of Lord Grim emerging from the lava, resembling the Human Torch.

Even though they knew this was only a game, to see someone drill underneath the lava and then emerge slashing out with their whole body on fire was still an awesome sight to see.

Applaud him?

We can’t! This was Ye Xiu, how could we applaud? Tyranny fans forcibly suppressed their impulses. The applause that was originally meant for Han Wenqing when he interrupted Shadow Clone Technique turned into background accompaniment for Ye Xiu’s retaliation in an instant. Tyranny fans were conflicted.

They had to suppress it. Everyone gritted their teeth. It wasn’t like they could boo such a spectacular play. That would be too heartless.

“Go Captain Han!” Tyranny fans could only change the topic like this. They were determined not to show any appreciation to Ye Xiu’s performance!

Even Han Wenqing, who had been ready for a follow up, did not expect Ye Xiu’s retaliation to be so swift and fierce.

Underground Tunnelling Technique, then a blade that went straight for the neck. Blood spurted out, and was instantly turned to steam by the scalding lava.

Desert Dust turned his body sharply and a fist flew out.

Did Ye Xiu want to follow up Underground Tunneling Technique with a Neck Bind Technique? Almost any somewhat-experienced Glory player would make this assessment, let alone Han Wenqing, who had ten years’ experience. Both Han Wenqing’s assessment and the follow-up strike were reflexive; it was precise and fast, and no Ninja could possibly continue their combo after his interrupting strike.

But there was no follow-up to begin with.

Han Wenqing’s reaction was followed immediately by distress.

Underground Tunneling Technique followed by Neck Bind Technique was a common Ninja tactic, but the bastard in front of him wasn’t a Ninja. Underground Tunneling Technique was already an additional skill bound to the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella. He wouldn’t waste another on Neck Bind Technique just for this simple combo.

Han Wenqing’s second assessment was correct. His reflexive strike had missed. Lord Grim did not use a Neck Bind Technique.

Then what is he going to do?

His mind immediately filled with the hundreds of Glory skills that existed. There was no way to make a judgment call.

He’d have to go by his experience and instincts!

Han Wenqing did not wait for Desert Dust to stabilize his stance, and directly sent out a Stomach Kick. Desert Dust raised his leg and then thrust directly backwards.

Oh oh oh oh!

Clap clap clap clap!

Tyranny fans were quick to cheer and applaud. This kick was perfect! The target was behind him and out of sight, yet he still managed to find Lord Grim’s chest so accurately. This was experience, this was awareness.

But they saw a blur straight after.

The Lord Grim that took a Stomach Kick was actually a Shadow Clone. Where was the real one? The real one was directly behind Desert Dust, and the blade that came from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was viciously trusted into Desert Dust’s waist.

From the viciousness and deadliness, you could instantly tell this was an Assassin skill.

Flickering Stab!

The skill only had a range of one unit away and didn’t sound as impressive as Teleporting Stab, which could ambush from three units away. But true experts knew that the one-unit distance of Flickering Stab was far more abrupt than the three-unit distance of Teleporting Stab, and was much harder or even almost impossible to guard against.

Once again, the Tyranny fans’ cheering and applause became accompaniment for Lord Grim’s attack. This time they couldn’t even spare the time to feel peeved. Seeing their captain come out at a disadvantage again made them extremely agitated. They really wanted to just whip out their account cards, log into the arena and tear Lord Grim a new one personally!

The blade slid out, bringing along with it beads of blood. But on this glowing red lava, the crimson blood was no longer striking to the eye, and it was visible for a second before it was evaporated into steam.

Back combo!

Ye Xiu would never miss an opportunity like this. Lord Grim continued to strike at Desert Dust’s back.

The lava gurgled and splashed.

The two characters stood in the middle of the field of lava. It seemed unlikely that they would be able to escape. The lava’s damage was not low, and any damage done by attacks on each other was just adding fuel to the fire. Anyone could see that this battle would not last for much longer. One combo was enough to defeat a character when combined with the lava damage. Victory would be decided within several seconds or even sooner.

Han Wenqing was currently at a disadvantage. Would he just lose like this?

Not yet!

Desert Dust suddenly twisted around.

Double Tiger Palm?

Ye Xiu’s experience was incomparably rich. He could tell which skill his opponent was about to use just from the way they squared their shoulders. He quickly had Lord Grim retreat a tiny step.

Bam!

Hit?

Ye Xiu was stunned.

The skill was indeed Double Tiger Palm. But what hit Lord Grim was not a palm, but an elbow!

Compared to the palm, attacking with the elbows would halve the effective attack range. But using the skill while twisting his body would increase the speed at which it was released.

So there was even an effect like this.

Even Ye Xiu was taken aback. He found that Han Wenqing had made many changes, of which there was no shortage of research and reform of the Striker’s battle tactics. However, using Double Tiger Palm like so was never seen before. Ye Xiu wasn’t sure if Han Wenqing was never given the chance, or if under the current life-threatening situation, this creation was forged on the spot from ten years of experience.

One hit to snatch back the initiative. Following the twist of his body, Desert Dust launched his offensive.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Directly following up with a high level skill. Straightforward and valiant.

Would Ferocious Tiger Flurry be enough to finish his opponent, combined with the damage over time from the lava?

No one could make this call in this moment. First, the unfamiliarity with the map meant the exact damage of the lava was unknown. Secondly, Ferocious Tiger Flurry was similar to a Blade Master’s Formless Phantom Blade; they were skills that required continual input to keep unleashing attacks, and the damage would thus depend on both the attacker’s execution and the defender’s reaction. The skill had begun, but the details would decide whether the full damage would be dealt in the end.

Right now, first punch, hit!

Double Tiger Palm comboing into a Ferocious Tiger Flurry. The first punch came from quickly extending the bent elbow. The strike was as natural as it was fast. There was no way to dodge or parry it. Han Wenqing did not decide to follow up with Ferocious Tiger Flurry just because he wanted to look courageous or heroic.

After the second hit, a disturbance could be seen in the lava. Then, a fist followed and hit again. However, the system’s combo count jumped twice. Three hits, four hits!

What? Many people were confused. How was it a four-hit combo?

“The third hit came from under the lava,” Li Yibo was rather quick to notice this time in the broadcast. He realised the third hit was a kick. But because Desert Dust’s body was submerged in the lava, which was not see-through like water, most people missed it.

Five hits!

The combo counter ticked up once again. But this time, there was a collective, regretful sigh from the stadium, because this time, Ye Xiu finally reacted. Lord Grim raised a half-section of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella, and used an attack to parry the hit.

Attacking to parry was to defend with an attack. The damage may or may not be fully mitigated, but regardless, it still counted as a hit for the attacker, and was different from directly avoiding the attack.

Directly after, six hits!

This attack was also parried, this time by the other half-section of the Umbrella in Lord Grim’s other hand.

“He’s dual-wielding!” Someone yelled.

Dual-wielding was the counter to parrying. It could also be used very effectively to parry with attacks. In many situations, using a skill to parry while dual-wielding could successfully parry an attack which would otherwise have much higher priority than the skill that was used. However, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust unleashed Ferocious Tiger Flurry, his attack speed increased explosively. It was absolutely impossible to dual-wield parry the whole skill. At this point, dual-wielding can only hope to keep up with the increased attack speed. Using only a single weapon would be able to parry one strike of Ferocious Tiger Flurry, and then leave the defender open to a second hit.

Despite this, only using the weapon’s dual-wield attribute in combination with normal attacks, how could he hope to completely stop the priority of a level 70 skill?

Every attack looked like it was parried, but in the end the attack still pressed onto his body. The attack damage was only reduced by tiny amounts.

Tiny amounts would still add up when the attacks came continuously. Right now, the major damage over time did not come from the attacks, but rather the lava’s burn damage. Lord Grim had the advantage in health from the initiative he gained earlier. Now, Desert Dust was retaliating, attempting to catch up from the deficit. Ye Xiu doing his best to parry was clearly a method to reduce as much of Desert Dust’s damage output as possible.

Everyone was fixated nervously on the two characters’ health bars. Lord Grim had more health, but it was also decreasing faster. Desert Dust had less health, but was only taking lava damage right now.

If this continued, who would win?

Their health bars were both depleting, and the values were getting closer.

The attacks from Ferocious Tiger Flurry were coming to an end.

They’re even!

The health bars of both sides were the same right now!

The stadium erupted in joy. Tyranny’s fans were excitedly anticipating their victory! The health bars were even, but there was the last and strongest hit of Ferocious Tiger Flurry left! This final strike will put Desert Dust in the lead. Although the lead was tiny, the lava damage would decide who would win, because their health bars were so close to being depleted. As long as Desert Dust avoided taking damage after this final strike, victory would surely be his!

Bang!

The final punch of Ferocious Tiger Flurry sent Lord Grin flying backwards. The distance between the two characters widened, and close combat skills would not have an effect anymore. The lava was about to determine the winner.

A flash of sword light was seen!

Sword Draw!

Lord Grim, who was currently flying backwards, somehow managed to send out a Sword Draw. Desert Dust could not take another hit, and at this moment all the Tyranny fans’ hearts jumped to their throats.

Right at that moment, they saw Desert Dust roll towards the side!

It’s all over!

Tyranny fans cried out in their minds.

In this key moment, how did the captain make such a mistake? Sword Draw’s slash was horizontal, what good would a horizontal roll do? Do you want to hide under the lava? That wouldn’t help either! Ye Xiu was crafty, this Sword Draw had an angle to it and maximized its coverage. Even the lava had been slashed apart.

Eh?

A spark of hope lit up the fans’ hearts. In the lava that was slashed apart by the Sword Draw, a molten rock was visible!

Ching!

The sword light landed on this rock. What about Desert Dust? After the roll, he ended up on the other side of the rock. Han Wenqing knew well in advance that Ye Xiu would rush to attack during the knockback and right after the last strike of Ferocious Tiger Flurry. He had an escape route in mind. Sheltering behind that rock would block any attack from the front.

He won!!

Tyranny’s fans were already cheering victoriously. The two health bars were sliding towards nothingness, and Lord Grim’s was shorter, so it would reach zero first. Even though securing a win by that tiny margin wasn’t meaningful for the group arena, a win was a win. More so, this win was against Ye Xiu, who had never lost an individual round yet. Was there any better feeling?

But just at that moment, Desert Dust’s life suddenly ticked down a chunk during the steady decrease due to the lava.

Glory!

When the large letters declared the end of the match, the last one standing was… Lord Grim?

WHAT!!

The stadium immediately exploded.

How.. how was this possible?

Where did that burst of damage come from? Did lava somehow have burst damage? If so, why would it suddenly happen at this moment in particular? That would be too cruel of a prank, right?

The righteous Tyranny fans all stood up in sync, as if they wanted to charge onto the stage. What the hell was this? There had to be some kind of explanation!!!

What the hell happened? What the hell happened?!

It wasn’t just the Tyranny fans who were confused by this sudden burst of damage. The broadcast team, the referees, the pro players… too many people were baffled.

This kind of situation called for an instant replay. There had to be an explanation for this. Right now, it hadn’t been found, so everything was being played back on the big screen. Even the holographic projection technology gave up the usual display of the winning character’s model. There was no need to draw needless aggro from the crowd – the holograms were also replaying the last moments of the fight.

The stadium was quiet as the grave. Everyone’s eyes were fixated on the replay of that single moment.

Once, twice, three times. The moment was very short, and could only be replayed like so. But where to look?

Some people were watching Lord Grim’s actions. Some were watching Desert Dust. Some were watching the change in the flowing lava. At this moment, the system’s final damage summary was pulled out. The system would not lie; it faithfully recorded every bit of the match from start to finish. These records would paint a picture and put everyone a step closer to the answer.

Lord Grim’s last damage taken: Ferocious Tiger Flurry’s last punch, plus lava damage.

Desert Dust’s last damage taken: lava damage, and… Waltzing Wave Sword?

Spellblade skill, Waltzing Wave Sword.

The silence in the stadium is still deafening. After the system’s damage summary appeared, the replay could finally zoom in to the area of interest.

Under the lava, Waltzing Wave Sword moved soundlessly. Any visible trace of movement was completely obscured by the intense battle of the two characters, which churned the lava furiously.

Waltzing Wave Sword actually happened before the Sword Draw.

Just like Desert Dust’s kick from under the lava during Ferocious Tiger Flurry, Waltzing Wave Sword was unleashed silently from under the lava. By the time the sword flickered, it was already the sword light from Sword Draw.

The Sword Draw was blocked by the rock. But Waltzing Wave Sword’s attack was not in a straight line; it traveled in an arc. It looped around the molten rock and managed to catch Desert Dust.

Turns out it wasn’t some burst damage from the lava. It did come from the player’s own hand, Lord Grim’s attack.

The silence was crushing…

The long silence was finally broken violently.

“Ye Xiu, you’re fucking shameless!!!”

“Ye Xiu go die in a hole!!!”

“Kill him!!!”

Chapter 1540 - No Need For Comfort

Tyranny’s fans could accept defeat. They had always prioritized the process over the end outcome. The 1v1 had been intense and high-level. It was absolutely a rare scene, and everyone was more than satisfied with it.

Although from Tyranny’s perspective, this outcome was truly very very very annoying. A second earlier, they had thought that Ye Xiu would lose. His 1v1 win streak would finally be broken. This sort of excitement would have reached the same levels as when Tyranny had toppled Excellent Era’s dynasty in the fourth season.

But it was only for one second.

Life was a rollercoaster. This single second fully embodied this saying. Tyranny’s fans could accept the defeat, but they could not accept the sudden drop from excitement to disappointment.

The main culprit: Ye Xiu!

Tyranny’s fans had always hated Ye Xiu. Right now, how could they be in the mood to congratulate the winner?

Han Wenqing walked out from Tyranny’s player booth. The angry clamor from Tyranny’s fans suddenly quieted down.

Their hearts hurt for their captain.

Wouldn’t he be the one who felt the sudden up and down the most?

Wouldn’t he be the one who felt the worst?

The noise from the crowd became quieter and quieter. Everyone was looking at Han Wenqing, who was walking down from the stage. His posture was as straight as ever. His footsteps were firm and powerful. As he walked, he waved his hands towards Tyranny’s fans. Then, he waved towards everyone in the crowd. It was the same as he always did every time a match ended.

Sure enough, their captain wouldn’t fall from a defeat, even if it had been from such an unexpected and disgusting reversal. The crowd instantly erupted again! Instead of wasting their efforts cursing at Ye Xiu, it’d be better to give their captain some applause.

Han Wenqing continued to wave his hands amidst the thunderous applause. And just like this, he walked back to Tyranny’s seats.

Everyone in Tyranny stood up and applauded their captain.

Console him? No need.

Their captain would never console a teammate who had lost. At the same time, he didn’t need any comforting either when he lost.

A defeat was nothing special. Tyranny had experienced it many times. Needing someone to comfort them was too shameful. If a man couldn’t even accept defeat, how could anyone comfort him?

“I’ve calculated how much damage the lava does. I recommend that Lin Jingyan go up next,” There wasn’t a single word about the battle that had just transpired. Tyranny’s vice-captain Zhang Xinjie directly brought up their arrangements for their next battle.

“Okay,” Han Wenqing nodded his head.

“Okay, I’ll go,” Lin Jingyan nodded his head. He left Tyranny’s bench and headed towards the stage.

“From the previous fight, we can see that Ye Xiu has added Heroic Leap, Poison Needle, Underground Tunneling Technique, Flickering Stab, and Waltzing Wave Slash onto his weapon forms,” When they finally talked about the battle that had just ended, it was from a review perspective. When the skill “Waltzing Wave Slash” was mentioned, the cause for the sudden reversal, their expressions didn’t change in the slightest.

“That’s not even half,” Han Wenqing said regretfully.

“Yes, the tempo is just too fast,” Zhang Xinjie said.

The fight between the two had happened mostly in the air. Once they fell into the lava, the lava dealt the majority of the damage came. The number of skills that the two could use effectively while in the lava was in fact quite limited. Lord Grim could attach a total of 12 bonus skills onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and he had only used 5 of those 12 thus far. That meant there were still 7 unknown skills. It would be an unknown factor in the team competition. The vice captain and captain of Tyranny were mainly concerned about this unknown factor.

Lin Jingyan probably wouldn’t be able to find any more of those bonus skills because Lord Grim’s health was almost zero. He was probably at 1 or 2% health. The battle would be over in an instant.

At the start of the second round, Ye Xiu even announced in the public chat: “You’ve won.”

“Haha, I’d be quite happy if you surrendered,” Lin Jingyan replied.

“I can’t do that! You’d better hurry!” Ye Xiu replied.

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder set out. Boos from the crowd soon followed. The boos obviously weren’t for Lin Jingyan, but Ye Xiu! Ye Xiu’s words were one thing, but his actions showed otherwise. His Lord Grim was healing himself at the moment.

Holy light flashed. When the match started, Lord Grim remained where he was and immediately started healing. Although with only low-level skills and no healing buffs, Lord Grim’s healing capabilities could only be used as emergency saves. Trying to completely heal himself to full like this wasn’t possible.

The 1v1 map wasn’t large. Even though Lin Jingyan was playing on this map for the first time, he had been watching the previous fight. And with everyone analyzing the map together, they had grasped bits and pieces of the map. His movements were firm, and he headed straight for the enemy spawn point.

“Hey, you’d better not be healing!” Lin Jingyan suddenly said in the chat.

“You really are going to win. I’ve been seen through!” Ye Xiu replied.

Lin Jingyan was helpless. It looked like he couldn’t take the easy way out. He had to be careful too. He couldn’t let Ye Xiu take out too much of health.

Soon, Lord Grim entered his line of sight. White light was flashing and flashing. Lord Grim had been healing the entire time, no? Ye Xiu soon saw the approaching Dark Thunder as well, and immediately typed out into the chat: “Can’t you wait a bit longer?”

Lin Jingyan ignored him. They were about to start fighting. He needed to concentrate. He couldn’t give Ye Xiu any opportunities. Chat? It was now time for him to ignore everything.

In terms of range, Lord Grim had a long range than Dark Thunder, so Dark Thunder had to enter Lord Grim’s range first. Lin Jingyan immediately became even more cautious. Dark Thunder started to slow down as he carefully observed Lord Grim’s movements and the terrain around him.

“I guess that’s it,” Ye Xiu sighed. During this time, he had been able to heal 6% of his health back. It was now a 7% health Lord Grim against a 100% health Dark Thunder.

It was very possible for one touch into death in this map due to the lava. Lin Jingyan subconsciously had his Dark Thunder stay farther away from the lava. If he wasn’t careful and was knocked into the lava, it would be devastating for him.

As he grew nearer, Lord Grim still didn’t act. Dark Thunder only needed three more steps for Lord Grim to enter his attack range, when finally, Lord Grim raised his umbrella in front of him.

Lin Jingyan immediately moved his mouse back and forth, so Dark Thunder would move erratically. He wouldn’t be moving in a straight line nor in a predictable left and right zig-zag. He wasn’t going to make it easy for Ye Xiu to hit him.

Bang bang!

Two gunshots. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim attack. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s gun form was a rifle, which could fire two times in a row.

The damage from normal attacks posed no threat, but if he could dodge them, why not dodge them?

After dodging the two bullets, he looked at Lord Grim again. Lord Grim wasn’t facing him, but rather, to the side.

He wants to play dirty!

Lin Jingyan had been Fang Rui’s partner for many years. He was very acute towards this sort of playing. Turning to the side to prevent the enemy from seeing everything. Fang Rui was an expert at it. He hid his character’s hands, so the opponent wouldn’t be able to figure out what skill he was planning on using.

The hand movements were crucial, so what skill did he plan on using?

Shadow Clone Technique?

That was Lin Jingyan’s first thought. Ninjas had been the first to come up with this technique of hiding their hands. Who made it so most of their skills required hand seals! Shadow Clone Technique required hand seals, and Ye Xiu often used it. Lin Jingyan’s thought process was very logical. He immediately had his character roll to the side, while swinging his claw towards the side.

One Night Eight Desolates!

This was the name of Dark Thunder’s Silver weapon. He had four claws on each hand. The color and luster were rather dull and didn’t give off any light. These claws swung in a semicircle motion.

“Old Lin, you over thought it!” Ye Xiu messaged.

One Night Eight Desolates missed. After Dark Thunder rolled, he adjusted his view, and now he was facing Lord Grim directly.

There weren’t any hand movements, just the muzzle of a gun.

Boom boom boom!

Anti-Tank Missiles.

Chapter 1541 - You've Won

Roll, another roll.

Lin Jingyan’s reacted surprisingly fast towards Lord Grim’s point-blank Anti-Tank Missiles. Dark Thunder rolled again, leaving the explosions behind him.

This time, Ye Xiu had encountered an opponent in dirtiness.

Lin Jingyan’s style in itself couldn’t be considered dirty, but he was extremely adept at dealing with people who played dirty. How could he not? He practice partner had been Fang Rui for many years.

Seeing Dark Thunder dodge the Anti-Tank Missile, the Tyranny players watching on the sidelines felt deeply moved.

“It’s up to him,” Zhang Jiale was confident.

Lin Jingyan was placed second in the group arena, and part of the reason for his placement was to deal with that 1% health on Lord Grim.

Yes, it was just 1%, but because it was Ye Xiu, Tyranny couldn’t underestimate him.

As old rivals of Ye Xiu, no one thought that Ye Xiu would just give up because he only had 1% of his health left. They were certain that he would use that 1% to annoy them as much as possible.

Sure enough, he started healing as soon as he spawned. Then, he even followed by saying “You’ve won.”

Yes, everyone had no doubt that Tyranny would win this fight, but at what cost?

As a result, they chose Lin Jingyan to play. With so little health left, Ye Xiu would certainly play dirty, and Lin Jingyan was the person with the most experience against it.

If it had been anyone else in Tyranny, that little trick of Ye Xiu’s might have really hit. But it was different with Lin Jingyan. He had dodged the Anti-Tank Missiles with ease.

When he got up, he launched himself towards Lord Grim with a Powerful Knee Strike.

The counterattack had been fast, but with the current distance between the two characters, the timing of this Powerful Knee Strike wasn’t good and it wouldn’t pose much of a threat.

This sort of rushed attack was quite good at restricting the dirty playstyle though. Playing dirty required observation, thinking, and set-up. By raising the tempo, it made it harder for the opponent to make these calculations. Although against those who were dirty to their bones, then their instinctive reactions would be dirty too. Just this sort of fast tempo wouldn’t be enough to suppress someone like that.

But Lin Jingyan had a lot of practice against this sort of dirtiness.

The Powerful Knee Strike wasn’t everything. As he leaped towards Lord Grim, Dark Thunder suddenly opened his hands and threw sand.

The purpose of the Powerful Knee Strike was simply as a movement skill. Sand Toss was the main focus. The Sand Toss transformed from a point attack to an AoE attack. Just moving to dodge the Powerful Knee Strike wouldn’t enough now, and it was too late to make any further movements.

Hua!

The sand crashed into Lord Grim. The grains of sand made crisp sounds as they hit. The only thing Ye Xiu could do was turn Lord Grim’s head around to avoid the Blind.

But Dark Thunder had already landed on the ground. He took step in the opposite direction of Lord Grim’s head turn. It was a subtle detail, but sometimes it was this sort of detail that was fatal. Dark Thunder threw out a punch.

Four sharp claws slashed upwards, but to everyone’s surprise, Lord Grim’s two hands had also extended out. He was looking in a different direction, but his hands were moving in this direction.

Fling!

Seeing these hand movements, Lin Jingyan immediately deduced what skill his opponent was using.

Perhaps one of their attacks might reach the other first, but either way, the Fling would go into effect. As for the Fling direction, it was obviously towards the lava.

Getting thrown into the lava by a 7% health Lord Grim was something that Lin Jingyan could not accept.

Jump back!

It’d be better if Lin Jingyan didn’t go through with his punch, instead of giving the opportunity away to Ye Xiu.

Dark Thunder jumped back to dodge the grab. Then, he stepped forward again to return the favor.

Fling, a Fling as well.

It was a Fling against a Fling, but when was starting up while the other was finishing up. After dodging the opponent’s Fling, he would use his own Fling as a counterattack. Lin Jingyan deserved to be someone who had played the game professionally for many years. Even though Fling was a Grappler skill, it was a skill no Fighter class would ever give up.

Unfortunately, Lin Jingyan had encountered an unspecialized, a class that was unprecedented in the competitive scene. What’s more, in the hands of that unspecialized was a miraculous weapon that had never been seen before.

Lord Grim was retracting his hands. It was the ending animation for Fling, but the umbrella that had split into two halves transformed back into one piece. The part that was extending outwards made its way past Dark Thunder’s hands and into his body.

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, spear form.

Battle Mage Skill: Circle Swing.

Dark Thunder was thrown into the sky. The only thing that Lin Jingyan could be glad about was that the Circle Swing could not throw him directly into the lava.

However, skills may be fixed, but people were alive. Lin Jingyan suddenly realized that Dark Thunder could move while in the air.

Grab skills locked the opponent’s movements while active. Right now, if his character could move, then it meant that the skill had ended.

By canceling Circle Swing midway through, a majority of the damage dealt by the skill was lost. But for Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder, if he continued following along his current path, he would be thrown into the far more terrifying lava.

Punch, kick…

Without the skill lock, Dark Thunder could do as he pleased in the air. But unfortunately, Brawlers didn’t have any movement skills while in the air. By punching and kicking, he could move his character’s trajectory slightly. However, the experienced Lin Jingyan already knew that it wasn’t enough.

Eagle Stamp!

Lin Jingyan thought of this move. He didn’t even need to put the skill on his weapon. All he needed was 20 skill points to learn it. If he had it, he could have turned this situation around.

But he didn’t have the luxury of these 20 skill points. His Dark Thunder didn’t have Eagle Stamp.

He could only have Dark Thunder throw out a Molotov Cocktail. He couldn’t just do nothing!

Unfortunately, this sort of venting didn’t pose any threat. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim easily dodged it. He raised his umbrella and fired two times.

Delivery Gun!

He wanted to use Delivery Gun to send him even farther away.

Lin Jingyan continued to have Dark Thunder punch and kick. The Delivery Gun technique required the player to hit the target’s center of mass to control the opponent’s movements. Only Sharpshooters with their rapid firing capabilities could occasionally grasp a moving target’s center of mass. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s gun form was a rifle. It could only fire twice before needing to reload and could not display the full effectiveness of Delivery Gun. But then, Lord Grim’s umbrella suddenly turned towards the sky. Ta ta ta ta ta, a burst of gunfire. Lin Jingyan wanted to cough blood. That shameless bastard was using Gatling Gun to execute a Delivery Gun.

The firing speed of Gatling Gun was fast to the point that it put the user’s aim to the test. How could Lin Jingyan have any doubts about Ye Xiu’s skill with it, though? The technique had been invented by him.

Unspecialized, ah, unspecialized. They were just ridiculously annoying.

Blood blossomed from Dark Thunder as he flew in an arc. The lava spread outwards to embrace him, and Dark Thunder cordially accepted it. Then, the lava began to burn away his health. Lin Jingyan turned around. On the shore, Ye Xiu was cordially waiting for him, ready to welcome him back.

Lin Jinyan wanted to cry. It would not be a good idea to challenge him directly. It’d be better to find a place farther away, so Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to block his escape.

Dark Thunder climbed out of the lava. Flames were still burning, dealing the last bits of damage. The crowd looked at the 48% health on Dark Thunder and were quiet. Then, they saw Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim run towards him, while typing out: “Old Lin, how could you be so careless, Old Lin. The lava’s pretty strong, no?”

The lava was indeed strong. He didn’t even have half his health anymore. How could Lin Jingyan reply back to it?

“You’ve won” was Lin Jingyan’s reply. It was what Ye Xiu had said at the start of the match.

But at this moment, it was the truth. For this fight to have turned out this way, it was a huge victory for Ye Xiu.

“You’re still alive. How could I say I’ve won :)” Ye Xiu even added a smiley face.

“I give you an inch, and you want a mile!” Lin Jingyan replied. Dark Thunder rushed forward to meet Lord Grim.

Technically speaking, Lin Jingyan had won.

But even the generous Tyranny fans found it hard to applaud for this sort of victory.

41%

This was Dark Thunder’s remaining health.

To get rid of that 7% from Lord Grim… or perhaps it would be better to say 1%, Tyranny had sacrificed far more than they would have liked.

Ye Xiu walked out from the player booth. Normally, there would definitely be boos being thrown at him. But right now, the Tyranny fans didn’t know if that was the right move, so they kept silent.

“Hm, this match… how do we describe it?” Pan Lin and Lin Yibo were having trouble finding words to summarize this fight.

You couldn’t really say Lin Jingyan’s performance was bad. It was because of the map that the single slip-up had cost him greatly.

“Maybe it’s better to say that Ye Xiu found the key point to this map first…” Li Yibo said.

Fuck off!

The vast majority of the people who heard his words cursed at him.

You’d have to be blind not to see what the key point to this map. Found it first? More like Ye Xiu was the first to successfully take advantage of it!

Chapter 1542 - Methodology

Ye Xiu… Ye Xiu…

The Tyranny fans stared silently at the bastard. They didn’t boo him, but they obviously weren’t going to clap for him. At this moment, they had no idea what they should do. Even the Happy fans that had come to support their team were affected by this atmosphere. The Happy fans weren’t used to a silent Tyranny stadium, and for a moment, they too didn’t know what to do.

“Is the entire stadium speechless from witnessing Ye Xiu’s skill?” Pan Lin sighed.

No one questioned Ye Xiu’s skill.

Even Tyranny fans. They might feel disgusted by Ye Xiu, but they would admit that Ye Xiu was very skilled. Perhaps in their hearts, Ye Xiu was the best. After all, only the best had the qualifications to make Tyranny hateful for ten years.

Their greatest losses had been at the hands of Ye Xiu. But at the same time, their greatest joys had also been come from him as well.

This time? It was only the group arena, and already, Tyranny’s fans had experienced heaven and then fallen into hell. In the end, not a single bit of happiness could be seen on them.

“YOU HAVE TO WIN!!”

No one knew who, but a shout suddenly came from the crowd.

The shout seemed to have resonated with everyone and instantly became their slogan, even if it wasn’t very suitable at this moment.

From a match standpoint, Ye Xiu was coming down from the stage as the loser! In theory, Tyranny had already beaten Ye Xiu.

But who could actually call that a win? No one did.

You have to win! It wasn’t just towards Ye Xiu, but towards all of Happy.

“Win, win!” The crowd roared.

The group arena had only just begun, and Tyranny’s fans were shouting as if it was matchpoint. The shouts from the Happy fans became more and more drowned out. They watched as Happy’s second player stood up and walked towards the stage. They were cheering as loud as they could, but they couldn’t even hear themselves.

Su Mucheng was Happy’s second player for the group arena. With Tyranny’s fans yelling “Win, win!”, if a stranger walked into the stadium, they would probably think that the crowd was cheering for Su Mucheng.

Tyranny’s fans didn’t care. They were giving themselves encouragement, pouring out their expectations for the team.

Win!

Win over Ye Xiu, win over Happy, win the championships!

The third round of the group arena, Happy’s Su Mucheng against Tyranny’s Lin Jingyan.

The match began. After spawning, both sides went towards the middle of the map. Soon, they were within each other’s sight.

“The player sent up is decided during the match. In that case, Su Mucheng’s appearance in the group arena certainly has a purpose to it,” Li Yibo analyzed, “I’m guessing that Happy wants to use the ultra-long range of a Launcher to use the natural barrier created from the field of lava to whittle down Lin Jingyan.”

That was what Li Yibo thought, and that was also what others thought, including Lin Jingyan. If Su Mucheng decided to stay back and harass him to death, it indeed wouldn’t be easy to deal with.

If it was difficult to deal with, then simply don’t deal with it.

Glory matches had no time limit, so there was no need to be afraid of dragging out the match. If Su Mucheng’s plan was to harass him to death from afar, then all he needed to do was not approach her. The lava was an obstacle for him and for Su Mucheng. No matter what Su Mucheng did, with the lava separating the two ends, there was a limit to her range.

If Su Mucheng insisted on waiting there until he approached, then both sides would just be sitting there. From a match standpoint, if both sides remained in a stalemate, then the referee would need to interfere. However, neither side could be blamed, so both sides would have to be penalized. Would it be a warning? A yellow card? Or even a red card?

If it was a red card, then Happy would lose out. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was at full health. She had a health lead. If both sides were given a red card, it would be mutual destruction. How could the one winning not be losing out on the trade?

Su Mucheng wasn’t so stupid as to give herself a red card, so these were just random thoughts from Lin Jingyan. It was doubtful that the referee would end the battle in such a crude fashion too. If the match really did turn into a stalemate, then the referee would likely interfere by having the system force them to spawn at two new locations and force them to fight.

Lin Jingyan had been a part of the Alliance for nine years. He had seen many things. The Glory competitive rules needed to be impartial to the competitors, while also needing to consider the spectators, the broadcast, the sponsors, and so on. Even after revising the rules many times, there were still many awkward rulings in place. The Alliance was still growing to this day. It wasn’t perfect.

Exploiting these sort of gray areas had become one type of strategy in Glory competitive play. The Alliance did not encourage this behavior, but there was nothing they could do to stop it. They could only try their best to create a more perfect ruleset and patch up these holes. But before these holes were patched, they could always be taken advantage of.

As a result, Dark Thunder stopped moving forward. He began moving horizontally. His current distance from the lava was around ten steps.

This is?

Many people were feeling somewhat conflicted about Lin Jingyan’s actions. However, Li Yibo had analyzed what methods Su Mucheng might use in this map, which weren’t difficult to guess. Seeing Dark Thunder’s movements, the viewers soon realized that even if Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain fired from the edge of the lava, she still wouldn’t be able to reach him. What would happen then? If the two sides didn’t make any changes, the match would turn into stalemate, and then what?

For people familiar with Glory, it wasn’t a difficult question at all.

Then, the referee would interfere and force the two characters to fight. Then, Su Mucheng would have lost her barrier. Perhaps the two characters would spawn too close together, making it so that her Launcher would immediately be in a dangerous position.

“He’s planning on taking advantage of the rules to change the situation…” Li Yibo said, “This…”

“This… Tyranny… this…” Pan Lin didn’t know what to say.

Taking advantage of a loophole was clearly something that Tyranny’s fans despised, yet right now, their player was using this exact method to win. This wasn’t a scene they should be seeing from their Team Tyranny…

How could Lin Jingyan not know this?

But he had never been one who could represent Tyranny!

Even though he now wore Tyranny’s jersey, his spirit had been tempered and completed during his seven years at Wind Howl. He had fought alone. He had fought together with Fang Rui as the Criminal Partners. On his path to glory, he had never been a straight and upright hero. Even so, during those seven years, he had never even made it into the playoffs.

Fighting with those geniuses was too difficult. He sometimes hated how his two hands didn’t have more fingers.

Take advantage of loopholes?

He didn’t care if it was shameful. All he cared about was winning and how he wasn’t doing enough.

He was just a normal person, but his thirst for victory was no less than anyone else’s. He might not be a genius of any kind, but he was willing to do anything to win. Exploiting loopholes? So what! That was one way to win.

If there was loophole that he could take advantage of, of course he should take advantage of it.

Lin Jingyan didn’t hesitate. Dark Thunder stopped moving forward. But then, he saw Dancing Rain head directly for him.

The referee didn’t need to interfere, but everyone could see that by exploiting the rules, Lin Jingyan created a disadvantageous situation for Happy. Perhaps it had forced Su Mucheng to give up on her original strategy of using her long range and the lava to win.

“She’s going straight for him. Lin Jingyan should be very satisfied, right?” Pan Lin said somewhat mockingly. After all, as an official staff member of the Alliance, he couldn’t approve of this sort of behavior.

Boom boom boom.

Dancing Rain fired artillery shells as she sprinted. She didn’t rely on the lava as a barrier, instead, going for a frontal assault. She created a path extending from her position to Dark Thunder’s position. If it were any other Tyranny player, they would have likely jumped out and rushed towards Dancing Rain’s barrage to try to close the distance with the Launcher.

But not Lin Jingyan. He was retreating. It seemed like he wasn’t satisfied with the terrain here. He was retreating back to a place where there were piles of limestone scattered about. These piles could act as cover. Lin Jingyan was luring Su Mucheng towards there. That area was obviously unfavorable for Su Mucheng, but what choice did she have?

If she didn’t keep going, Lin Jingyan would simly have Dark Thunder stop and wait. He would then keep his distance away from her, and the fight would reach a stalemate again…

He was still taking advantage of the rules!

If the referee interfered, they would likely be forced to spawn near each other, which would be unfavorable for the Launcher. He was utilizing this point to lure Su Mucheng into an area which was unfavorable for her.

“How despicable!!” Seeing Lin Jingyan’s actions, Happy’s fans roared out. Their boos went out in waves, and this time, Tyranny’s fans didn’t retaliate.

Tyranny’s fans felt embarrassed too.

Lin Jingyan had joined the team in the final years of his career. He had received no small measure of trust from them, and in turn, he had contributed greatly to Tyranny. They looked forward to him winning the championships together with Tyranny.

But this sort of method…

If they really won in this fashion, Tyranny’s fans would truly feel somewhat disgusted. They had always valued the journey over the end result. As a result, they cared about the way they won. Lin Jingyan’s method of winning was extremely displeasing to see.

Boo?

They couldn’t bear to either. After all, they had watched Lin Jingyan closely these past two years. They had seen his dedication and the effort he put in. They had seen how hard he and Tyranny worked.

But why, why did he need to use this sort of despicable method for such an important moment?

Tyranny’s fans were silent. Once again, they were silent.

Chapter 1543 - Late

Tyranny was the Alliance's boldest and most hot-blooded team, and likewise, their fans were also the most passionate and the fiercest. But at the same time, Tyranny was also Glory's most cultured team.

Cultured...

The word didn't seem to fit in with Tyranny's image. Do everything you can to win because winning is glory. This concept had no contradiction with Tyranny.　

Tyranny was their romance. Even though this so-called "romance" had no connection with the word.

Lin Jingyan's way of conduct didn't conform with their romance.

However, they could feel this old general's desire for victory. They didn't have to like his methods, but they had to recognize his efforts. It was similar to how even though they hated Ye Xiu, they recognized his might.　　

Tyranny's fans had well-defined likes and dislikes.

Love and hate had intertwined on a single person, and they didn't know how to feel.

The atmosphere of the stadium didn't interfere with the match.

Up ahead was favorable terrain for Lin Jingyan. If Su Mucheng didn't go after him though, Lin Jingyan could take advantage of the rules to create a favorable situation for him.

Either way, it wouldn't be good for Su Mucheng.

But Dancing Rain didn't stop. She continued to chase after Dark Thunder, but her pathing was shifted by a certain amount.

This is...

Everyone looked for where Dancing Rain was moving towards.　

Oh!!

The experts soon realized her gaol.　　

Su Mucheng was taking advantage of that fact that Lin Jingyan wasn't taking the initiative to attack her. She wasn't in a hurry to chase after Dark Thunder. Instead, she was taking a roundabout route so that she could enter Lin Jingyan's desired area from the side. In this way, even though she would still have to fight in unfavorable terrain, Lin Jingyan wouldn't have the initiative.

She hadn't completely eliminated the disadvantage, but she had reduced it.　

Lin Jingyan didn't have a good way to stop her. If he continued to try and restrict her movements, the referee would judge only him as being passive. Lin Jingyan dared to exploit the rules because he knew how the referee would judge the situation. In the end, he could only have Dark Thunder continue along his original path towards the region with limestones. Dark Thunder soon arrived there and hid behind a pile of limestone.

He had disappeared from Su Mucheng's view, but with Dancing Rain entering the region from the side, she could also hide herself using the limestones as cover.

Previously, the enemy would have known her location, while she would have been in the dark. Now, neither the enemy nor her knew her location. This was Su Mucheng's aim.

That was what practically everyone though, but to their surprise, Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain began attacking before she even stepped into the region.

Boom boom boom!

Artillery fire roared.

What?

Everyone was confused.

By doing this, wouldn't the enemy know where she was, while she didn't know where the enemy was? Even if Lin Jingyan couldn't see her, he could get her approximate location through sound alone. Everyone thought that Su Mucheng would do the same as Lin Jingyan. Her character would enter the region and use the limestones as cover. Then, through her long range attacks, she would search for her opponent. But before she even reached the area, she started attacking.

These attacks wouldn't be able to reach Lin Jingyan. It wasn't a matter of whether or not he could be seen. Lin Jingyan could use the limestone as cover to protect himself.

What is she doing?

Everyone looked at Dancing Rain curiously. The limestone was quite sturdy. Her Launcher attacks were only able to break off small pieces of it a time, so it wasn't like she could just blast away all the obstacles there.

However, Dancing Rain continued to attack as she moved.　

The sound of cannon fire and explosions were mixed together. Was she planning on making it so that Lin Jingyan wouldn't be able to find her through sound alone.　

It did have a masking effect, but wasn't it just to hide her true location? What was the difference between doing this and going into the region silently?

After the camera switched to Lin Jingyan's perspective, everyone understood.

There was a difference!

With a silent infiltration, neither side would know each other's position. They could only slowly search for each other. It would be a matter of luck, and if she suddenly encountered her opponent int close range, it would be extremely bad for her Launcher.

But now, by taking the initiative to attack, she was exposing her own position, but at the same time, she was baiting Lin Jingyan into making a move. Lin Jingyan's judgement was extremely important. If he made a mistake, he would expose himself to Su Mucheng's attacks. However, if he could clearly figure out her position amidst all this loud noise, then he could directly get close to her.

This was a gamble!

She was betting on Lin Jingyan's ability to find her.　　

And so how was Lin Jingyan doing?

The camera switched to Lin Jingyan's perspective. The viewers could hear whatever Lin Jingyan was hearing. They tried to get a feel for distance and direction like what Lin Jingyan was doing. Soon, the normal players felt defeated. What was all this! The noise was everywhere. There was no way to tell what was what. But Lin Jingyan? His Dark Thunder moved precisely, and from their bird's eye view of the map, they could see that he was moving towards Dancing Rain's position. When they put the two together, they could see that he was also using the limestones as cover as he approached.

Perhaps it was a hard to get her precise location now, but as he got closer, it would be easier.　　

But at this moment, the battle had taken a turn that no one had expected.

Although the limestones didn't completely crumble under Dancing Rain's attacks, bits and pieces would chip off. Gradually, the dust from the limestone began to fill the air, becoming more and more dense.

"A smoke bomb..." Pan Lin blurted out. The visibility in this area was decreasing as time went on, and the approaching Dark Thunder was gradually being surrounded by this dust.　

"This is part of Su Mucheng's plan too, right?" Pan Lin said.

"I... don't think so!" Li Yibo said. Because the dust was slowly accumulating, by the time they noticed it, the dust had already spread everywhere. Even though the dust hid her to some extent, it also hid the enemy. It was actually more unfavorable for the Launcher. Since it reduced her visibility, by the time she noticed her enemy, they would be at mid-distance and she wouldn't be able to display her long-ranged advantage.

This was definitely an accident.

Because she had to keep attacking the limestone relatively close to her, the situation had unknowingly turned out this way. The biggest proof was that she stopped firing. Su Mucheng clearly understood that she couldn't continue like this.

"Ah, random maps!" Li Yibo sighed. It was a situation brought about by random maps. The plan might be good, but there was no way to know everything about the map.

This was certainly a good opportunity for Lin Jingyan. After he discovered this point, he didn't hesitate for long. He used the dust as cover and had Dark Thunder dash towards Dancing Rain's approximate location.

Artillery fire could be heard again.

"What?" Seeing Dancing Rain suddenly attack again and seemingly faster too, Pan Lin was confused.

Too late!　　

Lin Jingyan had determined Dancing Rain's position because of the pause from Su Mucheng. It had probably been an instinctive pause. Su Mucheng quickly realized her mistake, so she started attacking more intensely than before.

But she was too late.

That pause was enough for Lin Jingyan to determine her precise location.　　

Launcher attacks weren't rapid-fire. After firing once, she had to reload. That was why she needed to mix in the sound of explosions to hide it. But by suddenly stopping, her final shot became incomparably clear, and Lin Jingyan grasped it.

Su Mucheng had realized it and hastily tried to cover for her mistake, but she was too late.　

Dark Thunder suddenly appeared in front of her. The distance was only five units.

Charge!

No hesitation.　

He couldn't miss such a rare opportunity. He needed to stick close and finish her.　　

Boom boom boom!

Dancing Rain immediately turned around and attacked.

Aerial Cannon, just like he expected!

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Dark Thunder immediately activated this Striker skill. The Super Armor protected him from being knocked back by the artillery shells. He took a wide step and launched himself from the ground, Powerful Knee Strike!

The knee strike was far faster than the retreating Dancing Rain. The distance between them was instantly wiped away, and with Reinforced Iron Bones activated, he wasn't affected by her attacks.

But he didn't want the knee strike to connect. He wanted to get close to Dancing Rain, not knock her away.

The instant he got close to her, he cancelled Powerful Knee Strike. His hands extended out.　　

Grab!　　

If he had been a Striker or a Grappler, this grab would have likely missed because the distance was rather far still. Their arms weren't long enough.

However, Brawlers were different. Brawlers could wear claws. Claws were the only Fighter weapons with a bit of reach. His two hands might not be able to grab onto Dancing Rain, but the claws on his hands could. His weapon, One Night Eight Desolates, extended his reach, making this distance just enough for him to land the grab. His claws latched onto Dancing Rain's shoulders.

Back Throw!

Lin Jingyan didn't use Fling. Instead, he used the sub Level 20 Grappler skill, Back Throw. The target would be thrown directly behind him, instead of far away.

The Back Throw was completed. Dark Thunder threw Dancing Rain behind him, but when he looked towards the ground, Lin Jingyan was stunned.

The dust from the limestone was very dense. He couldn't see the ground.

He couldn't see the ground...

Wait...

Lin Jingyan realized it too late! The two characters plunged into the lava.

Chapter 1544 - Mounted Gun

Dark Thunder was still in the middle of his Back Throw. With his body bent, he fell into the lava along with Dancing Rain. The fiery-red lava rippled across the hazy ash.

Lin Jingyan’s heart fell together with Dark Thunder.

Coincidence? Luck?

Of course not. The density of the ash in this area had to be much higher than in other areas to hide the lava like this. It was a smokescreen that Su Mucheng had intentionally set up.

It was a set up.

Everything was a set up.

The continuous attacks had been to hide her and to bait him to come over. The instinctive pause in her attacks and her haste to cover up her mistake had been an act. Everything had to been to lure Lin Jingyan into this trap.

Lava, lava again.

It was obvious that the lava dealt a lot of damage and shouldn’t be touched, yet everyone who had participated in this group arena had fallen into it. Lin Jingyan felt like couldn’t show his face.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had fallen together with Dancing Rain though. The Back Throw would still take effect, which meant that Lin Jingyan could continue attacking her in the lava.

Fight!

Lin Jingyan came to a decision. It’d be better to struggle in the lava than escape. Similar to the high DPS fight between Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing, the lava was also an opportunity to deal massive amounts of damage.

Touch the ground and twist around.

Dark Thunder moved freely in the lava. The instant Dancing Rain was thrown to the bottom, he twisted his body.

Tyrannical Chain Punch!

Dark Thunder immediately started with a high-level skill.

The follow-up had been perfect. There was nothing Su Mucheng could do. Her original intention was obviously for Dark Thunder to fall into the lava, while Dancing Rain stayed on shore attacking him. Unfortunately, she wasn’t able to fully achieve her goal. Lin Jingyan wasn’t so easy to deal with. Even though he probably hadn’t realized her plan at that time, his Back Throw had forced both of them to fall into the lava.

Su Mucheng wasn’t completely unprepared for this possibility, but Lin Jingyan had already decided to abandon everything. After the Back Throw, he didn’t hesitate to follow up with Tyrannical Chain Punch. This place happened to be a corner of the map. There was nowhere to run. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain could only take the attack.

Strike after strike landed, and the lava began to stir again.

Dark Thunder’s health was dropping, but Dancing Rain, who was taking damage from both the lava and enemy attacks, was losing health faster.

Maybe he can win?

Some people saw the speed at which Dancing Rain’s health was falling, and their eyes lit up. However, the experts didn’t think so. Right now, the high DPS was because of Tyrannical Chain Punch. Brawlers didn’t have ways to maintain this sort of damage output. This situation would only be temporary. Once the Tyrannical Chain Punch ended, it would end.

If this continued, there was no way Lin Jingyan could win. However, if he did well enough, he could deal a lot of damage to Dancing Rain. Lin Jingyan’s firm resolution was quite worthy of admiration.

Boom!

The final hit of Tyrannical Chain Punch created a small crater in the lava. Finally, Dancing Rain was able to escape. The shockwave had knocked her to the side. Dark Thunder was in the middle of the ending animation of the attack. However, during this brief period of time, Dancing Rain was stunned and couldn’t act either. It could be considered a sort of protection for the player who used Tyrannical Chain Punch.

It looks like everything depends on what happens next!

The experts in the crowd understood this point clearly. In theory, after using Tyrannical Chain Punch, it was possible to make any guaranteed follow-ups. As a result, whether or not the combo continued depended on the situation and the player.

Lin Jingyan needed to be on the offensive in order to deal as much damage as possible. Whether he succeeded would be the key to the outcome of this battle.

Paralysis Needle!

As soon as Dark Thunder could act again, a needle flew out.

Paralysis Needle paralyzed the target. With the crashing waves of lava all around, the needle was too small to see. After throwing out the needle, he rushed out. But with half of his body in the lava, the amount of resistance from it wasn’t small. The difference was that Dark Thunder had used another high-level skill.

Street Riot!

It was an offensive skill, but it could also be considered a support skill too. During Street Riot’s duration, all mid- and low-level Brawler skills were buffed. In addition, the usual skill cooldowns were eliminated.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Dark Thunder used another skill. The lava split apart, and Dark Thunder shot towards Dancing Rain. His two hands weren’t idle either. He threw out a brick with his left hand and sand with his right hand. In a short amount of time, he threw out who knew how many skills at Dancing Rain.

Hit!

Paralysis Needle hit, Brick hit, Sand Toss hit!

Dark Thunder was almost about to reach her, when a bright light suddenly shined from within the lava. Dancing Rain had quickly lifted her cannon and then fired at Dark Thunder.

It was a Quantum Bomb!

The light crashed towards Dark Thunder. At this distance and that speed, Lin Jingyan had no way to dodge.

The bright light engulfed him and then sent him flying. However, the powerful recoil didn’t affect Dancing Rain. As the lava was pushed aside by the shockwave, they could see that Dancing Rain stood firmly on top of a support.

The Paralysis Needle had hit. The Brick had hit. The Sand Toss had also hit. Why did the Quantom Bomb not get interrupted?

Quantum Bomb had a powerful recoil, yet Dancing Rain didn’t seem to be affected at all.

Everyone saw the reason for it.

Launcher Level 75 skill: Mounted Gun.

After the skill was used, the Launcher would be fixed to a spot unable to move. In exchange, the Launcher’s attack power would be greatly increased and the Launcher’s attacks could not be interrupted.

Su Mucheng had sneakily hidden a Mounted Gun underneath the lava. Lin Jingyan respected this play wholeheartedly. After blown back, Dark Thunder focused on Dancing Rain again. He saw the cannon on the Mounted Gun flash again.

Boom!

Another artillery shell shot towards Dancing Rain.

Damage from attacks and lava? That was what Lin Jingyan had been doing to Dancing Rain just before, and the blink of an eye, Su Mucheng returned the favor. With how much health Dancing Rain had, there was no chance for another opportunity to counterattack.

Glory!

Amidst the raging lava, Dark Thunder’s health fell to zero. In the third round of the group arena, Happy’s Su Mucheng won while losing 29% of her health. The Quantum Bomb parting the waves and revealing the Mounted Gun hidden beneath the lava was the biggest highlight of this match. The broadcast put on a replay of this scene. For the sake of appearances, since this was Tyranny’s home stadium, a highlight showcasing the away team’s might wouldn’t be good to keep looping no matter how incredible it was.

Lin Jingyan walked down from the stage. In this all-important match, his performance was unsatisfactory to say the least. He had only taken out 7% of Lord Grim’s health, which could even be considered as just 1%, and 29% of Dancing Rain’s health. That was what he was able to achieve in today’s group arena. The loss was big enough to lead to Tyranny’s overall loss in the group arena.

Was that all?

He had gone all out and even tried to exploit a loophole in the rules. Even so, he had suffered a crushing defeat. Lin Jingyan felt extremely disappointed in the outcome and in himself.

However, the applause from the crowd had made Lin Jingyan feel somewhat astonished.

Tyranny’s fans weren’t the type to just toss aside the loser. Whether in victory or defeat, the battle was what mattered. As long as the player performed to their satisfaction, it was good in the hearts of Tyranny’s fans.

But what about today’s match?

Lin Jingyan was quite clear that his performance wasn’t great. He had even done something that Tyranny’s fans didn’t like. Even so, why was the crowd applauding for him?

The applause couldn’t be considered enthusiastic, after all, Tyranny’s fans were still somewhat hesitant. Lin Jingyan didn’t perform the way they liked, and the outcome left much to be desired. However, they still applauded for him because they recognized Lin Jingyan’s efforts, especially in his final act, risking his life to try and pave the way for his teammates. Lin Jingyan was a part of Team Tyranny. He had tossed aside his honor for the sake of victory, for the tea’s victory. This sort of mentality was worthy of being praised.

Even if he had used a few unpleasant methods, these details could be ignored!

Tyranny fan after Tyranny fan began opening their hearts. The applause became more and more fervent. When the applause thundered across the stadium, Lin Jingyan felt stunned as he walked back to this seat.

“Go Tyranny!” A loud cheer came from the crowd.

Lin Jingyan wasn’t someone who was easily moved, but at this moment, he couldn’t restrain himself anymore. These two matches had been quite depressing. Right now, no one wanted Tyranny to win more than he did.

“Go Tyranny!” Lin Jingyan suddenly roared to the crowd. It was a display of passion that had never appeared before in his career. On Happy’s side, his friend Fang Rui felt surprised seeing his excitement.

“Go go go!!!” Tyranny’s fans felt another surge of energy seeing his response. Lin Jingyan waved his hands as he shouted towards the crowd. The atmosphere of the crowd gradually followed along with him.

Tyranny’s next player had already stood up from his eat.

Zhang Jiale, Tyranny’s third general.

“Go!” As he walked towards the stage, he passed by Lin Jingyan and gave him a high five. They were passing on their desire to win.

Chapter 1545 - Distance

When Zhang Jiale high-fived Lin Jingyan, the intensity of the crowd reached a peak. Zhang Jiale also waved his hands towards the audience. Then, he began calming himself down to steady his emotions.

Su Mucheng wasn’t someone who could be beaten just by being enthusiastic.

Su Mucheng had joined the Alliance in Season 4. In that sense, Zhang Jiale, who had joined in Season 2, could be considered her senior. The beginning of Season 4 was the when Ye Xiu and Excellent Era were at the peak, having won all three prior championships. However, several Excellent Era players had retired in that summer. Everyone was watching Excellent Era attentively, wondering whether they could fill in these gaps.

Then, Su Mucheng, a beautiful girl, entered their sights.

In terms of publicity, Excellent Era had succeeded.

Just having a female player join the team was enough to bring about much discussion from the public. But for pro players who cared about winning the championship trophy, whether or not this female player had the skill to back up her addition to the team was their main concern. She had to compete with those at the peak of Glory and stand alongside the most troublesome player in the competitive scene.

Soon afterwards, everyone quickly noticed the astonishing synergy between Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu. It was as if they had been practicing together as partners for many years. Later, they discovered that Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu had a long history together, so it made sense that the two would have a certain understanding of each other already. Some people even joked that Ye Xiu had truly deep schemes, raising a Glory partner for himself starting from when they were children.

From then on, the Golden Partners were born, and since it was a male and female duo, many people thought of them as lovers. There were even many pro players who were jealous. Partners with a girl, and a beautiful one at that, how could that bastard not be having the time of his life?

Unfortunately, despite being acclaimed as Glory’s Best Partners, they were unable to defend their championship title.

In Season 4, it could be blamed on the rookies not having enough experience. However, the ones who had stolen away Excellent Era’s crown was a team that had been assisted by a rookie. The three peats, Excellent Era, had been eliminated by Tyranny. Under the protection from the rookie Zhang Xinjie, Tyranny overthrew Excellent Era’s dynasty.

Then, Season 5, Season 6, Season 7…

Every year, the two remained as the Best Partners. There was no debate over it. Their synergy together was unmatched. But what about their achievements? Excellent Era was getting worse and worse each year.

As the core of the team, the Best Partners were the first to be picked at. The world had recognized Ye Xiu’s incredible skill long ago. One Autumn Leaf still looked as powerful as ever. Then, the question became: did the issue lie in Su Mucheng?

As a result, controversy gradually surrounded Su Mucheng, and her looks seemed to be the main focus of the attacks. All sorts of malicious words were thrown at her, and to this day, the debate hadn’t completely disappeared.

“If that really was the case, then things would be easy!”

The moment the two characters loaded into the map, Zhang Jiale had this thought.

Su Mucheng had changed. To players like Zhang Jiale, who had observed her as an opponent for many years, they could feel this change.

The former Su Mucheng focused on synergy and coordination with Ye Xiu. Because of this focus, her options would often lean more towards sentimentality than rationality. At the same time, it also made it so that she lacked autonomy. Of course, it wasn’t to the point where the outside world would fault her for it, but the flaw still existed nonetheless.

This flaw had gradually begun to improve after Ye Xiu’s retirement. She had lost the target of her coordination and synergy. She had lost her partner of many years. Perhaps Su Mucheng had no choice but to make adjustments. However, these adjustments had made her stronger. After joining Team Happy and returning to Ye Xiu’s side, she didn’t go back to the previous Su Mucheng, who only focused on synergy and coordination with Ye Xiu. She had assumed a completely new stance to fight alongside with Ye Xiu once again.

She was different. She was better!

Those familiar with Su Mucheng as an opponent quickly became aware of her improvement. As the season progressed, the skill that she displayed was becoming more and more formidable. It was because she was adapting to her new team. Even though Happy had Ye Xiu, the others were new teammates. It wasn’t until she completely assimilated herself into this new environment would her true skill be displayed.

It had been an entire season and half the playoffs, yet no one knew if she had reached her peak. All they knew was that throughout this entire season, she had been constantly improving. Whether or not she had a breakthrough in the future was also uncertain.

They had noticed her evolution long ago, and they should have strangled it long ago!

Zhang Jiale sighed. The match had begun. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms played around with the ammunition clip of his gun as he rushed forward.

Su Mucheng didn’t delay either. Dancing Rain set out quickly as well. The two were sprinting towards the center as if they wanted to be the first to reach it.

Encounter!

The two soon noticed each other. Even though both were long-ranged classes, Launchers had the highest range out of any class. Only the Sharpshooter’s Thunder Snipe skill could outrange a Launcher’s attacks. However, Sharpshooters couldn’t just rely on this one skill to fight with Launchers. It was a high-level skill. Once it was used, it would be on a long cooldown and couldn’t be spammed.

No class could contend with a Launcher’s range. When fighting against a Launcher, the distance had to be pulled closer. The difference between classes was just how much distance.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had not entered his effective firing range yet, when Dancing Rain had started attacking.

Boom!

Fire spouted out as the attacks arrived. But at such a far distance, there was quite a bit of time for him to dodge. At this distance, it usually wasn’t too big of a problem for most classes to avoid Launcher attacks. However, when trying to close the distance, you could easily tell that with every step, the threat of the Launcher’s attacks increased. When the firing line of the Launcher was reached, it became even more difficult to get past the heavy artillery fire.

Su Mucheng had let Tyranny experience a special skill from her, three intersecting firing lines. Tyranny had called it a “Snowflake” firing line.

Trying to break past Su Mucheng’s firing line was extremely difficult. As a result, last round, Lin Jingyan didn’t bother trying and took advantage of the ruleset.

What about Zhang Jiale?

After Dazzling Hundred Blossoms dodged Dancing Rain’s attack, he threw a grenade, not far from him, just three steps away.

Boom, the grenade exploded. Fire and smoke lifted up limestone into the air. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms seemed to flicker and turn hazy in the light. Then, a second and third grenade followed.

The explosions overlapped, and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms disappeared. He was using his Hundred Blossoms style as cover while he approached.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions rang continuously. Light and shadow spread, making it impossible to figure out Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s location. What’s more, he wasn’t moving in a straight line.

Ta ta ta ta ta!

Dancing Rain took out a Gatling Gun. Bullets flew and swept across the light.

“She knows a bit!”

Zhang Jiale saw the Gatling Gun and knew that Su Mucheng had done some research on his Hundred Blossoms style. After all, the two had fought against each other for many years. This time, they would be meeting in the playoffs. How could she not prepare herself for Zhang Jiale’s famed playstyle?

Unfortunately, it wasn’t enough!

If the Hundred Blossoms style could be destroyed so easily, how could it have become famous?

Dodge!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms dodged the Gatling Gun’s bullets, and it didn’t seem to affect his own attacks in the slightest. In the blink of an eye, the wave of light pushed forward another length. Suddenly, the light burst out like fireworks. This final display was the most brilliant and the most blinding. In that instant, everyone watching in the stadium were bedazzled by the light.

This sudden blossoming was no longer to hide him. The thorn hidden by the cluster of flowers shot out.

Bang bang bang bang…

The automatic pistol’s firing speed was above the commonly used Sharpshooter revolver. Sharpshooters commonly used revolvers because they could dual wield, allowing them to fire twice as many shots. It was what allowed them to suppress other Gunner classes.

Sharpshooters could dual wield automatic pistols as well. It would give them astonishing firing speed, but very few chose to do so because automatic pistols were considered magic weapons. On the other hand, Spitfires often used automatic pistols precisely because most of their attacks dealt magic damage.

Ice Bullet!

The Ice Bullet dealt ice damage. Every bullet had a layer of dull blue light emanating from it. Frosty air floated around it. As the bullet flew forward, it left a trail of crystals.

One after the other…

In a short moment, innumerable trails had concentrated together. After the class advancement skill “Ammunition Expansion” was raised to max level, special one-time bullets like Ice Bullet could be stored up to 20 times. In an instant, all 20 bullets were let out. Kaka. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms finished switching ammunition clips. Before the light completely dissipated, he rushed out.

Bang bang bang bang bang… another round of gunfire. This time, the bullets left a fiery red trail: Blazing Bullets.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had already entered his attack range, so he immediately launched his offense. Even though his firepower wasn’t as powerful as Launcher’s, he could attack much faster. His magic bullets would trigger special effects on contact as well. Zhang Jiale didn’t fear a fight at this distance.

As for Su Mucheng?

Kakaka and then a support fell to the ground. She placed her heavy cannon onto it, while she stood behind it, her two hands holding it stably.

She didn’t run.

Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain use Mounted Gun again. Last round, she had hidden it in the lava and used it to destroy Lin Jingyan’s plans. This time, she made no secret of it.

Wind began gathering around her cannon. Although the Ice Bullets hit her one after another, the wind roared out all at once!

It was another Level 75 skill.

Hurricane Cannon!

Chapter 1546 - Consolidating an Advantage

Unyielding. There was no way to be more unyielding than this.

Not moving an inch, her cannon lined up perfectly. Su Mucheng welcomed Dazzling Hundred Blossoms head on.

Whoosh!

Hurricane Cannon flew out accompanied by high-pitched whistling. When Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fired his second round of attacks after reloading, his shots were all caught in the Hurricane Cannon and were blown off-course.

Zheng Jiale was astonished. He did not expect Su Mucheng to attack so forcefully.

Last round, there were tricks upon tricks. This round, she couldn’t be more direct if she tried. Su Mucheng had become a player who could make an unwavering decision based on the current situation. She’s freed herself of the shackles of excessive cooperation with Ye Xiu, and no longer had the slight cluelessness she used to have when Ye Xiu wasn’t present.

Dodge!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, who was charging forward, had to dodge sideways. But how could Hurricane Cannon’s power be so easily escaped? Dazzling Hundred Blossoms managed to avoid being hit directly, but was still caught in the twisting, cannonball-like hurricane. His body immediately staggered from the force.

Boom!

Cannonfire still rang out. Su Mucheng was clearly not going to give Zhang Jiale any time to catch his breath. Explosion after explosion followed. However, Zhang Jiale was also not one to be so easily stopped. Even though Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was shaken by the Hurricane Cannon, he still managed to control his character accurately while staggering.

Flash Bullet!

A Flash Bullet flew out, followed closely by a gunshot. Zheng Jiale did not wait for the Flash Bullet to hit the ground, and directly shot and blew it up mid-air.

Blinding light instantly flashed out. At this moment, even the spectators were dazzled by the bright flash. The broadcast cut quickly to Su Mucheng’s first-person perspective. Everyone also hastily looked at the big screen, curious as to whether Su Mucheng was affected by this Flash Bullet.

She was somewhat, but not completely.

It seemed that Su Mucheng had immediately turned away when she noticed the Flash Bullet, but Zhang Jiale had been too quick in triggering the explosion. As a result, Dancing Rain was unable to avert her gaze entirely. In the end, even though she wasn’t completely blinded, there was definitely some haziness in her view of the surroundings. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, who was actively moving around, currently seemed like a hazy blur.

Another grenade was thrown.

What grenade was it?

Su Mucheng could only see a mosaic of pixels flying towards her, and had no chance to differentiate the type of grenade.

So she just completely ignored it, and simply continued to attack.

Under the effects of Mounted Gun, a character had no way to move from their position. Of course, the opponent also had no way to disrupt Dancing Rain’s position. Therefore, Su Mucheng might as well not care which attack was coming at her, and just use attacks in response to Zhang Jiale.

Mutual attacks.

An extremely crude exchange of attacks.

On this side, Su Mucheng had completely abandoned attempting to dodge any attacks. What about Zhang Jiale’s side? Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’s movement was not restricted like Su Mucheng’s was by Mounted Gun, but he had already advanced this far, and Su Mucheng was tanking all his attacks. In this situation, choosing to retreat would only be wasting his own health, while also surrendering the distance he’s worked so hard to gain.

Attack for attack, blood for blood. At this time, there was no alternative. Su Mucheng had forced Zhang Jiale to have an exchange like this.

A Launcher using Mounted Gun clearly had heavier fire-power. Zhang Jiale did not let go of his advantage of free movement. If he simply stood still and traded with Mounted Gun, it wouldn’t be any different from suicide.

This battle turned into a slugfest where neither combatant was willing to back down. But the outcome would really be decided by Zhang Jiale’s ability to dodge attacks. For Dancing Rain who was using Mounted Gun, dodging was out of the question.

Bang bang bang!

Boom boom boom!

Endless gunshots, cannonfire and explosions resounded.

In the end, Su Mucheng lost.

This result could not be considered unexpected since Dancing Rain began the round with a health disadvantage. However, the difference was only 29%. It wasn’t an overwhelming one. This kind of disadvantage could be wiped out with one successful combo.

But Su Mucheng decided not to do this. She resolutely exchanged health after meeting her opponent, which was disadvantageous for the side with lower health.

She did lose this round, but didn’t actually lose in the overall picture.

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms only had 21% of his life remaining.

71% to 79%. Su Mucheng came out slightly ahead. But in terms of the group arena, Happy was way ahead, and if they kept trading like this, they would be the victors in the group arena.

Su Mucheng managed to set a trap and deal with Lin Jingyan, and furthered the lead that Ye Xiu established against Tyranny. It would be hard for most people to miss out on an opportunity to further their lead when they already had an advantage. More kills meant more points. However, every new player in the group arena meant a potential reversal, especially for Tyranny who was richly experienced and strong-willed. It wasn’t that easy to shake them up.

Thus, when battling Zhang Jiale, Su Mucheng did not greedily look to further the their lead. Instead, she simply traded evenly.

A very wise strategy, and a very wise decision.

There didn’t seem to be a big change in the difference in health. But as the number of players went down, if the health difference stayed the same, the lead would actually widen.

Happy still had three players on full health. Tyranny had two plus a one-fifth health Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Who would Happy send out next?

Su Mucheng left the stage, bu everyone was fixated on the players’ area. The suspense for the next player was too much.

Mo Fan!

Mo Fan stood up on Happy’s side.

As expected!

Everyone felt this way. Mo Fan had already become a staple player on Happy’s group arena roster. His playstyle was also very suitable for the group arena.

“Good luck!” Su Mucheng smiled to Mo Fan as they met halfway from the stage.

“Mm.” Mo Fan nodded. Even a simple word from him had a very determined air to it.

Very soon, the fifth battle began. Mo Fan, who had full health, did not choose to charge forward at the start of the battle, and instead skirted around the edge of the map. The stadium instantly filled with boos. Mo Fan’s opponent Zhang Jiale only had 21% of his health remaining. In this situation, not fighting head-on would definitely be looked down upon by Tyranny fans.

But Mo Fan would never care about this. He would use the style he was familiar with, no matter the situation. However, there really weren’t many hiding spots on this map. After Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms reached the middle of the map without finding anyone, he moved diagonally. It wasn’t long before he spotted Deception, moving on the other side of the lava.

“This kind of flank really isn’t very productive!” Pan Lin commented in the broadcast.

“Yes… due to the map being divided by the lava, there are very few options for movement routes. There are only so many in any general direction. Add on the fact that the areas are quite open and visible, flanking really wouldn’t achieve much.” Li Yibo said.

“But Mo Fan still insists on doing so,” Pan Lin said.

“Yep. He persists.” Li Yibo nodded his head.

Pan Lin was speechless. He meant for Li Yibo to further explain Mo Fan’s intentions. Turns out, he just confirmed the “Mo Fan still persists”. Why is he persisting? It’s your job to explain it!

Pan Lin cursed inwardly. But he also knew that Li Yibo must be uncertain and hesitant, and so didn’t speak up.

Deception was already exposed and within Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’s line of sight. He still didn’t approach and continued to circle around. Zhang Jiale also did not pursue directly, and had Dazzling Hundred Blossoms also circle around to intercept.

When Li Yibo saw Zhang Jiale’s reaction, he suddenly got an idea.

“Mo Fan probably wants to fight at the limestones.” Li Yibo said.

The limestones was where Su Mucheng and Lin Jingyan fought. Over there, the stacks of limestone was the only place on the map where there was a bit of cover in some spots. Mo Fan’s intentions were the same as Lin Jingyan’s. It was just that Lin Jingyan took advantage of the rules and forced his opponent over to the limestones, yet Mo Fan couldn’t care less and charged over by himself. What if Zhang Jiale just decided to ignore him?

This “what if” could be forgotten, because Zhang Jiale did not ignore him. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Deception were still far away from each other, but they were both running towards the same direction. The broadcast displayed a small bird’s-eye view of the battle, indicating Zhang Jiale’s intentions: Dazzling Hundred Blossoms would intercept him.

Fight head-on? Everyone was speculating.

A head-on fight would certainly be disadvantageous for Zhang Jiale, whose character had only 21% of his life left. But what about Mo Fan? That guy always snuck about and used ambushes, but in many people’s eyes, he was more than skilled enough to fight head-on. The ones who did not understand Mo Fan’s character all felt that his so-called “fireworks style” was superfluous. Why couldn’t you just continue your explosive attacks? Why would you hit and and run and come back for another hit? There’s a limit to how prudent you can be!

But disdain was disdain; in the end, Mo Fan’s style still caused people headaches. He grinded his opponents down by using his patience and repeatedly attacking and backing off. He sat tight when there was no good opportunity. Right now, Tyranny was behind and was anxious for a comeback. Meeting this type of opponent was incredibly suffocating.

“Ye Xiu is so obnoxious. Sending out this kind of guy in this kind of situation!” Tyranny’s hate of Ye Xiu was deeply rooted and immovable within their hearts. Even at this time and place, they first turned their aggro onto Ye Xiu, who wasn’t even on stage.

The two characters drew closer and closer. There was no doubt that Dazzling Hundred Blossoms would be able to intercept Deception. Of course, Mo Fan could see that the opponent was blocking his way. He continued to control Deception to charge forward. Was he attempting to charge through the interception, or to decide the outcome of the match right here?

Chapter 1547 - A Clash of Skill and Technique

Zhang Jiale stared attentively at the approaching Deception and his two hands.

Reading the Ninja’s attacks was the most effective method against Ninjas. According to their analysis of Mo Fan, they noticed that Mo Fan didn’t tend to turn sideways to hide his hand seals like most Ninjas did. Perhaps this was related to how he often used sneak attacks.

But at this moment, Deception turned away slightly.

Just because he didn’t often use it didn’t mean he didn’t use it. And what team was Mo Fan on? With teammates like Fang Rui and Ye Xiu, how could he not pick up on such a useful technique?

Sure enough, it was just wishful thinking! Zhang Jiale sighed. A team that could reach the semifinals in the playoffs wouldn’t have anyone with such a glaring weakness.

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms moved to the side to reach an angle where he could see Deception’s hand movements. In practice, this forced the Ninja to act faster. The Ninja didn’t want their opponent to know their next move, but at the same time, the Ninja couldn’t just keep turning and turning to hide his hand movements. If the Ninja turned too far, they would lose sight of their opponent.

Instead, Deception followed along with Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and took a few steps to the side.

Zhang Jiale wouldn’t be able to move laterally to widen his view. If he kept going, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms would jump right into the lava. The area here was rather narrow, so there wasn’t too much else he could do.

Even now, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was only two or three steps away from the lava, which was already quite nerve-wracking for the audience.

Deception suddenly made his move.

He spent all that time hiding his hand movements, but he ended up using a move that didn’t require any hand seals.

Peng!

A cloud of purple smoke burst forth and spread outwards.

Ninja Tool – Smoke Bomb.

The purple smoke instantly swallowed Deception. The terrain didn’t have any places to hide and set up sneak attacks, so Mo Fan set it up himself. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was only two-three steps away from the lava. If Mo Fan used the Smoke Bomb as cover and landed a blow, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms would be knocked into the lava and the battle would be over!

This was what everyone thought at this moment.

These were Mo Fan’s thoughts as well. He had used Smoke Bomb to obtain this opportunity for a single deciding blow. As the smoke from Smoke Bomb spread, Deception began to move. After joining the pro scene, he had slowly learned this technique. It was harder for the opponent to notice the Ninja’s movements if the Ninja moved as the smoke spread. Waiting for the smoke bomb to fully spread out would give the Ninja more space to move, but at the same time, the flow of smoke was slow. If the Ninja moved too fast, the Ninja would disrupt the flow of the smoke, and an experienced player would be able to deduce the Ninja’s location.

When moving inside Smoke Bomb, you had to move at the same speed as the smoke’s expansion. In the competitive scene, there were countless details that needed to be accounted for. There were simply too many incredibly skilled players there, who would take advantage of even the slightest openings.

Mo Fan had good control over his movement speed. He matched the speed of the smoke, and gently made his way over as if he were smoke.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms!

Mo Fan didn’t relax his guard, but at this moment, light blossomed all around the area two-three steps away from the lava.

The light instantly enshrouded Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Should Mo Fan continue? Could he find Dazzling Hundred Blossoms within that blinding light and knock him into the lava?

If it were Tyranny’s Han Wenqing playing, he would have definitely done this. But not Mo Fan. With the light blinding him, he wasn’t certain he could do it. As a result, Deception stopped and waited quietly in the smoke for an opportunity.

He was an opportunist as well. Huang Shaotian was agile, fast, and decisive. Every move he made would certainly succeed. Mo Fan couldn’t compare to Huang Shaotian in these areas, but he was more patient. He could watch as an opportunity slipped by, while maintaing a steady heart.

Just like now. Deception had stopped, and how could Dazzling Hundred Blossoms continue staying in such a dangerous position near the lava?

Many people felt that it was a pity losing this opportunity to knock Dazzling Hundred Blossoms into the lava. Many people thought Mo Fan should have followed through. Mo Fan’ didn’t feel that way though, and he didn’t feel any regret.

On the other hand, Zhang Jiale was very regretful!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had put himself in this dangerous position as bait. He had thought up of four different ways to counterattack and send the approaching Deception into the lava instead.

However, Mo Fan gave up and didn’t continue forward.

Was my Hundred Blossoms too excessive?

Zhang Jiale began reviewing the circumstances. But if I didn’t do anything, wouldn’t my bait be too obvious if I just stood there? I could continue having Dazzling Hundred Blossoms stay by the lava, but that would also let Mo Fan know that something was up.

It wasn’t that my acting wasn’t good enough, but rather, Mo Fan is too cautious!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms left this dangerous position, but he couldn’t keep up this light cover. The Hundred Blossoms style was very mana-hungry. In the past, it had been him and Sun Zheping. One of them traded mana, the other traded health. Their styles were actually very unsuited for group arena play. In the regular season, the group arena was between three players though, so it wasn’t as obvious. But for the playoffs, with five players each in the group arena, trading health or mana for the opponent’s health was quite awkward.

Five players made it so that the consumption of mana or health in a fight was more important than with three players.

After getting away from the lava, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms immediately launched his offense. The Smoke Bomb hadn’t dispersed yet, so Zhang Jiale didn’t know Deception’s precise position. But his previous dangerous position should have been quite enticing. Even if Mo Fan gave up in the end, he had likely been tempted in the beginning. Therefore, Deception’s position.

Light, push forward!

Zhang Jiale only needed to know his opponent’s approximate location. The Hundred Blossoms wave of light covered an area even greater than what a Launcher could.

The light intruded into the smoke and raged through it, tearing the smoke apart.

A figure flickered from inside. Zhang Jiale quickly caught it and immediately started aiming towards there.

But the instant he turned, another figure immediately rushed out from the previous location.

It was a bait from Shadow Clone Technique!

Zhang Jiale was surprised, but he responded promptly. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms turned back, and his bullets blasted Deception into bits.

This time, Zhang Jiale was very surprised. It turned out that the one here was fake, and the other one was actually the real one!

He hastily tried to turn back again, but Deception had already arrived.

Now, Zhang Jiale only had time to throw an Implosion Grenade.

The powerful shockwave expanded outwards, and Deception was blown away. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms chased after him to continue attacking. This Implosion Grenade shockwave also disturbed the smoke even further. Now, several Deceptions could be seen.

It wasn’t Shadow Clone Technique, but Shadow Dance!

Zhang Jiale had realized it. But he had just used Implosion Grenade, which was very annoying for Shadow Dance users. He couldn’t use it again to destroy all of these clones.

The Deceptions rushed out in different directions and swarmed Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

It was true that the Hundred Blossom technique could cover a wide area and affect all of these clones, but expanding the area of effect would sacrifice the damage dealt per unit of area. While it was useful as a cover, it posed very little threat in terms of offensive prowess.

Focusing on a single point would allow him to quickly dispatch a clone, but it would be too late to deal with the others if he did that, especially when there were so many “others”.

As a result…

Chaotic Grenades!

High-level skill against high-level skill. Chaotic Thunder against Shadow Dance.

Both of these skills required the player to control them. As a result, the effects of the skill depended on the player. It would be better to call it as a confrontation in technique than rather than skills.

All sorts of grenades flew out from Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s hands. Impact, Timed, Poison Gas, and so on.

There was no time to rest. There was no time to think. Every action was instinctive. Were all of these grenades effective against the oncoming shadow clones?

Some were… some weren’t…

Because Mo Fan was also controlling his clones.

Some of the grenades were dodged, some were not.

Amidst these successive explosions, Deception’s shadow clones were able to reach Dazzling Hundred Blossoms in the end.

Ninja attacks were silent, but the blood that flew about was as brightly-colored as ever.

The scarlet blood was quickly engulfed by the flames, and then, new blood would take its place.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was using long-ranged weapons to fight against an opponent in close combat. His character weaving in and out was similar to the Sharpshooter’s Gun Fu.

But in the end, the farther the better.

After all, Spitfires didn’t have martial skills like Sharpshooters did. Sharpshooters had a “Firearms Martial Arts” skill too, which greatly enhanced the Gun Fu playstyle.

Zhang Jiale had no way to completely rout Mo Fan, and Mo Fan had no way to completely suppress Zhang Jiale.

It was a stalemate, and if it continued, the winner would be decided by who had more health to start with.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms only had 21% of his health when he started, far lower than Deception. This amount of health wasn’t enough for him to last long in a fight.

This sort of health wasn’t good for this sort of clash between skill and technique, but he had no other choice.

When Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fell, the smoke and light that was left behind hadn’t even completely dissipated yet.

Spitfires were considered the mages of the gunners, yet in the end, it became a clash at close quarters.

Even though Zhang Jiale had lost, his performance was brilliant.

“It was a brilliant match. I think everyone’s only regret is the same as mine. It was just too short,” Pan Lin sighed.

“Yes,” Li Yibo also nodded his head. There was no need to analyze all the details in this fight. Both players had played spectacularly.

Chapter 1548 - Impossible to Predict

Zhang Jiale walked down from the stage, while Mo Fan stayed. Deception still had 72% of his health left.

28% to trade for 21%. Happy held onto their lead.

Who would go up next for Tyranny?

People were used to watching the group arena in the playoffs by now. Everyone immediately looked towards the seats on the loser’s side. There was no point looking at the big screen to see the upcoming player. The information would come from those seats first.

A player stood up.

Tyranny’s fans clapped wildly, welcoming Zhang Jiale and cheering for the next player.

Qin Muyun.

The reliable fifth player alongside the four Gods of Tyranny had been sent up as the important anchor in the group arena. At this moment, everyone realized that besides Zhang Xinjie, whose Cleric wasn’t suited for the group arena, the remaining three Gods of Tyranny, Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Jiale had been defeated.

They had always been the pillars of Tyranny! Yet despite these three players having played, Tyranny was still in a losing position. Now, it was up to Tyranny’s remaining players to get them out of this predicament.

It wasn’t that the fans didn’t believe in the remaining players, but there was still a gap compared to those three. For a moment, they began to worry. All of a sudden, a bit of hesitation could be heard from their applause.

Those who weren’t attentive enough might not notice this detail, but Qin Muyun was not one of them.

He could hear the worry from the applause.

He wasn’t affected by it though. The more it was like this, the harder he needed to work. He wanted to show that he could sweep away these worries.

Qin Muyun walked onto the stage and entered the player booth. The match soon began.

On Happy’s side, Chen Guo was feeling quite solemn. She could deeply feel that anything could happen in the playoffs. Even if Happy had a lead right now, she couldn’t relax. When she saw Mo Fan’s opponent, she felt even more anxious.

Enemies on a narrow road, an inevitable clash.

Mo Fan and Qin Muyun had met on stage again.

For a time, Mo Fan had been called the Godslayer. But in his previous two matches against Qin Muyun, he had lost badly. It wasn’t just a matter of luck. Despite being a quiet player, Mo Fan would take the initiative to express his helplessness after the match. Qin Muyun was his bane. When they played, it felt like he had his hands bound.

Only three nights had passed since their last encounter. Even if Mo Fan had improved during these three days, it was unlikely for him to turn things around in such a short amount of time.

If you considered how the previous two matches between Qin Muyun and Mo Fan had gone, then Happy’s lead would most likely disappear.

“Good luck…” Chen Guo clenched her fists.

The match began.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees rushed forward, while Mo Fan’s Deception took a roundabout route. He did the same as last time, choosing the left path.

Because of the lava, there weren’t very many routes in this map to choose from. As a result, when the two players noticed where the other had went, the start of the fight played out exactly the same as before.

Mo Fan continued to have Deception move forward. Qin Muyun made the same choice as Zhang Jiale. His Negative Nine Degrees look around. His pathing was the same as Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s. There weren’t any other choices on this map!

Deception was still that Deception.

Negative Nine Degrees’ movement speed wasn’t much different from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’. In the end, the two combatants met in the same place.

However, this time, as soon as Deception was in range of Negative Nine Degrees, Qin Muyun immediately attacking. Gunfire spouted from his dual guns.

Bullets flew out.

Qin Muyun’s outstanding positioning skills had received no small measure of praise. In the beginning, he had been ignored. His existence seemed so thin compared to the four Gods surrounding him.

In reality, Qin Muyun’s strengths didn’t only lay in positioning. Positioning was one weapon, but the basis for his consistency lay in his solid fundamentals.

Perhaps it was because of this reason that he had been ignored for some time. The fundamentals were the basics. It wasn’t flashy. Even when he had his moments to shine, even experts would overlook it, let alone when there were four Gods stealing the spotlight.

But even for a stone that didn’t shine, if it stayed there for long enough, it would be noticed.

Qin Muyun’s ability was slowly discovered and recognized by everyone.

No one would ignore him anymore. Finding his hidden talents were even somewhat of a game for people now.

Just like now, he was moving while firing, yet his aim was extremely accurate. It was undoubtedly a show of his fundamentals.

Bullets flew. The aim was true.

For a player like Qin Muyun, there was no such thing as rashness. Every move had a clear purpose.

Peng! Purple smoke spread out.

Smoke Bomb. It was Smoke Bomb again. Mo Fan’s first move was the same as the previous round.

However, his opponent was not the same.

His previous opponent had been Zhang Jiale, who had been at a health disadvantage. For Zhang Jiale to beat Mo Fan, he had to try and trap him. But Qin Muyun was different. He had more health than Deception, so he wasn’t anxious at all. Seeing Deception’s Smoke Bomb, he immediately had Negative Nine Degrees retreat. At the same time, he fired normal attacks towards the fog.

Bang bang bang, bang bang bang.

Bullets tore through the smoke. Thin trails appeared in the smoke. Qin Muyun didn’t seem to care whether they hit. Mo Fan wanted to use the smoke as cover, but his Deception had no way of reaching Negative Nine Degrees. Qin Muyun kept a safe distance away.

Mo Fan didn’t waste any time. Deception immediately rushed out from the soke.

Qin Muyun immediately adjusted his aim, but Deception was moving extremely fast.

Shining Arc! An Assassin skill. Ye Xiu’s unspecialized often used it as a movement skill. Deception was using it in the same way.

Deception instantly traversed a length of distance. The bullets from Negative Nine Degrees missed.

Qin Muyun didn’t panic. Negative Nine Degrees’ hands were as steady as eve as he retreated while firing back. Aerial Gun? It was a form of movement. And for a positioning expert like Qin Muyun, his Aerial Gun technique was very skilled. His jumps backward and the recoil were paired perfectly. He would fire towards the ground as soon as he landed to maintain the maximum speed.

Suddenly, Deception completed a Shadow Clone Technique to instantly move forward, but there was still some distance between him and Negative Nine Degrees.

Deception formed a seal again!

His hands moved in a blur. By the time Qin Muyun readjusted his aim, he finished the hand seal.

Deception had clearly taken a single step, yet his character moved nearly two steps.

Ninjutsu – Ground Shrinking Technique!

Another movement skill.

Shining Arc, Shadow Clone Technique, Ground Shrinking Technique! Three skills were used in rapid succession. A large amount of distance was instantly covered. It didn’t seem like much, but when they saw where Deception had started, they were immediately shocked.

But what was more shocking was Qin Muyun.

Deception had directly used three movement skills, as for him? His Negative Nine Degrees had only use an Aerial Gun. But after Deception used these three skills, the amount of distance closed wasn’t enough.

In this chase, it wasn’t merely a contest of speed.

Any movement started from picking a location and then moving there. A contest of movement was also a contest of positioning.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees moved very efficiently. As he maintained his maximum movement speed, he also made it difficult for his opponent to move efficiently.

Three movement skills weren’t enough to catch up to Aerial Gun, but it didn’t meant that it hadn’t been possible. Deception had been restricted to a certain extent.

And at this distance, it didn’t gain him much of an advantage. It could even be said that by being neither close nor far was more disadvantageous for him.

But it looked like Mo Fan still had hope. After the Ground Shrinking Technique, he formed another seal.

What Ninjutsu would it be this time?

Mo Fan’s hands were too fast. Qin Muyun wasn’t able to tell what skill he was using. Even so, Negative Nine Degrees continued to attack.

Bang bang bang…

The bullets all landed on Deception, surprisingly. The shots made him slide backwards, but then, with a poof, he turned into a straw man.

Ninjutsu – Substitution Technique!

His real body had moved ahead similar to Shadow Clone Technique. However, Shadow Clone Technique could allow him to move towards the target, wherever he wanted. But Substitution Technique was random. What direction it went or how much distance was covered was randomly chosen.

As a result, Substitution Technique wasn’t a skill that could really be treated as a movement skill because it wasn’t reliable.

But even if it wasn’t reliable, it was possible!

A random direction and a random distance. What if luck got him to Negative Nine Degrees?

It was a gamble, a true gamble. No matter how experienced or how good you were at reads, it wasn’t possible to predict where Deception would appear.

Because even he didn’t know. No one would know.

Where would Deception appear?

The crowd gasped in astonishment. Empty Cicada Double Kill. Deception’s two daggers had cut into Negative Nine Degrees.

Mo Fan’s gamble was a success!

Deception appeared at an okay spot, but since there was no way to know where he would appear, Qin Muyun had no way to prepare. What was ordinarily an okay spot became that much more perfect as a result.

A silent attack from a Ninja, and it had hit!

Chapter 1549 - Chance

Hua!

The crowd erupted.

How could he be so lucky! Countless Tyranny fans were filled with grief.

Luck was luck, but it couldn’t be ignored. And at this moment, its importance was being displayed in front of everyone. He had been moved randomly to such a good spot. If it wasn’t luck, what was it?

For life or death to be decided by luck, the losing side was the most helpless and the most unwilling. It’s no wonder that Tyranny’s fans were unhappy.

“How surprising! To think Mo Fan would make a gamble! Who would have thought?” Pan Lin also cried out. The deepest impression that they had of Mo Fan was his patience and perhaps excessive caution. Yet this sort of player had chosen a method that he didn’t have a complete grasp of, betting on luck to succeed. It was truly unexpected.

But is that really the case?

At Tyranny’s seats, Zhang Xinjie had marked out on his electronic pad the distance between Deception and Negative Nine Degrees when the Substitution Technique had been used.

He had drawn a circle showing the maximum distance that could be traversed using Substitution Technique. He split the circle into several small sections. The circles in red were areas that were dangerous for Negative Nine Degrees. The circles in yellow were areas that posed a threat. Blue represented areas where the was no threat. Black represented areas unfavorable for Deception.

With the Substitution Technique’s range, the area in black was the smallest. The area in blue was the largest and then the yellow. Although the area in red was smaller than the area in yellow, it still took up around 15% of the total area. The area in black was only 8%.

It didn’t matter whether or not Mo Fan had a high chance of reaching a good position, the chances of him getting into an unfavorable position was only 8%.

This Substitution Technique wasn’t purely a gamble. With only an 8.2% of truly failing, there was in fact little risk for Mo Fan. In reality, this choice was very safe.

Mo Fan was still Mo Fan. He didn’t make risky moves. Although he made a gamble, it was because it was in his favor. The chances of failure was less than 10%.

In the end, he got lucky!

Deception was able to close the distance between himself and his opponent. Once his Empty Cicada Double Kill landed, a combo was started. The distance between them was too close. Qin Muyun had no way of starting up his Gun Fu, which required a certain amount of distance and space.

Negative Nine Degrees kept trying to retreat. He was in quite the defensive position.

Deception stayed in close pursuit. Fireworks Style? It didn’t appear! Mo Fan continued to have Deception attack relentlessly.

This was the difference between Mo Fan now and the Mo Fan of the past. Instead of immediately retreating as soon as his threat was starting to give out, he persevered. He recognized that there were many areas where he couldn’t compete with Qin Muyun. Facing an all-rounded opponent like Qin Muyun, it was very difficult to repeatedly employ his signature Fireworks Style in this sort of map. Perhaps this was his only chance. He had no choice. He could only surpass his limits and continue ahead.

How long could he last?

Those who truly understood Mo Fan’s style were wondering about this question. And this included Qin Muyun.

Mo Fan’s style was very distinct. Deconstructing someone with such distinct characteristics was easier. It wasn’t a style that could easily be overlooked, unlike Qin Muyun’s fundamental-heavy style.

In terms of playstyle and upbringing, these two were on opposite ends.

Mo Fan had taken a gamble to break through Qin Muyun’s defenses. As for Qin Muyun? Even though he was in a passive position at the moment, he was calm because he knew that Mo Fan wasn’t good at keeping up a long assault. Perhaps it was an issue of focus or an issue with his technique, but in either case, there was no need to panic. An opportunity would appear.

Persist!

Both players were thinking the same thing.

What a strange feeling.

Mo Fan started to feel numb. His mind seemed to come to a standstill. All he could see in front of him was Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees. Everything else had become a haze. His fingers were moving, but he didn’t know what they were doing. Sometimes, Mo Fan only realized what skills he had after using them.

His thoughts were starting to have trouble keeping up with his actions.

Chance!

Qin Muyun finally saw an opportunity. Negative Nine Degrees struck with his knee, while his other leg slid backwards, instantly pulling the distance apart.

With a bang, Qin Muyun immediately began his counterattack.

Everyone was stunned!

They hadn’t seen any signs of it coming. Hadn’t Deception been playing well?

But nevertheless, Qin Muyun had taken back the initiative.

With their positions suddenly reversed, Mo Fan was having trouble adjusting.

He wasn’t very good at defending. His expertise was at escaping.

But trying to completely escape from a Gunner’s attacks was quite troublesome. Gunners had a very long range.

From this perspective, Mo Fan’s Fireworks style was rather hard to use against long-ranged classes. Pulling apart the distance and retreating was exactly what long-ranged classes wanted you to do.

When playing against long-ranged classes, it wasn’t a good idea to try and completely escape from the opponent’s attacks and then coming back. It was giving up space, allowing the opponent to set up barriers. Facing long-ranged classes, close combat suppression was king. Even the Fireworks style could not stray from this principle.

But Mo Fan wasn’t doing this. His Deception began to run away. It looked as if he was only going to be happy when he completely escaped from Negative Nine Degrees.

“I don’t think… that’s a good idea?” Pan Lin said.

“He had already closed the distance with Negative Nine Degrees. He shouldn’t have given up so easily. Mo Fan is still lacking in experience!” Li Yibo agreed with Pan Lin’s judgement.

Mo Fan wanted to run, but Qin Muyun wasn’t going to let him go so easily. Negative Nine Degrees chased after Deception closely.

Mo Fan had no way of completely escaping. At this distance, Deception had no way of making any counter attacks against Negative Nine Degrees. He had taken the initiative to pull apart the distance between them. Qin Muyun was glad to see it happen and didn’t try to block him too hard. Right now, Mo Fan could only be bullied. Pan Lin and Li Yibo felt extremely proud of their foresight and kept talking about it on the broadcast.

But… even though Mo Fan was on the backfoot, Qin Muyun’s offense wasn’t anything impressive.

Deception moved nimbly, dodging and weaving the gunfire from Negative Nine Degrees. He wasn’t able to escape from Qin Muyun, but Qin Muyun had no way to kill him.

Mo Fan’s skill, trained from running for his life in huge chaotic wars, was being put on display in this 1v1.

Not only was this distance uncomfortable for Qin Muyun, Mo Fan was at ease dodging the incoming attacks.

I need to get closer!

For long-ranged attackers, the farther away they were, the lower the chances of hitting the target. This distance couldn’t be considered as far, but Mo Fan’s skill at dodging made it much harder to hit him.

Qin Muyun began having Negative Nine Degrees press a bit closer. Suddenly, Mo Fan’s Deception turned around and dashed towards him.

Shining Cut!

With this Assassin skill, Deception had instantly traversed a length of distance. Qin Muyun, who had Negative Nine Degrees press forward, felt that something was wrong.

This distance was too close!

Attack, leap backwards.

Qin Muyun had wanted to close the distance a split second ago, and now he wanted to pull away.

But this time, Mo Fan didn’t retreat. After Shining Cut, he used Shadow Clone Technique…

Something isn’t right.

Qin Muyun stared blankly. This scene felt like deja vu!

But he continued to have Negative Nine Degrees retreat, while controlling the distance between the two of them.

Ground Shrinking Technique!

This skill again.

Qin Muyun knew what was going to happen next. It was the same strategy as before.

Qin Muyun tried to block him, but failed. After Ground Shrinking Technique was Substitution Technique.

Where!

The usually steady and calm Qin Muyun started to panic. Negative Nine Degrees spun around.

This time, he wasn’t as unlucky. The position that the Substitution Technique had sent Deception wasn’t dangerous for him. However, Qin Muyun didn’t have any advantages either. Just like what Zhang Xinjie analyzed, the chances of Deception being placed in a bad position was only 8%.

This time, he didn’t win any opportunities, but he didn’t lose out. It basically amounted to nothing happening.

Mo Fan’s Deception immediately began to retreat, while Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees immediately pressed forward.

Attack, dodge…

Qin Muyun knew why Mo Fan wanted to run away before and why Mo Fan didn’t continue pressing him.

Because for Mo Fan, he had a better grasp of running and dodging than approaching and pressuring.

As he dodged, he waited for an opportunity for him to start a new round of gambling.

It sounded somewhat ridiculous.

He had already gotten close, yet he was insisting on retreating and then going through so much effort to get close again…

But that was Mo Fan’s style. It was what he was in control of. He wasn’t good at keeping close. He was good at burst attacks. Even if he tried to persist, it would end up being broken in the end and then he would be counterattacked. When that happened, he would have to run away, and that was exactly what he was best at.

Then, he turned around, re-established his position in close combat, his burst combos, and his stubbornness.

It was the same Fireworks style.

Mo Fan hadn’t changed. He didn’t bet on luck or do things by flukes. He used his terrifying patience and his own familiar methods to create this strategy of chance.

In the sixth round of the group arena, Happy’s Mo Fan won.

He had tried a total of twelve times. Three successes, seven resets, and two interrupted by Qin Muyun…

Chapter 1550 - Last Hope

Amidst a rain of bullets, Mo Fan repeatedly ran and dodged a total of twelve times. Two times he was interrupted. Seven times nothing came of it. However, he succeeded three times, and the battle ended in Mo Fan's victory.

The audience didn't know how to feel regardless if they supported Tyranny or Happy.

Mo Fan's performance couldn't be described as good or bad. His stubbornness seemed ridiculous, yet in the end, he was able to drag down Qin Muyun through patience and perseverance.

You might not like this sort of person, but you had no choice but to recognize his achievements.

Qin Muyun came down from the stage.

His opponent had used the exact same strategy twelve times to win. It sounded like a joke, but no one would think Qin Muyun played badly.

Qin Muyun played as steady as ever. As a player who had come from Tyranny's training camp and been trained meticulously, there was no way he would just let Mo Fan repeatedly use the same strategy over and over again. After realizing Mo Fan's intentions, he had kept trying to thwart Mo Fan's plans or directly kill him.

However many times Mo Fan repeated the strategy was however many times he had tried to thwart it.　

He lost. That was the outcome, but no one could criticize him for it because no one knew how he was supposed to have won. Qin Muyun had done everything they could think of. 　　

It was an outcome that couldn't be explained through common sense. Everyone was silent as they watched Qin Muyun return to Tyranny's seats.

Tyranny only had one player left. As for Happy? Apart from Mo Fan, they still had two players remaining. Their lead was enormous.

After recognizing the situation, Happy's fans finally recovered and began rooting for their team.

As for Tyranny's fans? They knew that the situation was extremely unfavorable for them, but they couldn't give up hope. They had to hope for a miracle. Even if they couldn't, they had to let Happy know that their conviction wouldn't be shaken even in this sort of situation.

Who would be Tyranny's last player?

The crowd watched attentively as a slim youth stood up from Tyranny's seats.

Song Qiying.　

Tyranny's rookie this season. The person who would inherit Tyranny's future. At this moment, he had become Tyranny's last hope.

Even though a loss in the group arena didn't mean the match was over, it was an incredibly important moment. Song Qiying's performance would set the momentum in the following team competition.

Just thinking about it made many people feel extremely nervous. Song Qiying stepped forward and set his sights on the stage.

"I definitely won't let your efforts go to waste," he said firmly.　　

Just because they were behind didn't mean that the efforts from the others on Tyranny were for nothing. Song Qiying wasn't only referring to their efforts in the group arena, but their efforts over this entire season and these ten years.

Team Tyranny's fifth player was Song Qiying. Class - Striker. Character - River Sunset.

The electronic screen displayed the results of the previous match before putting up the information on Tyranny's next player. Even though everyone already knew who it was, all of Tyranny's fans stared at the name on the screen.

At this moment, Song Qiying had become the symbol of Tyranny. Everyone was certain that this youth would hold up Tyranny for another ten years.

Steady. Never retreating.

The seventh round in the group arena.

Happy's Mo Fan versus Tyranny's final player, Song Qiying.

The battle began.

Song Qiying chose the middle road, and River Sunset cut across directly to the center.　

Mo Fan took a roundabout route just like in the previous two fights.

At this point, was he still planning on being so stubborn?

The camera stopped on Deception. The traces of the previous battle could still be seen on him. Qin Muyun had put up a fierce fight even if he had ended up losing. He had dealt a considerable amount of damage to Mo Fan.　

4%.

At this moment, Deception only had 4% of his health left. The outcome of this match was a foregone conclusion. But they felt like that if it was Mo Fan, he would certainly do something unexpected even if his character was nearly dead.

The course of events went the same way as the previous two battles.

Even though Song Qiying's River Sunset wasn't a long-ranged class, his vision was the same as there's. When it was about time, he noticed Deception. Then, he didn't hesitate to turn around and rush over in that direction.

It was the same as before!

Everyone thought to themselves. Mo Fan had played on this map against two opponents. He was certainly much more familiar with the map than Song Qiying. Would he take advantage of the terrain in some way? With only 4% of his health, would he actually be able to take out Song Qiying?

The audience was thinking of Mo Fan as some sort of monster, even daring to think that he could beat Song Qiying with only 4% of his health left. Let alone Deception's health, Deception barely even had any mana left. In the last fight, he had went back and forth with Qin Muyun twelve times. How could he not have expended an extraordinary amount of mana? Deception didn't have enough mana to kill a full-health character.

But then again, it wasn't without logic. There was lava, no?

It's starting!

The two characters approaching each other. This time, the one with the attack range advantage was Deception. As a result, he was the first to attack. After throwing a Shuriken, Deception wasn't in a hurry to continue forward. Against long-ranged classes, closing in on the opponent was fatal for them. Against Strikers, it was the opposite. If it wasn't from a sneak attack, then directly confronting a Striker was the same as sending yourself to death.

Deception wasn't in a hurry to approach. River Sunset didn't slow down though. He tilted his body to the side to dodge the Shuriken and sprinted forward. In the blink of an eye, his fists swung towards Deception.

Deception swiftly retreated. Mo Fan clearly didn't want a direct fight with Song Qiying. However, Song Qiying's advance didn't stop. River Sunset stepped forward in pursuit, while Deception continued to retreat. Not long afterwards, he was forced to the edge of the lava.

Double Tiger Palm!

River Sunset's two arms shot out, blocking Deception's path to the left and right. Behind was lava, but if he didn't dodge, he would be pushed into the lava.

In the end, Mo Fan made one last struggle. Deception made feints left and right, then suddenly turned right.

Unfortunately Song Qiying wasn't tricked. His Double Tiger Palm didn't leave any openings.　

Pa!

A hit. Deception poofed into smoke.

Oh oh oh!

All sorts of cries came out.

The feint to the left had been a feint. The feint to the right was a feint as well, but its true purpose was to hide his hand movements.

Shadow Clone Technique!

After his real body appeared behind River Sunset, with just a push, he could send River Sunset into the lava.

Deception kicked out, Annihilation!

As for River Sunset? Using the momentum from Double Tiger Palm, his body jumped up, Whirlwind Kick!

Bang bang!

Two sounds.　　

Annihilation was extremely fast. It arrived at River Sunset first, but River Sunset was already moving backwards. In the end, the Whirlwind Kick had struck Deception as well.　

Tong!

River Sunset fell into the lava, but Deception had lost his last remaining health from the Whirlwind Kick.　　

Even though River Sunset had fallen into the lava, he had already won. His health was locked into place, and the lava would not hurt him any further.

Sigh!

At this moment, quite a few people felt for Mo Fan. If he had been able to dodge it, then his performance today would have been even more perfect.　

The seventh round of the group arena ended with sighs. Most of these sighs didn't come from the people in the crowd though, since most of those people were Tyranny fans.

"Beautiful!" They were cheering for their young general, Song Qiying. When Deception had used Shadow Clone Technique, they had been very worried. But at the critical juncture, Song Qiying's River Sunset executed a beautiful and precise Whirlwind Kick.

How courageous! Truly deserving of Tyranny's future.

"Keep winning!" They shouted.

Happy's fourth player stood up.

Fang Rui, the dirty Fang Rui. For rookies, he was the most difficult player to deal with. Rookies with weak willpower would sometimes even lose their confidence facing this sort of opponent.

Although Song Qiying wouldn't go so far as to be afraid, it truly was unlucky for him to encounter Fang Rui here.

No, it couldn't be said to be luck. Fang Rui had been chosen by Happy to come up. Perhaps it was to target a rookie like Song Qiying.

Fang Rui's footsteps were gentle and light as if he were under no pressure. He winked at Mo Fan and said a few words as they passed by. Unfortunately, Mo Fan simply walked by him expressionlessly. This was exactly what the phrase giving the cold-shoulder described.

Fang Rui didn't seem to mind. As he walked onto the stage, he even said a few words to the referee. Soon, the match began.

"Friend, is there anything meaningful that you want to chat about today?"　

And the trash talk began as well.

Tyranny's fans looked at Fang Rui disdainfully. Although from his words, it sounded like there was some background to it.

Those with good memory immediately thought of the fourth round of this season when Tyranny faced Happy in their away game. That round, Song Qiying had also met with Fang Rui. While Fang Rui was chattering non-stop, Song Qiying responded with a "I won't respond to anything that's meaningless" and then ignored Fang Rui.

To think Fang Rui would actually remember those words. It seemed like his trash talk even needed some history to spice it up.

The master of playing dirty was truly diligent.　

As for Song Qiying's reply today?

"I'm going to win!" It was just three words.

Chapter 1551 - An Unexpected Counter

I will win!

This declaration could not be anymore sincere. It was what all pro players seeked. These three plain and simple words didn't give rise to much of a reaction though.　

Fang Rui laughed indifferently: "Haha, you'll win? You haven't asked me yet!"

No answer.

Sure enough, Song Qiying acted the same way as he did in the fourth round of the regular season. He ignored any meaningless words.

But just because he ignored them didn't mean that he didn't see them. Last time, Fang Rui didn't stop talking just because he was ignored, and it was the same this time. His trash talk wasn't as dense as Huang Shaotian's, but his ability to provoke people was no worse.

Would Song Qiying be affected by his trash talk?

No one knew. They could only see that Song Qiying's River Sunset continued with the decision that he had made in the beginning and kept moving forward. Soon, the two characters met in the center. Fang Rui had also chosen to cut straight to the center.

Strikers could only fight at a close range, but Qi Masters had decent mid-ranged options.

Thus, the first to act was Fang Rui.

Qi Bullet!

The damage dealt by this skill wasn't high, and it didn't have any crowd control effects. It was mostly used as a harassment skill to probe how the opponent would react. Fang Rui often aimed this skill directly at the opponent's face. Then, by taking advantage of the Qi Bullet blocking the opponent's vision, he would follow with another attack.

This time was no exception.

The Qi Bullet flew directly towards River Sunset's face. Fang Rui quickly predicted where his Song Qiying's dead angles would be located as well as what he might do in response.

Move!

Boundless Sea immediately moved into a different position and followed with another attack.　　

Then, he saw River Sunset swing his fists.

Pa!

The Qi Bullet suddenly exploded into a hazy mist. The dead angle that Fang Rui had originally anticipated was now no longer a dead angle.　

Song Qiying's River Sunset had unexpectedly used a Qi Bullet too. He fired it at Boundless Sea's Qi Bullet, blocking it.

"You'll even bicker with your senior over something like this?" Fang Rui had lost his opportunity to seize the initiative, but he wasn't going to miss an opportunity to talk trash. His plan had clearly been disrupted, but he sounded like everything was going as expected. Just when he found a new angle to attack from, he saw a fist quickly pierce through the haze.

Pa!

The punch hadn't landed yet, but the impact between the fist and the air let out a crisp ring. River Sunset had stepped forward and used a Collapsing Fist right in front of Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui was startled and immediately had Boundless Sea stop. The Collapsing Fist had been on point. The timing and placement had predicted Fang Rui's actions perfectly. Boundless Sea had nearly walked right into the punch.

A coincidence?

As soon as Fang Rui had this thought, he immediately knew that it wasn't a coincidence.

Because River Sunset had followed with another punch. Such fluid and decisive movements didn't seem like something he had come up with on the spot. This was a well-practiced sequence of movements.

The other side had specifically practiced for his Qi Bullet!　　

Fang Rui realized this point and felt even more surprised. To put it simply, the Qi Master technique that he had created was difficult to execute with meager results. Up until now, apart from him, no other Qi Master had bothered to learn it. It wasn't because Qi Masters looked down on Fang Rui's dirty methods, but rather that it wasn't anything incredible. It was just a small trick. Spending so much time to study and practice a small trick wasn't worth it.

However, the Tyranny player in front of him had specifically practiced to counter this small trick.

This wasn't a situation that Fang Rui had anticipated.

It was a very difficult but not very effective trick that other players didn't bother to learn. However, Fang Rui was happy to do so. This was where his cunning lay.

It was precisely because this small trick was troublesome to learn that Fang Rui was certain that no one would study and analyze it too deeply. Because of this reason, the effectiveness of the trick became much greater.

But right now, this young Tyranny player had unexpectedly analyzed it and come up with a counter. Fang Rui was surprised. The thoughts of the new generation... was he not able to see through them?

Cloud Body, Straight Punch, Stomach Kick...

River Sunset completed all of these attacks in one breath. Fang Rui hadn't expected anyone to study and come up with a counter to his trick. This time, it backfired on him. After his trick failed him, he was now in a very disadvantageous position. Under River Sunset's fierce assault, he had no choice but to retreat.

Trash talk? Right now, Fang Rui really wanted to, but he didn't have the time!　

Four classes comprised the Fighter superclass. Qi Masters were the weakest out of them in close combat capabilities. Now that River Sunset had completely closed the distance between them, Boundless Sea was in a precarious situation. Many Qi Master skills required cast times to gather up qi. With a Striker punching and kicking him, how could he have any time to prep any skills?

Fang Rui could only have Boundless Sea swing his fists as well, dodging, blocking, and waiting for an opening.

But River Sunset's attacks were tight-knit and thought-out. His rhythm was on point. There was no opening to be seen. Song Qiying didn't look like a rookie. Of the Strikers in the pro circle, even Strikers who had played the class for three years might not be able to do this.

This is bad!

This is very bad!　

I'm not going to lose like this, am I?

Fang Rui had thought of the worst-case scenario. If River Sunset could keep this up, there was no way for him to take back the initiative.

Retreat.

Retreat, retreat. Soon, Boundless Sea had nowhere to run to. Behind him was boiling lava.　

Am I really not able to do anything?

Fang Rui was furious, but who could he blame?　

He had put himself into this predicament. He hadn't underestimated Song Qiying, but he hadn't thought of him highly enough.

After his Qi Bullet trick was broken through, he had even added in a few words to taunt him. It was because of these extra words that he had lost too much focus. If he had been paying more attention to his opponent's actions, perhaps he might have noticed River Sunset's attack.

If he had noticed it just a bit earlier, perhaps he wouldn't be in this situation.

Unfortunately, the present Fang Rui had no choice but to solve the issue of Song Qiying forcing him into the lava if he wasn't able to break out.

Left, right, front, above...

Was there really no way out?　

The options available to him seemed to be covered by River Sunset's attacks.　

Pa!

River Sunset finally landed a punch. In the end, it was because Fang Rui was unable to find an opening and had no way to dodge the punch.

He kept leaning backwards. Previously, he could step back to steady himself again.

But if he stepped back now, he would step into lava and take massive amounts of damage.

However, from the perspective of the viewers, whether or not he took the step didn't make much of a difference. There was only one possibility: Boundless Sea would fall into the lava. If Song Qiying defended the shore, he would likely win with a huge lead. If that happened, the likelihood of him beating Happy's next player increased drastically. A comeback from Tyranny didn't seem so impossible anymore.

For a moment, all of the Tyranny fans were thinking of this scenario. To them, this fight was already over.　

In the end, Boundless Sea took the step backwards. Facing this sort of attack, any pro player would instinctively retreat to try and avoid the follow-ups.

Only the lava was behind him though, and Boundless Sea slid into the lava.

"Oh oh oh oh!" The Tyranny crowd gave their victory cheer. They thought that the fight was over.

But very very few people noticed that as Boundless Sea fell, his two arms extended out in front of him. After the lower half of his body sunk into the lava, he slammed his hands down on the ground.　　

Landmine Quake!

Facing a dire situation, Fang Rui made a sudden move in response to River Sunset's attack. As he fell, he made his counterattack.

His two palms slammed into the ground, sending out a powerful shockwave. River Sunset, who was standing right in front, would take the brunt of it. Fang Rui was planning on using this opportunity to get out of the lava.

But before Boundless Sea could even jump, River Sunset was already in the air.　

Everyone had already thought that Song Qiying's victory was set in stone. Song Qiying didn't think the same though. His opponent still had 63% of his health left. How was his victory set in stone?

He continued to closely follow Boundless Sea's movements. Very few people had noticed Boundless Sea extending out his arms as he fell, but Song Qiying was one of them.

When the Landmine Quake came down, River Sunset jumped up.

Then, Thousand Ton Drop!

Landmine Quake's shockwave would damage River Sunset, it wouldn't be able to knock him away because of the Thousand Ton Drop. River Sunset was like a mountain as he pressed down, blocking Boundless Sea's escape. From this close distance, Fang Rui could see this young character clearly, while his surroundings seemed to lose their color.

The eight round of the group arena. Fang Rui lost, Song Qiying won.

It wasn't close either.

Tyranny had already been celebrating long beforehand. The victory from Song QIying instantly brought Tyranny back from the brink of death. After his fight with Fang Rui, River Sunset still had 79% of his health left. He definitely had a chance of beating Happy's final player.

With Tyranny's fans riled up, they began booing at their opponents. Because Happy's previous few players had played spectacularly, they had no way to boo them. But with Fang Rui, they had an opportunity. Even though Lin Jingyan hadn't done too well on his turn, they could at least accept his efforts. But Fang Rui? All they saw was a careless fool. Maybe that was a method of getting the opponent to become numb to his feints, but in this match, it was the reason why he had lost.

Fang Rui returned to Happy's seats amidst the boos.　

Fang Rui's expression seemed somewhat unnatural when he faced his teammates.

"You suck. You got destroyed by a rookie," Ye Xiu was merciless.

"Disgusting," Wei Chen followed.

"In these situations, the only way you'll be forgiven is if you go on your knees and beg for mercy," Steamed Bun also added. He wasn't really talking to Fang Rui though. He was talking to Qiao Yifan, Luo Ji, and An Wenyi, the other rookies. It was more like him watching a show and making a comment.

"Fuck, it wasn't that bad!" Fang Rui said, "I'll go to a corner and reflect back on what happened." After saying these words, he put his hands behind his head and crouched down at the corner, reviewing the fight.

"Hey, this..." Chen Guo felt like it wasn't quite appropriate.　　

"Let him reflect on it!" Ye Xiu didn't stop him. Instead, he looked towards Happy's final player. Their huge lead had been reduced to this extent. The side being caught up would be under great pressure.

But Happy's next player didn't seem to mind.

"It's finally my turn!" Tang Rou exclaimed.

Chapter 1552 - Wrestling Along the Shore

Tang Rou walked onto the stage.

Tyranny’s fans very much admired this controversial player. Her style possessed the fearlessness that they liked to see. In comparison, while their rookies, Qin Muyun and Song Qiying, were outstanding as well, they never felt quite right.

Right now, Tang Rou would be playing against Song Qiying in the group arena’s final battle. How could they root against him and destroy their own morale? As Tang Rou walked to the stage, she was met with much noise.

Tang Rou ignored them. After the referee went over how she would leave the stage after the group arena was over, she went into the designated player booth.

It was the deciding battle. If she won, she would put a halt to the opponent’s momentum. All of these factors only made Tang Rou’s fighting spirit rise even higher. What’s more, the two had fought the deciding battle in last round’s group arena. In that match, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had started with less health. Even though she was able to catch up quite a bit, in the end, she still lost to Song Qiying.

What about this round? Song Qiying’s River Sunset had 79% of his health left. This time, it was Song Qiying who would be starting with less health.

In the past, Tang Rou wouldn’t have cared about her lead. But now, after experiencing the pro scene for herself and seeing how hard the pro players worked for the sake of winning, Tang Rou could no longer be indifferent about it.

Because this victory no longer concerned just herself. This lead had been earned through the efforts of the four previous players. Indifferent? That would be disrespectful to their efforts.

She couldn’t ignore this lead. She should try her hardest to protect it!

As soon as the match began, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist rushed out. She went straight for the center like Fang Rui did last round. However, in comparison to Fang Rui, everyone felt like Tang Rou had a different energy to her. Tang Rou’s Battle Mage looked grand and imposing. On the other hand, Fang Rui’s Qi Master had been ruined. His Qi Master looked like he was dying.

Applause!

Happy’s fans wanted to show their support in this deciding round and started cheering for their team. But in the blink of an eye, Tyranny’s fans overwhelmed them with their cheers for Song Qiying.

Song Qiying also went straight for the center.

The lava covered a large portion of the map, and because of how open the terrain was, taking a roundabout path didn’t have much value. Song Qiying wasn’t a player who liked to beat around the bush. There didn’t seem to be any reason for him to circle around even if he only had a fifth of his health left.

Soon, the two sides met.

Song Qiying’s River Sunset immediately slowed down his footsteps. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist? She continued to charge forward!

As expected of someone with that sort of personality and playstyle!

Song Qiying sighed.

Tang Rou’s thought process was too easy for Tyranny’s players to predict. They had practically grown up seeing this sort of playstyle.

Dragon Tooth!

Soft Mist thrust her spear, Dancing Fire Flowing Flames, and it nipped at River Sunset like a viper.

River Sunset swiftly backed away, dodging the Dragon Tooth and putting a distance of two steps between them. But this distance of two steps was instantly traversed by Soft Mist, Double Stab!

Her spear flew out along nearly the same route as the Dragon Tooth. River Sunset retreated again, dodging the first stab. At the same time, he crossed his hands, welcoming the second stab.

Empty-Handed Blade Block!

Facing Tang Rou’s fierce assault, Song QIying suddenly chose a forceful response after retreating twice.

Why?

The lava three steps away from him could be the answer. Was it because he had nowhere left to escape to? People who thought this might want to recall that Song Qiying had chosen on his own initiative to retreat, which was what led River Sunset into this situation.

How did he respond?

Empty-Handed Blade Block!

This move wasn’t purely defensive. It relied on the system to block the attack and then turned it into a throw. There were many options for the throw. In this current situation, a practiced Striker could easily use the throw to send his opponent into the lava three steps away.

This was Song Qiying’s true purpose. It was a response filled with bravery and confidence. He had courage too. It was just that it differed in the way that Tyranny’s fans were familiar with. His courage hid many schemes. Rapidly retreat three times to bait the opponent into chasing after him. He didn’t hurry to use Empty-Handed Blade Block. Instead, he waited for second hit from Double Stab.

The execution difficulty was higher, but it also made it harder for the opponent to react.

Song Qiying succeeded!

River Sunset’s hands locked Soft Mist’s spear into place.

Without any hesitation, the throw followed the block. He twisted his body, and Soft Mist was thrown towards the lava.

Only three skills had been used so far in their battle, yet one of the players was about to fall into the lava. With this fall, Happy’s lead would likely be destroyed.

Fast and fierce.

Tsk tsk tsk… those who didn’t think highly of Happy clicked their tongues.

But as Soft Mist flew out, she thrust out her Dancing Fire Flowing Flames. The instant River Sunset threw Soft Mist using Empty-Handed Blade Block, her spear became free and stabbed towards River Sunset.

This was the fastest counterattack she could do after being hit by Empty-Handed Blade Block!

River Sunset retreated as fast as he could, but he was still too slow. He was backing away from Soft Mist, but her spear had already struck his chest.

Circle Swing!

The airborne Soft Mist swung her arms, and River Sunset was launched into the air. There was nothing he could do against a grab skill.

Splash! Splash!

The two characters had fallen into the lava simultaneously. However, River Sunset had been thrown deeper into the lava than Soft Mist…

Only four skills had been exchanged between the two of them.

One person falling into the lava? Wrong!

The outcome was far bolder than they could have imagined.

And this situation was much more unfavorable for Song Qiying, who had started with less health to begin with. As a result, as soon as he hit the bottom of the lava, he immediately rolled. He needed to hurry and pull away and get River Sunset onto the shore. Since he was already in the lava, he might as well use it to hide his roll.

Tang Rou’s situation was much less dire than Song Qiying’s. She had the health advantage, so she wasn’t afraid of a fight in the lava. Plus, she was closer to the shore than River Sunset, and she would have an easier time getting out.

A normal player might think of using this advantage to get to the shore first and establish an invincible position.

Tang Rou thought the same. It was just that her method of doing such was more aggressive.

Shattering the Lands!

She had Soft Mist use a high-level skill to directly leap out of the lava. The flames clung to Soft Mist, making her seem like a gigantic fireball, as she crashed towards the shore.

The shockwave of magic erupted outwards. Not only did it the waves thrash violently, it created a deep crater on the shore, which suddenly sunk down towards the lava.

Song Qiying had thought that Tang Rou would get to shore first and defend the area to prevent him from getting out. As a result, he had River Sunset circle around from the bottom of the lava. He would take more damage from the lava, but it was more likely that he would be able to get out of the lava safely.

He hadn’t thought that Tang Rou would make such a huge movement while on land. River Sunset was in the range of the shockwave from Shattering the Lands. He could suddenly feel his character sway left and right, and knew that the situation wasn’t good. The violent waves would better hide him though. Song Qiying wanted to use this chance to quickly get back onto land, when the land that he was about to jump onto suddenly collapsed…

Having just jumped out of the lava, Song Qiying’s expression went ashen. His position had been exposed. The moment his feet landed on the ground, the ground began to crumble, and Soft Mist had come as well.

There was nowhere to retreat. His only choice was to fight.

Despite swaying, River Sunset let out a steady step. His left hand trembled slightly, while his right hand made a punch. It seemed like a very normal and very slow straight punch, but everyone could feel how heavy the blow was. This was the Striker’s killing move: Emperor’s Fist! It didn’t look flashy, but the explosive damage contained within the first was something that no one dared to confront.

No one dared to. That was why Song Qiying believed that this attack would at least create an opening for him.

Others might not, but Tang Rou dared to, or perhaps she simply didn’t care what River Sunset was going to do.

Soft Mist rushed forward! Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks couldn’t be stopped. Behind River Sunset was lava, and even the ground beneath his feet might turn to lava any second. Tang Rou ignored all of this. Soft Mist rushed straight for River Sunset. She was clearly planning on bringing her opponent down in the lava with her, and it wasn’t something that could be stopped.

Boom!

River Sunset’s fist struck Soft Mist’s spear.

Emperor’s Fist versus Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Which one was stronger?

People had tested it. With both characters on equal levels, the answer was that the two skills were equal in a clash. The Striker using Emperor’s Fist better not think that he could hold his ground, and the Battle Mage using Dragon Breaks the Ranks better not think that he could break past Emperor’s Fist.

But this sort of test was meaningless. The characters were different classes with different sets of equipment. In practice, it was impossible for the characters to be on the exact same level. Moreover, in real combat, there were a lot of factors in play that could affect skill priority. The characters themselves and their circumstances could all affect the outcome of a clash between two skills.

In this clash, it seemed like River Sunset’s Emperor’s Fist had the advantage. Not only had Soft Mist’s Dragon Breaks the Ranks failed to break past him, Soft Mist had been knocked back by the punch.

To think someone using Dragon Breaks the Ranks would be forced to step back. It was truly a rare sight. But then again, for the character struck by Emperor’s Fist not to be blown away, the might of Dragon Breaks the Ranks could also clearly be seen.

River Sunset’s Emperor’s Fist had the advantage, but his situation wasn’t much better. He had originally been standing on a crumbling ground. After the impact from the clash, the ground couldn’t support him any longer, and half of River Sunset’s body disappeared into the lava along with the ground.

Song Qiying immediately had River Sunset jump. In the end, this Emperor’s Fist had given him an opening.

But this small opening had already been exhausted with his jump. Before River Sunset could land back onto the ground, Song Qiying saw Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flames bare its fangs at him.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Soft Mist ferociously used this high-level attack as she was forced back. The momentum from Dragon Breaks the Ranks was no small matter. Although Emperor’s Fist had forced her back, she hadn’t been stunned for too long from its impact, and she quickly went in pursuit.

If the ground beneath River Sunset hadn’t given out, he wouldn’t have been in a dangerous spot. It was because of that dip into the lava that he needed to make that jump. The opening that he had created had already been patched up by a Rising Dragon!

Chapter 1553: Like a Flag Waving in the Air

Reinforced Iron Bones? Thousand Ton Drop?

No good. None of these skills could allow him to tank the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. That attack possessed grab priority, thus, it ignored Super Armor effects.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky could only be dodged, not blocked!

Eagle Stamp!

River Sunset stepped on the air, lifting himself up, but it wasn't enough! Just this slight increase in elevation wouldn't be enough to get out of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky's range. The magic dragon tore through the air as it opened its jaws to bite River Sunset. But right before it could clamp down its jaws, River Sunset suddenly stopped and twisted his body, Whirlwind Kick!　　

This skill was not a movement skill, but it changed his posture. His two legs swept over the top of the dragon, when suddenly, the dragon twisted its head...

Dragon Raises Its Head!

Everyone was astonished. This was Ye Xiu's signature technique back in the day, but nowadays, the Battle Mages of the new generation were grasping it one after the other. First, it was Sun Xiang. Now, it was Tang Rou.

The young will surpass the old.

And in the Glory competitive scene, it was this pursuit that made the scene flourish.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, hit!

The dragon clamped down on River Sunset. Dazzling light engulfed him as the magic exploded. River Sunset was launched into the air above the lava. When the skill ended, he fell into the lava.

River Sunset moved along with the tumultuous waves of lava.

Quick Recover and then jump out!

Song Qiying reacted extremely fast, not wasting a single second. River Sunset no longer had the health to swim over to the far-away shore. Every second in the lava was a blow to him. Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had a long ending animation. During this time, he needed to get back onto the shore. It was his only chance for a comeback.

After he jumped, he was right next to the shore. With another jump, River Sunset was about to land back onto the shore. Soft Mist could only just start moving again. At a distance of several steps away, it wasn't possible for her to instantly reach River Sunset and intercept him. However, she could still send out magic Chasers. A blue and a purple ball of light shot towards River Sunset.　

The blue light was an Ice Chaser that had been created when she had used Double Stab. The purple light was a Dark Chaser that had been created when she landed Circle Swing.

Tang Rou hadn't immediately used these Chasers, and now, it seemed like her decision had paid off. River Sunset was still mid-jump and couldn't dodge. The two Chasers exploded, and of these two Chasers, the Ice Chaser's CC went into effect.

For every level in Ice Chaser, the Battle Mage's physical defense would increase by 2%. For a Battle Mage with Leather Armor Proficiency, it wasn't too great of a buff. The strength buff from Fire Chasers was far better, and the attack speed buff from Light Chasers was more useful. However, when the Ice Chaser hit the target, its CC effect was the best out of all five types of Chasers.

The Ice Chaser stunned the target briefly and had a 50% chance of lowering the target's movement speed. This was the effect for a Level 1 Ice Chaser, and it was already very useful.

Taking advantage of River Sunset's stunned state, Soft Mist rushed forward. She thrust her spear, and the air began to crackle, Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike.

Countless scarlet spears appeared. It was too late for Song Qiying to activate a Super Armor skill like Reinforced Iron Bones. Right when River Sunset's stun wore off, the spear reached him. Then, more attacks followed. As Soft Mist closed the distance, the attacks became more and more dense. Finally, she reached two steps away from River Sunset, she launched River Sunset into the air. Every attack from her carefully considered how the attack would affect the target. Despite needing to maintain a fast tempo, she was still able to accurately make these precise calculations. There was no doubt that Tang Rou deserved the title of Best Rookie this season.

Pu!

Hundred Dragon Meteor Striker's final strike sent River Sunset at a new angle in the air. Droplets of blood dripped out from his flying figure. Who knew how much damage her combo had dealt to River Sunset. Now, the two were face to face. Soft Mist's Dancing Fire Flowing Flames leapt up, and a Sky Strike struck River Sunset, launching him into the air. Then, Draconic Crusher!

Soft Mist swung downwards like a spike, sending River Sunset crashing towards the lava.

The high priority Draconic Crusher sent River Sunset into the lava for a third time. The wave of lava created by the plunge from River Sunset was more than two people tall, reaching high enough to even splash onto Soft Mist.

Tang Rou ignored the damage and followed with another attack.

Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

Her spear twisted, producing a whirlwind of magic that shot towards the lava, giving the attack an even deeper color. Scarlet flames swallowed River Sunset, and there was nothing Song Qiying could do. The previous Draconic Crusher had forced a knockdown. Until River Sunset was flat on the ground, he wouldn't be able to move.

The Cloud Whirling Windstorm mixed in with the lava, striking River Sunset and forced him flat on the bottom of the floor of lava.

Roll!

Song Qiying immediately had River Sunset roll, when he saw from up above, the Dancing Fire Flowing Flames in Soft Mist's hands descend like a bolt of lightning.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

The successive strikes made it such that the surrounding lava pushed away was unable to return. An empty piece of ground was laid bare in the lava. River Sunset was rolling on the ground, when Soft Mist's spear stabbed through his heart and nailed him to the ground.

The lava flooded back. In the blink of an eye, it engulfed River Sunset, who was bent like a small shrimp, and then Soft Mist, who had harpooned him.

Glory...

The winner had been determined. Tang Rou had won. Happy had won. And the one who won did it in the most flashy way possible. The scene made Tyranny's side feel awkward. When Soft Mist threw her spear downwards, River Sunset hung on the top of the spear like a shrimp. He almost looked like a flag waving in the air.

When Song Qiying walked out from the player booth, he saw his character hanging on the opponent's spear.

Shameful?

Song Qiying felt a bit embarrassed, but he also knew that it was just Tang Rou seizing the opportunity to give the fatal blow. Tang Rou hadn't been trying to humiliate him on purpose. He was more concerned with the fact that he hadn't been able to win this deciding battle. He had failed to live up to everyone's expectations. This was what made him disappointed the most.　

The Tyranny fans weren't in high spirits. A Striker losing to a Battle Mage was reminiscent of past pains. Han Wenqing had lost to Ye Xiu in the first round, and in the fight between the symbols of the future of the two teams, they had also suffered a defeat.,

Song Qiying had played well enough though. He had eliminated Happy's lead and brought Tyranny an opportunity to win. But in the end, Tyranny lost. The final scene of River Sunset hanging off of Soft Mist's spear only made the pain worse.

Even so, when Song Qiying walked down from the stage, they gave him their applause. They didn't want their future to lose hope. They would always encourage and cheer for their players.

The concern shown by Tyranny's fans only made Song Qiying feel even more ashamed. After returning to his teammates, he felt like he couldn't face them.

"Don't blame yourself. You played amazing out there. It was because we played poorly that we left too big of a burden on you," Lin Jingyan said. He had played the worst in the group arena today. Tyranny falling behind was practically his fault. As he consoled Song Qiying, he also pushed the blame onto himself.

"You have to win next time!" Han Wenqing didn't say too much and simply expressed his expectations in the future.

"Hm? It's not too big of a problem, no? Losing by one point in the group arena is practically no different from even." Zhang Jiale felt that the atmosphere felt abnormally gloomy. He hoped that he could bring up everyone's spirits.

"There's still a difference," Zhang Xinjie immediately retorted.

Zhang Jiale was helpless. Their vice-captain was too serious.

"Whether we lost by two points, by one point, by zero points, or if we win by one point, by two points, nothing changes," Han Wenqing said, "We have to win the team competition!"

"Of course!"

"That's obvious."

"Definitely."

Tyranny reorganized their thoughts, ready to face the true deciding battle in today's match.

As for Happy? Tang Rou's decisive victory had naturally given the team a boost to their morale, but they remained clear-headed in their excitement. Whether they truly won or lost this match depended on the following battle.

The two teams stared at the screen in the stadium. The team competition map would be chosen soon. At the same time, there would be a simple description of it, allowing the two players to make arrangements to their lineup accordingly.

Map choosing begin!

The projection technology displayed a big question mark at the center of the stage, which kept on spinning.　

Ding!　

The crisp ring echoed through the stadium. The map had been chosen, and the electronic screen displayed the map's name: Seven Color Spring. At the center of the stage, the projection technology began to slowly reveal the structure of the map.

The two teams immediately began to observe and discuss it up until the referee called for the two teams to come onto the stage.

The crowd immediately quieted down. Everyone looked towards the two teams to see which of their six players would be sent onto the stage. They would know soon.

First, it was Tyranny.

There was no fooling around. Practically the moment the referee called them over, six players stood up together and walked towards the stage.

Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Song Qiying, Zhang Xinjie, Qin Muyun.

Chapter 1554 - Random

Tyranny’s six players were the usual six, though it was somewhat surprising that they picked Song Qiying to play.

After all, he had lost rather embarrassingly just before in the group arena. It was unlikely that he would be unaffected by the loss. The following team competition was extremely important. It would have been less risky to send the more experienced Bai Yanfei. However, in the end, Tyranny had trust in their young general, fielding him in this crucial, deciding battle.

“It isn’t the time to train their rookies…” Pan Lin couldn’t help but criticize this arrangement.

“Haha,” Li Yibo, who had once been a part of Tyranny, laughed, “They’re not having him play for the experience. They have absolute trust in him, that’s it. Tyranny’s players need this sort of confidence and courage.”

Pan Lin was speechless. This absolute trust in Song Qiying wasn’t rational! Were Tyranny’s generals really planning on entrusting perhaps their final opportunity for a reason like that?

As the two talked, Happy’s six players got up from their seats and walked towards the stage.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, the three experienced All-Star players. These three had always been the core of Happy, and the most stable positions in the team competition.

An Wenyi, Happy’s Cleric, also had a stable position in the team competition because of his class.

Then, it was Tang Rou! She had just crushed Tyranny’s momentum in the group arena. In her confrontation with Tyranny’s rookie, Song Qiying, she had won in a dominating fashion. Her deserving of the title Best Rookie was becoming more and more convincing.

Finally, their sixth player was Luo Ji! He had played the fewest times in the regular season, but in the first round of Happy’s semifinals game with Tyranny, he had single-handedly turned the situation around, triggering a heated discussion amongst the community. The discussion had been interrupted for a moment by the match between Samsara and Tiny Herb, but when it was time for the second game between Happy and Tyranny, Luo Ji’s name often came up in the discussion and predictions.

In the second game, Tyranny chose the map, and Happy did not send out Luo Ji. The map that Tyranny had chosen indeed didn’t have any areas that could be dismantled. Tyranny had showed some worry over Luo Ji.

For this third game, after getting a general overview of the random map, Happy immediately sent out Luo Ji in this important deciding match. This map was a map that had specifically been prepared for the playoffs. It had never been seen before, so it wasn’t possible for anyone to have made any preparations for it. Could it be that Luo Ji’s ability to “instantly understand the structure of the terrain and then dismantle it” was real?

For a moment, the discussion began to revolve around Luo Ji. Pan Lin had felt that Tyranny had been bold, daring to send out Song Qiying. Now, he had no idea what to say for Happy.

No matter how you put it, Song Qiying had been a prime candidate for the title of Best Rookie this season. That was a proof of his skill. As for Luo Ji? The few times that he had appeared in the regular season, he had rarely made any especially great plays. It wasn’t until the semifinals of the playoffs did he suddenly attract everyone’s attention. However, Pan Lin didn’t believe in that so-called ability of his. If Luo Ji didn’t have that ability, then wasn’t Luo Ji’s appearance a bluff? Then what? There was no then. Happy had sent out an inexperienced and average rookie as a diversion. It was far more risky than Tyranny fielding Song Qiying.

Amidst the clamor, the players on the two teams lined up at the center of the stage.

It wasn’t until the referee confirmed their lineups were their names displayed on the screen.

The two sides shook hands silently. The tense atmosphere overwhelmed everything. The air seemed to have turned solid. The players quietly completed the pre-match ceremony, and under the referee’s directions, they headed to their respective player booths.

There was no provocation from anyone. No one tried to probe the other side’s mentality. There was also no “friends first, competition second” behavior either. The battle that would decide their efforts over this entire year began in this way. The audience could feel this terrifying oppressiveness and were silent as well.

If even the spectators were like this, how were the players themselves feeling?

The two teams spawned on the map. This map, “Seven Color Springs”, was shaped like a square. The spawn locations weren’t the usual corners, but rather at the 12 o’clock, 3 o’clock, 6 o’clock, and 9 o’clock positions. What was more astonishing was that the two teams didn’t spawn symmetrical to each other. Team Happy spawned at the 6 o’clock position, while Team Tyranny spawned at the 3 o’clock position.

This was the first time the spawn locations had broken Glory traditions. But then again, whether it was the Alliance’s rules or the competitive rules, neither of them specified that the spawn locations needed to be opposite of each other. From the numerous maps over the years though, it seemed to be a tacit agreement. However, in this crucial battle, this tacit agreement was broken, immediately leading to a large commotion outside of the stage.

“Their spawn locations aren’t symmetrical!” Pan Lin was astonished, “Coach Li, how do you think this will affect the match?”

“It will definitely have an effect on the match. The two teams don’t know about this situation. They will likely assume that their opponents spawned on the opposite end, and then based on this assumption, they’ll make predictions on when and where the opponent might come from. But with this current situation, the two teams’ predictions will be wrong. Their first encounter will come as a surprise to both teams. It will be a test of their reaction speed and ability to adapt to unexpected situations. Whichever side is able to figure out the reason for the issue the fastest will have a better grasp of the situation.”

Li Yibo went into a fairly lengthy analysis. The two teams also began to move. After their intentions gradually became clear, the crowd once again went into a commotion.

The straightforward and direct Tyranny didn’t lose their inherent traits in this random map and cut straight towards the center.

On the other hand, Happy took a roundabout route, and they split into two parties. Lord Grim, Dancing Rain, Boundless Sea, and Little Cold Hands went to the left, while Tang Rou’s Soft Mist went to the right.

If the two teams had spawned normally at opposite ends of the map, Team Tyranny would have been caught in a pincer attack from the left and right. However, with Tyranny coming in from the 3 o’clock direction, Tang Rou’s Soft Mist would run into the entirety of Team Tyranny all alone first. An individual’s movement speed was faster than a group’s movement speed.

The asymmetric spawn locations spelled trouble for Happy. From a time perspective, Tang Rou definitely wouldn’t be able to expect that Tyranny would be coming from the side.

The three parties continued to move along their respective paths. Happy’s four player group was ignored by the projection technology and the broadcast. Everyone was watching Tyranny’s and Tang Rou’s movements, predicting where they would meet based on their movement speeds.

The broadcast team had people to analyze it and help from software. Soon, the screen displayed a drawing showing their likely routes. Then, a bright red dot was placed on where the two sides would meet. The camera zoomed in and showed the terrain of this location.

The terrain was not favorable for Tang Rou!

If the terrain was flat, then she would be able to notice Tyranny from far away. She would have plenty of time to adjust and wouldn’t need to be worried. However, this “Seven Color Spring” wasn’t a flat map. The four spawn locations were situated on four high grounds. The rest of the map was filled with steep and precipitous terrain. This map was rather similar to a canyon area. It was just that it was intermixed with other elements. In particular, the Seven Color Spring in the middle didn’t fit in with the setting of a desolate highland. The areas surrounding the spring was verdant and lush. The shadows of the overlooking trees covered the waters of the spring. When the light made its way past the leaves, the reflection of the light glittered with seven colors. As the leaves swayed in the wind, the seven colored light moved as well, creating a psychedelic display of light.

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist wouldn’t be able to reach the Seven Color Spring. Her path was restricted by two high grounds to her left and right. And Team Tyranny was heading towards the canyon junction ahead from the east side. It was where the broadcast had predicted the two sides would meet. Maybe it wouldn’t be precisely on the dot, but the two sides would certainly meet at that junction. What mattered was the distance between the two sides when they noticed each other. This distance would decide Tang Rou’s fate. No one believed in a miracle like a 1v5. When the two sides met, Tang Rou would definitely be fleeing for her life.

The Happy fans were naturally very anxious. They didn’t know how things could get better. Soft Mist’s movement speed and direction hadn’t changed. As she approached that junction, Pan Lin sucked in a deep breath of air waiting for the moment when the two sides collided. As the two sides neared, the predictions became more and more accurate… it seemed like the two sides would notice each other at a very close distance. The situation was becoming worse and worse for Happy.

“They’re close. Just a bit more..” Pan Lin’s voice started getting louder as he stared at the scene: “Soon, it’s the entrance of the juncture. Soft Mist is running towards it… running… she stopped?” Pan Lin was about to shout “She’s charged out!” but in the end, he wasn’t able to say them. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had unexpectedly stopped the instant she reached the juncture.

“What’s going on?” Pan Lin was puzzled. Soft Mist had already started retreating. She stuck to the side of a wall as she carefully retreated back.

The cameraman had noticed the issue, and switched to Tang Rou’s point of view. This point of view didn’t just show what Tang Rou saw but what she was hearing.

Footsteps!

It was the sound of jumbled footsteps.

Chapter 1555 - An Unknown Coincidence

“Found five!” Tang Rou quickly typed in Happy’s chat. She also gave Soft Mist’s coordinates.

The audience was astonished. Team Tyranny hadn’t even appeared in her sights yet, but just through those jumbled footsteps, she was able to deduce that there were five people? She must be quite confident in her listening abilities! Several pro players shut their eyes and tried, but even though they knew that were five people there, they couldn’t distinguish between these footsteps at all. All they could get was that there was more than one person.

“Where are they?” Ye Xiu was surprised.

“From the east.”

“That can’t be right.”

Tang Rou didn’t have time to continue chatting with Ye Xiu. Even though she had noticed Tyranny’s movements ahead of time and retreated, this canyon area was very flat and straight. True, she could back away, but there was nowhere for her to hide. During this time, Tyranny’s five players had arrived at the entrance of the canyon. Hoping that they wouldn’t look straight was unrealistic. When an intersection was reached, pro players would always check their surroundings out of instinct.

As a result, Tyranny quickly noticed Tang Rou’s Soft Mist.

Everyone in Tyranny was startled.

For experienced players, as soon as the size of the map was known, estimating approximately what time the two sides would meet was an easy task. They only saw Soft Mist, but even considering that an individual moved relatively faster than a group, encountering her here shouldn’t be possible.

The spawn locations were different than normal.

The spectators could see it with their own eyes, but for the players on stage, there was no way they would think of something that had never happened before. As a result, whether it was Tyranny or Happy, everyone was at a loss. They weren’t able to figure out what the reason was.

Happy’s response to it was rather simple. Tang Rou was only one person. She was in a 1v5 situation, what more was there to think about? The Thirty-Six Stratagems. If all else fails, retreat.

But it was more complicated for Tyranny.

Bait? Trap?

These words went through their heads. As a result, although Tang Rou was alone, they didn’t dare rashly attack her. Facing this unfamiliar map, they thought about it and felt like Happy must have discovered something particular about this area. How else could Tang Rou have gotten to this area so abnormally fast? If Soft Mist was already here, who knew if there were others behind her?

Tang Rou didn’t think too much. First, retreat. But seeing Tyranny hesitate, she immediately reported the information to the team.

The rest of Happy was hurrying over to Tang Rou’s location. As soon as Y e Xiu saw the report, he immediately threw out his previous analysis.

His previous analysis had been the same as Tyranny’s. Tyranny must have found some sort of secret in this map to be able to have reached that location so fast. But when Tang Rou reported that Tyranny was hesitating on whether they should chase after her, Ye Xiu knew that his analysis had been wrong.

For a team like Tyranny to hesitate this much, it meant that they must be feeling very apprehensive about the situation. From this, it could be seen that they hadn’t expected to meet anyone from Happy there. In other words, their encounter with Soft Mist came as much of a surprise to them as it did to Happy.

Therefore, there must be a different reason, leading to this abnormal situation to occur.

Because of this small difference, Happy was a step ahead of Tyranny in solving this mystery. They at least knew that Tyranny didn’t have the initiative. It was a surprise encounter.

In that case…

“Try and harass them!” Ye Xiu messaged.

“Harass?” Tang Rou was surprised. She obviously knew what the word meant. It was just that harassing required a bit of finesse. It wasn’t Tang Rou’s strong suit. She also lacked experience in reading the situation, so it was a rather difficult task for her.

“Give them something more to think about,” Ye Xiu explained his intentions.

“Got it,” Tang Rou wasn’t stupid. It was a 5v1, yet Tyranny was hesitating. The other side was clearly apprehensive about something. Ye Xiu’s meaning was to make a bluff and mislead them into thinking their misgivings were correct.

Go back and attack?

Tang Rou pondered over it. For now, she had Soft Mist stop retreating.

This sudden pause magnified that shadow of doubt in Tyranny’s hearts. They had previously been hesitating, but when they noticed how quick and decisive Soft Mist’s retreat was, they gradually became aware of Tang Rou’s misgivings towards them. Just when they were about to come to the same conclusion as Ye Xiu, Soft Mist suddenly stopped and turned around to look at them.

Was it because they hadn’t gone forward that the other side had no other choice?

Which meant that the other side had set this up, and it really had been a bait?

Tang Rou was still thinking of how to harass them! But she hadn’t thought that the other side would analyze her move to that extent. Just this pause made the other side doubtful. Tang Rou was already misleading them.

But at this moment, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie ordered: “We attack.”

“Ah?” Zhang Jiale was somewhat surprised. If the order had come from Han Wenqing, he wouldn’t have been surprised. Only their captain wouldn’t bother thinking about whether it was a trap or not; just use brute force to break through it. But Zhang Jiale was different. He always considered every detail no matter how small it was, yet he was willing to take such a risk despite being in the unknown?

“Charge forward, and get a clear look. I’ll heal.” Zhang Xinjie clarified.

He didn’t say much, but his aggressiveness and boldness came through. It wasn’t an aggressiveness or boldness in terms of offense, but in terms of healing. Zhang Xinjie was stating: go look, I’ll protect you.

Using force to suppress. But this time, they weren’t relying on offense, but on healing. This aggressiveness wasn’t without caution. Tyranny’s and Zhang Xinjie’s playstyle never lacked caution.

“Understood! We’ll go forward!” Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms immediately rushed out. For this type of scouting, a long-ranged class was safer.

“Qiying, protect the healer,” Han Wenqiny ordered and then Desert Dust rushed forward as well. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder followed. Song Qiying followed the order, and River Sunset kept close to Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock.

Team Tyranny finally moved forward. However, they still displayed a defensive stance.

“They’re coming” Tang Rou reported to her teammates, and Soft Mist turned around and retreated again.

“Already? How decisive! Protect yourself.” Ye Xiu replied.

If he had said this to anyone else, they would have most likely wanted to cry. It was a 1v5. Saying “protect yourself” was easier said than done!

Chapter 1556 - Blossoming Grenades

Bang bang bang!

The silence had finally been broken.

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms took advantage of his long range and began to attack.

But Soft Mist didn’t even turn her head back. Soft Mist swayed left and right, dodging all of Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s bullets.

The crowd went into an uproar.

It was like she practically had eyes on the back of her head! That was too ridiculous, no?

It was quite ridiculous. Not many pro players could do the same. Tang Rou was different. Her listening abilities had been trained professionally, allowing her to more keenly catch the minute differences in sound. When she began seriously playing Glory, she immediately realized how valuable this talent was. As a result, she specifically trained her ears for Glory and improved it even further.

Using sound to locate the position of the bullets?

It wasn’t possible to do it very precisely. It could be seen from how Soft Mist dodged the bullets. If she could grasp the direction of all of the incoming bullets, her dodge wouldn’t have been so exaggerated. Compared to other pro players, Tang Rou’s strength lay in her ability to make this judgement for several bullets. Other pro players could probably dodge one or two bullets based on sound, but the sort of dense gunfire from an automatic pistol likely couldn’t be done.

Tang Rou was able to do it though. Soft Mist swayed left and right repeatedly like a race car constantly making turns, dodging the bullets again and again without slowing down.

“How impressive!” Zhang Jiale couldn’t help but praise. This time, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms stopped firing, instead quietly tossing a Grenade out. Then, bang bang bang, he began firing again.

His experience and cunning was being put on display. If it had just been a quiet grenade toss, the other side would likely be suspicious. But by tossing the grenade while simultaneously firing, the other side would continue hearing gunshots and would likely ignore the possibility of a grenade toss.

Zhang Jiale’s thoughts were very logical, but unfortunately, it didn’t work because Soft Mist turned her head.

The reason was very simple. Ye Xiu had told her that she shouldn’t completely rely on her listening abilities because many attacks and skills didn’t have sound.

As a result, Tang Rou wouldn’t completely rely on her listening abilities. She would occasionally turn her head back, which she happened to do so when Dazzling Hundred Blossoms threw his Grenade.

She saw it and determined what it was.

Implosion Grenade. If Soft Mist had dodged to the side like she did with the bullets, the shockwave from the Implosion Grenade would have thrown her to the walls of the canyon. This delay would be enough for Tyranny to catch up to her.

They believed that Happy had likely set up something in this area and were planning on seeing what it was with their own eyes, but if they could intercept Soft Mist before she could make it there, then that would obviously be the best scenario. The situation would turn around, and they would have the initiative.

But unfortunately, she noticed it…

Zhang Jiale didn’t hold back. The sky rained down with grenades.

With caution in mind, Tyranny chased after her taking up a more defensive stance, and thus, the team formation could not scatter. As a result, their collective movement speed wouldn’t be as fast as Soft Mist. There wouldn’t be many opportunities to hold her here, and soon afterwards, they would be stepping right into where the enemy side wanted them to be. Right now wasn’t the time to hold back.

The grenades filled the sky like the petals of a flower bud. Everyone could already see the blossoms of light scattered through the air…

Tang Rou quickly tried to analyze where these grenades would fall. This required lots of Glory experience to do so, which was what Tang Rou was lacking in. She could only do her best.

Bang bang! Two gunshots rang out followed by two explosions. Light filled the sky. Zhang Jiale had taken the initiative to make two grenades explode. In a split second, the rest of the grenades were swallowed by the blinding light. Tang Rou had already been having trouble figuring out where the grenades would land when she could see them. Now that the grenades couldn’t be seen, she might as well not even try. Soft Mist disregarded them and sprinted away as fast as she could. The farther she ran, the better. As for the grenades, she would have to rely on her reaction speed to deal with them!

Boom!

The first grenade exploded. A giant fireball rippled through the air. It was a Flame Grenade.

The fire burned and dealt damage, but it didn’t have any effects on movement speed. Soft Mist simply dashed right through the flames.

Boom!

Another grenade landed beside Soft Mist. It was a normal Impact Grenade that exploded on impact. The explosion not only dealt damage, but it would hinder her movements to a certain extent. Out of reflex, Tang Rou had Soft Mist twist her body to the side, shaking off the explosion.

Boom boom boom!

Grenades continued to fall, and light continued to blossom. The viewers weren’t able to clearly distinguish between the different grandes. All they could see was a mess of explosions. Yet Soft Mist was moving left and right amidst this light.

Tang Rou also wasn’t able to distinguish between the grenades. Her reactions were based on what she saw and heard when the grenades exploded. Soft Mist’s dodging wasn’t perfect, but even so, it was already very impressive. More importantly, the consecutive explosions weren’t able to block her. Soft Mist was on fire, but she was still moving forward. At this moment, another grenade quietly fell. With so much light and so much sound all around, it was already very difficult to notice it.

And as soon as this grenade touched the ground, the surrounding air suddenly compressed and then expanded outwards, instantly creating a large shockwave.

Implosion Grenade. The first grenade that Dazzling Hundred Blossom had tossed was tossed again. The grenade didn’t deal much damage, but it had a powerful CC effect. For Soft Mist, it was a huge obstacle. And this time, Tang Rou finally slipped up and reacted too slow to it. The shockwave expanded, and Tang Rou’s reaction was unexpectedly to move a step closer to it.

The shockwave struck her, and Soft Mist was immediately knocked flying. But because she had stepped closer to it, the angle had changed slightly, and she was blown diagonally outwards instead of backwards. It hadn’t completely destroyed her escape attempt.

Tyranny still hadn’t been able to hold her here?

Everyone was dumbstruck. After the Implosion Grenade sent Soft Mist flying, the other grenades weren’t able to keep up, and the explosions lagged behind Soft Mist.

“Close enough!” Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder suddenly picked up speed.

Chapter 1557 - Protect Yourself

Although the wave of attacks from Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms failed to completely hold down Tang Rou’s Soft Mist, it had still proved a significant hindrance to her escape. Soft Mist couldn’t keep moving straight and had to change directions many times to dodge, allowing Tyranny to close the distance by a considerable amount. The final Implosion Grenade had helped Soft Mist move forward a bit because she had taken that extra step, but it had also disrupted Tang Rou’s rhythm. While Soft Mist was sent forward, it had been diagonally. And to her sides were the walls of the canyon. She wouldn’t be going very far before she crashed.

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder had predicted where she would end up and suddenly picked up his speed. He was breaking away from the team’s formation. However, battles were constantly changing. Formations had to adapt according to the circumstances. Dark Thunder broke away from the team to deal with the change in circumstances.

Poison Needle!

Dark Thunder flicked his wrists and threw out a needle.

The needle was as thin as an oxen hair. It was practically invisible to the eye. Lin Jingyan was even borrowing the light cover from Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s attacks. Let alone Tang Rou, even the spectators who could see the entire picture hadn’t noticed, keeping everyone but himself in the dark.

Tang Rou hadn’t noticed it. She didn’t have the energy to keep an eye on everything at the moment.

The Implosion Grenade had sent Soft Mist flying extremely fast. In the blink of an eye, she had reached the wall. But just when everyone thought that a crash was inevitable, Soft Mist suddenly rolled up into a ball.

Roll!

She completed a roll on the wall, Quick Recover!

The impact was negated by the Quick Recover. As a result, when she landed back onto the ground, she had complete control over her balance. Then, a nearly imperceptible needle whistled by her. It was the Poison Needle from Dark Thunder.

It was only then did everyone realize that Dark Thunder had let out this sneak attack. The broadcast quickly rewinded to figure out when the needle had been thrown. People were now even more shocked at Tang Rou’s keen senses. Although this time, they went ahead of themselves. Tang Rou hadn’t noticed the Poison Needle either. In reality, she had dodged it by a stroke of luck.

That’s too crazy, no?

Countless viewers were awestruck. The Tyranny players weren’t in shock though. In an instant, the entire team accelerated. The fastest member, Dark Thunder, didn’t land the Poison Needle, but before the light had faded, he had followed with a Powerful Knee Strike, chaining the attacks tightly. The needle had missed, but he was there now!

Soft Mist hadn’t steadied herself yet. She didn’t have time to dodge, so she lashed out with her spear, wanting to use an attack to parry the blow and keep her balance. Then, she could use the impact from Powerful Knee Strike to help her escape.

Bang!

Dark Thunder struck Soft Mist’s spear, causing Soft Mist to sway. Tang Rou immediately knew that something wasn’t right. The Powerful Knee Strike from Lin Jingyan had been quick and fierce, but when it struck, the impact put a downwards pressure onto her. At the final moment, he had adjusted the angle of his attack, not wanting to give her a chance to use the impact to escape. Instead, he was going to pressure her into place.

Tang Rou was very sharp, noticing the change. Soft Mist sunk down and then rolled back.

She wasn’t able to borrow the force of the impact to move away, but she wasn’t suppressed by Lin Jingyan’s Powerful Knee Strike. With this roll, she still took damage from the attack, but she was able to eliminate the skill effects.

The normal viewers hadn’t noticed the little sneaky trick in Lin Jingyan’s Powerful Knee Strike. They just thought that Tang Rou had been forced into a hasty response because the attack had come too quickly.

Just a roll backwards wasn’t ideal. Lin Jingyan had seized the initiative, and his Dark Thunder could still cover Soft Mist’s backwards roll. The Powerful Knee Strike didn’t have the effect that Lin Jingyan had wanted, but Tang Rou was now held in place. He simply needed to follow up with a few attacks to make sure she didn’t escape. Then, the rest of Tyranny would arrive, and the rest was exactly what Tyranny specialized at.

Brick!

Sure enough, Lin Jingyan grasped the timing of the roll. Before Soft Mist was able to get up from the roll, Dark Thunder threw a Brick at her. Tang Rou knew that her situation was worrying. As she rolled, she tried her best to observe Dark Thunder’s movements and saw the Brick coming. While rolling, she flicked her spear, using the tail of her spear to knock the Brick aside. Flying weapons generally had very weak priority.

Lin Jingyan seemed to have predicted it would happen. The moment Soft Mist knocked the Brick away, Dark Thunder quickly stepped forward and pushed out with his hands. Tyrannical Chain Punch! He wanted to directly knock Soft Mist down.

But to his surprise, after Soft Mist knocked the Brick aside, her spear continued to move.

Tyrant’s Destruction!

When she knocked the Brick away, the swing had been the start of a skill. Tyranny’s Destruction was unleashed. The fire attribute Dancing Fire Flowing Flames flashed out in a streak of red. Although Tyrannical Chain Punch was a high-level skill as well, it didn’t have extremely priority like a Dragon Breaks the Ranks. The Tyrant’s Destruction was enough to sweep aside the Tyrannical Chain Punch.

Lin Jingyan hadn’t expected there to be a counterattack. Seeing that he was about to be caught in the attack, he immediately canceled his skill. Dark Thunder dodged to the side, unfortunately wasting one of his high-level skills.

Soft Mist immediately leapt backwards to pull apart the distance. Although Dark Thunder’s attack didn’t achieve Lin Jingyan’s original goals, similar to Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s assault, it had resulted in a significant hindrance to her escape. She was able to use Tyrant’s Destruction to widen the distance between her and Dark Thunder, but Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s assault had begun again, and on the other end, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust had arrived.

Soaring Tiger!

Han Wenqing didn’t hold back. His very first move was fierce and resolute. Desert Dust had arrived even before Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s bullets did as he rushed towards Soft Mist.

Soaring Tiger had very high priority. Learning from her experience with Powerful Knee Strike, Tang Rou didn’t dare to try and borrow the force of its impact to escape. She was still too inexperienced against these old generals in the usage of these small tricks.

Dodge.

Desert Dust came afterwards, so he was still a bit far away. Tang Rou had time to dodge. Desert Dust’s kick missed, whistling past Soft Mist. Although the attack missed, Desert Dust had landed in a position that cut off Tang Rou’s retreat path.

The moment Desert Dust swept past Soft Mist, she thrust her spear at him.

Circle Swing!

Tang Rou had noticed his intent and wanted to try and toss Desert Dust back.

The Circle Swing had been extremely accurate. Just when she was about to land the grab, Soft Mist suddenly leapt to the side. The Circle Swing missed. Suddenly, white flames roared to life where Soft Mist had been standing previously.

Sacred Fire!

Immovable Rock’s Backlight cross was still glowing from using the skill. Tang Rou had no choice but to give up on the Circle Swing.

Desert Dust landed on the ground and turned around. His imposing figure made it seem as if the canyon was impenetrable as long as he stood there.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ attacks arrived in an instant. Having dodged the Sacred Fire, Tang Rou had no room to breathe. Soft Mist quickly ran, avoiding the rain of bullets from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder and Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust had formed a pincer on Soft Mist, the former in front, the latter behind. They kept a distance from her, not immediately rushing at her just in case. Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock and Song Qiying’s River Sunset, who was protecting him, was hurrying over as well.

A 1v5. It was now a true 1v5.

Tyranny was no longer harassing her from a safe distance, nor were they just sending out probing attacks. In the end, Tyranny had trapped Tang Rou’s Soft Mist. These old generals weren’t going to miss an opportunity just out of caution. Their caution only made their choices timed more perfectly.

After making sure that their encirclement was faultless, Tyranny began their assault!

With this sort of encirclement, how long would it take for them to kill a single character?

It was hard to give a precise answer. Compared to the five with the overwhelming advantage, it was more dependent on the single player defending against the five.

Intuition, reaction speed, technique… in these moments, these attributes were key, but more importantly was the player’s willpower.

A 1v5…

It wasn’t an equal playing field. Many people would give up facing this kind of situation.

Tang Rou didn’t though. No pro player would so easily give up in such a crucial match.

But Tang Rou’s current situation was particularly troublesome.

She didn’t have a strategic goal in mind. She also didn’t know if there was any hope the others could get to her in time. She could only give it her all and survive as long as she could.

Soft Mist’s health dropped rapidly, but her struggle could clearly be seen.

Protect yourself.

Who knew why, but Ye Xiu’s previous instructions to Tang Rou suddenly floated to many people’s minds.

1v5. Protect yourself.

Everyone just thought of it as a casual remark, but it looked like these words spoke true. While in this encirclement, she was doing her utmost to carry out these orders.

Just a bit more…

People began to pray. Because they could see the situation more clearly than Tang Rou. From their omniscient view of the map, they could see Happy’s other four players hurrying over to her location. For Tang Rou, it was hope.

But since they were trying to get here as fast as possible, they gave up on moving together as a whole. For example, Happy’s fastest member was undoubtedly Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. By using movement skill after movement skill, he had left the other three in the dust. In an unbelievably short amount of time, he had reached the battlefield.

Even so, wasn’t it still a 2v5? When comparing it to a 1v5, it wasn’t really that much better. Ye Xiu had Lord Grim rush over nonetheless. After locating Tyranny, he didn’t hide himself and went straight for them.

“I’m here!” Ye Xiu announced his arrival in the public chat.

Chapter 1558 - Appetizer

I’m here.

It was a very ordinary phrase, but saying it in this situation gave off a “you’ve been surrounded” air to it. What made it even more unbearable was that Tang Rou’s Soft Mist was currently surrounded by Tyranny. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had come charging in alone. He was simply adding oil to the fire. If he had just quietly rushed in, it would have been fine. But he just had to announce himself in the public chat.

This was a Glory match. There could only be at most five players on a side. You can yell all you want, but the other side wasn’t going to think you had brought 100 people with you.

They couldn’t understand the reason for Ye Xiu’s bravado, but Tyranny’s reaction left them even more puzzled.

Tyranny had unexpectedly been scared by Ye Xiu, quickly pulling back. The way they positioned themselves made it appear as if they were about to face an imminent disaster. They didn’t look like they were about to face a single lone person.

“Go die!”

Ye Xiu was still typing in the chat. For a moment, the viewers were confused about which side was the one surrounded.

Boom boom boom!

Ye Xiu did as he said. As soon as the message was typed out, he made his move. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shot out three Anti-Tank Missiles, aimed unambiguously towards three different people.

Dodge!

Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Xinjie dodged the missiles aimed at them. There was still a bit of distance between the two sides, so it wasn’t hard to dodge. The three were more concerned with what Ye Xiu would do next, or perhaps, what Happy would do next.

The other strategists watching the match such as Yu Wenzhou and Xiao Shiqin were already chuckling.

Through their spectator view, they could see the map and the chat. They knew exactly what Ye Xiu wanted to do.

He was bluffing. He had been setting up this bluff ever since Tang Rou encountered Tyranny. Because of the change in the usual spawn locations, Tang Rou and Tyranny had a surprise encounter. For Tang Rou, who had been by herself, she was at a huge disadvantage. As a result, she didn’t hesitate and immediately retreated. On the other hand, Tyranny, who had the overwhelming advantage, had hesitated because of this unusual occurrence.

Overwhelming advantage, hesitate.

Just through this reaction, Ye Xiu was able to grasp a clearer message from Tyranny: both sides were surprised by the encounter.

But that didn’t mean Tang Rou wasn’t in a crisis. Ye Xiu had Tang Rou try to harass them as a way to perhaps scare them away.

If she didn’t try to harass them and instead let Tyranny dispel their suspicions, Tyranny would have immediately started chasing her, and at that point, even a god wouldn’t be able to save her.

Ye Xiu had given out the extremely daring order for this reason, and it was because had given out this order that there would be a chance to rescue Tang Rou.

Lord Grim went in alone, yet Tyranny reacted defensively. Because from beginning to end, Tyranny hadn’t been able to determine whether their encounter with Tang Rou had been a coincidence. They thought that Tang Rou was bait. They thought that they had caught the bait before falling into a trap. They thought that they had taken the initiative as a result. Next, Happy would be forced to appear. As a result, during this process, they had been on guard against the possibility of the other four members of Happy appearing.

Then, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim appeared right on time, going along perfectly with Tyranny’s expectations.

As a result, Tyranny responded immediately, moving into a formation that they had prepared for ahead of time. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had quickly started attacking. Three Anti-Tank Missiles split between three enemies. The three instinctively dodged. Then, they saw Soft Mist, with four chasers floating around her, use Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Out!

An opening had appeared in Tyranny’s encirclement.

Had they overlooked Tang Rou?

No!

In their eyes, Tang Rou had been bait from start to finish. Previously, she had been bait to lure Tyranny over to Happy’s trap. After catching her, they were now using her as bait to lure out Happy. The fish hadn’t been caught on the hook yet. How could that be overlooking her?

Ye Xiu’s appearance was like a weight off their minds. They had been on guard against him this entire time, and now they no longer needed to. It was hard to avoid a shift in balance under these circumstances. If it had been a bit longer, Tyranny would have certainly readjusted the balance. After all, they had been using Tang Rou to pin down Happy..

But Ye Xiu sent out attacks the instant the balance shifted, affecting Tyranny’s plans for him. And Tang Rou seemed like she had been waiting for this moment. Soft Mist’s chasers suddenly shot out. At the same time, she charged out with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Everything had happened so quickly. Soft Mist escaped from Tyranny’s encirclement, and Lord Grim went forward, raising his umbrella up as a shield, blocking the long-ranged attacks from Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist turned around and ran for their lives.

2v5? That would be a joke. At this point, Soft Mist couldn’t even be considered a 1. She was more like 0.2. Ye Xiu had come charging in bravely, and once he picked up Tang Rou, he didn’t hesitate to turn tail and run.

The two left behind a trail of dust in the canyon.

And… that’s it?

Everyone was petrified.

In their eyes, Tyranny was looking extremely incompetent. They had Soft Mist trapped. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was alone. What could he do? Yet he just charged in, fired an Anti-Tank Missile, and then rescued her? How could there be an even more worthless team?

Only the experts understood why. Ye Xiu had made the best of what he had, and Tyranny cautiously responded. It had been an exchange filled with complexities.

From an overall perspective, Tyranny had lost an opportunity, but not much else. As for Happy? Happy hadn’t gained anything. After a huge struggle at great risks, they had escaped from the crisis. During this escape, Soft Mist had lost a considerable amount of health and mana. Life could be healed, but healing would use up mana. And mana could not be replenished.

From this perspective, Happy had lost much from this exchange.

“A good appetizer!” The pro player QQ chat group was quite lively. Of the 20 teams in the Alliance, 17 had been eliminated this season. However, many of them were still quite interested in the playoffs. There were quite a few of them watching this deciding semifinals game, whether that was live, through the computer, or through their cell phones. Many of them were watching while discussing in the GG chat group. Team Void’s Li Xuan had commented, calling the exchange an “appetizer”.

“Yeah yeah!” The other players agreed and then continued to watch the match. For people at their skill level, there was no playoffs match that would be boring to watch. Others might find it boring because they didn’t understand the small intricacies involved.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist said goodbye, and Tyranny was just going to quietly send them off?

Of course not.

Tyranny had tried to stop them. Zhang Jiale had been the fastest to react. It was just that Lord Grim’s umbrella shield weakened his long-ranged attacks by a large degree. Happy’s two players had already started picking up speed. In a race, the differences in speed would result in the group separating. And Tyranny continued to be cautious, keeping their formation intact, as they chased calmly after Lord Grim and Soft Mist.

Team Tyranny had looked incompetent just before, and now, their lack of decisiveness looked as if it would make that impression worse. In reality, that was not the case.

Through their omniscient view, the viewers could clearly see the instructions left by Ye Xiu as he ran away. The other three on Happy, who hadn’t arrived yet, received instructions to set up an ambush. As Ye Xiu hurried over to this area, he had been taking note of the terrain, so he gave them coordinates for the ambush location. At that moment, he had thought up a plan. He was like an outstanding chess player. He wasn’t thinking just one step ahead, but two or even three steps…

Tyranny was reacting cautiously, and to the spectators, it was a very smart move. After all, Glory was a game. An ambush would only result in having the initiative. It was very difficult to kill an opponent with one strike. And with Tyranny keeping their guard up, Happy had no way to focus on a target and surprise kill an opponent. Through a sturdy defense, Tyranny would be able to hold their ground against Happy’s ambush and then search for an opportunity to counterattack. That was the plan that Tyranny had intended to do when they chased after Soft Mist. This time, their plans didn’t change. Seeing their two targets turn at the corner up ahead and disappear from their view, Tyranny didn’t panic. They continued to move at the same pace. When they reached this corner, they raised their guards and rushed through it.

But all they saw was Lord Grim.

“Can you guys hurry up? I’m afraid I’ll lose you guys,” Ye Xiu typed into the chat.

“Then stop running! You come over here!” Zhang Jiale shouted.

“It’s not just me who’ll be coming!” Ye Xiu replied.

Dancing Rain appeared from up above on the canyon, looking down. Her cannon was aimed straight at Tyranny.

“Hi everyone!” Su Mucheng greeted. Dancing Rain attacked!

Chapter 1559 - Bait

Bang! Boom!

A shot, and then an explosion.

A Stinger fired into the air, exploding like a firework. Missiles rained down lighting up the canyon with flames. It wasn’t over yet. More artillery shells followed, creating shadows on the ground. The shadows grew larger and larger until the missiles exploded.

In a short moment, the canyon was filled with rising spirals of smoke. Tyranny had five people, but at this height difference, only Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms could reach her. However, he wasn’t able to display his full potential because Spitfire attacks didn’t all have the same range. Bullets could reach farther, grenades closer. Only Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s bullets could reach the top of the canyon. He wasn’t able to throw his grenades up there. This sort of Spitfire could only display no more than a third of his true capabilities.

But Tyranny didn’t panic.

They had noticed the tall canyon walls to the side of them. They also hadn’t forgotten that Happy had Su Mucheng’s Launcher. If Happy had any ambushes set up, it would be the easiest to do it from up there, so Tyranny was most prepared for it. No communication was needed. Everyone knew what to do. First, they headed towards the canyon wall that Dancing Rain was situation on. The canyon wall wasn’t flat. As a result, if they were perpendicular to Dancing Rain, there would be numerous obstacles in the way of her attacks. Even so, Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms didn’t directly contest against Dancing Rain. Although he knew that his grenades couldn’t reach up there, he threw them anyways, shooting them in midair.

Light blossomed in the air, creating a wall of light from above.

“Nice!” Even Ye Xiu praised it.

Even Ye Xiu could copy the Hundred Blossoms style pretty decently if he was given a Spitfire, but even he could tell that he wouldn’t be able to copy what Zhang Jiale had just done. After all, this was Zhang Jiale’s specialty. He had immersed himself in this playstyle for years. Certain techniques couldn’t be copied so easily.

The uneven wall along with the light cover minimized Su Mucheng’s threat to them. The five stuck to the wall as they quickly rushed towards Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu didn’t rush over to welcome them. Lord Grim moved horizontally, sticking to the other side of the wall and shooting at them from afar.

The viewers saw what he was doing and cursed. He was clearly bullying Tyranny.

Han Wenqing and Song Qiying could only fight at close range. Lin Jingyan had a few mid-ranged attacks, but he couldn’t be considered a mid-ranged attacker. The majority of his attacks were at a close range. If the three of them wanted to attack Lord Grim, they would need to get closer to him, which would again make them easy targets for Dancing Rain.

As for long-ranged attackers, apart from Zhang Xinjie’s Cleric, there was Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. His Spitfire was a true long-ranged attackers, but at the moment, he was spraying light into the air to interfere with Dancing Rain’s attacks. How could he have time to attack Lord Grim?

Tyranny’s team competition starting line up usually had Qin Muyun or Bai Yanfei, so they wouldn’t be lacking a second long-ranged attacker. However, today, Song Qiying’s River Sunset was put in instead, and now, Ye Xiu was taking advantage of it.

From the eyes of the spectators, Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had control of Tyranny’s left, right, up, and down. Tyranny could do nothing, and it would likely spell misfortune for them. But in the end, nothing happened with Tyranny. So what if Lord Grim was on the other side of the wall? We’ll just ignore him and keep going.

Ignore Lord Grim? The viewers forgot that was an option, but what would the outcome be?

Lord Grim began attacking from afar relentlessly, starting with a Gatling Gun. The muzzle of the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella shook violently, firing a chain of bullets at Tyranny. The bullets hit the wall of the canyon, lifting a cloud of dust into the air. But so what? Dust didn’t deal damage to them. A bullet or two hitting them didn’t matter either. Tyranny’s advance didn’t slow down.

Grenade!

Anti-Tank Missiles!

Ye Xiu had Lord Grim follow with heavier attacks. These attacks dealt AoE damage, dodging them wouldn’t be so easy. However, Tyranny didn’t consist of a bunch of normal tenth server players. Tyranny wouldn’t be overwhelmed so easily. They were very familiar with these attacks and dodged them without their formation breaking apart.

The distance was still a bit far.

Ye Xiu had noticed this point. In order to make things more difficult for Tyranny, Lord Grim moved a bit farther.

Floating Bullet, Stun Bullet!

This time, Lord Grim’s attacks had CC. Bang bang, the bullets flew.

Hit!

Both bullets landed.

But none of the characters were knocked into the air or stunned. Desert Dust activated Reinforced Iron Bones and body blocked the bullets.

Then, Lord Grim cast a few magic spells, but as long as the attacks had no CC, Tyranny ignored them completely. The damage dealt by an unspecialized’s low-level skills was insignificant.

But drops of water could still pierce stone. Although the damage was low, they couldn’t keep ignoring it. The road wasn’t short!

Tyranny was venturing into unknown territory, but the spectators knew that Ye Xiu and Tang Rou were luring Tyranny into the longest ravine on the map. Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng could control the left, right, above, and below for a long time. Just this alone would rack up quite a bit of damage onto Tyranny. Happy still had two attackers who hadn’t joined yet either!

The crowd was having a hard time sitting still seeing Tyranny’s patience, especially the Tyranny fans. They felt like Tyranny was continuing with their plans because they didn’t know the map. However, if they continued like this, they would suffer greatly. It wouldn’t be worth it!

Just when they were thinking this, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms suddenly shifted targets. Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, he shot at Lord Grim. Desert Dust, River Sunset, and Dark Thunder, the three Fighters, rushed towards Lord Grim.

What’s going on?

What happened?

Although the fans were feeling anxious about Tyranny, when they suddenly switched up the tempo, they still felt anxious. For them to have suddenly made a move, was it because an opportunity had appeared? What was it? Dancing Rain was still above them!

“Hahaha, I know her a hundred times better than you guys!”

Ye Xiu left a message in the chat. At the same time, when Tyranny suddenly made their move, Lord Grim retreated, dodging Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s attacks. He leapt up, his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transforming into a ninjato, as he scaled up the wall of the canyon.

With just a few swings, Lord Grim was at a height where Han Wenqing and Song Qiying, who had the lowest range, could only grind their teeth. Lin Jingyan and Zhan Jiale, in particular, could still continue attacking. However, up above, although the cannonfire had weakened, it was concentrated on Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. With this harrassment, Zhang Jiale couldn’t focus his attention on Ye Xiu. And just dealing with a few mid-ranged attacks from a Brawler was nothing difficult for Ye Xiu. Lord Grim went up and down several times and then activated Rotor Wings to fly directly to the top.

“My friends below, how are you all doing?” Ye Xiu was still taunting them.

Zhang Jiale was furious. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fired at him fiercely, but Lord Grim simply shrunk his head back and dodged them all. Dancing Rain’s cannonfire seemed to weaken again. Tyranny immediately went back towards the canyon wall that she was on.

Finally, the audience realized what had happened.

Tyranny hadn’t made their move because they had lost their patience. They had found an opportunity, which came from Dancing Rain’s cooldowns!

After a wave of attacks, a portion of her skills would go on cooldown. If you wanted to keep a steady DPS, you had to cycle your skills properly. PvE players, who played against bosses in-game, understood this well. However, PvP was different, because PvP was full of changes. While in PvE, it was often best to keep a steady damage output, but in PvP, it might be necessary to bursts of damage, especially in the team competition.

Dancing Rain had the high grounds and couldn’t be touched, so if Su Mucheng wanted to fight as if this were PvE, she could do so.

But Tyranny’s players weren’t as easy to deal with as in-game bosses. Although they wouldn’t attack back, they had ways of defending against her attacks. Tyranny seemed to just be sticking close to the wall and keeping up a cover of light as they moved, but in reality, their overall movement restrained her offense to a certain extent. If she wanted to be a threat to them, she needed to go along with their pace.

As such, she could not cycle through her skills perfectly. Her skill cooldowns would result in a decrease in her firepower. It was just a matter of time.

Tyranny had grasped this point and seized this timing. However, Ye Xiu understood this even better than them.

Lord Grim retreated, while Dancing Rain held back for her cooldowns to come back up. They weren’t big enough of a threat to suppress Tyranny, but they could still force them into a corner. As a result, once they suppressed Tyranny’s only long-ranged attacker, Lord Grim backed away.

It seemed like an ordinary change in the battle, but it contained a deeper layer to it. The more skilled normal players could see that Dancing Rain had quite a lot of skills on cooldown, but they didn’t know that Tyranny had led it to this situation. They hadn’t simply been waiting for an opportunity, they had created it.

It had been a good move, but Ye Xiu had broken it apart.

“It’s finally my turn!” Fang Rui popped up in the chat. Happy’s next move was coming.

Chapter 1560 - Chat Statistics

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was situated on the left canyon wall.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was situated on the right canyon wall.

Tyranny could interfere with Su Mucheng’s influence on the left through their usage of the uneven surface of the canyon wall and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ light cover. However, there was nothing they could to stop the attacks from Lord Grim’s side.

Tyranny didn’t make any adjustments.

The threat posed by the left and right was not equally balanced. In terms of long-ranged capabilities, Dancing Rain’s firepower was more fearsome. Most of Lord Grim’s long-ranged attacks required him to rely on the differences in height to land. This meant that Tyranny was at the very edge of his attack range. These sort of attacks were relatively easy to dodge. The problem was that constantly dodging was tiresome. Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style was also very mana-hungry. Previously, he had used his skills rather lavishly so that Su Mucheng would not be able to cycle through her skills perfectly. Keeping up this Hundred Blossoms cover would be too wasteful.

Fang Rui’s trash talk popped up in the public chat during Tyranny’s predicament. In the next second, a few of Tyranny’s players could see him.

Why only a few?

Because all five of Tyranny’s players were sticking close to the wall, and the wall was not straight. By moving along the wall, their vision was restricted. Fang Rui had said that he had arrived, but to put it more accurately, his appearance hadn’t been proactive. Rather, it was because Tyranny had constantly been pushing forward. Once they reached this area, Boundless Sea, who had been waiting by the walls of the canyon, could finally see Tyranny.

Boundless Sea had been gathering qi in his palms. The viewers weren’t surprised. They could see the communication between Happy. While Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng had been harrassing Tyranny, they had also been informing Fang Rui of their location. When the time came, Boundless Sea began charging Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, waiting for Tyranny to enter his range.

Tyranny appeared.

So Fang Rui released the qi.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

Boundless Sea moved laterally. As a result, the qi that he released moved somewhat differently than when standing. The qi formed a rainbow, but instead of cutting through the sky, it moved along the wall in an arc.

Pierce through all of Tyranny, skewering them like tanghulu with Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

Fang Rui had been charging his attack for a long time. The viewers had noticed it a while ago, but to Tyranny, it was very sudden. The moment Fang Rui typed out his message into the chat, he had already released his attack. This was his usual tactic of using trash talk to distract his opponents. It was inherently different from Huang Shaotian’s trash talk, who did it simply because he was talkative.

The one at the front of Tyranny’s formation was Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust.

Body block it?

No.

The class advancement skill, Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, had even higher piercing power than the Launcher’s Laser Beam. Unless he had a shield or if the teammates behind him wouldn’t be hit by the attack, there was no way for him to lower the destructiveness of the attack.

Don’t block it?

If he didn’t block it, then his only option was to dodge it? But would the others behind him be able to react in time?

Because of their formation, Desert Dust was blocking everyone’s line of sight. Han Wenqing could see the arc of the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow vividly, but the others behind him might not be able to. It was very possible that they were looking around trying to find where that dirty bastard was!

Fang Rui’s choice in positioning and timing was dripping with dirtiness.

It was dirty to the point that normal viewers weren’t even aware of the dirtiness. Only the experts who put themselves in Tyranny’s position would know just how disgusting this attack was.

Perhaps taking the hit would be the wisest choice. At the very least, they would be able to maintain their formation… that was what many pro players believed. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust stepped to the side though, dodging the attack.

Behind him, Dark Thunder also stepped to the side.

Behind Dark Thunder, Immovable Rock stepped to the side.

Then, River Sunset.

And finally, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Tyranny’s chat was completely clean, but all of Tyranny reacted nearly simultaneously and stepped to the side, dodging the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

This was a silent trust, trust that the person at the front, their captain Han Wenqing, would never make a meaningless move.

It was a trust that everyone would act promptly and effectively to not delay the next player’s action.

And just like this, the dirty attack had been avoided through the tacit coordination between Tyanny’s team members.

Throughout this process, there had been no communication through the chat. Not even an exclamation point.

The Alliance had a stat specifically to track how many messages each team sent every match. Of the twenty teams in the Alliance, Tyranny typed the fewest words, whether it was in the team or the public chat.

The team chat was mainly used to communicate information and strategies between team members. Less communication in the team chat meant a higher level of team synergy. The messages would be short and precise. Tyranny’s current line up had only been created last season, yet they had already reached such a high level of synergy. Much of it had to do with the experience and awareness of the old generals that supported the team.

This statistic had become a measure of a team’s strength. Behind Tyranny in terms of messages in the team chat was the defending champion, Samsara, and then Tiny Herb. All of them were top teams.

There were exceptions, of course.

Such as Team Thunderclap. Their performance in the regular season had been outstanding, but for them, not only did the number of messages in the team chat not decrease, it increased. This was because Xiao Shiqing’s shotcalling had become more detailed.

Another notable example was Team Blue Rain, but that was because of a very obvious reason. This statistic for Blue Rain was skewed heavily because of a certain outlier.

Apart from that, there was the statistics for the number of messages in the public chat.

The public chat was used as communication between the competing teams, which mostly consisted of trash talk. This statistic was more dependent on the personalities of the individual players and didn’t reflect a team’s strength. Of course, for the same reason, this statistic for Blue Rain was heavily skewed.

In comparison, the team chat statistic for Happy was very average. Their communication wasn’t as concise as those of the top teams, but it also wasn’t as noisy as those of most new teams. On the other hand, for the public chat statistic, Happy was in the top three. It could be seen that their talent for trash talk wasn’t low!

Chapter 1561 - Scheming Tyranny

Tyranny dodged Fang Rui’s precisely calculated attack by relying on their extraordinary synergy with one another.

An attack had been dodged, that was all, but it was a very meaningful dodge. The average viewers might not understand, but the pro player chat group did.

As the pro players praised Tyranny’s coordination, Tyranny promptly went back to sticking close to the wall. The five players were like a wave rising and falling. The Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow pushed them aside, and when the qi moved past them, they fell back into place.

The attack had missed, and it hadn’t even been able to create an opening for Su Mucheng. The rise and fall had happened in the blink of an eye. Tyranny’s members were already back in their original positions.

Of course, Fang Rui’s calculated offensive wasn’t done yet.

The moment Boundless Sea fired Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he began preparing for the next attack.

Dragon Wave!

Boundless Sea attacked again. The qi swirled into a dragon that flew towards Tyranny with a roar. This Dragon Wave could be controlled manually by the player. As a result, the attack would be more nimble. Tyranny wouldn’t be able to dodge it mechanically like the last attack.

However, Dragon Wave didn’t have the same sort of piercing power as Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow. On Tyranny’s side, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust rushed forward and activated Reinforced Iron Bones. He was clearly planning on tanking the Dragon Wave.

On the battlefield, it was never a good idea to go along with what the opponent wanted. This was the only way to firmly take the initiative.

Han Wenqing wanted Desert Dust to tank it, but Fang Rui wasn’t going to let him. With a flick of his wrist, Boundless Sea lifted his arm, and the Dragon Wave rose into the air, passing over Desert Dust’s head.

It was only by going against what the opponent wanted would you be able to disrupt the opponent’s rhythm!

But Han Wenqing’s rhythm wasn’t broken. The Dragon Wave flew past his head, but his movements hadn’t changed.

Continue charging straight forward.

Ahead was Boundless Sea! Since the Dragon Wave missed, he might as well attack Boundless Sea. With a sudden burst of speed, he instantly closed the distance between them. The Dragon Wave that flew past Desert Dust made Fang Rui feel like it wasn’t going to make it.

On the other canyon wall, Ye Xiu noticed that the situation on Fang Rui’s end wasn’t looking good. Tyranny had suddenly changed their intentions. Happy was making it uncomfortable for them to their left and right. As a result, they began letting to take the offensive. Desert Dust’s charge was simply a prelude. Tyranny was planning on ignoring the two long-ranged harassers and going straight for the kill on Boundless Sea. Desert Dust didn’t turn back, tearing apart Fang Rui’s original plans.

Tyranny never lacked courage. Despite knowing that Happy had likely set up an ambush, they still pressed forward because they were confident that they could break through Happy’s arrangements.

It was true that they had become more cautious, but their direct playstyle hadn’t changed.

Boundless Sea was their target!

Desert Dust threw a heavy punch. Behind him, Dark Thunder, Immovable Rock, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, and River Sunset stopped hiding near the wall and spread out. Next, Fang Rui needed to figure out which target for his Dragon Wave to pursue. But right now, Fang Rui had no time to hesitate. In the blink of an eye, Desert Dust arrived.

Cancel!

Fang Rui wanted to cancel the skill, but suddenly, a figure appeared in what he felt was a very convenient position…

Nice!

Fang Rui was delighted. It was obviously better not to waste a skill.The figure was in such a perfect position. Fang Rui didn’t hesitate and turned the Dragon Wave.

But that figure seemed to know that the Dragon Wave would come. The figure suddenly moved outwards, and Fang Rui instinctively followed the other side’s movements. But then, he realized: not good!

Pu!

Desert Dust’s fist smashed into Boundless Sea. The Dragon Wave was interrupted. Boundless Sea was sent flying like a broken kite. His gaze was still fixed towards the figure that had baited him into continuing with the Dragon Wave. Although in reality, he didn’t need to look to know who it was.

Lin Jingyan. Whether it was personality or tactics, no one was more familiar with Fang Rui than Lin Jingyan. Only he would have the awareness to bait Fang Rui into not cancelling his skill.

Fang Rui was a very experienced player, but like ginger, the older, the spicier.

Heroic Leap!

Lord Grim jumped off the canyon wall and fell rapidly.

Tyranny had acted quickly, and Ye Xiu didn’t react slowly either. As soon as he saw Desert Dust swing his fists towards Boundless Sea, he immediately gave up on trying to interfere through long-ranged attacks. The long-ranged capabilities of an unspecialized, whether it was damage or CC, was too poor.

Heroic Leap!

Lord Grim leapt into the air and then plummeted downwards. He had reacted fast, but Boundless Sea had already been sent flying. Tyranny noticed his movements and immediately spread out to surround him.

Tyranny’s five players stood quite far apart, making it difficult for Su Mucheng to cover all of them. With a character attacking them from above, going near the wall wasn’t Tyranny’s only option. They had simply been making the best choice in that situation. At that time, Happy only had two people in front of them. With the others on Happy in unknown locations, they erred on the side of caution and prioritized defense. Now, not only was their left and right being attacked, Fang Rui was harassing them from the front. Tyranny took action and immediately scattered, splitting Su Mucheng’s attention as each of them locked onto a target.

Desert Dust continued to attack Boundless Sea. The remaining four set up a net, intending on catching the falling Lord Grim.

Satellite Beam!

Dancing Rain let out a high-level skill. Her purpose wasn’t to attack, but to defend. The powerful beam of light seemed to envelop Lord Grim as he fell. The smaller pillars of light immediately began to revolve around it. Under this protection, Tyranny couldn’t easily attack Lord Grim. Only Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms could shoot a few bullets at him from afar.

Zhang Jiale set up a light cover, engulfing the Satellite Beam and the surrounding area. Zhang Jiale wasn’t just attacking. He wanted to use the light cover to shield his teammates. At the same time, it would prove a hindrance to Su Mucheng.

The two sides seemed to have no way of immediately attacking each other. However, Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style was too grand, requiring an enormous consumption. Soon, because many of his skills were on cooldown, he had no way of keeping up the cover of light. But gradually, as the light dispersed, it revealed two figures that were unexpectedly rushing towards Boundless Sea instead of Lord Grim.

River Sunset and Dark Thunder, two Fighter classes, also targeted Boundless Sea. Their intentions on surrounding Lord Grim had been a feint to seal off Ye Xiu’s next movements and to attract Su Mucheng’s attention. With the cover from Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, by the time their intentions were revealed, Happy would have lost the opportunity to respond immediately.

Boom boom boom!

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain tried to stop them, but both Fighters had activated Reinforced Iron Bones. Under Supor Armor, they marched through Dancing Rain’s attacks. At the same time, their bodies flashed with white light. Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock was healing them.

Attack these two? Or interrupt the healer? Either way, there was no way for Su Mucheng to stop the two from reaching Boundless Sea.

What about Ye Xiu?

Lord Grim was trapped by Zhang Jiale’s shrinking blossoms of light. Previously, he had spread the light cover too wide. After the skills went on cooldown, he had no way of keeping it up. But he could do it if he shrunk the area of effect since he was only facing against Ye Xiu. Zhang Jiale didn’t only respond to the situation at hand, but also thinking ahead.

A few seconds ago, Tyranny had been in an uncomfortable position. But in a short moment, they had turned it around. Under Tyranny’s pressure, Happy’s weakness at the moment was made clear: they had less people!

Why?

Why didn’t Happy go all out with their ambush?

Because Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had suffered heavy injuries during her escape. She needed time to heal. With her way of fighting, if she had entered the battle at critical health, Tyranny would have likely killed her off in one wave. Not even Happy’s healer would be able to save her. Happy had set up their ambush, slowly bringing their players in to stall for time and let Soft Mist recover more health.

But when their ambush was broken through, a fatal weakness was revealed.

“No wonder Tyranny pursued them so closely.”

“They were biting fiercely onto Soft Mist’s low health!”

“Because of Soft Mist’s low health, Happy is practically lacking a combatant. She can’t directly join the fight!”

“Could they have intentionally let Soft Mist go? They guided Happy into setting up this flimsy ambush. If Soft Mist had died, Happy would have a full-health character on the battlefield. Wouldn’t Happy’s ambush be much more threatening then?

When the pro players saw this scene, they started typing like crazy into the QQ chat group, discussing their viewpoints.

“Happy being in a disadvantageous spot hasn’t changed since Tang Rou ran into Tyranny!”

“Tyranny has been taking advantage of this point!”

“Truly cunning.”

“Just watching it scares me!”

“What will Happy do?”

“What about Tang Rou? Soft Mist? She has to come out and attack now, no?”

“Maybe switch with that Summoner?”

“But it’ll be difficult for a Summoner to open up this situation!”

“She’s coming out!” The pro players also had the spectator view. The broadcast also knew where the key point lay, and a small window appeared, focusing on Soft Mist.

“Fuck, this is staking it all on one throw!!” Everyone was surprised by Happy’s move.

Both Happy’s Battle Mage and Summoner had come out. In other words, they had switched out their healer…

Chapter 1562: Former Radiance

In the team competition of the playoffs, Happy switched out their healer…

Everyone in the Alliance knew how bold Happy was and knew that they would occasionally make an unconventional gambit. However, no one thought that they would dare to do so in this life-and-death playoffs match.

A fully offensive team, staking everything in one throw.

In competitive play, these two phrases went hand-in-hand. When the formation came into play, it meant that there was no retreating. A team without a healer could only push forward and attack. There was no second option.

However, in the eyes of the pro players spectating the match, none of them felt like Happy was at a point where they needed to take this step. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain stood at an absolutely safe position, and with her support, it wouldn’t be a problem for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim to climb back up again and reach a safe position. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was being attacked by three players and was indeed in a difficult situation, but with his cunning, he should be able to escape if that was his only goal.

The confidence in Fang Rui from the pro players showed just how much trouble he had given them over his career. However, after watching for awhile longer, they realized that if Fang Rui wanted to rely on his dirtiness to escape today, he would encounter an obstacle that he had never encountered before. Among the players attacking him was one called Lin Jingyan.

The one who understood him the best was his opponent.

Roll, twist, feint, turn!

Through Boundless Sea’s dirty tricks, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust staggered into a bad position. Song Qiying was still too inexperienced and lacked the foresight. His River Sunset wanted to attack, but he discovered that he was being blocked by his teammate, Desert Dust.

Did he escape?

A Brick crashed into Boundless Sea’s face.

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder.

The attack wasn’t nearly as striking as the attacks from the two Strikers, but whenever Boundless Sea was able to create an opening, Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder would always be there to seal it off.

It had only been a short moment, yet it had already happened three times.

It had only been a short moment, yet Boundless Sea had already lost a third of his health.

Because of Lin Jingyan, Han Wenqing and Song Qiying could focus fully on attacking because the task of preventing Fang Rui from escaping belonged to Lin Jingyan. If not, Han Wenqing’s and Song Qiying’s assault wouldn’t have been so lacking that Fang Rui could find three openings in such a short amount of time. All of it was because Han Wenqing and Song Qiying didn’t care about giving him openings because Lin Jingyan had their backs.

In the group arena, Lin Jingyan had been the main reason that Tyranny had fallen behind. However, he was now Tyranny’s most trusted player.

Number four!

He had successfully stopped Fang Rui for a fourth time.

Fang Rui was starting to panic. Not a single peep came from him. Of the three players attacking him, two of them were Strikers, who were close-quarter specialists. How could he have any time to spare to type out any trash talk? In the beginning, he thought that he would be able to easily escape from those two blockheads, but after being stopped twice by Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder, he realized that those two weren’t stupid.

If he wanted to escape, his opponents weren’t those two, but his old partner!

After changing classes, he had taken advantage of the fact that his opponents were unfamiliar with the new “Qi Master Fang Rui”. Unfortunately, his old partner was still able to keep up with his thoughts and his pace even after he had changed classes.

If he wanted to escape, he needed to find a way to break through. He needed to do something he had never done before.

Fang Rui suddenly stopped trying to escape and started defending and dodging, doing his best to survive.

Give up on escaping? Quietly wait to be rescued?

The spectators were all thinking the same thing. After all, they knew about Happy’s strategic decision, and Fang Rui obviously knew about it too. An Wenyi was switched out for Luo Ji. This sort of decision wasn’t something that An Wenyi could decide on his own. Ye Xiu had clearly given the order in Happy’s team chat. As a result, Fang Rui also knew that his team was coming full force to rescue him.

It was unlikely that Tyranny wouldn’t think of Happy coming to rescue him, but it was unlikely that they would expect Happy to give up on their healer. In Tyranny’s preparations against Happy’s rescue operation, Tyranny would likely be considering either a Battle Mage and Cleric, or a Summoner and Cleric situation.

Was Happy trying to surprise Tyranny?

The pro players thought about this question, but it didn’t look like Tyranny planned on making any changes. After Fang Rui stopped trying to escape, the three attackers kept the same formation. The two Strikers went all-out in their offense, while Lin Jingyan was on guard.

Fang Rui was even more annoyed.

However, he hadn’t given up on escaping! Because he was quite clear about the high risks of switching out their healer. He knew that the reason Happy had made such a risky decision was because of his current predicament. If he could safely escape, Su Mucheng was already safe, and Ye Xiu could easily escape as well. In that case, Happy could regroup and try a different strategy. There was no need to gamble everything on one throw.

Fang Rui’s thoughts had originally been the same as the other pro players watching. Happy shouldn’t need to have to make such a risky play in this important life-and-death match yet. But soon, he changed his mind. Right now, he was in the predicament. He was the breakthrough that Tyranny had seized. He was the one who wasn’t able to escape, pulling Happy down along with him. Although it wasn’t like escaping from a 1v3 was ever an easy task, Fang Rui hated how he was the weak point.

Tang Rou and Luo Ji would come soon, but Fang Rui still wanted to try and change the current situation before they arrived.

However, Tyranny wasn’t going to fall for it. He faked his true intentions to try bait Tyranny into changing their approach, but Tyranny refused to do so.

Truly a bunch of stubborn bastards!!

With no time to type out any words, Fang Rui could only curse at them inwardly. He was truly annoyed at Tyranny. How could he know that in reality, when he began faking his true intentions, Lin Jingyan immediately warned Tyranny: “Ignore it.”

In the end, Lin Jingyan had seen through him.

After Fang Rui changed classes, Lin Jingyan wasn’t used to the way his Qi Master played either. However, Lin Jingyan understood how Fang Rui thought. Oftentimes, he wasn’t predicting what Fang Rui would do, but predicting how Fang Rui wanted to do it. He wasn’t looking at Fang Rui’s methods, but rather his intentions. With his two teammates pressuring Fang Rui, he was able to get a more precise read on him.

Fang Rui saw that his plan wasn’t working and could only try switch it up again.

If trickery doesn’t work, then try brute force!

Fang Rui decided. He tossed aside his dirtiness and suddenly began trying to brute force his way out.

At this moment, a message popped up in Happy’s team chat: Lin.

The message came from Ye Xiu. Artillery fire soon followed.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain suddenly increased the pressure towards his side. In an instant, artillery shells rained down.

Perfect!

Fang Rui cheered. This sort of surprise almost made him cry out in excitement.

Team competition. On this stage, you were never alone. When you needed help the most, your teammate would always support you.

Boom boom boom.

Artillery shells blotted the sky. Amidst the flames, Boundless Sea swung his fists, Spiri

The swirling qi carried Boundless Sea as he shot forward.

His target, Dark Thunder!

To break through, Fang Rui chose his old partner. Familiarity was something both sides could use as weapons. Fang Rui felt like he had a better chance breaking through against Lin Jingyan than those two Strikers. Moreover, Su Mucheng was providing support towards this side, which came from Ye Xiu’s orders. It seemed like Ye Xiu had thought the same as him!

Dark Thunder backed away.

He dodged Dancing Rain’s artillery fire, while also getting out of the way of the spiralling qi. His retreat was straight as an arrow. He tried his hardest to maintain the distance between the two of them, refusing to let out an opening.

Tyranny had lost one point in the group arena because of him. He wasn’t going to give up another opening, not just for this match, but for this entire year, perhaps even for his entire life.

In this short moment, Lin Jingyan had completely forgotten his age. He completely forgot what would come next. He only knew that he needed to stop Fang Rui from escaping no matter what.

Right now, Dark Thunder wasn’t a character controlled by a faltering old general, but by a dazzling one. He was clearly just jumping backwards, but the rhythm he did it at felt smooth and easy.

Jump jump jump. He jumped backwards in a straight line. The Spiral Qi Rush tore through the air, but it was never able to reach Dark Thunder. This attack, supported by Dancing Rain’s artillery fire, was unexpectedly unable to dig out an opening from Lin Jingyan.

Fang Rui immediately wanted to attack again, but to his surprise, Lin Jingyan reacted far faster than he could. It was as if Lin Jingyan had been waiting for this moment.

Tiger Flips the Mountain!

Double Crescent!

Pain of Scars!

The outdated Demon Subduer three-hit combo once again shined brightly.

Boundless Sea was knocked backwards. Two injuries were torn out from Boundless Sea as the two crescents struck, leaving him bleeding.

Boundless Sea had been completely blocked.

Fang Rui was in a daze. He hadn’t thought that Lin Jingyan would be able to reach this step. He thought that he had understood Lin Jingyan well enough. He was sure that his Spiral Qi Rush would have been enough to break past Lin Jingyan’s limits and send him flying back or forcing him to the side.

But it wasn’t enough!

Lin Jingyan used the most direct method to dodge the Spiral Qi Rush, using that outdated combo of his to counterattack.

Fang Rui wanted to try break through by force, but in the end, Lin Jingyan had beaten him.

Fang Rui suddenly realized that perhaps he only understood a portion of Lin Jingyan. The signature technique of Lin Jingyan’s unexpectedly seemed so unfamiliar to him.

Chapter 1563 - Cleric Blockade

Boundless Sea fell, and in that instant, the sky and earth flipped for Fang Rui. All he could see was a flurry of fists and feet. Han Wenqing's Desert Dust and Song Qiying's River Sunset had chased after him and attacked ferociously!

His health dropped rapidly. Dancing Rain's artillery support wasn't enough to stop them. Tyranny's three Fighters attacked fiercely amidst the fire and smoke. White light continued to flash on top of them. Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock was going all-out to heal them. This was how Tyranny operated. Even the smallest thing wouldn't be missed by them. Their arrangements had multiple layers to them. Each and every member of Tyranny contributed towards the pressure on Happy, making their opponents appear weak and insignificant.

Tyranny was like an impregnable war machine, slowly crushing down on Happy. Scheme? Trap? Ambush?

None of those were important. Zhang Xinjie had always been considered incompatible with Tyranny's style, but once he began to truly integrate himself into Tyranny, people realized that it was as if the final piece of the puzzle had been placed down for Tyranny. The new Tyranny was both bold yet cautious, more reliable and stronger. Wasn't this the overwhelming power that Tyranny had always seeked?

Even the people watching felt a shudder. How could this sort of Tyranny be beaten? Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was just their first stepping stone. And then? Lord Grim? Dancing Rain? Or Soft Mist and Concealed Light who were on the verge of arriving?

Facing such a domineering Tyranny, Happy had unexpectedly chosen to go with a healer-less team composition?

The broadcast occasionally switched over to Soft Mist's and Concealed Light's direction. What these two did next would likely determine the outcome of this match.

Would these two rookies be enough to shake the domineering Tyranny?

Almost no one had any confidence in them, showing just how powerful Tyranny appeared to everyone. With such meticulous coordination and efficiency, an opening? No such thing!

"Stop!" A message suddenly popped up in Happy's chat from Ye Xiu. When Tang Rou and Luo Ji saw the message, they immediately stopped.

Were they giving up?

Was there no way for them to rescue this situation?

Was the miracle worker Ye Xiu also helpless today?

Tang Rou and Luo Ji had stopped. The situation couldn't be saved. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain suddenly shifted her target to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Dancing Rain focused on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to provide cover for Lord Grim to retreat.

Under the heavy gunfire, the light cover from Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms began to falter, and Lord Grim immediately seized this opening.　

Climb the wall?

No!

Lord Grim twisted around, and with a Shining Cut, he headed towards the battle between four Fighters on the other end. Ye Xiu was going in alone to save Fang Rui's Boundless Sea.　　

Happy hasn't given up? So why did Ye Xiu tell Tang Rou and Luo Ji to stop?

Everyone was at a loss, even the pro players watching couldn't understand.

Lord Grim moved like lightning, but he wasn't able to use the Shining Arc to make it all the way over, only two thirds of the way over. Suddenly, a figure flashed in front of him.

Ding!

A clash of weapons, and then white light flashed.

Immovable Rock!

The one blocking Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was unexpectedly Zhang Xinjie's Cleric, Immovable Rock. The Backlight Cross in his hands parried the incoming Shining Cut.

However, Clerics were lacking in Strength and wouldn't be looking for the stat in their equipment. Although they could also swing their weapons as a basic attack, due to their low Strength, it was very ineffective. Cleric basic attacks had no way to parry a Shining Cut, but Lord Grim had truly been stopped. The Shining Cut had somehow been knocked aside by Immovable Rock's cross.

Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock had equipment with Strength?

That was everyone's first thought, but everyone knew that it didn't really make any sense. Clerics weren't going to sacrifice other important stats just to buff their basic attacks.

Then what was the reason?

Everyone was doubtful. Then, they saw Immovable Rock continue moving. After blocking the Shining Cut, his cross swung towards Lord Grim. This seemingly decorative cross moved like a meteor in Immovable Rock's hands. White light rippled, once, twice, forcing Lord Grim back.

"This is... Crusader's Trials??" In the end, the Knight players amongst the pro player chat group recognized the skill.

"Your Clerics actually choose to use Crusader's Trials??" The player added. The player instinctively worded it as "your Clerics". He was Team 301's newly-transferred European player, Bai Shu. As someone in a different competitive scene, seeing something he had never seen before, he immediately thought that it was a China-specific strategy, hence the "your Clerics".

"Hah, what's special about that? It's pretty common here!" Royal Style's Lin Sen expressed.

"Yeah yeah!" The other players added with a sense of satisfaction. They felt like Zhang Xinjie was truly giving face to their country's Glory scene. Making this foreign player feel as if he was seeing a whole new world was too awesome of a feeling.

They forgot that Bai Shu had teammates too. Team 301's Yang Cong private messaged Bai Shu, telling him that the others were messing with him. It was their first time seeing Crusader's Trials on a Cleric too.

Crusader's Trials.

The Knight's Level 70 skill used basic attacks as the foundation. However, the priority of these basic attacks would naturally be much higher than usual. As the skill stacked up, the priority would only increase. Although the first strike had successfully interrupted Lord Grim's Shining Arc, it could be seen that because it was a Level 1 skill from a Cleric, it had only barely succeeded. If it had been a maxed Crusader's Trials from a true Knight, the first strike would have overwhelmed a skill like Shining Arc. The Assassin's Shining Arc was actually considered an attack with rather weak priority.

Immovable Rock's Crusader's Trials had only just barely been able to parry the Shining Arc, but he quickly followed up with successive trials. Ye Xiu clearly hadn't expected Zhang Xinjie's skill choice and was caught off guard. No matter how experienced he may be, he had never met a Cleric whacking him with a cross.

Because of this surprise, the slight pause was enough for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to catch up. Zhang Jiale was no longer spreading a cover of light. He was focusing on Lord Grim, who was now caught between a flurry of cross strikes and a barrage of bullets.

With this delay, the distance between Ye Xiu's Lord Grim and Boundless Sea had pulled away.

Ye Xiu perhaps felt it more clearer than anyone else how troublesome the current situation was. The battle strength that Tyranny displayed had surprised him. He hadn't thought that Tyranny would be able to find their rhythm in this life-and-death match.

The current Tyranny was no longer the Tyranny that Ye Xiu was familiar with. Tyranny had reached a new realm.

Ye Xiu could only tell Tang Rou and Luo Ji to stop. They had no way to break past Tyranny's wall at the moment, which was why he tried to scout them out himself, while seeing if he could help Fang Rui as well.　

In the end, nothing came out of it. Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock had blocked his way forward.

Crusader's Trials.

For a Cleric to choose this sort of skill, why? Was it in order to contest with the enemy for a short if the enemy closed in?

In any case, the Crusader's Trials had been very effective. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had just stepped on the gas pedal, but before he could even accelerate, he had to step on the brakes.

"Don't worry about me!"

Fang Rui typed out in the public chat.　　

The enemies had surrounded him, and since Tyranny was suppressing Happy, it wasn't hard for Tyranny to figure out what Happy wanted to do. For example, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim suddenly turning around. Zhang Xinjie immediately realized that Ye Xiu still wanted to save Boundless Sea, so he was able to react in time and block him.

If this sort of suppression could be utilized well, it was enough to decide the winner of the match.

Fang Rui's declaration was rather solemn.

He was Happy's left and right arm, but right now, it was as if he were poisoned. If this continued, the poison would likely spread to the entire body. If he was cut off promptly, although it would be a heavy blow to the team, it would not be fatal.

How this situation should be handled was a difficult problem, especially in such an important match.

It was difficult, and there was no time for any hesitation.　　

What would Ye Xiu do? Everyone was focused on Lord Grim. The broadcast felt like if they moved the camera even slightly away from him, the crowd would start cursing violently at them.

Lord Grim stepped forward and sword light flashed!

Sword Draw!

Ye Xiu hadn't given up. He still pressed forward. Clerics didn't have any close-range methods. Crusader's Trials was now on cooldown. Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock could only use his body to block. However, this sort of sacrifice was bearable.

Sword light struck Immovable Rock. Although he had also swung his cross, without help from a skill, it was practically ignored. Moreover, Sword Draw itself had high priority.

But this seemingly negligible resistance was able to provide an opportunity for Immovable Rock.

Immovable Rock wasn't pushed back as far as a result.　　

A beautiful bullet shot towards Lord Grim from behind. Zhang Xinjie had tanked the hit because he didn't want Lord Grim to get past him. Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was behind Lord Grim, carefully watching over him.

Hua!

Suddenly, at this moment, the umbrella unexpectedly opened while the sword was halfway pulled out. But the shield was only for a split second, as another sword light flashed out. Compared to the previous one, it was brighter and stronger.

Downwind Sword Slash!

A streak of blood flew into the air, and Immovable Rock was thrown to the side. Lord Grim had opened up a path!

Chapter 1564 - Magnetic Field Coil

Lord Grim swept past Immovable Rock. Zhang Xinjie saw it, but he had no way to stop him. However, from his angle, he was able to see Lord Grim pull something out from his folded umbrella.

What is that?　　

This sort of movement must be a skill, but what was it? The worst part about the unspecialized was that it was practically impossible to make any predictions on one.

"Careful!" Zhang Xinjie could only give out a vague warning, but with how little Tyranny communicated in the chat, it could be seen just how concerned Zhang Xinjie was. For him, the unknown was the most terrifying.

Tyranny couldn't ignore Ye Xiu. Even the inexperienced rookie, Song Qiying, had learned to never underestimate Ye Xiu. Facing him, anything could happen.

However, that didn't make Zhang Xinjie's warning meaningless. Tyranny's players knew very well that Zhang Xinjie wouldn't warn them simply as a reminder. If he spoke, it meant that something had happened already. It wasn't clear what that something was, but it was enough for them to be "careful".

Tyranny's three Strikers immediately looked towards Ye Xiu's Lord Grim after the warning.

Was an attacking coming?

This was the signal that they got from Zhang Xinjie's warning.　　

Sure enough!

Lord Grim had yet to close in, when he threw a grenade with his left hand.　　

The three were surprised.

If it was just a normal grenade, it wouldn't be hard to deal with. But for an unspecialized, it might not be a normal grenade. Was it a special grenade from a Spitfire skill? Such as an Implosion Grenade?

There was too little time for Tyranny to ponder over it. This would be a test of their eyesight. What did the grenade look like? If they couldn't tell, they wouldn't be able to respond.

"Norm"

A single word popped up in Tyranny's team chat. Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was being suppressed by Dancing Rain, but his eyes were mainly focused on Lord Grim. He was the farthest from that grenade, yet he was the first to deduce what the grenade was. He didn't put his years of experience as a Spitfire to shame.

Norm, a normal one.

It was a low-level grenade with no special effects.

No one doubted Zhang Jiale's judgement. Han Wenqing's Desert Dust stepped forward and used a High Kick.

Boom!　

An explosion occurred at his feet. Although it was the lowest-level grenade, the explosion would produce a small shockwave. However, by moving back as he retracted his kick at the right time, he was able to cancel out the impact.

Boom boom boom!　　

Ye Xiu wasn't so quick to give up. He fired three Anti-Tank Missiles from his umbrella. Since he hadn't yet closed in onto the three Fighters, he sent out long-ranged attacks.

The three Anti-Tank Missiles fired towards separate targets. As long as one of them failed to deal with their missile, Fang Rui would likely be able to escape. However, the three Fighters near Tyranny turned nearly in sync. Their formation hadn't been broken. It was as if none of them had even moved, yet all three Anti-Tank Missiles missed.

What else?

Tyranny hadn't relaxed yet. Lord Grim suddenly stepped to the side and fired a shot.

A Stun Bullet shot towards River Sunset. The sidestep wasn't without purpose either. With this step, River Sunset and Desert Dust were lined up. If River Sunset dodged this bullet, Desert Dust would need to dodge as well. However, Han Wenqing's line of sight would be blocked by River Sunset. It was rather similar to when Fang Rui surprise attacked at the beginning with a Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow.

Dodge!

One to the left, the other to the right!　　

River Sunset and Desert Dust seemed to swap places. The bullet seemed to pass right through them.

Dodged again!　　

Song Qiying had reacted fast, but what about Han Wenqing? Han Wenqing had relied on his experience and intuition. With Lord Grim's side-step, the three of them would be in a line. Hearing the gunshot, he quickly deduced that a bullet was heading towards him. He didn't need to see it. Song Qiying had gone left, so he went right. In this way, there wouldn't be any openings for Boundless Sea to take advantage of.

None of Ye Xiu's attacks were working, and Ye Xiu didn't have the time to stand around and keep trying. Zhang Jiale was being suppressed by Su Mucheng, but it wasn't a complete suppression. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was shuttling back and forth amidst the explosions, and all of his attacks were aimed towards Lord Grim.

There was also Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock. Clerics had ways to control a battlefield as well.

There was also the three Fighters surrounding Boundless Sea. Those three could turn on him at any moment. Coming to rescue Fang Rui but ending up trapped alongside him wasn't the outcome that Ye Xiu wanted to see.

That's all that can be done.

That was what everyone was thinking, including the pro players in the chat group.　

Happy was at a numbers disadvantage at the moment. Ye Xiu didn't dare let Lord Grim get too close, afraid that Tyranny would entrap him and Fang Rui together. He prioritized his own safety first. But with five enemies around him, how long could he stay safe? It was already quite impressive for him to be able to get out those three attacks.

Lord Grim turned around and rushed towards one of the canyon walls. His intention to climb up the wall and escape was clear as day. However, he hadn't completely given up on trying to rescue Fang Rui. A 1% chance was still better than none.

Bang!

Another gunshot. This time, it was a Floating Bullet. If the bullet hit, it would knock the target into the air and create an opening in Tyranny's encirclement.

Unfortunately, this attack had missed. River Sunset, who had been the target, sidestepped it.

"Out", the moment the gunshot rang, Ye Xiu typed out a message in the chat.

Out?

Were Tang Rou and Luo Ji going to start moving again?　　

Brief but imprecise messages were like torture towards the audience. Fortunately, the answer would soon be revealed. The person going out was Fang Rui. Boundless Sea immediately moved towards where River Sunset had originally been.

That was considered an opening?

Would he be able to break out?

It was just half a body length of distance. River Sunset needed only one step to get back to where he had been positioned originally and attack. Would Boundless Sea be able to break past this sort of defense from a Striker?

Fang Rui didn't seem to even consider it. Boundless Sea rushed forward and even attacked back, using what Strikers specialized in.

Front Kick.

A low-level Striker skill. Although in reality, even Strikers didn't like using this skill because this skill had a knockback effect. For Strikers who wanted to be as close as possible to their opponents, how could they want their target to be knocked back? Of course, it was occasionally useful when you were in a disadvantageous position and wanted to reset the field. As a result, this sort of skill wouldn't be completely tossed aside, although usually only a point or two would be put into it.

Fang Rui wanted to use this skill to create a path out for himself? And seeing Boundless Sea's kick, it looked like he had only put in a point or two as well as a defensive skill.

Yet this Front Kick had unexpectedly landed on River Sunset. The viewers watched dumbstruck as River Sunset slid back. Boundless Sea didn't stop for even a moment, kicking as he moved. He had been struggling to get out for so long, and he was going to do it in this way?

How is that possible!

Everyone was doubtful. Whether it was dodging the Front Kick or stopping it, let along a pro player like Song Qiying, even an average player could do it. That was why no one had considered it an opening of any sort.　　

But Song Qiying, Han Wenqing's future successor, had actually been kicked away? Had he been distracted?

No!　　

Boundless Sea had escaped. The two old generals on Tyranny didn't have time to figure out the reason. They needed to rescue the situation. However, when the two raised their arms, everyone noticed that their movements seemed rather slow. Then, they saw that the two characters, no, three including Song Qiying's River Sunset, were being pulled in place by some sort of force.

"Magnetic Field Coil!!" In the end, the pro players figured it out first. This time, the answer came from Xiao Shiqing. This Mechanic was the first to see through the reason for their slowed movements. It was the Mechanic skill: Magnetic Field Coil.

Everyone immediately understood.

It wasn't that Song Qiying had reacted too slow or gotten distracted, but rather that Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had placed down a Magnetic Field Coil at an unknown time. When he yelled "Out", he had attacked in coordination with the Magnetic Field Coil. River Sunset had been affected by the skill and his movements were slowed. That was why he wasn't able to react properly to Boundless Sea's Front Kick. By the time he noticed it, Boundless Sea had already sent him flying back.

This was the limit to what Ye Xiu could do. He needed to prioritize his own safety. After that Floating Bullet, Lord Grim had gotten to the wall and started climbing.

They escaped. In the end, they were able to escape...

Just when everyone was thinking this, Han Wenqing's Desert Dust suddenly leapt into the air.

Magnetic Field Coil?

Magnetic Field Coil didn't completely seal a character's movement. The character would simply be heavier. And for Lord Grim to have Magnetic Field Coil, the skill could only be at level one. Its effects would be weak. If it hadn't caught them off guard, Fang Rui might not have been able to get past Song Qiying. Right now, Desert Dust was using an attack under the effects of Magnetic Field Coil, a Soaring Tiger.

It was a skill with powerful jump. It would be slower than usual due to the Magnetic Field Coil, but he would still be able to reach Boundless Sea.

Hit!

Tyranny's fans prayed, but in the end, it was off by a bit. It hadn't been easy for Fang Rui to get out, so he immediately activated Qi Flowing Cloud to increase his movement speed. Boundless Sea was currently running for his life. Desert Dust had been restricted by the Magnetic Field Coil. Although the effects were small, it still weakened the jump enough.

Just off by a bit!

Everyone felt regretful over it, when suddenly, Desert Dust dropped down.　

Thousand Ton Drop!

At the final moment, he cancelled the Soaring Tiger and switched skills.

Boom!

His legs touched the ground, shaking the earth with the force of a thousand tons. Under the effects of Magnetic Field Coil, the effects of Thousand Ton Drop were buffed. Boundless Sea had only been half a body length away from Desert Dust, and he was launched into the air from the impact.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Desert Dust rushed forward, his clothes fluttering in the wind. Fang Rui was still stabilizing his Boundless Sea, when the first punch struck.

Pu!

The punch had struck him squarely in the waist. Just when it seemed like Boundless Sea would be sent flying away, Desert Dust's other fist smashed downwards. With a bang, Boundless Sea crashed into the earth.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry, all of the attacks hit!　　

Han Wenqing was deal with the effects of the Magnetic Field Coil effectively. After the fourth strike, he was outside of its range. His attack speed immediately surged, and Boundless Sea was hit repeatedly. After being attacked by three Fighters for so long, Boundless Sea didn't have much health left. Qi Masters were a Cloth armor class. Their defense wasn't anything noteworthy.

Ye Xiu? Lord Grim was up on the wall, unable to help.

Su Mucheng? Even though she had the high grounds, it was too difficult to expect her to cover everything. It wasn't only a matter of stopping Han Wenqing. Lin Jingyan and Song Qiying were also rushing towards Boundless Sea.

After ten minutes and forty-two seconds, Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was killed.

Chapter 1565 - A Poor Performance

The cheers were thunderous.

No matter how low Soft Mist’s health may be, she wasn’t dead. This sort of lead felt unstable. No matter how dire Boundless Sea’s circumstances may be, if he wasn’t dead, circumstances could always change.

But now, they could finally be at ease.

Boundless Sea was dead. His name had turned gray. He had already left the match. Tyranny had won a one point lead.

In terms of overall points, it seemed to be even. However, a one point lead in the team competition also meant a numbers advantage. The point wasn’t the most significant part. This lead would tip the balance of the team competition.

Tyranny’s stadium resounded with an ocean of cheers. Even the Li Yibo began livening up and started shouting rapidly…

Happy’s side was silent.

Facing Tyranny, they had never felt like they had the upper hand. And now, their team was down a member, a key member like Fang Rui too.

The Happy fans sitting in the away team seats fell silent. The people sitting at Happy’s bench like Chen Guo were silent as well.

The match would stop for no one though.

Boundless Sea was killed. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had climbed up to the top of the canyon wall and began coordinating a pincer attack with Su Mucheng again. This time, Tyranny no longer dodged as cautiously as before, instead pushing forward swiftly and resolutely. Fortunately, Tang Rou and Luo Ji had received Ye Xiu’s message and retreated beforehand. However, from the looks of it, Happy was in disarray, and the attacks from Lord Grim and Dancing Rain didn’t seem to pose much of a threat to Tyranny. Their attacks didn’t seem as focused as before. It looked as if the two were just casually throwing out a few attacks here and there.

“Don’t panic. We’ll take our time,” Ye Xiu’s comforting words were plain and simple. For the Happy fans watching, not only did it not put their hearts at ease, it made them feel as if Ye Xiu’s confidence and fighting spirit were waning.

But soon, message after message jumped out in the chat.

These weren’t words of comfort or encouragement, but instructions.

The match wasn’t over yet!

Ye Xiu gave out clear orders, showing his belief in his team.

Fang Rui could also see these messages, but he no longer had the ability to carry them out anymore.

What was I able to do?

Fang Rui couldn’t help but ask himself.

He had come to Team Happy as an All-Star player and held the highest salary in the team. Even if he wasn’t the main pillar, he could still be considered a core member of the team.

This was how the public saw him as, and Fang Rui believed it as well. Happy’s team competition lineup always included himself, Su Mucheng, and Ye Xiu, the three All-Stars as the core. Their positions in the team competition were unshakeable.

And how had he performed?

His class change was indeed a big uncertain factor, but many of his high points this season had been a result of his class change catching his opponents off guard.

The class change wasn’t an excuse. Fang Rui was very clear on this point because the more he played the Qi Master, the better he got. He didn’t feel like the class was hindering him in any way.

Was this the best he could do?

In the playoffs, Happy had fought against Blue Rain and now, Tyranny. Although he was a core member of Happy, he had never been the deciding factor in their wins. Wei Chen and Luo Ji, the two players with the fewest appearances on stage, had been more important in the playoffs. The few times that they had appeared, they had contributed significantly to their wins.

And himself?

In the group arena, Tyranny had pulled back the lead through him. If not for that, Happy might have been able to go into the team competition with a two point lead.

In the team competition, he had unexpectedly been the first to be killed. His teammates had set things up well for him, but what was he able to do with it? A Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, and then? Fang Rui felt too ashamed to think of everything else that came afterwards. Even at the end, Ye Xiu had done his best to give him an opportunity to escape, and the outcome? Tyranny had caught him.

An unfavorable position? A numbers disadvantage?

Fang Rui didn’t want this sort of excuse. In Wei Chen’s game against Blue Rain and Luo Ji’s game against Tyranny, they had made decisive plays, pulling Happy back from a disadvantageous situation.

Yet he wasn’t able to do so!

Fang Rui felt ashamed. At the same time, he also kept watching the unfinished match attentively.

We have to win! I still want to play, play well…

Fang Rui mumbled to himself as he watched his teammates on the stage.

Back on the battlefield, Happy had regrouped under Ye Xiu’s orders. They clearly didn’t want to continue fighting with Tyranny here. They wanted to reset the battle and fight in a different place. During this gradual process, Happy’s players began to regain their calm. Even Ye Xiu had felt distressed over the loss of Fang Rui. He wasn’t nearly as calm as he appeared. The others were even more so. Luo Ji’s palms were covered in sweat. Although this was his second time in a playoffs match, this was his first time in a deciding game. The pressure for this match was different than before. And now, Luo Ji had become the biggest deciding factor for Happy’s win. Under this enormous pressure, he nearly fell behind twice while retreating with Tang Rou’s Soft Mist because he wasn’t able to keep up his movement pacing.

However, Ye Xiu’s step-by-step instructions that followed help Luo Ji calm down.

I can’t make a mistake! I definitely can’t.

Luo Ji was different from Fang Rui, who was unhappy with not being the deciding factor for their win. Luo Ji didn’t dare have any such hopes. Don’t make a mistake. That was all he wanted. It was his bottom line, and he felt that it could be done if he tried his hardest.

Luo Ji carried out Ye Xiu’s orders meticulously. Through this focused attention on these orders, Happy was able to recoup their morale.

Tyranny didn’t like for things to be this calm. They had wanted to strike when the iron was hot and chase after them, but they weren’t able to reach Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng above them. They hadn’t even seen the other members on Happy yet. Since it was a random map, everyone only had a rough understanding of the map. There was no way to get a grasp of the details before the team competition. The area that Tyranny was heading into was unknown territory. They had no way of predicting what Happy would do next.

They could only see that Happy had given up on this canyon region. Ahead was the exit to the canyon. The canyon walls sloped downwards until it was flat at the exit. Outside, to the left, was the spawn point at the left end of the map. To the right was the path to the Seven Color Springs at the center of the map. The two sides knew about these paths through the brief introduction to the map.

Left? Right? Or continue forward?

Tyranny didn’t make any decisions yet. When they reached the canyon exit, they needed to check for ambushes.

Chapter 1566 - Powerless Ambush

Tyranny slowed their steps as they approached the canyon exit. Up above, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was still harassing them. On the other hand, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had already disappeared. Had she gone over to the canyon exit in preparation to ambush them?

Tyranny was in the dark, but they had no intention of cowering. They simply slowed down, putting on a safer and more cautious attitude as they exited the canyon.

Left?

Right?

Each of the five members of Tyranny looked in a different direction as soon as they exited the canyon.

Both left and right!

Wyvern, Thunder Eagle, Spirit Cat, Frost Wolf.

Two above, two below hiding to the left and right of the exit. Concealed Light had summoned his four beasts and had them lie in wait for Tyranny to come. As soon as Tyranny rushed out, before the summons moved, a cannon shot could be heard. Dancing Rain, who had rushed down from the canyon wall ahead of time, also came to the exit to set up an ambush. When she saw Tyranny, she immediately attacked.

Artillery shells and the four beasts flew towards Tyranny. At the same time, a Devil’s World Flower appeared in the center of Tyranny’s formation.

Boom boom!

Explosions sounded, not just once either. Dancing Rain’s artillery fire had arrived. However, a grenade had also been thrown by Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. At the same time, three fists swung towards the Devil World Flower. The poor Devil World Flower had only dug halfway out from the ground, its petals still unfolding, when Tyranny instantly destroyed it.

Tyranny had been on guard against an ambush. Now that an ambush had come, they were ready. With one glance, they saw how the four beasts were arranged, as well as Dancing Rain’s position. The Devil World Flower had no chance to sneak attack them. Before it could even display its abilities, it was destroyed. Then, the entire team turned right and rushed out!

Tyranny ignored the wyvern and frost wolf to their left, as well as Dancing Rain firing from afar. All of them headed right towards the Thunder Eagle and Spirit Cat. Behind them was their Summoner, Concealed Light.

From rushing out of the canyon, examining their situation, dodging the cannonfire, killing the Devil World Flower, and rushing towards the right, all of it had taken place in less than a second. Let alone being shaken by the ambush, Tyranny didn’t even let their opponents take the initiative. Not even a second had passed, and their counterattack had begun. Their entire focus was on Concealed Light. In an instant, Happy seemed to be in a dire situation.

Thunder Eagle?

Spirit Cat?

Tyranny wasn’t concerned with these two summons. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms attacked as he moved. The Thunder Eagle swayed unsteadily as it was shot. The Spirit Cat moved about nimbly like a shadow, but in the next second, an imprint of a punch appeared on the shadow. The Spirit Cat was knocked several steps back before rolling on the ground and disappearing.

Emperor’s Fist!

It was a high-level Striker skill, instantly killing the Spirit Cat.

Who had used it?

Everyone thought that it was Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust, but when they saw who it was, they realized that it had come from Song Qiying’s River Sunset.

“Beautiful!”

Han Wenqing praised. Desert Dust charged forward.

In the blink of an eye, Tyranny had eliminated the two summons. Luo Ji’s only choice was to retreat, and Concealed Light was already backing away.

This was Happy’s ambush?

This obviously couldn’t be all. Soft Mist had been healed to full health by An Wenyi. With her spear raised, she rushed out towards Tyranny from behind Concealed Light.

Even so, no one thought that anything would change.

The terrain surrounding the canyon exit was rather simple. There was no way to set up any elaborate ambushes. All anyone could do was make the first move when the enemy side rushed out.

This sort of ambush couldn’t threaten Tyranny. Happy wasn’t able to establish any sort of advantage with their initiation, and in the blink of an eye, Tyranny had turned it around on them. Of the five creatures summoned by Concealed Light, only three were left. He wasn’t even able to use Elemental Beast King Formation before his summons died. The long-ranged Dancing Rain had no way to stop Tyranny either. All Tang Rou’s Soft Mist could do was protect Luo Ji for a bit. How could she contend against the entirety of Tyranny alone?

As for Ye Xiu?

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was hopping down from the canyon wall. His rapid descent looked imposing, but how could he be the meteor that wiped out the dinosaurs?

Even so, Tyranny paid the most attention to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. The approaching Soft Mist could easily be held off.

Brick!

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder lifted his hands and threw a Brick towards Lord Grim.

Hua! The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up, blocking the Brick. But Han Wenqing used Ye Xiu’s dead angle from opening the umbrella to close in and let out a punch.

“It’s a counterattack!!” Zhang Xinjie warned. Previously, when Ye Xiu had broken past him to rescue Fang Rui, Zhang Xinjie had been paying close attention to him. In the end, he hadn’t noticed the Magnetic Field Coil being placed down either. When he thought back, the scene of Lord Grim fishing something out from his umbrella might have been Lord Grim placing down the Magnetic Field Coil.

Unfortunately, he hadn’t been able the call back then. However, experience was accumulated bit by bit. Zhang Xinjie was already aware that to call out Ye Xiu’s moves might be impossible with only one person. Not only did his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella making things complicated by opening up such a wide range of skills, Ye Xiu could also use it to hide his character’s movements.

As a result, when Lord Grim jumped down from the canyon wall, Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock had moved to a different angle to observe Lord Grim’s movements. When the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened, Immovable Rock moved to Lord Grim’s side. He saw that after the umbrella opened, the canvas separated from the umbrella rod.

The canvas was a shield. In the other hand was something else, but either way, it was a common move from Knights.

Through his different viewpoint, Zhang Xinjie was able to immediately determine what skill Lord Grim would likely use.

Maelstrom Counterattack!

It was a skill where the shield absorbed a blow, while the other hand counterattacked. When the Knight awakening skill, Knight’s Spirit, was used, the skill transformed into Honest Maelstrom Counterattack, reflecting the damage back fully.

Lord Grim couldn’t learn Knight’s Spirit. His Maelstrom Counterattack was only level one, so the reflected damage was rather limited. But the damage was secondary. This sort of counterattack was enough to disrupt Tyranny’s current formation and tempo.

Luckily, Zhang Xinjie had noticed it and promptly gave out a warning. Desert Dust immediately stopped his punch and jumped out of the way.

For Maelstrom Counterattack to work, the opponent had to attack first. It couldn’t be used as a standalone attack. The previous second, Tyranny had been lying in wait for Lord Grim. The next second, Lord Grim had become nothing but air to them. Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan went to help River Sunset take down Soft Mist.

By now, Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossom had killed off the Thunder Eagle. He turned fire, keeping the Frost Wolf and Wyvern at bay. The health of summoned creatures wasn’t nearly as precious as a player’s. Oftentimes, sacrificing some health to attack was okay. However, Spitfire attacks didn’t only deal damage. The vast majority of their bullets had special effects. By using these additional effects, blocking off two summons wasn’t anything difficult for Zhang Jiale.

The situation was completely under Tyranny’s control. Lord Grim’s descent became rather embarrassing. Lord Grim had indeed prepared a Maelstrom Counterattack. Ye Xiu had predicted that Tyranny would focus him. As soon as he came down, he would certainly be attacked, so use a Maelstrom Counterattack to scatter them. That was Ye Xiu’s plan.

But this time, Zhang Xinjie had seen through it. Tyranny had completely avoided him. His Maelstrom Counterattack immediately became worthless.

Ye Xiu wasn’t able to see Tyranny’s team chat, but seeing how Tyranny had seen through his plan, trying to make his plan work would be a waste of time.

Charge!

Ye Xiu cancelled Maelstrom Counterattack. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella form didn’t change forms. He used another Knight skill to make his way towards them.

But Tyranny had seen through it once again. Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan had only pretended to go attack Soft Mist. In reality, their attention had been on Lord Grim. They weren’t surprised by Ye Xiu’s quick decision to give up on the Maelstrom Counterattack.

Desert Dust twisted his body and swung his arm.

Collapsing Fist!

Directly towards the incoming Lord Grim.

Chapter 1567 - Push and Pull

Desert Dust’s fist struck Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. These two rivals of ten years would always clash against each other, neither one backing down.

Lord Grim’s Charge was stopped, while Desert Dust stumbled back. The Knight’s Charge had slightly higher priority than Collapsing Fist. With this advantage, getting past Desert Dust was an easy matter. The problem was that Han Wenqing wasn’t the only person that Ye Xiu needed to get past.

Tiger Flips the Mountain!

Ye Xiu had opened a path past Desert Dust, but Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder blocked it with a Tiger Flips the Mountain. Ye Xiu had no way to advance and could only retreat.

During this time, Han Wenqing was able to stabilize his Desert Dust. Dark Thunder’s Tiger Flips the Mountain had missed, so he quickly followed it with his own attack.

Launching Kick!

Desert Dust flew threw the air with a kick.

If it was a 1v1, Launching Kick was a very punishable attack. However, Han Wenqing had an experienced helper, Lin Jingyan, by his side, who would patch up any openings.

Ye Xiu could only have Lord Grim jump back again. He unsheathed a sword from his umbrella, sending out a Sword Draw.

Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan were in a 2v1 situation, and they didn’t hesitate to take advantage of it. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder put up his arms, tanking the Sword Draw. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust rushed out again. Lord Grim raised his sword, following with an Earthquake Sword.

Ye Xiu had slashed horizontally and vertically with these two low-level skills, mimicking the Berserker’s Gore Cross. The Sword Draw was blocked by Lin Jingyan. The Earthquake Sword seized this small gap. Han Wenqing had rushed out too quickly and had no time to react to it. The Earthquake Sword swept him up along with the earth.

Ye Xiu didn’t dare continue fighting. He immediately used a Shadow Clone Technique, his two hands quickly forming the seals. Dark Thunder closed in and swiped his claws at him, but he was too slow. Lord Grim’s shadow clone disappeared into smoke as the real body moved away safely.

Turn around, Falling Flower Palm!

Lord Grim attacked again, coordinating with Soft Mist.

Tang Rou had been blocked by Song Qiying. At the moment, their fight was even. But Lord Grim’s sudden appearance caught Song Qiying off guard. With a “pa!”, Song Qiying’s River Sunset was sent flying towards Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock.

Each and every detail on the battlefield had been considered by Ye Xiu. Although his Maelstrom Counterattack had been seen through, his following attacks had given Tyranny quite some trouble.

Immovable Rock dodged River Sunset, but Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain decided that it was time to give him special care and coordinated with Lord Grim’s Falling Flower Palm. Dancing Rain had fired a Satellite Beam right where Immovable Rock had dodged to. In an instant, Immovable Rock was swallowed by the light.

The damage dealt by Satellite Beam wasn’t low, but it was as if it hadn’t affected Tyranny in the slightest. River Sunset ignored it. Immovable Rock ignored it.

After destroying Lord Grim’s shadow clone, Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder gave chase, throwing out a Paralysis Needle.

As for Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust. The Earthquake Sword had knocked him back, but by twisting his body, he was able to spring off the wave of earth. Desert Dust rolled and then sprinted forward. In the blink of an eye, he had closed the distance. In contrast, Soft Mist’s spear seemed dull and slow.

Punch!

His fists moved like a blur as they twinkled with light.

Bang, bang, bang, bang. Lord Grim and Soft Mist were both hit by the flurry of punches.

Striker Level 75 skill, Light Speed Punch.

The speed of light was just a description. It wasn’t so fast that it couldn’t blocked. However, the attack came out far faster than most other skills. The afterimages formed from the skill were rather deceiving as a result.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist were knocked back. The Tyranny crowd erupted into cheers.

They were beaten!

The viewers all thought the same, but not Han Wenqing. The two looked as if they had been sent flying, but in reality, both of them had jumped back. To put it more precisely, the Light Speed Punch had landed as they jumped back, making them lose their balance.

A loss of balance wouldn’t pose a problem for those two just based on the fact that they had been able to react so quickly and jump back.

Attack!

Continue attacking. Don’t give the enemy any room to breath.

Han Wenqing thought to himself. Desert Dust had already charged forward, but he hadn’t expected them to counterattack before even steadying themselves.

Cloud Whirling Storm!

Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had been able to sneak in a high-level skill. Soft Mist didn’t know what she would need to do to balance herself when she landed. It was very easy to mess up one’s rhythm when attacking under these circumstances. Usually, most players would use a quick low-level skill to defend themselves, but she unexpectedly decided to use a high-level skill instead.

Magic danced around her spear and then burst out.

This is Cloud Whirling Storm?

Dark Thunder immediately stopped. Lin Jingyan had originally thought that he had enough space to circle around it, but when the Cloud Whirling Storm burst forth, the range of the magic AoE was far greater than he had expected. It moved extremely irregularly too, so he had no way to predict where it would move to.

What is this?

The camera switched over to Soft Mist’s perspective. She had used the skill while adjusting her balance. Because of her multitasking, her control over the Cloud Whirling Storm was rather messy, but this messiness was what made it unpredictable.

Lin Jingyan was gloomy. He knew that the Paralysis Needle he had thrown struck his target. Lord Grim wasn’t moving, no? It was because the moment that he had jumped back, the Paralysis Needle had hit him, putting him in a Paralyzed state.

If they could catch and kill him, their victory would be certain!

Lin Jingyan grit his teeth. Dark Thunder immediately activated Reinforced Iron Bones and charged into the Cloud Whirling Storm.

The magic assaulted Dark Thunder, crackling as it burned away his health.

But with his Super Armor, Dark Thunder was able to quickly move through it.

Powerful Knee Strike!

Dark Thunder immediately leapt towards Lord Grim, who had yet to land on the ground.

Bang!

He had only made it halfway through before hitting a target. A Spirit Cat pounced into the air, intercepting Dark Thunder.

The Spirit Cat’s had lower priority than Dark Thunder’s Powerful Knee Strike, but it could still take the hit in place of someone else. Dark Thunder landed on the ground, while the Spirit Cat rolled to the side. It was then quickly killed, leaving behind a piece of scorched earth. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had cleared away the summons behind him by now and had shifted his attention to this side. But just when he turned around, Concealed Light resummoned his dead beasts. As a result, Han Wenqing quickly went to finish off the Spirit Cat blocking Dark Thunder.

The Elemental Beast King Formation created through the four beasts was nothing to be scoffed at. As a result, when facing a Four Beast style Summoner, killing off one of the beasts to prevent it from coming into play was very crucial.

The Spirit Cat was instantly killed. The newly-summoned Thunder Eagle, Wyvern, and Frost Wolf continued to harass their enemies fearlessly.

“Ye Xiu!!” Lin Jingyan shouted in the chat.

There was no time to lose! Tyranny was about to attack Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, when they saw a bright light shine on top of Lord Grim before dissipating.

Lord Grim landed on the ground and rolled. A black shadow slithered from his sleeves, Shadow Cloak!

Everyone on Tyranny was experienced enough to recognize that bright light.

Purify, a Paladin skill that dispelled debuffs and status effects from the target’s body. Happy’s healer, An Wenyi, had chosen it to put on his Little Cold Hand’s weapon.

It was a level one Purify, and could only remove one status effect. However, Lord Grim only had one status effect on him, Paralysis. After being Purified, he could immediately move normally again. He Quick Recovered and used Shadow Cloak. Tyranny was able to react in time though, if not, Lord Grim would have been able to catch all of them.

The initiative was still held by Tyranny though. After dodging the Shadow Cloak, Tyranny immediately pushed forward again.

Happy pulled back.

Lord Grim and Soft Mist coordinated with Concealed Light’s summons, protecting Concealed Light and Little Cold Hands, attacking and retreating. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain wandered around on the edges of the battlefield, harassing and disrupting Tyranny’s offensive maneuvers.

But Tyranny continued to push forward.

Although it was a 5v5 again, Tyranny still had a sixth player that could be subbed in. They had the numbers advantage, which allowed them to be bolder and make aggressive moves.

Bold and aggressive was exactly what Tyranny was best at. Their offense was relentless. Happy was unable to escape from it. They could only face it, fighting while retreating.

Wave after wave of cheers came from Tyranny’s fans. As long as Tyranny kept up this pressure, it seemed as if Tyranny’s victory would only be a matter of time.

However, Tyranny’s players weren’t celebrating yet. They didn’t dare get careless.

“Careful.” Zhang Xinjie typed into the team chat. In his eyes, although Happy was retreating, they weren’t retreating because they had no other choice. Their control over their tempo was quite firm. The direction of their retreat was within their grasp.

Happy was waiting for an opportunity to counterattack. Zhang Xinjie was certain of it. Did that mean this opportunity was lying in wait in the direction that they were retreating towards.

That area was the center of the map, the Seven Color Springs. It was an area that Tyranny had never ventured into. Was there a feature in that area that could be taken advantage of by Happy?

Was it another area that could collapse?

Seeing Concealed Light now and then recalling how Happy had only now come together as five after so long, Zhang Xinjie couldn’t help but think of this possibility.

Chapter 1568 - Switch

Who should we send to scout out the terrain?

This was Zhang Xinjie's first thought, but he quickly dispelled it. On paper, Tyranny should be stronger than Happy, but if one of their members left to scout their surroundings, it would be a 4v5. Right now, Happy was on the defensive. A 4v5 under these circumstances wouldn't be too big of an issue, but circumstances could change. If it became a 4v5, Happy would certainly turn on them and attack. Ye Xiu wasn't someone who would just stay idle at such a prime opportunity.

We can't send someone out to scout ahead. We can only see what we can do given our present situation.

Does Luo Ji really have that sort of talent?

When, Zhang Xinjie's gaze shifted towards Concealed Light, he couldn't help but think of this question. The vast majority of people considered Luo Ji's talent at "seeing through the terrain with a single glance" was a bluff and couldn't be believed. But it wasn't as if it was impossible. For someone like Zhang Xinjie, it would constantly weigh on his mind. He even guessed that this might have been Happy's goal, but there was nothing he could do about it. He wasn't paranoid about it or anything. He would simply take it into account when he made his plans.

The terrain collapsing was only one of many possibilities. It might not be the case. Perhaps it might just be that the terrain gave Happy certain advantages that they could use against Tyranny.　

Be more cautious and continue with their pursuit?

It would be a perfectly good option under normal circumstances, but what if it was a trap?

In the end, the safest option seemed to be to shy away from Happy's preferred route.　

Zhang Xinjie concluded after careful consideration.

Increase our aggression!

He gave out an order to Tyranny.

Han Wenqing was the first to understand his intentions. He was also the first to carry out the order.

Desert Dust had just forced Soft Mist back. With a step forward, he followed up with a kick.

Soft Mist blocked the kick with her spear. To Desert Dust's side, Lord Grim sneakily sent out a Circle Swing.

Cloud Body, Double Tiger Palm!

Desert Dust twisted his body, just barely dodging Lord Grim's umbrella. Then, he followed with a Double Tiger Palm, one palm towards Lord Grim, and the other towards Soft Mist.

Lord Grim jumped back and dodged it. Soft Mist sidestepped it and then slid forward, stabbing towards Desert Dust with a Dragon Tooth.

Han Wenqing didn't dodge or block it, striking back with a Straight Punch. Desert Dust avoided the Dragon Tooth using the dash provided by the skill, while simultaneously throwing a punch towards Lord Grim.

But as Lord Grim jumped back, Ye Xiu counterattacked, using a Dragon Tooth as well. The Dragon Tooth collided with Desert Dust's Straight Punch. Both sides trembled from the impact. Neither skill trumped the other, an even match.

The words "increase our aggression" wasn't a buff. It didn't mean the team's battle strength would suddenly rise to another level. To be more aggressive, the players needed to make adjustments to the tempo of the match.

To put it simply, it was to shift the balance between offense and defense towards offense. In other words, sacrifice defense for offense.

The outcome would be more aggressive exchanges. When one would normally choose to dodge or defend, one would instead continue to attack. Taking more damage didn't matter.　

Desert Dust's Straight Punch didn't seem to embody this philosophy, but Han Wenqing had made his decisions with it in mind. The main purpose of the Straight Punch had been to deal damage to Lord Grim, dodging Soft Mist's Dragon Tooth was simply in the passing. It could be seen as a reflection of Han Wenqing's many years of experience. Even if attacking was his priority, it was best to minimize the damage.

Soft Mist's Dragon Tooth had missed, but Han Wenqing wouldn't be able to dodge her next attacks. Soft Mist followed with a Double Stab, both strikes hitting Desert Dust. At the same time, a grenade appeared in front of her face. With a boom, Soft Mist was thrown to the side. Soft Mist immediately rolled to reduce the impact. Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder was rushing towards her, when a black shadow cut him off. Concealed Light's Spirit Cat pounced towards Dark Thunder.

The team competition was closely linked together. As soon as Han Wenqing became more aggressive, the rest of the team followed. In response to Tyranny's sudden aggression, Happy immediately responded with a tighter defense.

Zhang Xinjie immediately became even busier. Not only did he need to carefully survey the situation, these intense trades were a test for healers. As the team's biggest support, if the healer wasn't able to keep up, Happy would likely take advantage of it and find an opening.

Small Heal, Great Cure, Focus, God's Protection, Spirit Enlightenment, Sacred Fire...

White glow poured out from Immovable Rock's Backlight Cross. Glory's number one healer was number one for a reason. Despite such a complex and chaotic battle taking place, his Cleric was the most eye-catching one. When measuring a Cleric's performance, the easiest way to do so was to look at the health on the respective teams. At the moment, the health on Tyranny's five members were lined up together, bouncing up and down like a song.

As for the musician?

Immovable Rock was given a close-up along with the movement of the health bars. His movements weren't nearly as graceful as the health bars. Immovable Rock was traveling back and forth amidst artillery fire, his originally spotless robe had turned into a mess.

How could Happy not have noticed Tyranny's increased aggression?　

Interfering with the healer was the counter to aggressive trades.

Happy was aware of this point, but Tyranny was aware of it too. As a result, close-ranged fighters like Soft Mist weren't able to even get close to Immovable Rock.

However, Soft Mist was Happy's easiest member to block. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain wandered around the edges of the battlefield. Tyranny's three Fighters couldn't touch her. Only Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms could fire back but the threat he posed to her was extremely limited. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had consumed an enormous amount of mana setting up light covers in the previous fights. Right now, he needed to play more conservatively. He couldn't maintain a cover of light, and in terms of attack range, Spitfires lost to Launchers.

Su Mucheng wasn't the only one Zhang Jiale needed to deal with either. The Wyvern and Frost Eagle summoned by Concealed Light were flying beasts. The three Fighters naturally had a much harder time against these summons compared to a long-ranged gunner like him. As a result, Zhang Jiale needed to keep both Dancing Rain and Concealed Light busy.

Finally, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was the most annoying and most nauseating enemy. Lord Grim was both a close-ranged and a long-ranged threat. If you focused on him, he was like a general with a hundred tricks up his sleeves. If you ignored him, he would take any chance he could get to attack Immovable Rock and interrupt his healing.

There were numerous forces trying to disrupt Immovable Rock, trying to destroy Tyranny's aggression and force Tyranny into defense. During the most critical moments, Tyranny's vice-captain would keep ordering for Tyranny to maintain the same tempo.

"Keep up the aggression!"

"Keep up the aggression!"

Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie would say the same thing.

As a result, Tyranny continued to attack and put pressure on Happy, minimizing their protection over Zhang Xinjie to restrict Happy's freedom. Tyranny was able to keep up this tempo going, but Zhang Xinjie needed to deal with the attacks coming towards him on his own.

Dodge and tank. Immovable Rock dealt with the attacks this way, while preserving his healing. The difficult situations that he faced along with the harmonious healing that he produced were two intense opposites, making it even more clear just how skilled Zhang Xinjie was.

Attack while ignoring defense!　　

For defense, the others on Tyranny would be relying on Zhang Xinjie!　　

How could this sort of Tyranny lose?

Tyranny had won. Happy had no way to deal with Zhang Xinjie. This was what countless people thought. Tyranny's fans had already started shouting victory cries. The threat of the Seven Color Springs? Could Happy even hold on until then? Even if they could, how many of them would be left?

What else can Happy do?

The pro players in the chat group were discussing this question.

When they watched matches, they would pretend that they were the ones playing the match. If they were winning, how could they widen the lead? If they were losing, how could they bring it back?

The chat group became a war room. People would put in their thoughts, while others would argue against it. Their words were like a simulation of the battle.

"It's time to go all in," Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi said.

He was referring to Happy, of course. If Tyranny kept this up without making a mistake, they would win. Happy needed to do something to save themselves.

Everyone knew that interrupting Zhang Xinjie was key. From the looks of it, disrupting Zhang Xinjie was the only way to affect Tyranny significantly.

But doing so wasn't easy. Happy had interrupted Zhang Xinjie's healing here and there, but it wasn't enough. Once or twice would throw off Tyranny's rhythm. Right now, Happy needed to completely suppress Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock to turn around the situation.

Attack!　　

Forcing their way through was Happy's last remaining option.　　

Their focus would need to be Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock!

Who would initiate it? The pro players paid attention to this question. They didn't believe that Happy would just sit there and watch Tyranny defeat them. Happy would certainly struggle. Even if they lost in the end, they wouldn't go down without a fight.　

Soft Mist!

The camera suddenly shifted over to Soft Mist.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Magic gathered at the tip of her spear. Soft Mist raised her weapon, ready to charge through.

Was she planning on breaking past the surrounding enemies to open up a path? However, Tyranny reacted promptly. River Sunset, Emperor's Fist!　　

Spear versus fist!

The clash between the two rookies continued. Dragon Breaks the Ranks was slightly stronger than Emperor's Fist, but not to the point of completely overwhelming the opponent. River Sunset staggered back, but Soft Mist's momentum had been stopped completely.　

A figure dashed for the opening created from River Sunset's stumble.　　

Lord Grim! Shining Cut! An arc of light flashed across the field. Suddenly, an arm reached towards him from the side.

Tiger Flips the Mountain!

A Brawler mid-level skill, strong enough to block the Shining Cut. Ye Xiu had wanted to seize this opening to break through Tyranny's defenses, but who knew how many people were carefully watching over his every move.

Lord Grim immediately stopped.

Lin Jingyan had done his best to time the Tiger Flips the Mountain so that Ye Xiu wouldn't be able to dodge it, but he hadn't thought that Ye Xiu could suddenly stop moving. Had he predicted he would be intercepted?

Lin Jingyan could not wait for Ye Xiu to make his next move. If he saw the move and then countered, Ye Xiu would act before he did. As a result, he decided to take the initiative.

Turn, Double Crescent Fang!

He swung his arms in an arc, his claws slicing at all possible openings.　

What could he do?

Lin Jingyan looked at Lord Grim and saw his hands moving.　　

Ninjutsu - Shadow Clone Technique.

It was Shadow Clone Technique again. But isn't it a bit far? If Tyranny wasn't even on guard against this move from Ye Xiu, then their years of experience were a waste. They couldn't guarantee that Lord Grim wouldn't use Shadow Clone Technique, after all, the hand seals to form it were extremely quick. Ninja seals could be done whenever he wanted to. It was difficult to interrupt it. They couldn't stop him from using Shadow Clone Technique, they could at least prevent it from being an effective tool.

The shadow clone was destroyed by Dark Thunder, while the real body teleported elsewhere. However, Lord Grim was still a distance of three body lengths away from Immovable Rock. That was the limit of Shadow Clone Technique. Afterwards, he saw a grenade fall one body length away from Immovable Rock.

Does he have a way to get in front of the grenade?

Flickering Stab?

They had seen Ye Xiu use it in the group arena against Han Wenqing, so they knew that Lord Grim had this skill in his arsenal. However, Flickering Stab would only move him one unit forward. He was two units away from the grenade though, so it wouldn't be able to get him where he wanted.

Ye Xiu had no way to get past the grenade in time. The grenade exploded, Implosion Grenade! The powerful shockwave sent Lord Grim flying back to where he came from. But before he reached his destination, a figure jumped out to receive Lord Grim.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry!

Han Wenqing directly used a high-level skill. Desert Dust began his dangerous dance in the air. Lord Grim also answered back though, fighting until they reached the ground. But under the pressure from Ferocious Tiger Flurry, Lord Grim could only retreat. Han Wenqing focused his attention here, ignoring everything else. For such a huge threat like Ye Xiu, having someone specifically on guard against him was completely reasonable.

Su Mucheng's long-ranged support? She was too far. She couldn't put enough pressure onto Zhang Xinjie. Su Mucheng had tried to push forward to pressure him harder and get Immovable Rock into her firing line to completely suppress his healing. But at that distance, Dancing Rain became well into Dazzling Hundred Blossom's range. Under the threat of a Spitfire's numerous special bullets, how could she set up her firing line?

Mounted Gun!

Su Mucheng activated another high-level skill. However, many of the pro players saw this move and had their doubts. It was true that while under Mounted Gun's effects, she couldn't be interrupted. The problem was that it also restricted her movements. Her goal was to attack Immovable Rock, not to win over Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. Immovable Rocks could simply move away, and Dancing Rain couldn't follow. Mounted Gun? What use was that? She wasn't fighting with Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Zhang Xinjie did as everyone expected him to. As soon as he saw Dancing Rain use Mounted Gun, he immediately moved away. But after only a few steps, the ground in front of him suddenly lit up. Magic began to flow. It was a summoning formation.

The pro players' eyes lit up!

So Happy's had made arrangements here?

Dancing Rain had forced Immovable Rock into the jaws of the beast?

The camera shifted over to Concealed Light. They saw him stick close to a wall, trying to make himself invisible as he waved his staff.

In reality, none of Tyranny had overlooked him. You could see it simply by noticing that Concealed Light had never able to get his four summons to gather together. Tyranny had been on guard against his most threatening move, Elemental Beast King Formation, the entire time!

The present situation showed this. There were three summons: Frost Eagle, Wyvern, Spirit Cat, all surrounding Dark Thunder. Otherwise, Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder would have rushed forward to take out Concealed Light or Little Cold Hands. These two characters had constantly been under Happy's protection, but now that Happy had begun going on the offense, they didn't have time to take care of them.

Lin Jingyan's Dark Thunder had leapt into the air to swipe his claws at the Thunder Eagle. Fighting with summons was treating the symptoms but not the cause. Lin Jingyan wanted to quickly break away from these three summons to directly attack the summoner. However, just when he swiped his claws, the Thunder Eagle turned into a bolt of lightning and disappeared.

Hit?

Lin Jingyan knew that he hadn't. This only happened when the summon was killed, or when the summon was resummoned!

Lin Jingyan heard an eagle cry and turned to look over. A new Thunder Eagle had flown out from the summoning circle in front of Immovable Rock. With a thunderclap, it dove towards Immovable Rock.

Immovable Rock dodged, but a second summoning circle had appeared next to him.

The Wyvern and Spirit Cat next to Dark Thunder immediately rushed towards Immovable Rock.

Lin Jingyan had no one on him now, but his heart began to drop. Two of the summons were moving towards there, and over there was a new Thunder Eagle and and a Frost Wolf. All four beasts were on the verge of gathering together!

He had to stop one of them no matter what.

Dark Thunder twisted his body to attack, but the Spirit Cat was too nimble and dodged it. Lin Jingyan didn't try again. The Spirit Cat was the hardest of the four to hit. He tapped lightly on his keyboard and Dark Thunder leapt into the air. He stretched out his hand, grabbing the tail of the Wyvern.

His two hands pulled!

Fling!

The Wyvern was thrown as far away as possible, and then Powerful Knee Strike!

Dark Thunder rushed towards Concealed Light. Killing the Wyvern wouldn't solve the problem. Throwing it far away was the smartest choice.

The Frost Wolf walked out from the summoning circle. As for Immovable Rock? The Backlight Cross in his hands glowed as he fought against the Frost Wolf. Crusader's Trials. The skill he had brought into the match was being used again to contend with the Frost Wolf.

A third summoning circle appeared. Luo Ji was preparing to re-summon a Wyvern, but Dark Thunder had already closed in. He raised his hands and threw a Brick.

A figure flashed by, blocking it.

An Wenyi had used Little Cold Hands to body block the Brick, preventing Concealed Light's summon from being interrupted.

The Wyvern would be summoned again, but... he'd better not think of trying to use Elemental Beast King Formation. There was more than enough time for Dark Thunder to reach Concealed Light.

Little Cold Hands?

With a Slap, he swatted him aside.

The healer was always the focal point in a team competition, yet Lin Jingyan had ignored him. Concealed Light, only Concealed Light had the power for Happy to make a comeback!

Four Elemental Beast King...

Concealed Light shook his wand. The four beasts seemed to hear the owner's command and began to circulate their elemental power. The four elements gathered together, but before the spell could be completed, the summoning circle shtattered.

Interrupted!

A Strangle. Dark Thunder held Concealed Light by the throat. He was pinned against the wall, unable to continue casting.

It's over...

The pro player chat group fell silent. It wasn't to say that they wanted Happy to win, but rather that they had hoped for more twists and turns in the match.　　

It was true that Immovable Rock had four summons surrounding him, but he was able to use Crusader's Trials to protect himself for a bit. Then, he used Angel's Wings to float into the air, greatly reducing the threat from the Frost Wolf and Spirit Cat. Zhang Jiale's Dazzling Hundred Blossoms also provided some support, shooting Ice Bullets at the Fire Wyvern, dealing bonus damage. Killing it would take a blink of an eye.

Summons without the Summoner controlling them was easy for pro players to deal with. As a result, the pro players no longer considered them as threats. After Zhang Xinjie's Immovable Rock used Angel's Wings and received help from his teammates, he was safe again.

Victory was certain.

Even the pro player chat group were sure of it as well. The camera had switched to Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were already giving him a eulogy as if the match was over.

"Ye Xiu built the team up from scratch, ravaging through the Challenger League, slaughtering their way through the playoffs, playing three close games against Tyranny. These accomplishments could be already considered a miracle," Pan Lin said.　　

"Yes, even if Happy doesn't end up making it into the finals and winning the championships, their achievements are unprecedented in the history of Glory. With the Alliance continuing to develop, I doubt that anyone else would be able to ever do better. Once again, Ye Xiu has made history," Li Yibo said.

"And the team that he formed has endless potential. We've seen just how extraordinary each of their members are. They still have a lot of room to grow," Pan Lin said.

"Honorable even in defeat."

"Honorable even in defeat."

The two finished and observed a moment of silence. Desert Dust was swinging his fist towards Lord Grim.

If this punch killed Lord Grim, then it would be timed perfectly with their ending words. Pan Lin and Li Yibo couldn't help but think this thought. When they looked, Lord Grim had quite a lot of health left. The two sighed helplessly.

In reality, let alone killing instantly, landing the blow wasn't likely. However, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim's hands didn't open up to block the strike.

Han Wenqing was startled. Such an egregious mistake shouldn't happen on Ye Xiu, no? He suddenly felt uneasy.

Hit!

Lord Grim seemed to shatter into pieces. At the same time, the sound of a cat crying could be heard. The black Spirit Cat was sent flying by Desert Dust's punch.

What happened? Everyone saw it clearly: Lord Grim had turned into a Spirit Cat?

Glory didn't have transformation skills. There was only one other possibility.

Summoner skill: Switch.

"THE FUCK?!"

"The Spirit Cat had been summoned by fucking Lord Grim?!" The pro player chat group went into an uproar.　

Lord Grim appeared behind Immovable Rock.

"Angel's Wing! The light has blinded you!" Ye Xiu exclaimed.

Assassin skill: Life-Risking Strike.

"How the fuck, where'd that come from!!!"

"He has two Night Walker weapon forms? I thought he already used both Night Walker skills!!" The pro player chat group was in an uproar again.

Chapter 1569 - Life-Risking Strike

Everything was a mess.

The broadcast team was in chaos. Pan Lin and Li Yibo had just been lamenting over Ye Xiu’s accomplishments. Then, they watched as their grieved person turned into a Spirit Cat.

“Angel’s Wing! The light has blinded you!” Ye Xiu had already started his taunts. The broadcast hadn’t been able to catch that Switch. When they hastily switched over to Immovable Rock, Lord Grim had already jumped into the air, slashing towards Immovable Rock’s back with a Life-Risking Strike.

The pro player chat group was in chaos too. Too many things had happened all at once. Even they didn’t know where to start. The biggest question right now: where did that Life-Risking Stike come from?

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had a total of 12 forms, giving Lord Grim a total of 12 high-level skills excluding class advancement and awakening ones. Every match with Ye Xiu turned into a sort of guessing game in the Glory community to which 12 skills he possessed. These 12 skills would occasionally be revealed during a match. After all, there was a purpose to every skill choice. The skill would be used if it could help him win.

What about today’s match? Those playing the guessing game were naturally keeping track of which skills had been used, and the pro players loved to play this game.

Heroic Leap, Poison Needle, Underground Tunneling Technique, Flickering Stab, Wind Wave Sword, Magnetic Field Coil, Maelstrom Counterattack.

Everyone had been counting. He had also just summoned a Spirit Cat and used Switch, making it a total of 9 out of 12 skills revealed.

Life-Risking Strike seemed to be one, but it didn’t make sense. Everyone knew what forms the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could transform into. Three Priest forms, two Mage forms, two Fighter forms, two Swordmaster forms, two Night Walker forms, and one Gunner form, a total of twelve.

In today’s match, he had already used two Night Walker skills, Underground Tunneling Technique and Flickering Stab.

He only had two Night Walker weapon forms, so how could he have a third Night Walker skill like Life-Risking Strike?

There was a thirteenth weapon form?

It was everyone’s first thought, but when they took a closer look, everyone coughed blood.

Myriad Manifestations Umbrella? Lord Grim had put it away in his inventory. Lord Grim was currently holding a Dagger.

He had switched weapons…

For Gunners, switching weapons was called Dual Gun Style. For Swordmasters, switching weapons was called Dual Sword Style, and so on and so forth. They could all be collectively referred to as Weapon Switching Style.

Unspecialized… to use skills from different classes, they needed to equip different class weapons to fight. They were the biggest proponent of this Weapon Switching Style. The reason why other classes would choose to use a Weapon Switching Style was to make their movesets more flexible. On the other hand, unspecialized players chose to switch weapons out of helplessness. If they didn’t, there was no way for them to play. As a result, among the classes that could employ a Weapon Switching Style, unspecialized players actually hated it the most.

For unspecialized players, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Ye Xiu’s hands was their biggest dream. It was a weapon that could transform into twelve different weapon forms. It would let them say bye-bye to the Weapon Switching Style.

However, despite already having a weapon with 12 different forms, Lord Grim unexpectedly carried a 12th one so that he could switch weapons. No one knew what to say.

The pro players instantly began to curse at him, showing off their hand speed.

As for the live crowd? Because of the projection technology, the live crowd hadn’t missed it just because the broadcast had. They had seen Desert Dust strike the SPirit Cat, while Lord Grim appeared where the Spirit Cat had originally been.

Life-Risking Strike!

Blood for blood, life for life.

The damage dealt by the skill depended on the user’s health. The proportion between damage dealt and health burned was determined by the level of the skill.

Lord Grim had added it to his weapon as a bonus skill, so it could only be level one. The amount of damage it dealt was limited.

Was this strike enough to instant kill Immovable Rock? No one bothered to make calculations because the answer would soon be revealed.

The ones in the most chaos were Tyranny’s players. This change had been too sudden. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred BLossoms was currently attacking Dancing Rain. Song Qiying’s River Sunset was in an intense fight with Tang Rou’s Soft Mist. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder was trying to eliminate the threat of Happy’s Summoner. In that instant, their backs had been facing there. They didn’t know about what had just happened.

Up until Ye Xiu’s taunting. Han Wenqing typed.

“Healer”

When Desert Dust struck the Spirit Cat, he immediately sent out a warning. He hadn’t panicked. He had commanded the team as the captain for ten years. Giving out clear orders was instinct to him.

Others might have warned with a “Switch”.

But that was too vague. Switch? Switch to where?

Even if Tyranny’s players were experienced, if they saw this instruction, they wouldn’t have thought of the Summoner’s Switch skill.

The word Switch had multiple meanings. Giving this sort of order would only confuse the team even further.

But Han Wenqing wouldn’t make this sort of mistake.

The Switch had happened already. The players fighting didn’t need anyone to explain what was going on in the battlefield. What they needed to know was what the next step should be and how they should take it.

“Healer”

A single clear word!

On the other hand, Ye Xiu’s taunting was eight words along with two exclamation marks.

There were many players who talked trash, but there were very few who let their trash talking get in the way of their playing. Everyone knew what the priority was.

While Han Wenqing had hastily warned his team using just a single word, Ye Xiu took his time to type out his message. Just from this comparison, it could be seen which side was in a more dire situation.

Tyranny’s three players turned to look. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms even fired towards there as he did so. With hundreds of matches of experience, he had unconsciously noticed how abnormal Han Wenqing’s sudden warning had been.

By the time they turned their heads to look, all they saw was Lord Grim with his dagger pierced through Immovable Rock’s heart. Immovable Rock hadn’t turned to look. He was holding his Backlight Cross, about to cast an Instant Heal on himself.

But it was too late.

Dead.

When he saw his rapidly dropping health bar, Zhang Xinjie knew it already.

He had guessed that it was a Life-Risking Strike. And right now, only Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had the ability to use this skill.

Everyone else was waiting to see the outcome of this strike, but Zhang Xinjie? He was very confident in Ye Xiu. For him to use as risky of a move as Life-Risking Strike, he was certain that Ye Xiu had calculated it. This strike wouldn’t give him any opportunity to turn things around. One hit certain death, OHKO.

The glow from Backlight Cross receded.

The Angel’s Wings lost its luster and then shattered.

Immovable Rock plunged towards the ground, his name had turned gray.

31 minutes 58 seconds. Team Tyranny had lost Zhang Xinjie, their healer.

Apart from Han Wenqing, the other Tyranny members didn’t know how it had happened, including Zhang Xinjie.

All they saw was Lord Grim next to the dead Immovable Rock, as well as the dagger in Lord Grim’s hands.

Life-Risking Strike!

It had to be Life-Risking Strike. There was no other skill that had such explosive burst.

If it was Life-Risking Strike, then you die too!

Having lost their healer, Tyranny needed to kill Ye Xiu, and the opportunity was right there.

After Life-Risking Strike, he wouldn’t be able to get healed for a certain amount of time.

For a level one Life-Risking Strike, the proportion between health burned and damage dealt couldn’t be high. Thus, Lord Grim’ had burned away nearly all his health, leaving him with only 7% left.

With 7% health left, a group attack would instantly kill him.

But Tyranny couldn’t be happy just yet. Of their four attackers, three of them were close-ranged and quite far from Lord Grim. Song Qiying and Tang Rou were fighting against each other. The two were interlocked, unable to escape from each other. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was free to move around, but he was the farthest away. By the time he reached there, who knew if Ye Xiu would still be around.

In order to eliminate the threat of Ye Xiu from the rest of the team, Han Wenqing had tried his best to push Lord Grim as far away from them as possible. But with this Switch, Lord Grim instantly returned back to where he was. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was now all alone. For a moment, he would have no impact on the battle. He had originally been the clearest on Tyranny about the situation and the first to react. But because of how far away he was, and because he was a Striker, all he could do was type… type!!!!!

There was no need for him to type anymore. Everyone on Tyranny knew what to do. Desert Dust rushed back. Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder left Concealed Light to attack Lord Grim. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms continued to attack. He had always been the biggest threat towards Ye Xiu, but right now, he wasn’t able to do what he wanted. As soon as he turned, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain immediately multiplied the pressure onto him.

Burst!

Before Zhang Jiale could send out a burst of attacks, Su Mucheng acted first. She went all out, using everything she had, turning the surroundings into scorched earth. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was in the middle of the storm, taking a huge chunk of damage. As for Lord Grim? That Frost Wolf was running towards him, becoming Lord Grim’s protection. The three summons that had previously been attacking Immovable Rock were still alive!

Chapter 1570 - : Substitute Attack with Defense

The Frost Wolf blocked Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s attack, while the other summons surrounded Lord Grim in a defensive formation. As for Ye Xiu, he was perfectly fine with that and hid behind the summons.

At the same time, a summoning circle quietly began to form. But Dark Thunder, who was rushing towards Lord Grim, suddenly counterattacked and threw a Brick towards Concealed Light.

His Dark Thunder had Luo Ji’s Concealed Light completely suppressed previously so that he wouldn’t be able to summon any more creatures. However, there was no such thing as interrupting a Summoner from commanding his summons. Under these circumstances, most Summoners would instruct their summons to rescue them, but Luo Ji did not. His summons had continued to surround Immovable Rock, and then after the Life-Risking Strike, they stayed to protect Lord Grim.

As for himself?

He did his best to dodge Dark Thunder’s attacks. If he couldn’t dodge them… then he relied on Little Cold Hands.

White light constantly shined on Concealed Light, healing him. With a healer protecting him, a single character alone would find it difficult to kill him.

Lin Jingyan knew that if he could keep both Concealed Light and Little Cold Hands preoccupied that was the best scenario. However, although Luo Ji and An Wenyi were rookies, they weren’t stupid. Even when the others on Happy were protecting them, they never stood together to prevent Tyranny from hitting two birds with one stone.

Even before, when An Wenyi had Little Cold Hands charge out to block a hit for Concealed Light, he had kept a certain distance from him.

The two from Happy were always on guard against the best case scenario that Lin Jingyan had been hoping for.

As a result, when Lin Jingyan saw the situation change, he had Dark Thunder turn his attention to Lord Grim. Of course, once he turned away, Luo Ji would definitely make a move, so as soon as he saw the summoning circle begin to form, he immediately threw a Brick at him. At the same time, he turned around and rushed back.

Luo Ji had previously been completely suppressed by him. Was there a need for him to attack in such a roundabout way? Of course not!

Lin Jingyan was scheming. He wanted to use this Brick to lure An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands into blocking it. He had calculated the distance. This time, if Little Cold Hands rushed back and he caught them off guard, he would definitely be able to keep both of them suppressed.

Right now, Tyranny was temporarily in a 4v5 situation. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust needed time to get back as well. There was no one watching over An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands. Having complete freedom, An Wenyi’s healing abilities were comparable to Zhang Xinjie’s. If you looked at Happy’s health, their health bars were even and stable.

Control the healer!

The pro players in the chat group began discussing again. Keeping the healer in check was probably more important than killing Lord Grim. If the healer was kept under control, even if Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was able to hang on past the no-healing period after Life-Risking Strike, he would continue to be in danger because the healer couldn’t heal him. It was two birds with one stone.

No one realized this point. At first, the pro players were puzzled by Lin Jingyan’s actions. It wasn’t until Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder rushed back did they understand his intentions.

It wasn’t that Tyranny didn’t understand the situation they were in. However, the experience Lin Jingyan was ambitious. He wanted to suppress both Luo Ji’s Concealed Light and An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands simultaneously.

After turning back, Lin Jingyan saw Dark Thunder’s Brick strike Concealed Light’s head.

The summoning was interrupted, but Little Cold Hands didn’t come in to block it like he had expected.

Had he been seen through?

Lin Jingyan didn’t care for the answer. It was just like how the pro players analyzed it. Keeping Happy’s healer in check was the most important. Little Cold Hands didn’t have anyone protecting him right now. It was a rare opportunity. If he couldn’t bait him into it, then he would have to make his way over himself.

Dark Thunder rushed towards Little Cold Hands.

His bait seemed to have been a waste of time, but Lin Jingyan didn’t think so. Happy’s main healing target was Lord Grim, but for a period of time, Lord Grim couldn’t be healed. As long as he could suppress Little Cold Hands during this period of time, everything would be fine. That slight delay wouldn’t affect anything.

Suppress Little Cold Hands and Lord Grim would certainly die.

That was what everyone thought.

But despite having such a pitiful amount of health left, Lord Grim unexpectedly assume an aggressive posture.

With Lord Grim following behind, the Frost Wolf, Wyvern, and Frost Eagle charged at Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

This wasn’t a protection, but a screen. Dancing Rain coordinated with Lord Grim and bombarded Dazzling Hundred Blossoms with artillery shells.

Is he looking to die!!!

Everyone had the same thought.

With only 7% of his health left, not only did Lord Grim not run away, he was sending himself right to their door. If this wasn’t suicide, what was it?

But the opinions and emojis that filled the pro player chat group showed that they didn’t think Ye Xiu was looking to kill himself.

If you counted carefully.

1, 2, 3!

Zhang Jiale was being attacked on three sides, a 1v3.

Ignore everything else and kill Lord Grim?

Many people thought it was the right decision. The opponent had less health, so just finish it off.

The problem was that for a Spitfire, ignoring everything else couldn’t be done. Spitfires didn’t have any Super Armor skills. All attacks would affect them. If his gun was knocked to the side, his bullets would likely miss. If his hands were knocked askew, the grenades that he threw wouldn’t go where he wanted them to go.

Lord Grim still had 7% of his health left. One or two attacks wouldn’t do it. If Zhang Jiale wanted to kill him under these circumstances, he needed to maintain a certain level of attack efficiency.

The pro players all agreed that this would clearly be a huge test for Zhang Jiale.

Zhang Jiale also understood this point.

The Wyvern spat out a fireball, while the Thunder Eagle fired a bolt of lightning towards him. He was immediately facing attacks from all directions. The Frost Wolf roared and charged at him, its frost breath spread out to obscure his vision.

Chance!

Zhang Jiale saw an opening to attack Lord Grim. He rolled, while throwing a Grenade. Compared to shooting, grenades had AoE damage. Even if his aim was slightly off, the AoE might hit Lord Grim. It was more likely for the grenade to deal damage compared to his bullets.

Bang! A gunshot. Just when he threw the grenade, it exploded. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had fired a shot.

Ye Xiu wasn’t the one being protected. He was one of the attackers!

Zhang Jiale was under attack from all sides, making it difficult for him to aim properly. In comparison, Lord Grim had it easy.

The best defense is a good offense. Happy was using this adage to suppress Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, who was trying to kill Lord Grim.

Chapter 1571 - Who Will Break the Deadlock

No one had expected the situation to turn out this way. Everyone had thought that Lord Grim would be running for his life. Everyone had been wondering whether Lord Grim would end up dying or living. But now? The one who needed to worry about dying or living was Zhang Jiale and his Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

It was a pincer attack. Just splitting your attention between two ends was a headache already. Even if pro players practiced for these situations, that didn’t mean defending against a pincer attack was by all means easy.

Kill Lord Grim?

As time went on, Zhang Jiale felt more and more that his priority should be his own survival instead. If he tried to kill Lord Grim in this situation, Dazzling Hundred Blossom would lose health at a frightening speed, and his attacks towards Lord Grim wouldn’t be very effective either. He would mostly likely end up as the one dying.

Retreat?

It seemed to be the safe option. If Little Cold Hands was suppressed, they wouldn’t need to be in a hurry to kill Lord Grim, and Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust would soon arrive as well.

That’s what it looked like on the surface, but Zhang Jiale knew that this “safe” option was wishful thinking. As soon as the pressure that he put on Happy was put to a halt, Happy wouldn’t need to continue attacking because their goal would have been accomplished. In that case, Happy would certainly shift their attention towards Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder to rescue Little Cold Hands.

Once Little Cold Hands was safe, their advantage would be consolidated.

No matter how many twists and turns occurred in the team competition, attacking the healer would always be a good move. By pressuring Lord Grim with his attacks, Zhang Jiale became a chain preventing Happy from protecting their healer. From a certain perspective, it showed just how important Ye Xiu was to Happy.

Any other team would have likely abandoned one of their players to prioritize protecting their healer. Even if it ended up becoming a 4v5 later, having a healer while the other side didn’t meant that their chances of winning wouldn’t be low. This principle was backed by hard data. In all ten years of Glory pro play, this sort of 4 with healer versus 5 without healer situation had happened 101 times. In 74 of these 101 matches, the 4 with healer side won.

It had happened in Season 4, when Zhang Xinjie helped Han Wenqing topple Team Excellent Era’s reign. In Season 5 and Season 7, the God of Healing, Fang Shiqian helped Wang Jiexi lead Team Tiny Herb to two championship wins, giving birth to the saying “Whoever has the healer rules the world.”

The healer was immensely important to a team, and as a result, many strategies targeting healers had been created. During the regular season, Happy’s healer wasn’t looked upon highly, but Happy took advantage of this opinion, setting up traps around their healer. It was a classic example of using the value of a healer to one’s advantage.

Healers wouldn’t be sacrificed. Even if Happy was currently using Little Cold Hands to protect Lord Grim, as soon as the pressure on Lord Grim lessened, Happy would immediately turn fire.

As a result, he definitely could not back down.

It was a 1v3, but he had to fight it. Attack Lord Grim!

Zhang Jiale didn’t retreat. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms didn’t retreat.

Everyone could feel his determination and the meaning behind it. Happy wanted to force Zhang Jiale back and then save Little Cold Hands. It would be killing two birds with one stone. However, Zhang Jiale refused to back down.

If he didn’t back down, Happy could not turn fire. If they turned fire, an opening would appear, and Zhang Jiale would certainly take seize it to kill off the 7% health Lord Grim.

What now?

Happy’s one hit kill against Immovable Rock had been a miraculous play. And now? How would they get out of this impasse? Desert Dust was getting closer and closer. Farther away, Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees was also approaching.

Could he burst down Dazzling Hundred Blossoms before they arrived?

Unlikely!

Even if it was a 3v1, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim couldn’t play too boldly. After all, he only had a sliver of health left. He needed to attack cautiously with safety in mind. As for Concealed Light’s summons and Dancing Rain’s artillery fire, although their damage was impressive, it wouldn’t be enough to burst him down instantly. After all, Zhang Jiale wasn’t a dead tree.

Ye Xiu would most likely have to risk it, using his 7% health Lord Grim to get close to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

The camera had switched over to Lord Grim. Suddenly, light shone from beneath Little Cold Hands and Dark Thunder. A summoning circle had formed, turning the soil black. A Devil World’s Flower broke through the earth and bloomed!

Shua!

Vines immediately shot towards Dark Thunder’s feet. He had no choice but to dodge them. If he didn’t, he would be CCed, and it was exactly because Devil World Flower had outstanding crowd control that every Summoner would learn it. Whenever anyone faced against a Summoner, killing it was their first priority.

Luo Ji’s presence was too tiny. No one had thought that he would be the one to break the impasse.

With the interference from Devil World Flower, Dark Thunder’s attacks towards Little Cold Hands immediately stopped. An Wenyi seized this opportunity to get Little Cold Hands away from him. But Lin Jingyan was old and experienced. He continued to keep pressure onto Little Cold Hands while inside the Devil World Flower’s range. The difference was that his pressure was considerably lower than before. However, with this reduction in pressure, An Wenyi was more than capable enough to escape. It was just a matter of time.

Luo Ji seemed to have gotten the sweet taste of success. Concealed Light waved his staff again, and another summoning circle began to form. Summoners had the advantage of using summons to fight for them, allowing them to fight in multiple places at once. Luo Ji was putting this advantage to use.

The summoning circle quickly completed. The summon clearly wasn’t a high-level one.

Goblin.

The Summoner’s lowest-level skill. But since it was a prerequisite for many other skills, every Summoner could summon one. This extremely weak summon very rarely posed a threat on the battlefield. It was usually used as a sacrifice.

But for Lin Jingyan, who was urgently trying to keep pressure onto Little Cold Hands, this Goblin was extremely annoying.

No matter how weak it was, the Goblin could still attack. To dodge the attack or get rid of the Goblin, Dark Thunder would have to perform an action. Whatever this action was would be an opening for An Wenyi.

The Goblin hobbled its way over and threw a rock as if it were throwing a difficult problem towards Lin Jingyan.

At the same time, Lin Jingyan saw a third summoning circle…

Luo Ji’s Concealed Light played the Four Beast Style, so the number of beasts he could control well at one time was around four or five. However, that didn’t mean his Concealed Light only had those four beasts and a Devil World Flower.

Hua… a Death Knight walked out from the summoning circle. It was the core of a different Summoner style, so for a Four Beast style Summoner, it could only play a small role. As a result, it was a very rare choice, after all, the skill points needed to learn Death Knight was rather high.

But… skill points happened to be the area where Happy was number one in…

Chapter 1572 - Like a Dream

The shadow created by the overtowering Death Knight covered the entirety of Dark Thunder. The Death Knight lifted his enormous rusty sword and swung downwards.

Dodge. Lin Jingyan’s only choice was to dodge. The Death Knight wasn’t a Goblin. If that strike hit, it wouldn’t be just a small impact, it would likely knock him down.

Devil World Flower, Goblin, Death Knight.

The three summons by themselves weren’t enough of a threat to make Lin Jingyan helpless, but completely suppressing An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands under these circumstances wasn’t likely. Lin Jingyan would probably be able to interrupt longer casts, but Clerics had access to three instant cast heals: Small, Great, and Holy Cure. Knowing that Lord Grim would need to be healed after using Life-Risking Strike, An Wenyi had intentionally saved these skills for him.

Happy had stabilized the situation!

Everyone realized this point, and the one who helped Happy stabilize it was Luo Ji. This inexperienced rookie had shined brightly in both team competitions against Tyranny.

Last time, it had been through his outrageous Dismantle style. And this time? He had done it by putting to use one of the most fundamental characterstics of a Summoner.

Luo Ji’s hands were shaking. He could sense his hurried breathing. More than thirty minutes had passed since the start of the match, and he was still nervous. However, his thoughts were exceptionally clear. His hands may be trembling uncontrollably, but he did what he had to do bit by bit.

He didn’t even know himself how much of an impact his actions would have on the battle, but he kept telling himself that he needed to succeed. He needed to do the only thing that he could do: not make any mistakes!

Everything he did turned into a reality, and it showed.

He didn’t overlook a single detail. He was playing perfectly. It wasn’t easy for him to control six summons split between two different areas, but fortunately, his summons didn’t need to fight too precisely.

If this continued, Happy would win!

That was what the pro player chat group thought. Luo Ji had no one on him. He had complete freedom in the battlefield. For Tyranny, who needed to focus on Lord Grim, Luo Ji had become their greatest hindrance.

Was Tyranny going to lose because of this rookie?

Luo Ji had been the decisive factor in both the team competitions that he had participated in.

Lose?

No!

Not yet!

Han Wenqing and his Desert Dust had arrived! For a Striker, he had initially been relatively far away from the battle, but he had finally returned. He had no one on him either. Didn’t that mean he could go directly for Lord Grim? Or he could fend off Dancing Rain and the summons to let Dazzling Hundred Blossoms finish off Lord Grim. Or he could help Dark Thunder shut down Little Cold Hands.

Han Wenqing had several options, but at this moment, Zhang Jiale suddenly noticed Luo Ji casting something. It wasn’t a summon, but a spell.

What was it?

For a moment, Zhang Jiale couldn’t think of anything. However, his many years of experience was giving him feeling of danger. He could sense that if he didn’t interrupt Concealed Light, things might truly be over for Tyranny.

Bang bang bang!

Ignoring everything else around him, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fired three shots at Concealed Light. The Frost Wolf immediately pounced on him and knocked him to the ground.

It’ll reach! Zhang Jiale was still looking towards Concealed LIght. He saw Concealed Light’s staff glowing with magic, but it wasn’t yet complete. It was a spell with a very long casting time. His three bullets would make it in time.

But suddenly, a figure suddenly flashed into Zhang Jiale’s view. Peng peng peng, the three bullets bounced off that shameless Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

With only 4% of his health left, Lord Grim rushed into protect Concealed Light. Who would have thought?

The gathered magic burst out!

Concealed Light was able to cast his spell. Zhang Jiale could feel a biting chill. It was as if the spell had penetrated through to reality.

Absolute Zero!

Not towards him, but Desert Dust. The Elementalist Level 75 skill had completely frozen Desert Dust, who was perhaps Tyranny’s hope for a reversal.

This was the skill that Luo Ji had chosen to put on his weapon, a powerful CC skill. With no one interfering with him, using a long-casting skill was naturally a suitable choice. But in the end, he had underestimated his opponents. He hadn’t thought that Zhang Jiale would unexpectedly be able to notice it and even try to interrupt it. He had thought that with the enormous pressure on Zhang Jiale right now, he would be the last one to make a move against him.

The moment Dazzling Hundred Blossoms attacked him, his heart had turned cold. He had almost cancelled the skill, but at the last moment, Lord Grim appeared in front of him and blocked the attacks. Luo Ji had seen this sort of protection from Ye Xiu many times on the bench, and this time, he was the one being protected.

Absolute Zero was unleashed.

At this moment, Luo Ji suddenly had absolute confidence in winning because he knew that he wasn’t as insignificant as he had thought. Everything he had done had influenced the battle.

Hit!

Due to Ye Xiu blocking Zhang Jiale’s attempt to interrupt Luo Ji, Han Wenqing took the brunt of the after effects. By the time he saw the Absolute Zero come out, it was too late for him to dodge. This skill created a new dimension, instantly affecting all those within its range. Desert Dust was instantly frozen, and once again, he wouldn’t be able to participate in the battle for some time.

The freeze time was rather limited though, since it was only a level one skill without Ice Elemental Affinity to buff the Absolute Zero’s effects, but in a situation where every second counted, it was enough to be a deciding factor. If not for this Absolute Zero, Desert Dust might be swinging his fist at Lord Grim. But right now, all hope was lost. An Wenyi didn’t drop the ball just because he was a rookie. The no-healing period of time after Life-Risking Strike had finally ended. He quickly seized the opportunity and cast a Holy Cure.

Light flashed, a crit.

Lord Grim’s health instantly shot up. It was now high enough to make the fans on Tyranny despair, even if they could see Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees approaching closer and closer.

His Sharpshooter would soon be able to provide support for Tyranny, but it was too late…

Ye Xiu had dared to body block attacks with only 4% of his health left. Now that he had received a critical Holy Cure, what wouldn’t he dare to do?

Target, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms!

Lord Grim instantly closed in. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had only just climbed back up onto his feet, and now he was trapped inside an unspecialized combo. To make things worse, there was Dancing Rain’s artillery barrage from behind, as well as attacks from the Wyvern and Thunder Eagle. In his attempts to finish off Lord Grim, he had lost a considerable amount of health. How much longer could he last?

Absolute Zero’s effects ended, and Desert Dust rushed out.

A crisp gunshot could be heard from the other end. Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees had finally arrived.

But Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was already at his last breath. Ye Xiu didn’t even need to waste time on him anymore. Lord Grim turned around and went directly for Desert Dust. Concealed Light’s Frost Wolf immediately took his place, and along with Dancing Rain’s artillery support, they finished off Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

It was a 5v4, and the side with 5 had the healer.

The Tyranny fans in the crowd were silent. The fans, who never became discouraged and never gave up, could already see their defeat.

Happy didn’t give Tyranny any opportunities to turn things around. With such control over the battle, a comeback from Tyranny would only happen if Happy made a disastrous mistake.

“Don’t relax!” Ye Xiu reminded everyone. Only now did the crowd realize that no one had said anything in chat for a very long time. Play after play had happened one after the other, yet during this time, there had been no communication on either team between any of the players.

Happy won!

This was the final outcome, yet no one had expected that after it became a 5v4, the match would take another half an hour to finish. Happy had relied on their healer advantage to win, sacrificing two of their players to take down the remaining four on Tyranny.

Happy clearly had control over the pace of the match, but Tyranny hadn’t crumbled as fast as people had imagined.

Only now did people realize how important his seemingly modest “Don’t relax” was.

Against a team like Tyranny, even if they were at such a huge disadvantage, if you relaxed for even a moment, it might come back to bite you.

Ye Xiu understood Tyranny too well. He knew how the team played, and he wouldn’t give Tyranny this kind of opportunity. He led Happy, keeping up the same level of determination and perseverance until the last second.

It was over…

Happy had officially won. With this team competition, they won this round and this best of three. Happy would move on to the finals.

The stadium was quiet.

Tyranny’s fans were silent. As for Happy’s fans? The last half-hour had been nerve wracking to watch too. Although Happy had the clear advantage, it always felt like Tyranny would suddenly turn things around. The match didn’t feel like it was over even when Happy stabilized their advantage. It wasn’t until Happy finally won did they begin to regain their composure.

The crowd continued to be silent even as the players exited from the player booths, even as the two teams lined up at the center of the stage, even as the screen displayed its congratulations to the winners.

Finally, reality hit.

Happy had won. They had started at the bottom of the Challenger League, and now they would be moving on to the highest stage in Glory. It was all like a dream.

Chapter 1573 - Their Own Roads

The simple celebration that Tyranny had set up in order to celebrate their own team making it to the finals ultimately couldn’t be used. On the display screen in the stadium, there was just a rather standard congratulations to the winning team.

The two teams lined up in the center of the stage.

Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale…

On this stage built from passion, these old generals met each other, knew each other, killed each other; some felt joy, others felt sadness, others felt moved.

Perhaps they couldn’t be called friends, but their mutual understanding was no inferior to that between any pair of closest friends. They had the same desires and the same goal. On this stage, they shed the same sweat, burned with the same passion.

But it was a shame, for not everyone could achieve the results they desired. Every time, there would always be those who had to leave the stage partway through.

It was over…

Han Wenqing looked at this familiar stage, at the silent stadium.

Another season was over. The tenth season of his professional career had come to an end.

Another failure.

Yes. In Han Wenqing’s heart, not obtaining the championship was a failure. “Glorious defeat” was not a phrase that he liked.

And this time, the one who had orchestrated his failure – Ye Xiu, Ye Xiu once again, although in the past he had been called Ye Qiu.

Han Wenqing did not care at all about why he had to change his name. No matter what it was changed to, he would always immediately recognize this person onstage. This was the person who had left him the most memories over his ten-year career, from start to finish, from happiness to tragedy.

And this time, this was the fourth time, the fourth time that Ye Xiu had brought him and his Tyranny to bitter defeat in the playoffs. But after it was over, the first word that Han Wenqing said to Ye Xiu was: “Congratulations.”

Congratulations, congratulating victory. His own grief was the other side’s joy. Competition was simply this cruel.

“Thank you,” Ye Xiu answered, and the two shook hands.

In the silent stadium, applause suddenly rose forth, applause that lasted for a long time This was truly a pair of opponents worthy of respect. Ten years of Glory, they continued to persevere. No matter what difficulties they faced, their pursuit of the championship never faltered.

But between the two of them, only one of them could remain. This was truly an incomparably saddening fact.

Tyranny’s fans disliked and even hated Ye Xiu, but in this moment, they couldn’t help but think: if Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing were on the same team, if they could lift that championship trophy together instead of constantly being at each other’s throats, then how wonderful would that be?

But these two players did not have such melancholy.

Countless cameras were focused on these two at this moment, desperately hoping that they would have some moving interaction, but there was none.

Congratulations, thanks, separation.

Never mind a hug or anything like that, when the two of them shook hands they hadn’t even lingered very long before separating. And then the two of them each turned away, walking toward their next goal…

The next person that Han Wenqing met was Su Mucheng. What about Ye Xiu? He saw Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale.

Normally, when the teams lined up to shake hands after a match, they would follow a certain order. The captain first, and then the vice-captain, continuing down from there.

Happy only had Ye Xiu as the captain, and no one set as the vice-captain, so they were a bit more casual in their lineup. On Tyranny’s side, vice-captain Zhang Xinjie’s presence was very strong, but right now, Zhang Xinjie hadn’t followed the typical order of shaking hands with Ye Xiu after Han Wenqing had. Instead, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale arrived at about the same time in front of Ye Xiu.

“An excellent match,” Lin Jingyan said, shaking hands with Ye Xiu first.

“Thank you.” Ye Xiu still only had this simple reply.

These two in front of him now hadn’t fought with him for ten years like Han Wenqing had, but they were perhaps more tragic than Han Wenqing.

The pair of Han Wenqing and Zhang Xinjie had at least defeated Ye Xiu in Season 4, overthrowing Excellent Era’s dynasty and obtaining a championship. With that, they had somewhat of a foundation, so that even if they did not manage to obtain any results for the rest of their careers, they would not be considered a total tragedy.

But Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale, these two Season 2 debuts, had fought for only one less year than Ye Xiu and Han Wenqing had. Yet they still were unable to obtain that championship.

Lin Jingyan, last season was the first time he had even made it to the finals; Zhang Jiale, the synonym of unlucky in Glory, four times in the finals, four times his hand brushed against that championship trophy, yet in the end he still had nothing to show for it. And this time, he hadn’t even had the chance to touch that trophy.

“Good luck,” Zhang Jiale said to Ye Xiu. At this moment, he would still think of that summer two years ago, when he and Ye Xiu, the two retired pro players, met in-game.

They had seemingly already said farewell to Glory, but their championship hearts refused to die, and in the end they chose different paths. Ye Xiu picked up a new account, trained it up through the game, recruited soldiers and bought equipment. He built his opportunity himself, built hope himself, and ultimately created a team. And Zhang Jiale, he chose an easier and more direct road, he returned and chose to join Tyranny, creating an incomparably beautiful roster with Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Xinjie.

Zhang Jiale wouldn’t forget that Ye Xiu, too, had given him an invitation at that time. If he had agreed, he would be a member of Happy right now.

But Zhang Jiale wouldn’t deny, either, that at that time he didn’t look favorably upon Ye Xiu’s starting over from scratch. At the time, he’d thought, Ye Xiu is someone who already holds three whole championships, maybe he would attach more importance to this more difficult path. But Zhang Jiale himself? All he wanted was to have a single championship trophy. No matter the method, he hoped that his professional career wouldn’t have this blank space.

The two walked their own paths in the pursuit of victory.

Ye Xiu and his Happy defeated Excellent Era in the Challenger League. Zhang Jiale and Tyranny together lost last year’s finals to Samsara.

Continue, again!

The two continued their pursuit. Ye Xiu broke through the Challenger League and arrived at the Pro Alliance, boldly carrying his Happy toward the championship. Zhang Jiale, with his Tyranny teammates, once again mounted a charge against the championship. In the end, the two teams met outside the doors to the finals, and in the end, Ye Xiu and his Happy won, while Zhang Jiale and Tyranny together fell at the doorway.

Did he regret it?

Did he regret rejecting Ye Xiu’s invitation to join Happy?

No, he didn’t.

If it were still the Zhang Jiale of two years past, after directly falling to Happy, he would probably be extremely upset about his decision. But the Zhang Jiale of today was not. He had walked together with Tyranny for two seasons now, had fought and killed together with these teammates for two years now. He still prioritized results, but he now deeply appreciated the process. These two years, he had experienced much, and his mentality had changed a lot as well.

Last season they’d had the chance to obtain a championship. This season, Happy had only taken the chance that they’d had last season. Even if Happy did ultimately manage to win the championship, Zhang Jiale would not have any regrets because of that. This Happy was this kind of Happy, and if he were there, it would be a different Happy.

Even if this kind of Happy could win the championship, that didn’t mean that a Happy with him could also win. There were no absolutes when it came to victory and defeat on the professional stage, and these kinds of regrets were completely unnecessary. This was what Zhang Jiale had learned over these past two years.

There were many roads to the championship.

Ye Xiu had chosen one, he had chosen another.

The road that Ye Xiu had chosen was filled with difficulties, so he hadn’t thought it would end well. And his own choice? He might have thought before that his choice was a shortcut, but now he understood that this absolutely wasn’t the case. There were no shortcuts to the championship. Those who thought that obtaining top-level players and top-level characters was enough to easily take the championship were far underestimating Glory and underestimating the nature of competition.

Zhang Jiale didn’t dare underestimate that, and so he would not regret his own choice. Refusing Ye Xiu’s invitation, joining Tyranny instead of returning to Hundred Blossoms, he regretted none of it.

Now, he gave his congratulations to the victor. He still needed to rely on himself to walk his own road.

Just like this, the four generals completed their post-match greetings. Simple, without any unnecessary words, just exchanging those plain, almost boring phrases.

But everyone who watched this scene already felt their hearts tightening.

Even if it was so simple, even if it was just these boring phrases, would they have the chance to ever hear this again?

The four of them were already at the final stages of their careers. Would they ever have this kind of chance again, to stand onstage and exchange congratulations and thanks?

Good luck, thank you.

To these people now, just these kinds of phrases were already such a luxury. Did they still have a tomorrow? How many more tomorrows did they have? Everyone was left with only restlessness in their hearts.

“An extremely interesting performance.” After the three old generals, Tyranny’s vice-captain finally arrived before Ye Xiu.

“You too,” said Ye Xiu.

“This team is very strong.” Zhang Xinjie’s gaze slid toward the other members of Happy standing behind Ye Xiu. “Everyone has an area where they can’t be overlooked.”

Ye Xiu smiled. He knew that Zhang Xinjie could see much more than most other people. Happy was able to defeat Tyranny not because of one person or one thrilling moment. Their team’s operation was thorough and outstanding. In that thrilling battle to reverse the disadvantage, Happy hadn’t communicated in the chat at all – this was the greatest proof. This showed that their teamwork was well-trained, this showed that they had a shared awareness in that kind of situation, that they could cooperate, pushing themselves and the team in the direction of victory.

“Keep working hard,” Zhang Xinjie said.

“You too,” Ye Xiu said.

Zhang Xinjie nodded. He wasn’t someone who would say insincere polite words. Happy still had areas to improve, and their Tyranny did as well. Even though he had brought Ye Xiu to a downfall as soon as he joined the Alliance, he had never underestimated him. When it came to the strategic system of Happy, the team that Ye Xiu had pulled together, there was just too much to learn from and analyze.

The contents of the Glory Textbook were constantly updating, constantly evolving.

Chapter 1574 - Real Analysis

Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Zhang Xinjie…

Tyranny appeared invincible because of these four, but Tyranny wasn’t only just these four. Song Qiying and Qin Muyun had played in this round’s team competition. By the time Qin Muyun joined the battle, Happy already held the upper hand. He didn’t lose his fighting spirit, though. He tried his best to turn things around, contributing greatly towards extending the intense battle by another half an hour.

As for Song Qiying?

He had been the team’s last hope in the group arena, but in the end, he failed to make a comeback. He had played in the team competition as well, playing until the last moment, but all that he received was another bitter defeat.

“Why?” Song Qiying was trying his hardest not to cry, but tears were already racing down his cheeks.

“You seniors were all working so hard, but why, why did we still…” Song Qiying couldn’t accept this. He didn’t understand. He himself was still young and had a future, and as a man of Tyranny, he wouldn’t start crying uncontrollably just because of a single defeat. However, even if he had the future, what about his teammates, who were on the verge of retirement?

Their youthful days were over, and they no longer had any opportunities to waste. The amount of time that they could still remain on the Glory stage could be counted on one hand. It was because of this that they practiced no less than anyone else. Even at their final moments, they wouldn’t give up on even the slightest chance of improving themselves.

Song Qiying had seen their efforts with his own eyes.

They treasured every chance they had, but in the end, why did opportunity never gaze upon them?

Their efforts, their sweat, their everything, they had sacrificed it all, yet all they got in exchange was defeat.

Why?

Song Qiying didn’t know who he was asking.

Qin Muyun patted his shoulders to comfort him. Zhang Xinjie was ready to bring him away when he heard Ye Xiu say calmly: “Effort alone can’t win you everything. Don’t be so conceited!”

Conceited?

How was Song Qiying being conceited? He couldn’t help but feel stunned at that word.

“In terms of effort, do you think our Happy would lose to you? No, not Happy, and not any team,” Ye Xiu said.

“On this Glory stage, effort is the last thing you should brag about, because it’s a given, it’s something everyone will put in, it’s the lowest and smallest thing. Recognize this and keep climbing!

“Keep working hard!”

As Ye Xiu said this, he shook hands with Tyranny’s sixth player, Qin Muyun, and then waved to the crowd, even if this was Tyranny’s home stadium, even if this place was filled with Glory fans who hated him.

Applause came, but it was rather reserved.

Although there were people who were moved by Ye Xiu’s words, their hatred stood strong. Today’s match was another addition to the list. The crowd didn’t boo, instead giving Ye Xiu a bit of applause. It showed just how moving Ye Xiu’s words were today.

The referee announced Team Happy’s victory. This time, the fans in the away team seats gave thunderous cheers, looking more like winners than before. The applause from Tyranny’s fans wasn’t too soft either, but their applause wasn’t for the winners, but the losers, Tyranny. Although their applause hid their disappointment, they had to tell their team that even in defeat, Tyranny would always be heroes in their heart.

The two teams entered the stadium’s passageway. Neither team said anything as they walked to their prep rooms. The two teams were required to participate in the following press conference. The order wouldn’t be by home and away team, but by losing and winning team.

The first to go up was Team Tyranny. Their loss didn’t only symbolize the end of this round, but the end of this set and this season. The questions that Tyranny would need to face wouldn’t be limited to just today’s match.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale.

These four went out for the press conference. Their gathering ignited sparks among the Glory community. Just the names alone were enough to spark interest from Glory fans.

But after last year’s defeat, they had lost again.

Everyone knew the weakness in this exciting lineup. Perhaps it was because of this weakness that such a luxurious team could be formed.

But they had failed two seasons in a row. This luxurious lineup failed to meet their fan’s expectations, as well as their own. What would they do next? Compared to the contents of today’s match, the future of Tyranny was a more important topic.

Questions needed to be asked in sequence though, especially when facing such an intimidating group of stars, who deserved respect. No reporter planned on making it hard for them.

“Tyranny’s loss against Happy is regrettable.” The first reporter to speak would often start off with this sort of opening remark before moving onto the next logical step: “How do you think your opponents played today?”

“Extremely well.” As the captain, Han Wenqing answered back, giving a reply that every reporter hated. Luckily for the reporters, he turned his head to the side and added: “How about we have Xinjie give a more detailed explanation?”

“Of course, of course!” No one would object to that. Zhang Xinjie always said things as they were. Questions asking about how the opponents did were the easiest to brush off, but if Zhang Xinjie was answering it, that wouldn’t be the case.

“Group arena or team competition?” After Zhang Xinjie received the question, he immediately asked for clarification.

“Team competition, team competition,” the reporters replied. The team competition had elements of teamwork and individual play, so there were more things to talk about than the group arena.

“For the team competition, we confirmed after the match that the spawn point was determined randomly, right? ” Zhang Xinjie began, showing how strict and serious he was with the game. As soon as the match ended, he immediately made clear what doubts he had.

“Yeah,” the reporters nodded their heads in agreement.

Zhang Xinjie nodded his head and pondered for a moment. Then, starting from this point, he summarized what happened in the team competition before cautiously saying: “There are many things that we can learn from Happy in today’s team competition.”

“Because of the random spawn locations, Happy’s Tang Rou ended up coming across the five of us alone. This was an extremely bad situation for her. Tang Rou quickly came to a decision, while we hesitated slightly. This was all because neither of us nor Happy knew about the random spawn locations. On the surface, Happy was at a disadvantage. However, because of our hesitation, Happy was able to seize the initiative. They had Tang Rou try and bait us into chasing after her. Later on, by using the surrounding terrain, they were able to safely set up ambush locations to wear us down…”

Zhang Xinjie replied to the reporter’s question in detail. The reporter had simply asked about Happy’s performance, so that’s what he talked about. He didn’t say anything regarding how Tyranny played, let alone criticism.

Even so, the reporters didn’t feel that it was boring because of how honest Zhang Xinjie was. From his words, they could hear things that they might have missed, trying to analyze it themselves. Although everyone was more concerned with Tyranny’s future, today’s match had indeed been spectacular, especially Ye Xiu’s Life-Risking Strike. Everyone wanted to hear about Tyranny’s opinion on it.

The reporters hadn’t asked about it specifically, but because it was an important part of the match, perhaps even the climax of it, Zhang Xinjie naturally talking about it in more detail when he got there.

“Luo Ji coming out into play can already be considered a set up. Because of the first game in our best of three, Luo Ji’s presence made us mindful of the terrain.

“Happy’s ambush at the canyon exit wasn’t successful. It could be said that Happy had relied on Ye Xiu’s outstanding playing to stabilize the situation. At this point, Happy was in a defensive position, but they had a clear retreat path. Their destination was the center of the map, the Seven Color Springs. We had yet to explore this area.

“We had thought that this destination was the turning point that Happy was waiting for, but it turned out that our judgement was incorrect.” Zhang Xinjie didn’t cover up his mistake, directly calling it out.

“Happy had been waiting for an opportunity. This opportunity wasn’t the Seven Color Springs, but rather us thinking that the Seven Color Springs was the turning point.

“Once we made this prediction, the most effective method to eliminate this possibility was to win before the Seven Color Springs was reached.

“Starting from when we killed Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, we had the lead and the initiative. As a result, we adopted a more aggressive posture.

“And this was the opportunity that Happy was waiting for. Their plan had begun the moment Fang Rui was killed. They were being pressured by us, but by creating a certain image of themselves, it gave them space to bounce back. Afterwards, they needed to wait, wait for us to increase our aggression to lure us into bringing out our healer.

“This is a strategy. I realized it after the match. During this course of events, there had been no communication within Happy. It was all an enormous and complex set-up. If it had been devised on the spot, there would definitely have been communication. Thus, this is a strategy that Happy has practiced before. At some point, everyone had received the signal to carry out this strategy. For the Switch to work, the Spirit Cat must have been summoned by Lord Grim, and none of us had noticed it. This was extremely critical because Luo Ji was a very important part of this strategy. Lord Grim’s Spirit Cat had to be hidden among Concealed Light’s summons, and the possibility of an Elemental Beast King Formation was a huge bait. If we had known that the Spirit Cat was Lord Grim’s, we wouldn’t have worried about it as much, and Lin Jingyan would not have been lured over by Luo Ji. Even if he had started casting Elemental Beast King Formation, since the Spirit Cat wasn’t Concealed Light’s, it would not have worked… but unfortunately, we had been tricked, beginning with us not knowing that the Spirit Cat was Lord Grim’s.”

Chapter 1575 - Farewell, Lin Jingyan

Clear, accurate, logical.

The reporters present had all heard Zhang Xinjie make this kind of post-match analysis before, but they were still amazed at Zhang Xinjie’s calm. Even after this defeat, which had ruined a year’s worth of hard work, no one could tell that his mood had been affected at all.

Was he not bitter? Was he not disappointed? Was he not regretful?

Of course he felt those things!

No pro player could remain completely unaffected after this kind of defeat. But Zhang Xinjie could hide his own mood like this, could control himself to do the appropriate thing at the appropriate time. The reporters ask for our opinion of the opponents? Alright, whether you actually want to know or are just making conversation, since you’ve asked this, when it’s my turn to answer, I will answer in a direct manner.

The reporters couldn’t be more satisfied.

With the post-match analysis that Zhang Xinjie gave, their reports on this match could be much more sophisticated.

But now, how could they bring up the topic that everyone was more concerned about? Zhang Xinjie only talked about strategy, not emotion, so they couldn’t find a good transition point anywhere in the whole speech he gave. This was Zhang Xinjie’s consistently strict style in accepting interviews. His answers always addressed the current question, nothing more. You couldn’t find any content in them that would give rise to new topics. Not a single drop ever leaked.

There was no way to progress naturally from here, so the reporters could only start anew.

“It really was an incredibly thrilling match.” One reporter followed Zhang Xinjie’s analysis with a word of praise, then began to change the topic. “Then, after today’s loss, what are all of your plans for the future?”

The question was very direct.

And this was exactly the question that everyone was most concerned about. Instantly, the press conference quieted down.

“I can still continue to fight,” said Captain Han Wenqing.

The keen reporters immediately realized something. Han Wenqing had used the word “I.” Even though he was the captain, at this moment, he did not speak for the whole team. Everyone immediately guessed the hidden news revealed by this sentence: Han Wenqing could continue to fight, but some people could not…

“I as well,” Zhang Xinjie answered after him.

Of course he could… He was of the Golden Generation. Compared to Season 1 and 2 debuts, he still had plenty of matches left to fight. The question that everyone cared about had never been directed at him.

“I won’t give up either,” the next person said. But when the reporters’ gazes turned, they already began to recognize something even more clearly.

Tyranny’s current seating order onstage: Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale.

As the captain, Han Wenqing answered first, but he didn’t represent the whole team, he only spoke for himself.

And then Zhang Xinjie. And then, it wasn’t the next person in line, Lin Jingyan, who spoke, but Zhang Jiale.

Lin Jingyan was skipped. Evidently, it was because they knew that what Lin Jingyan was going to say wouldn’t be of the same atmosphere as the rest of them.

Everyone’s gazes turned back to Lin Jingyan. Cameras and everything were all at the ready. They had all already guessed: an ending had finally arrived.

Lin Jingyan stood up. He wore a smile on his face. This representative of Glory’s Brawler class, he himself had always had a refined and gentle air about him.

“I think, it’s about time I finished…” Lin Jingyan finally opened his mouth. The prepared reporters instantly clicked the shutters of their cameras. They needed to record these images, these sounds, this scene.

And of the other three Tyranny players sitting onstage, Han Wenqing’s face was as strong and unyielding as ever, and Zhang Xinjie was also calm. Only Zhang Jiale’s face showed a bit of sadness at this moment. Was it because of today’s loss? Or was it because of Lin Jingyan’s imminent retirement? Or a bit of both?

It seemed like he wanted to say something, but in the end he didn’t open his mouth.

It was clear that his Tyranny teammates already knew Lin Jingyan’s decision. Perhaps they had tried to persuade him otherwise, but in the end, they chose to respect his decision. None of them said anything, giving this moment entirely to him.

“And in this end, I want to give thanks,” Lin Jingyan continued to say.

“First, I want to thank the teammates sitting beside me. Before coming to Tyranny, I never thought that one day I’d have the chance to fight alongside all of you for the championship. You are all the most outstanding players in the Alliance. To be able to fight side by side with you is my fortune, and the glory of my lifetime.

“Therefore, I also want to give special thanks to Tyranny as a team. I thank this team for giving me such a good opportunity, even in the twilight years of my career. These two years, for me, have been fulfilling and happy. My only regret is that I was still unable to lift that championship trophy alongside everyone, and here I would like to apologize to Tyranny, that I… cannot continue to work hard with everyone.

“This decision does not come lightly. It is a careful decision that I have made after considering my own condition. I believe that my professional career should end here.

“No life is perfect, and it’s unfortunate that I wasn’t able to win a championship. But from Wind Howl to Tyranny, I have always had the most outstanding teammates at my side. It is Glory that allowed me to meet you all. What I want to say is, to be able to play Glory, to become a Glory pro player, this is the greatest fortune of my entire life.

“Today, I leave this stage first. But I won’t leave Glory – I never will. I will still watch you, and I hope that you will fulfill your dreams.

“In the end, I want to give my best wishes to everyone, everyone connected to Glory. It is Glory that has linked us all together, this will be the glory of our lifetimes!

“Thank you everyone, I wish you all the best…” Lin Jingyan bowed, concluding his farewell speech. The reporters had finally gotten to a relatively interesting topic, but in this moment, they wished that this news didn’t exist. They wished that Lin Jingyan could be like Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Zhang Jiale, and express his intent to continue working hard.

But, no.

Everything that had just happened was real.

Lin Jingyan had already declared his retirement. He was leaving. This Season 2 debut, this pinnacle player, the number one Brawler, had finally finished walking the path of his professional career.

He hadn’t won a championship, and he hadn’t had any special individual accomplishments. Before he’d joined Tyranny, he’d never even made it to the finals.

And yet he still was indomitable, he still pressed on relentlessly, he still worked hard for victory.

No one would laugh at him, even if he was already surpassed by his junior during his career. Because, this was an inevitable law created from the passage of time, there was nothing laughable about this. What everyone saw was that, even when Tang Hao seized the title of number one Brawler from him, seized his position in Wind Howl, seized the character with which he’d fought for seven years, he hadn’t seized his fighting spirit, nor had he seized his championship heart.

Lin Jingyan came to Tyranny, and with joy and elegance he fought alongside his new teammates for another two years, all the way until he himself felt that he’d reached his end. Only then did he set everything down.

No one could force him to choose to leave, no one but himself.

“Thank you everyone, I wish you all the best,” Lin Jingyan had said.

And now, the other three Tyranny players onstage had already turned around. They shook hands with Lin Jingyan, they embraced him, they gave him their well-wishes.

Perhaps there was sadness in their hearts, but on their faces, nothing but determination brimmed. No matter where the road led, they would continue to walk it with determination. No compromise, no regret, no hesitation. Walk forward, straight ahead.

“Goodbye!”

After he finished his exchanges with his teammates, Lin Jingyan waved to the reporters below. He gave a final nod to his three teammates, before turning and walking toward the exit passageway.

Was it over?

The reporters were a bit stunned, but soon, they realized that Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Zhang Jiale, these three players had already sat back down at their seats. It was as though nothing had happened, as though that empty seat had been empty since the beginning.

Lin Jingyan had made his decision, and they had made theirs as well.

Lin Jingyan had already bid farewell to this stage, and so he left; and they had chosen to stay, chosen to continue, and so, this press conference would continue.

The reporters were in a daze. Having never experienced this kind of scene before, they didn’t know what they should ask the three remaining players. They even hoped that this press conference would quickly come to an end, which was something they’d never felt before. Tyranny’s determination, Tyranny’s unwavering spirit, they felt it, and they almost couldn’t bear the weight of it.

“Then, after Lin Jingyan’s retirement, what adjustments will Tyranny make?” In the end, someone still stood up to ask a question.

“Naturally, there will be someone to fill the opening,” said Han Wenqing.

“Then could you reveal who it’ll be? Will it be someone in Tyranny, or will moves be made during the transfer window?” one reporter asked.

“This hasn’t been decided yet,” said Han Wenqing.

“Alright…” By this point, the reporters no longer had their normal strength to desperately fight for answers. The atmosphere was completely smothered, and after these two questions, it instantly became silent again.

At last, Tyranny’s news official stood up and said, “Then, if there are no further questions, the press conference can end here?”

“Alright, that’s fine…” The reporters quickly agreed.

It was over.

Tyranny’s press conference was over, and the professional career of a top player was also over. But on this stage, even as some people left, others would continue to resolutely walk onward.

Others of Tyranny would walk onward. And right now, Happy, this team, their road this season hadn’t ended yet, they still had more to walk. The finals, the championship, this newbie team in the Alliance had actually made it to the finals. Just making it here was already a miracle, just this step was enough of an explosive topic.

Happy walked onstage.

They’d sent out three representatives.

Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, Luo Ji.

Excellent! These people got the reporters excited. After Tyranny left, they’d returned to their normal condition and instantly detected the interesting topic here. Without even asking about Happy themselves, someone had already stood up and asked, “Do you know that Lin Jingyan just announced his retirement?”

As soon as the question came out, everyone looked at Fang Rui, Lin Jingyan’s partner of many years in Wind Howl.

Chapter 1576 - Storm’s End

The silence of the press conference was far quieter than Happy’s prep room. Even though they could see the live broadcast of Lin Jingyan’s retirement announcement on the television, the Alliance rookies still had limited experience with the helplessness and grief of retirement. Moreover, they were still immersed in the wild joy of having made it to the finals. The news of Lin Jingyan’s retirement didn’t change the atmosphere in Happy’s prep room.

The young players were still laughing merrily, but at that moment, melancholy still spread in Happy’s prep room.

Ye Xiu had known Lin Jingyan for a long time. They’d fought against each other from Season 2 until now, so they were no strangers. Ye Xiu had played from Season 1 all the way until today, and over the course of these years, he’d seen familiar faces leaving one after another. Some had been teammates, some had been opponents, but in that moment of departure, everyone would forget these identities. All they would feel was the departure of a partner.

Today was the same. Another familiar face was fading away.

Ye Xiu was silent.

Fang Rui, too, was silent. He hadn’t known Lin Jingyan for as long as Ye Xiu had, but he, who had debuted in Season 5, had immediately come to Lin Jingyan’s side. It was Lin Jingyan who had watched him grow, and then they’d become a famous duo. And then after Season 8, Season 9, they’d gone their separate ways.

To Fang Rui, Lin Jingyan had been both a teacher and a friend. If he had to pick the player in the Alliance that he respected the most, Fang Rui would vote for Lin Jingyan without any hesitation, even if Lin Jingyan wasn’t the best player in the circle.

And now, he had left.

Fang Rui, who now already had several years of professional experience, had realized that this day would come eventually. But he had never imagined that he would witness Lin Jingyan’s departure like this.

He’d originally thought that the two of them would fight side by side, until one day, Lin Jingyan would suddenly smile and say he couldn’t fight any longer. And then Fang Rui would make fun of him for it, but Lin Jingyan wouldn’t change his mind, and just like that, smiling, he would say goodbye.

And today, he saw it.

Lin Jingyan was smiling, he said farewell to everyone, but it was after being defeated by the team that Fang Rui represented…

The sadness hidden beneath the smile, how many people could feel it?

Fang Rui knew, Lin Jingyan definitely still hoped to win a championship. He hoped so, so much.

But the ones who had ultimately destroyed that hope were himself and Happy.

Lin Jingyan would have no more chances.

Because he had already chosen to leave.

I wish you all the best.

He gave his well-wishes to everyone, and this, of course, included Fang Rui.

But how could this kind of well-wishing make someone feel better? Fang Rui, at least, wouldn’t. He couldn’t bear to watch any longer, and in that moment, he found an excuse and left Happy’s prep room. After him, Wei Chen, this old guy who had retired early on only to return many years later, ignored the rules that forbade smoking in the prep room, and roughly pulled out a cigarette.

Unlike normal, Chen Guo didn’t go to scold him. As a senior Glory fan, even though she had never personally experienced this kind of goodbye, she had seen it happen like this many times before. And now that she had entered this circle, she felt the pain, and she was aware that she would gradually see these farewells occurring next to her. Wei Chen, Ye Xiu, and then after that, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui…

Chen Guo was scared, truly very scared.

She watched as Fang Rui mumbled something and left the prep room. No one tried to stop him. Even the still-celebrating rookies, at this time, recognized that the prep room wasn’t entirely this joyful atmosphere, and they quieted down as they saw Fang Rui leave. And then, they saw the broadcast of the press conference, as Lin Jingyan hugged and said goodbye to the other three Tyranny players, thanked everyone, and left.

Um…

Those whose brains moved a little faster already realized something.

Fang Rui had left the prep room, and Lin Jingyan was returning from the press conference. Then, wouldn’t these two meet in the passageway?

The prep room instantly went quiet, and someone had even muted the television, as though it would disrupt the two talking in the passageway. No one moved, no one made a sound, until the door to the prep room was pushed open again.

“It’s our turn,” Fang Rui said calmly, standing in the doorway.

And so Ye Xiu and Luo Ji, the two that Happy had already arranged to participate in the press conference, walked out of the prep room. In the passageway, they saw Lin Jingyan, who smiled at them, and then patted Fang Rui. He didn’t return to Tyranny’s prep room, but instead continue to walk down this passageway, which would eventually lead outside the stadium.

“Let’s go.” Ye Xiu didn’t watch him any longer. He waved at the others, and the three Happy players walked out of the passageway, toward the press conference.

“Do you know that Lin Jingyan just announced his retirement?”

The reporters had already pulled out their first question.

“Yes,” Ye Xiu nodded.

“Could each of you say some of your thoughts on this?” The reporter emphasized “each of you.” Evidently, they weren’t very interested in Ye Xiu answering this question. What they wanted to hear was Fang Rui’s thoughts.

Fang Rui didn’t shy away, voluntarily taking the microphone, so Ye Xiu didn’t try to say anything first. Just as the reporters wanted, he waited for Fang Rui to say his thoughts.

“I wish him the best.” Fang Rui took the microphone and said five words.

Everyone quietly waited. But then, there was nothing after. Fang Rui said only these five words. To his partner of many years, to his teacher and friend, to Lin Jingyan, whose lifelong dream he’d personally ruined, Fang Rui only said these five words.

“That’s all?” The reporters didn’t give up. They wanted to hear some more deeply moving thoughts.

“That’s all.” But Fang Rui shook his head, smiling, just like Lin Jingyan. All of his thoughts, all that he’d wanted to say, he’d already said to Lin Jingyan when they met in that passageway. To Fang Rui, this was enough. There was no need to retell it to these reporters.

After that, there was nothing left but to wish him well. Him, and only him.

But the reporters still refused to give up easily. Even if Lin Jingyan hadn’t retired today, as a former partnership, meeting onstage was still a big topic.

“Forgive my bluntness.” Another reporter opened his mouth. “It seemed like your performance today didn’t meet expectations. Was it because your former partner was among your opponents, and you found it difficult to fight against him?”

“My performance today was indeed not very good, so it was lucky that the team could still win the match. In the upcoming matches, I will continue to fight to my fullest,” Fang Rui said.

It seemed like a very ordinary response, but at this moment it was quite clever, completely avoiding the issue of “former partners,” and then taking responsibility for his poor performance, analyzing the results, and facing the future.

How were the reporters supposed to continue? What else could they ask?

There was no way they could continue to tangle with questions about Lin Jingyan. They could only begin to ask serious questions about Happy’s performance this match. The analysis that Zhang Xinjie had provided in the press conference suddenly became important data that everyone could use to ask Happy questions.

“Was Happy completing a Life-Risking Strike against Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock in the team round today a carefully-trained tactic prepared beforehand?” a reporter asked.

“Hahaha,” Ye Xiu laughed, “don’t use Zhang Xinjie’s analysis to ask me questions. I was watching the broadcast. Everything he analyzed was wrong.”

The reporters instantly felt like facepalming. Everyone knew that Ye Xiu was spouting nonsense. But he so rudely scorned Zhang Xinjie’s analysis just like that, what were the reporters supposed to do?

Before, Ye Xiu never appeared at these sorts of events. When it came to press conferences, in reality, both Ye Xiu and Luo Ji were rookies. But this rookie was terrifyingly difficult to deal with. Compared to those who were very slippery when answering questions, Ye Xiu simply didn’t care about them. When a question came, he would just casually make something up, and when you turned around to ask clarification, he could forget what he’d just said. Worst of all was that he never tried to avoid this point. He would simply reply to you, very honestly, “Really? Did I say that?”

So what if he’d said it? So what if he hadn’t said it?

Could the reporters report on the sort of made-up nonsense he spouted? Of course not. Wouldn’t it make the reporters look like they had very low IQ, for believing that kind of nonsense?

Seeing Ye Xiu activate this status once again, the reporters internally freaked out, but on the surface they still gave off a very even-tempered and good-humored air.

“Then, was there any special reason for sending out Luo Ji in this match?” someone asked.

“Training rookies, training rookies on the big stage. It’s just like how Tyranny sent out Song Qiying; we sent out Luo Ji,” Ye Xiu said, very seriously.

Motherfucker!

The reporters raged in their hearts.

This kind of reply here was simply evasive. Maybe you didn’t believe it, but what he said followed logic; maybe you believed it, but you’d always feel that something was wrong with what he said, that you were being taken for a ride.

“And we’re braver than Tyranny. In this critical match, we actually sent out as many as three rookies,” Ye Xiu continued to speak.

The reporters wanted to cry.

Try not sending them up! In your Happy, aside from you, Fang Rui, Su Mucheng, and Wei Chen, who’s not a rookie?

“Perhaps in the finals, we’ll experiment with a full rookie roster. Let them accept the toughest test of all,” Ye Xiu said.

Who believed that?

Who would believe that?

Send rookies into the finals to train? This was taking the joke to the extreme!

The reporters all looked miserable. How were they supposed to write today’s article? Some were already mentally in a different place. It looked like this press conference wasn’t going to give them any material.

“Then, shall we end here today?” In the end, Happy’s press conference hastily came to a close, The reporters didn’t resist much, they weren’t even in the mood to snap a few extra pictures. Once upon a time, getting a picture of Ye Xiu had been such a beautiful and rare accomplishment, but now, seeing this guy appear in the camera lens, everyone only felt like their mouths were dry. They didn’t know what to ask, and they didn’t know what they should listen for.

The press conference ended.

At last, the curtain fell on the winds and storms of today’s match.

The losers, the victors, they all walked their own paths.

But no matter what kind of path they took, the direction in which they charged was always the same. They each took their own path, but it was always the path chasing victory, the path to be champions.

Chapter 1577 - The Potential World War

After fighting for almost a week in City Q, Team Happy finally returned to their home City H. What awaited them was a torrential downpour.

Samsara, Happy.

One was a championship team that had won two consecutive championships, while the other was a new team that had just joined the Alliance. These two teams, with a world of disparity between them, ultimately entered the finals together.

No one would dare underestimate Happy ever again. No one would dismiss them as a grassroots team ever again.

Sixth place in the regular season, defeating the powerhouses Blue Rain and Tyranny in the playoffs, Happy was currently attracting everyone’s attention with an unstoppable momentum.

Now, not only did people want to see the birth of a new dynasty, a number of Glory players also wanted to see the birth of a miracle – a new team that had just entered the Alliance, with never-resting footsteps, snatching the championship.

At midnight, the victory polls for the first round of the finals and the finals as a whole had all opened. By 8:00 in the morning, after eight hours, the support that both teams had received was actually tied.

Before this, whether facing Blue Rain or Tyranny, the rate of support that Happy received was always lower by a huge margin. Even if their team had no lack of All-Stars, even if their team had the Best Rookie, even if they had brought surprise after surprise over the course of this season. Despite all that, in the playoffs, the Glory fans still didn’t look favorably upon them.

Until today. Until now.

They defeated Blue Rain, defeated Tyranny.

Happy had received enough trust. In the pre-match support poll, they were in fact tied with Samsara.

Samsara: 51.6%.

Happy: 48.4%.

Samsara had a slight lead, but such a small difference was really nothing. For Happy to be able to split the vote so evenly with Samsara, that was already enough to prove how remarkable they were. Even if it were Blue Rain or Tyranny who had entered the finals, it was possible that they wouldn’t be able to tie the vote like this. But Happy, under unfavorable circumstances, defied all expectations to make it here. This led more people to become interested in them, and people began to once again look forward to the unexpected.

Three days later, City H, Xiaoshan Stadium, would that be where the miracle began?

The rain washed clean Xiaoshan Stadium, and because it was such a downpour, the streets were unusually cool and clear. No matter how passionate or enthusiastic the Happy fans were, in this kind of weather, they couldn’t cheer on Happy with all the energy they would have liked. But business at Happy Internet Café was exploding in this weather. The internet café no longer seemed like an internet café, even the aisles were packed. Using excuses like finding shelter from the rain, everyone scurried into the internet café and began enthusiastically talking about the upcoming finals match. Even those who were sitting at computers weren’t really using their computers. Everyone was discussing with the people next to them.

They might know each other, or they might not.

This wasn’t important. Right now, those who were gathered here, they all had the same hope, the same anticipation: for Happy to win the championship!

The second floor of Happy Internet Café could be considered Team Happy’s base of operations. Even though they were a team that had already made it to the finals, the team’s simple infrastructure couldn’t be changed immediately.

Right now, all the members of Happy had gathered in this training room that was definitely last place in the Alliance.

Yesterday, they had traveled through the night to return to City H. Luckily, the ugly weather hadn’t affected their flight. And this morning, they were once again unaffected by the weather, and right on time, they arrived at the training room.

This kind of discipline was required during the regular season. After the playoffs began, Ye Xiu advocated individual adjustment more. The team didn’t schedule too many training plans, and instead allowed the players to arrange their own time.

But now, they were at the finals, only one step away from winning the championship. Happy’s players had spontaneously complied with the discipline of the regular season, and gathered here just like this.

“What’s going on? Didn’t I say that there were no plans this morning, and that you all should rest up?” Ye Xiu said, seeing the room full of people.

Everyone scoffed. Look at you, when you’re talking, can’t you look at your own standpoint first? You said there were no plans in the morning and that we should rest, but aren’t you also standing here right now anyway? When you’re saying something like this, could you not be so matter-of-fact?

“Alright! Since everyone’s here, then let’s enjoy Samsara’s exciting performance in the playoffs!” As Ye Xiu spoke, he was already setting up the screen to display data on Samsara that no one knew when he’d organized.

Samsara’s strength couldn’t be doubted, and Happy had recognized this point long ago. In the first match of the regular season, they were swept by Samsara, and at the halfway point of the season, when the teams switched stadiums and fought again, Happy had only won three points.

But the results of the regular season didn’t affect Happy too much.

Blue Rain, Tyranny.

Hadn’t these two teams each defeated Happy twice in the regular season? But the one who had the last laugh in the finals was Happy.

To use past victory and defeat as the basis of judgment, that was something the media loved doing. Their work was to find topics to discuss, and discussing the past encounters of two teams was undoubtedly a very accurate line of thought.

But for pro players, for pro teams, past defeats were simply sources of experience. They wouldn’t feel unduly humbled, nor would this make them feel that defeating the opponent was too difficult. Every match was a new start; every victory required two hands to build once again.

Failing to defeat Samsara in the regular season had nothing to do with the present.

On this point, Happy’s faith was unshakeable. They weren’t tied down by their past failures. Under Ye Xiu’s leadership, they clearly and logically analyzed the Samsara that they were about to face in the playoffs.

One day, two days…

The sky was clear after the rain.

This was Happy’s home, these were the streets where past Excellent Era fans and current Happy fans ruled. When, gradually, chants rose up in support of Samsara, everyone knew, Samsara was here. The reigning champions, the ones who were currently gunning for their third straight championship, Team Samsara had arrived in City H.

As the saying went, a powerful dragon could not crush a snake in its home.

But the atmosphere changed that occurred in Happy’s home streets after Samsara arrived, there was the impression of a fierce dragon crossing the river.

At this time, security was increased in the area to prevent clashes between the fans of the two teams. Luckily, these fans were all Glory players, so if there were any real conflicts, 80% of the time they would just find some computers and begin a round of Glory PK. A street brawl didn’t really fit the spirit of Glory’s diehard fans.

So Glory, as a competition, would always see its fans clashing, but very rarely would situations escalate to harming physical safety, precisely because they had this different way of resolving conflict. Most of them preferred to display their brains and power in Glory.

The match day approached steadily, and the fans of the two teams steadily gathered. In the streets, the atmosphere seemed harmonious, but beneath that calm, the surrounding internet cafes had seen countless ferocious Glory PKs. One day, Happy’s Wu Chen with a dark expression had gathered a whole group of people and left the café, killing his way to who knows where. But afterward, he had returned with that same dark expression, so he probably hadn’t managed to accomplish anything good.

On Happy’s side, Wu Chen was still at the head. But because Samsara had made it to the finals, guild leader Three Realms Six Paths, as an in-game leader, of course came to City H himself. He brought a whole group of Samsara workers with him and took over Grand Internet Café, making it their battle headquarters. The two teams hadn’t even officially begun to fight, but the battle between the fans of the two teams was already escalating non-stop. But under the control of the two guild leaders, the battle at least hadn’t escalated to wild PK in-game. For now, everyone still resolved things in the Arena.

Clearly, under these circumstances, the two guild leaders still hadn’t lost their cool. Wild PK, no matter who had the upper hand, would always end up harming both sides, and it would give the rest of the guilds an opportunity to get ahead. The two guild leaders didn’t forget their true responsibilities at this time, and they didn’t let the finals affect the balance in-game.

But this was only temporary. After all, the matches hadn’t even been fought yet. If the players really were provoked by what happened in the matches, then nothing could stop the explosion. In past years, more often than not, large-scale wild battles would erupt between the two guilds, all because after a certain point, the guild leader could no longer keep control.

Guild Excellent Dynasty, supporting Excellent Era’s dynasty, was originally the most powerful guild in-game, but precisely because the team entered the finals four times, it had gone through all of those world wars. This time it’d be war against one, next time war against another, again and again for four years. They’d had to fight every year, but their opponent was always changing. They’d fought for four years, and then Excellent Era’s dynasty was broken, and Excellent Dynasty’s strength was greatly weakened. After that, when the Three Great Guilds were named in-game, they were Tyrannical Ambition, Herb Garden, and Blue Brook. The once all-powerful Excellent Dynasty could not lift this title to Four Great Guilds.

And because of this lesson learned from Excellent Dynasty’s mistakes, after that, guilds would always be very, very careful.

After Excellent Era, Tiny Herb entered the finals three times. There was one small war, one large war, and finally the third time passed calmly.

The small war was Season 5, against Hundred Blossoms. In the middle of that season, Hundred Blossoms’ Sun Zheping’s injury rendered him unable to fight. When the finals arrived, Hundred Blossoms was filled with a determination to win the championship for Sun Zheping, but, unfortunately, they lost to Tiny Herb. After the match, the fans immediately began fighting in-game, but then, Sun Zheping made the official announcement that he was retiring due to his injury. Hundred Blossoms was in no mood to engage in a world war, so in the end, it was no more than a small war.

And then in Season 6, Tiny Herb’s consecutive championship was fiercely stolen away by Blue Rain. The world war that came afterward was shocking, the fiercest in history. It was from this battle that the deep feud between the two teams was born.

And then in Season 7, Tiny Herb once again met Hundred Blossoms. The two teams both had experience with the finals and very much understood the harm of allowing the flames of battle spread to the guilds. Thus, this time, with the hard work of the guild leaders to maintain the peace, they managed to control the situation in game, and no war occurred. This became the only time so far that everything ended peacefully.

And then Seasons 8 and 9 had both seen guild world wars, but under the leadership and control of the guild leaders, they ended fairly quickly after everyone vented their emotions, and there were no lasting injuries.

And this time, Samsara, Happy. In-game, they couldn’t be considered top guilds, but the tide began to build toward a potential world war.

Chapter 1578 - Little People Sneaking into the Stadium

Three days’ time, not too long, not too short, but it passed by in a flash.

As the sun shone down upon City H after the rain, the city seemed refreshed and pure. After being washed, even the familiar streets seemed to have something new about them.

One hour until the match’s start, the audience had been let into the stadium long before, but the area outside of the stadium was still bustling with crowds of people.

Far too many Glory players hoped for the chance to watch the finals live, but unfortunately, tickets were hard to obtain. There were a number of people who hung around near the stadium to try their luck, some who wanted to sneak their way in, some who were asking around to see if anyone had an extra ticket. In any case, no one was idle.

Fu Chao was one of these Glory players, and his goal was the same as those of these gathered gamers, but from the very start, Fu Chao hadn’t joined the crowd. There were too many people here, it would be much too difficult to try and sneak in through the front or get a ticket from someone.

Fu Chao stayed far away from the crowds, and instead lingered around another area of the stadium, paying close attention to his surroundings.

There were many passageways leading in and out of Xiaoshan Stadium. Right now, during such a large event, they of course opened the main doors, which were the largest and could accommodate the most traffic. And the side doors, the small doors, wouldn’t be freely open for use at this time, of course.

But just because they weren’t open for use didn’t mean that they couldn’t be used. Fu Chao planned to use one of these side doors. After he walked away from the main doors, the surroundings became much calmer, and just ahead, Fu Chao saw a small unassuming door, closed shut.

Fu Chao went up to it. He didn’t know whether to push or pull it, but either way, after several tries, the little door didn’t budge. Clearly, it was tightly locked.

Fu Chao didn’t give up. He hadn’t thought that the stadium workers would be that careless, anyway, he’d just come here to try his luck.

Just casually walking in through an unlocked door hadn’t been his real plan, either.

What he wanted to do was find a worker passageway. There might be stadium workers there, but he could try and find a good opportunity to sneak in through there.

There should be!

Fu Chao had a great deal of faith in his assumption. He believed that there must be these kinds of staff passageways convenient for workers. He just didn’t know whether Xiaoshan Stadium’s workers could be bribed that easily.

No matter what, he had to give it a try.

Fu Chao continued to walk, until he heard the indistinct sound of voices coming from up ahead. He quickened his footsteps, turned a corner, and saw another side door, which was just about to be closed by the last person entering.

“Wait up!” Fu Chao disregarded all else as he shouted and sprinted toward it. This was a chance he didn’t want to miss.

That person had clearly heard the shout and stopped moving, turning around to take a look. As Fu Chao ran, he waved his right hand to get attention, while his left hand was already clutching the wallet in his pocket.

The side door wasn’t far, and Fu Chao closed the distance in a few steps, just as the other person completely turned around. Their eyes met, and Fu Chao suddenly tripped, nearly toppling over. When he stabilized, shock was written all over his face, and he was at a loss as he stared at this person who had stopped to look at him.

This was a face that Fu Chao wasn’t unfamiliar with, but he’d never thought he’d have the chance to see this person at this close of a distance. Fu Chao suddenly felt like the fingers clutching his wallet were a bit stiff.

Han Wenqing?

Tyranny’s Captain Han Wenqing?

Fu Chao’s brain had completely shut down. How did the stadium worker he’d been planning to bribe suddenly turn into Han Wenqing?

He just looked like him. That must be it, right?

Just as Fu Chao thought this, he heard another voice from inside the doorway.

“What’s going on?”

And then another person walked out, one hand adjusting his glasses, and looked at Fu Chao.

Zhang… Zhang Xinjie?

Fu Chao loosened the hand clutching his wallet in his pants pocket, and pinched his leg. It hurt.

“Who’s shouting?”

Another sound, another person walked out.

Zhang… Zhang Jiale?

Tyranny’s three fierce generals were actually standing in front of him right now, living and breathing.

“How come you’re not coming?”

Another new voice.

Was it Lin Jingyan? Evidently, Fu Chao had adjusted, and was already beginning to subconsciously make predictions. But the person who came out…

Wang… Wang Jiexi?

Fu Chao felt another wave of dizziness. It was actually Tiny Herb’s Captain Wang Jiexi, another impossibly major figure.

“What’s going on?”

“What are you guys doing?”

One voice after another, one person after another. Less than three meters in front of him, Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Li Xuan, Chu Yunxiu, Yang Cong, Yu Feng…

Fu Chao felt like his five senses were destroyed for good.

Is this magic? Is this some cosplay group? How come so many gods suddenly appeared out of this little door? Glory’s top gods!

And then – what are they doing here? Are they all looking at me? What am I supposed to do? Immediately kneel on the ground and beg forgiveness? That’s not right, I don’t think I had the chance to do anything wrong yet? Then what should I do? Go up to them and say “it is an honor to meet you all”? Damn, isn’t that a bit dramatic? I have to change the tone, but how should I say it?

As Fu Chao pondered, the pro gods all exchanged glances, each with expressions of confusion. In the end, it was Han Wenqing who, unsure whether to laugh or cry, swept his gaze over everyone and said, “Someone just shouted to hold the door. What are you all doing?” After that, he simply entered the door first.

As soon as everyone heard that it was just that, that they’d all dragged each other into this for nothing, they all laughed and re-entered the door. The last one to enter was Tiny Herb’s Xu Bin, who looked at Fu Chao, and left the door open for him.

This is…

Fu Chao hadn’t yet figured out how to greet so many gods when they’d all already went back inside. But they’d left the door for him, and Fu Chao, remembering his original intention, rushed forward and caught the door. Looking around, there were people not too far away, but none of them seemed to be paying attention to this area, so Fu Chao entered, closed the door, and then realized that he’d actually managed to sneak in just like that. And the people that had led the way for him were all of Glory’s top gods.

This is… they misunderstood, and thought he was a worker?

Fu Chao’s mind was actually quite good, being able to think of a plan like this. Just earlier, he had been knocked a bit silly by the continuous appearance of so many gods, but now he returned to normal, and it only took a moment to realize what had happened.

These pro gods of course weren’t any cosplay group, they’d also come to watch the finals live. But to have them walk in through the front doors would definitely cause unthinkable chaos, so the stadium had specially prepared for them an unassuming side passageway. Fu Chao had mistakenly ended up here, just in time to see all of these gods entering. He’d shouted without seeing who it was, and so the gods had mistakenly thought that he was a stadium worker, and he’d cheated his way in just like that.

So lucky!

How excited he felt! Excited at being able to enter the stadium, and even more excited at having done so through this kind of method. At this moment, Fu Chao felt like his desire to see the match wasn’t even as strong as before. He was more excited to get online and gossip about this legendary encounter to all of his friends.

His heart was surging, but Fu Chao didn’t dare show it on his face. He had to maintain this misunderstanding.

Soon, there was a bright light coming from up ahead, and the sounds of cheering rang clearer and clearer. He was just about to enter the main stadium area, the stadium of the finals.

Fu Chao’s thoughts instantly returned to the match. He didn’t just come to the finals for the excitement. Fu Chao, as a City H resident, had been converted into a hardcore Happy fan after a season of matches, and he couldn’t wait to see Happy defeat Samsara, a never-before-seen black horse miracle.

Go Happy!

Go Samsara!

The stadium echoed with the sounds of cheering from the two teams’ fanclubs. Although Samsara was the away team, they had a very strong following, as expected of the current most powerful team in the Alliance. Aside from the fans that had followed the team here, even in City H they had a number of supporters. Right now, even though they couldn’t overturn Happy’s home stadium, they could still make some waves here. They weren’t suppressed by Happy’s home at all.

“Defeat Samsara!!”

Fu Chao was instantly angry. This was Happy’s stadium. No matter what team came, this sort of pride and arrogance just wasn’t allowed. Although he didn’t even have a seat, he simply stood in the passageway and started shouting. As for where the pro gods had gone to sit down after arriving, Fu Chao forgot to pay attention.

“Sir, please quickly return to your seat.”

Jumping around like this in the passageway, Fu Chao quickly drew attention, and a worker came over. But the worker didn’t suspect that he didn’t have a ticket, and simply instructed him to return to his seat in the interest of maintaining order.

“Alright alright, as soon as I go to the bathroom I’ll return to my seat.” Fu Chao had already thought about how to remain undetected after making it into the stadium. Just now, he’d forgotten himself and attracted attention, and when the worker came up to speak to him, he regretted it so much that he wanted to hit himself. He’d hurriedly used a bathroom excuse, and the worker hadn’t become suspicious, so he quickly headed to the bathroom.

He hid in the bathroom for quite a while.

Watching the time, hearing the shouts from the stadium, Fu Chao grit his teeth and endured. The stadium stopped letting people in half an hour before the match officially began, and during that half an hour, the stadium went through strict procedures to secure the area. To stay in the stadium during this time without a seat, he would be discovered very easily. Fu Chao had to last through this period of time. After the match officially began, if there wasn’t an absolute need, there wouldn’t be any large movements from security. At that time, if workers were still wandering around everywhere and disrupting the audience, they would probably be blasted to death.

8:30…

Fu Chao’s watch had slid to this time, and he could hear the sounds from the stadium. The match was indeed just about to begin.

Group arena, Happy’s first player was still Ye Xiu. That “full rookie roster” he’d talked about in the press conference last time indeed turned out to be nonsense.

Samsara’s first player was Lu Boyuan, the All-Star Grappler player.

“You have to win!” Fu Chao could only sit in the bathroom, grind his teeth, and pray. The match had only just begun, so to be safe, he was prepared to wait for a few more minutes. On one hand, he hoped for Happy to win quickly; on the other, he hoped they could play a little longer so he wouldn’t miss as much. One could only imagine the conflict in his heart.

Two minutes passed…

He couldn’t hold back any longer!

Fu Chao charged out of the bathroom, and flew back toward the main stadium area.

Victory!

Happy opened strong. Ye Xiu, undefeated in individual match, continued his brilliant record this season, coming onstage first and defeating Samsara’s Lu Boyuan.

“Beautiful!!!” By the time Fu Chao arrived, all he saw was the word “GLORY,” but even so, he was as thrilled and excited as if he’d seen the entire process. But after waving his fist once, he immediately remembered that he was supposed to be lying low, and after carefully examining his surroundings, Fu Chao began to sneak around, looking for a corner where he wouldn’t be noticed.

The match continued.

Only now did Fu Chao remember that so many top gods had come to this stadium to watch the match live. Where were these people sitting now?

With how large this stadium was, there was of course no way he could find them. But when he thought about it, he knew that these people would definitely be gathered together, and the stadium would definitely have special security measures around them. As someone who didn’t even have a ticket, Fu Chao would be looking for death if he tried to find where they were and slip in among them.

Here’s a good spot!

Fu Chao finally found a seat that he was relatively satisfied with. Standing, sitting, or crouching, just being able to sneak in here and enjoy this match was satisfying enough.

That was what Fu Chao had originally thought, at least. But in the end, he found that he was wrong.

To be truly satisfying, the match itself needed to have a satisfying outcome. But today’s match ended in Happy’s defeat. In the finals, Samsara took the lead in their away game.

Chapter 1579 - Heart’s Longing

Happy lost.

The result of the first match of the finals was like a bucket of cold water, instantly splashing many people awake.

Just before this match had begun, when the poll had finally closed, Happy had actually obtained a 51.1% support rate. They had actually surpassed the defending champions Samsara.

Because of this, Happy's supporters were very excited. They forgot that this poll only represented people's hopes. Happy had more support only because people were curious and excited to see the black horse, the underdogs, overturn the giants.

Votes didn't determine the teams' strengths.

Votes certainly couldn't determine this match's outcome.

Happy didn't lose faith from their two losses to Samsara in the regular season. And Samsara? They weren't scared of how Happy had consecutively defeated Blue Rain and Tyranny in the playoffs.

In comparison, it was clearly Samsara, having eliminated both of their opponents 2-0, who was more at ease in the playoffs.

Because they were more at ease, Samsara obtained more sufficient time to rest. While Happy was bitterly fighting their third match against Tyranny, Samsara had rested for a full six days.

This battle had been very exhausting for Happy, especially the last half-hour of the team round. Tyranny, with only four players left and no healer, had stubbornly and fiercely fought against Happy for half an hour. They had still lost, but Happy had paid a large price for this victory.

After that bitter battle, Happy returned to City H that night. After rushing about, they really only had two full days of rest. And then they met Samsara, who had calmly adjusted their condition for six days.

Six days without battle wouldn't cause any deterioration in condition, because the span of six days was just about the length of time between matches in the regular season. Pro teams and players had more experience using six days to adjust their condition than they did using three days.

From the contents of the first match, it could be seen that although Happy still carried that fierce excitement from their battle with Tyranny, this excitement soon turned into their burden. Their spirits, not having relaxed enough from that battle, were once again tightened, and they quickly lost the tension that they needed.

Happy lost.

This shouldn't have been too surprising of an outcome.

But because of their earlier excellent performance, because it was their home game, people placed high hopes on Happy. In the face of this outcome, these people were helpless.

There were many analyses searching for reasons for Happy's loss, and practically every article pointed to their exhaustion from Tyranny's match.

The reason was there, but now, could Happy solve it?

After this, there was still only three days of rest time. Samsara had won at their away game, and their spirits were high. And Happy? Could they stabilize when they were one game down?

That night at midnight, voting for the second match opened, and Samsara's support rate surged…

Sometimes gamers would vote for the team they hoped would win, but usually they voted for the team they expected to win.

Hope was a type of aspiration, while expectation came from a type of trust.

Happy was still a black horse, and people still could only put their hopes of a revolution on them. But now, their hopes weren't as energetic as they'd been at the start. Because of the first round's loss, these hopes had wavered, had been shaken.

Happy's support rate trembled in the balance.

Three days passed, and they returned to City S, Samsara's home stadium. When the poll closed before the match, Happy's support rate had fallen to 39.1%.

There were still a number of people who hoped for a miracle. But a greater number people now followed logic in their prediction, giving their vote to Samsara.

61.9%.

With this kind of support rate, Samsara was about to turn this support into reality. They were about to win the Season 10 championship, their third consecutive championship, and build the second dynasty in Glory history – the Samsara dynasty.

This kind of slogan was already being proclaimed in the stadium. Samsara's fans couldn't wait to welcome this day. And Samsara's stadium had already prepared a magnificent celebratory ceremony, celebrating the establishment of the Samsara dynasty.

The stadium's atmosphere was joyous. It felt nothing like the tense excitement of a playoffs match, it felt like an award ceremony.

"How irritating!"

Pro players had a very sharp sense of the atmosphere of a stadium. That crowd of Glory stars who watched the first match in Xiaoshan Stadium now gathered in City S to watch the showdown of this second round. This atmosphere in Samsara's stadium of a dynasty being born, as though they'd already won the championship, was very irritating to these competitive players, exceptionally irritating.

"Ye Xiu, that guy, can't he show some promise? Where's the spirit he had when he fought us!" Huang Shaotian shouted indignantly. To be honest, for these people, watching from the audience as two teams fought for the championship was quite painful. No one wanted to see Samsara establish their dynasty, but they also weren't happy at all at the prospect of Happy winning the championship. So even as they were upset at Samsara, they had to criticize Happy as well. And they definitely had to criticize Ye Xiu. Criticize and criticize again.

"Say, all of us running here together to see this finals match, are we looking for pain or looking for pain?" said Void's Li Xuan, deeply understanding this uncomfortable feeling.

"We will witness history!" said Zhang Xinjie.

If Samsara won the championship, a new dynasty would be born, and history would be made. If Happy won the championship, they were a black horse, a new team that won the championship just after joining the Alliance. That, too, would enter Glory's history books.

"So we're standing in a historical moment!" Tang Hao said sarcastically, even mocking himself along with everyone.

These people didn't want to witness any history. They came here, came to Glory's battlefield, in order to create their own history. Each of them wanted to be a participant. But now, they had become bystanders.

Pop!

Next to Li Xuan, Wu Yuce cracked open a drink, the sound crisp. Everyone else was silent. To explain in relation to the fans in the rest of the audience, these players here were all fans, far more dedicated and loyal than any other fan. They were fans of themselves, their own teams, and this would never change at any moment. So, when they watched this match, they didn't particularly wish for either side's victory. What they wished most of all was to go onstage themselves and destroy both of those teams, and of course, if they could destroy all these people around them right now, that would be nice too.

The atmosphere was oppressive.

"Captain do you want to drink anything, I'll go buy!" Tiny Herb's Liu Xiaobie jumped up. He didn't like this kind of pressure, and so he found an excuse to temporarily escape.

"A Coke, thanks," Wang Jiexi said.

"Get two bottles for me too," Royal Style's Tian Sen said.

"I'd like a mineral water," Li Xuan said, nodding.

"Get me a bottle of milk tea," Chu Yunxiu also requested of Liu Xiaobie.

"I want a green tea."

"I want a black tea."

With everyone talking at the same time, Liu Xiaobie instantly collapsed. "I can't remember that many!"

"Write it down on your phone," Xiao Shiqin suggested, very kind-heartedly.

Liu Xiaobie sighed and pulled out his phone.

"Come on, faster, get that hand speed up!" Misty Rain's Li Hua said, pushing forward to watch Liu Xiaobie type.

On his phone, a long list of requests quickly stretched out. Practically no one was polite with him. Liu Xiaobie felt like crying. He suddenly felt like that oppressive atmosphere earlier was quite good, a great time to examine his own strengths and faults!

"This many, I can't hold them all…" Liu Xiaobie said weakly, after writing down everyone's requests.

"Just make a few extra trips," said Xiao Shiqin. As expected of the most detail-oriented Master Tactician, the king of ideas.

"With such fast hands, your legs should be pretty quick too, no?" Dai Yanqi supported her captain.

Liu Xiaobie was already despairing. He slowly began to trudge away, but when he felt at his pocket, his spirits suddenly lifted. He flipped his pockets inside-out and then laughed loudly. "Ahahaha, I forgot to bring my wallet today."

"We're already giving you so much trouble, how could we let you pay out of pocket too!" Yu Wenzhou, calm as always, pulled out his own wallet. "I'll treat everyone."

"Alright!!" Yu Feng led the applause, boosting his former captain.

"Captain, save me!!" Liu Xiaobie was about to kneel down in front of Wang Jiexi.

"A few others go with him, the match is about to start." Wang Jiexi spoke justice.

And so the younger players of the various teams here all voluntarily stood up, teaming up to carry out this task.

Everyone began to quietly wait for the match to begin.

These pro players didn't care too much about who would win, and there was no need to come to watch the match live if they just wanted to analyze their opponents. Yet even so, they had all gathered here.

In the end, their heart's longing still haunted them. Everyone here wished that they were the ones standing on that stage.

They couldn't participate in the finals. Then, it was still nice to come here and experience the atmosphere live…

Chapter 1580 - Win Streak Pattern

The finals. Countless pro players and even ordinary gamers would dream of this ultimate PK stage, and now, the ones standing on that stage were Happy and Samsara.

After losing the first round, Happy had no room for error. But defeating Samsara in their home stadium, so far, not a single team had accomplished it this season. Samsara’s stadium had become territory that no one in the Alliance could capture. Tyranny, Blue Rain, Tiny Herb, these powerful names had found only defeat here. The team that had come closest was actually Hundred Blossoms, in Round 38 of the regular season, ending their battle against Samsara with 4-6. And what they’d approached was only a tie…

After leaving their city first, the upcoming matches would both occur in their defended fortress, and this round’s fortress was undoubtedly the strongest. This round, Samsara had the advantage of map choice.

“This time we won’t hold back anymore!”

But before the match, the one who spoke first was actually Happy’s Ye Xiu. When he said this, his attitude was so confident and righteous that even the judge felt a bit embarrassed. Without context, one could actually believe that Happy had purposely let Samsara win in the first round.

How could that be true.

This was the playoffs, the teams were fighting for every inch of land. And moreover, this was the finals, the stage where ownership of the championship would be determined – even that description of the struggle didn’t feel strong enough!

“Who will Happy send up first?” Looking at the large display screen, the pro players in the audience were all deep in discussion. If they went from habit, then it would definitely be Ye Xiu. All this time, Ye Xiu had fought Happy’s first battle.

But if this arrangement became a certainty in the minds of the opponents, then if there was a sudden change or adjustment, then it would be a very surprising blow.

Among the pros, there was no lack of smart and resourceful people. In their minds, Happy may have used this arrangement all this time just so that they could surprise their opponents in a crucial moment.

And now, this was the finals, and Happy was down one game. They had no more path of retreat. If they didn’t use this surprise tactic now, wouldn’t they have wasted the set way of thinking that they’d built up in their opponents’ minds over the course of this season?

“Ye Xiu.” But in the crowd of pro players, someone spoke with complete certainty that Ye Xiu would be the first onstage.

Han Wenqing.

The one who understood Ye Xiu even more than the Happy players did.

Han Wenqing of course understood that Ye Xiu wasn’t a rigid and unchanging person. As long as it was for victory, anything could happen when it came to Ye Xiu.

But at the same time, he also understood clearly, Ye Xiu wasn’t someone who would shy away from responsibility at a crucial point. Ye Xiu’s win streak exerted a great pressure on his opponents, but when the win streak became a fixed pattern, this pressure would gradually transfer to Ye Xiu as well. Once this pattern was broken, Team Happy would suffer the effects, so Ye Xiu had to maintain this pattern.

And it was exactly because of this that many people would think that not going first was a smart thing to do. This way, the pattern wouldn’t be broken, and there would be no risk of it being broken.

But this would be deceiving the self as well as the enemy.

Now that Ye Xiu had solidified his win streak pattern to this extent, for him to suddenly change it, too many people would probably think that this was a sign of weakness. Even if there was very logical strategy to explain it, it couldn’t completely eliminate the shadow over the heart.

A shadow over others, that didn’t matter, but if Happy’s own players had no way of dispelling this shadow, and it affected their condition, then there wouldn’t be much difference between this and the win streak pattern directly breaking.

Comparing the two situations, there was greater opportunity if Ye Xiu continued to go first. And Han Wenqing still believed firmly that Ye Xiu had the bravery to take up this kind of pressure.

As expected!

Looking at the players onstage, everyone quickly realized that while the pros on both sides were showing signs of leaving the stage, only Ye Xiu took a step forward.

“Who’s coming to die first?” Ye Xiu asked Samsara. Happy’s first player was still him.

Hua!

Applause.

The Happy fans, in this deadly Samsara stadium, desperately sent applause to their team and their captain.

Knowing that the mountain hid a tiger, yet advancing toward that mountain anyway. Just this bravery was worthy of great recognition.

“Senior really is quite cunning!” But then, someone from Samsara spoke, unhurried, wearing a smile.

“To be able to win consecutively for so long, everyone feels that it only gets harder and harder. If another win can be gotten under these circumstances, the morale boost to your own team and the blow to the other team reaches a peak. On the other hand, because the win streak has gone on for so long, everyone has recognized the difficulty, so perhaps too many people have already made mental preparations for the streak to be broken, right? Even if the streak was broken, I imagine it wouldn’t hurt your team’s morale too much either,” said Samsara’s vice-captain Jiang Botao. “You have this double-edged sword, yet the side facing you has already been blunted, while the side facing us is as sharp as ever. Senior, you have sharpened a good sword!”

“It looks like you recognized this pretty clearly!” Ye Xiu also smiled.

“What I know more clearly is this: the side of Senior’s sword that faces us is, in fact, not that sharp. A win streak is only a record. Five wins, ten wins, a hundred wins, in reality, it doesn’t have any impact on the outcome of the upcoming match. It’s like flipping a coin. If it came up heads last time, everyone feels that it’s a bit more likely that it’ll come up tails the next time. But actually, every time you flip a coin, the chance of heads is always the same, 50%. The chance of flipping 10 heads consecutively is the same as the chance of flipping any other sequence of outcomes.”

“This is a very complicated math problem, you can’t draw a conclusion lightly! In a bit, come over and learn from the outstanding student in our team. As for right now, are you ready to meet your death?” Ye Xiu said.

“No, no. It’s not me.” Jiang Botao smiled, and took two steps back.

And at the same time, the stadium display lit up with the rosters of the two teams for the group arena. And onstage, Samsara’s first player walked forward from the rest of the team.

Whoa!

Instantly, the stadium was filled with shocked exclamations.

Zhou Zekai!

It was actually Zhou Zekai. Samsara’s first player in the group arena was actually their core player, the one currently called the number one of Glory, Zhou Zekai.

“Oh…” Ye Xiu was also caught off-guard, and then he glanced at Jiang Botao and smiled. “It looks like you guys are pretty cunning too.”

“Likewise.” Jiang Botao smiled as well.

Jiang Botao had clearly laid out all of the implications and deceptions hidden beneath Ye Xiu’s win streak pattern, but Samsara still didn’t back down. They actually sent out their strongest player to deal a strong blow to Happy’s spirit, just like many teams had tried before.

But they had made this arrangement while knowing all of the depths of Ye Xiu’s win streak. This was psychological warfare at a higher level. They were using their powerful self-confidence to pressure Happy. And this kind of confidence came from their past championships, from their huge lead throughout the regular season, from their two 2-0 victories in the playoffs, from defeating Happy in their away game.

They thoroughly used their advantage and their situational lead. Without doubt, Samsara was not a team that had only outstanding skill and no brains.

Jiang Botao, huh?

Ye Xiu smiled. The opponent before him was Zhou Zekai, but his gaze still lingered on Jiang Botao.

“The younger generation is worthy of respect,” Ye Xiu said.

“Thank you for the compliment.” Jiang Botao smiled modestly.

“It looks like I have the responsibility to show you guys how fearsome we seniors are!” Ye Xiu said.

Jiang Botao continued to smile, and didn’t respond. After all, he wasn’t the one going onstage right now.

“Little Zhou, don’t get too confident,” Ye Xiu said to Zhou Zekai.

“I won’t.” Zhou Zekai shook his head and walked toward Samsara’s competitor booth.

“Good luck, Senior!” Jiang Botao shouted to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu lifted his head to look at the roster on the display, and nodded in satisfaction. “The next one is you! I like this arrangement very much.”

“Senior should focus on the upcoming match first!” Jiang Botao said.

“Don’t worry, just wait for me.” He actually said that kind of sentence to the opponent. The judge looked like his world was being fundamentally changed. And then, Ye Xiu also walked toward the competitor booth, while the rest of the players quickly left the stage. Round 2 of the finals, first battle of the group arena, was just about to begin. Players: Happy’s Ye Xiu versus Samsara’s Zhou Zekai.

One was the past, one was the present. Both called the number one players in Glory, they now met onstage. Today’s face-off was already off to an extremely thrilling start.

Chapter 1581 - Three Minute Coincidence

It was as if a tempest had suddenly burst onto the scene, a match between Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai.

The former versus current number one would be a sensational confrontation. But at first, even the news reporters didn’t have high hopes for it happening.

Ye Xiu playing first was a given at this point. On the other hand, Samsara had always acted according to convention, placing their ace player at the third or fourth position. The likelihood of these two encountering each other in the group arena was miniscule. Even if Samsara wanted to break Ye Xiu’s legendary win streak, their team had another reliable 1v1 expert: Sun Xiang. Placing Sun Xiang first and then having Zhou Zekai guard the third or fourth position seemed to be a more likely lineup for Samsara.

Sun Xiang and Ye Xiu had a lot of history between them as well, but their confrontation had already peaked at the Challenger League finals last season.Ye Xiu had left Excellent Era and then led Happy to eliminate Excellent Era. It was a fierce slap in the face to Excellent Era and his successor, Sun Xiang.

The story had ended, and the media had been satisfied with the conclusion. Bringing it up again wouldn’t bring anything new to the table. But seeing that it was unlikely for a confrontation between the current and former number one player, it seemed like they would have to settle for the next best thing. They could talk about Sun Xiang’s growth in Samsara,whether he had walked out from the shadows of his past failures, and so on.

As it turned out, there was no need for any of that, and the media wasn’t at all sorry.

Compared to a match between the former and current number one player, who cared about a revenge story for Sun Xiang!

The reporters were ecstatic.

Everyone was excited.

Even the people who felt like Samsara’s arrangements might not be the most optimal move were hyped for the match.

Ye Xiu had once been the dominant number one player in Glory, but after his retirement, Zhou Zekai had taken that title for himself. Between the two, who was truly number one? The outcome of a 1v1 between the two players would be the most persuasive support for one side, even if making a conclusion from a single match was rather negligent…

Why hasn’t it started yet?

Both players had entered their respective player booths, but it wasn’t yet time for the scheduled match to start. Their thoughts showed how hyped they were for this match.

“To think they would send Zhou Zekai to start!!” The pro players were discussing this topic amongst each other as well. They were very curious too.

But today’s referee wouldn’t be swayed by the hype. He knew that everyone was waiting impatiently to see the fight, but he still followed the schedule strictly, waiting until it was 8 o’clock sharp.

Begin!

All sorts of sound effects and lights came on to hype up the audience.

Was there really a need?

Not really. The finals was hype in and of itself. Lights, sound effects? At this moment, they couldn’t hold a candle to thunderous cheers and applause from the crowd.

The characters were loading.

The map was loading.

As for the viewers watching in front of their TV and their computers? They were listening to Pan Lin and Li Yibo talking rapid-fire. There were too many things to talk about, and the two were scrambling excitedly to get their thoughts out. To listeners, it as almost like a bombardment of words.

“Map, Dripstone Cave.”

Although the two commentators were fighting to speak, the content of their commentary was on point. The things that they needed to talk about were talked about. The map had finished loading. For this match, Samsara had chosen Dripstone Cave.

“Oh… this map…”

“The stalagmites and stalactites in the cave aren’t actually packed together as tightly as a forest, so even Gunners have a good amount of room to maneuver around in.” Li Yibo wasn’t sure how to describe it, so Pan Lin immediately picked up on the explanation.

“Good doesn’t do it justice. The way the stalactites are arranged make it extremely suitable for Gunners. Large open areas aren’t necessarily the best for long-ranged classes like Gunners. Terrain that provides cover for them is very advantageous for them too,” Li Yibo added, all in one breath.

“For Samsara, who has Zhou Zekai, this map seems to be quite favorable for them,” Pan Lin followed.

“Although Ye Xiu’s unspecialized can play up close or from afar, the unspecialized is far more threatening up close. As a result, this map isn’t as favorable for his unspecialized compared to Zhou Zekai’s Sharpshooter,” Li Yibo said.

“By choosing this map, Samsara takes the upper hand first,” Pan Lin said.

The map was still loading, and the two had already gone back and forth and said so much.

“Okay, it’s done loading. The match has officially begun.” This sort of announcement was oftentimes Pan Lin’s responsibility, so he had more experience timing it. Li Yibo was just about to say it, but in the end, he still fell behind.

Dripstone Cave took place in an enclosed circular cave. Mineral formations were scattered all throughout the area. These were the one special feature of this map.

As Li Yibo had analyzed, the dripstones – the stalagmites and stalactites – weren’t densely packed together. For a practiced Sharpshooter, there was a lot of space to maneuver around in. It could be considered a very technical map.

Zhou Zekai was considered the number one player in Glory at the moment. His mastery over his class didn’t need to be said. In addition, Samsara had chosen this map, so there was no doubt about his familiarity with the terrain.

Cloud Piercer walked lightly and quickly. The broadcast switched it over to his perspective to let everyone see how he moved.

As for Ye Xiu? He didn’t move as freely or confidently as Zhou Zekai. Starting from his very first step, Lord Grim moved around very cautiously. He would constantly be looking around, taking careful note of where he had already gone. He clearly wasn’t as familiar with this map as Zhou Zekai. Under these circumstances, choosing to move in a roundabout manner was standard, and Ye Xiu was no exception. The only notable part was that the detour that he took was very large. It didn’t look like he was planning on circling around to get behind his opponent but rather to get as far as away as possible from him.

A minute passed. If the two sides had chosen to go straight towards the center, sparks would already be flying. But right now? A minute had passed, and the fight that everyone had been waiting for was nowhere to be seen. It was all because Ye Xiu’s detour was too excessive.

“He probably wants to explore the map first…” Pan Lin said as he watched Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim hug the wall and go around in a big circle.

“Ye Xiu might not be familiar with this particular map, but he should have experience with this sort of terrain! He shouldn’t need this much time to get used to it. It seems like he’s being very prudent with this match,” Li Yibo said.

“Of course he needs to be prudent, his opponent is Zhou Zekai!” Pan Lin said.

Zhou Zekai!

Zhou Zekai!

A burst of thunderous cheers erupted from the crowd. Even though nothing had happened for a minute, the passion from Zhou Zekai’s fans hadn’t diminished. The fight between the former and current number one? They didn’t care about it. In their eyes, Zhou Zekai was without a doubt the best. Their excitement for this fight was because they were waiting for Zhou Zekai to win and settle this debate once and for all.

A minute had passed, the hype was still there.

A minute and a half…

Two minutes…

Three minutes…

The hype was still there because the two still hadn’t started fighting yet. As for Pan Lin and Li Yibo, they were starting to run out of things to say.

The map wasn’t large, so if two had just been randomly wandering around, they would have likely bumped into each other during these three minutes. However, the two seemed to move along parallel lines. Even now, they had yet to meet.

Was he deliberately trying to avoid fighting?

It was hard to tell!

Besides the big detour that Ye Xiu had Lord Grim take in the beginning, he seemed to be actively looking for Zhou Zekai, but the two never seemed to be able to find each other.

Was it all just a coincidence?

Everyone was speechless. The referee wasn’t sure either. He didn’t see any illegal conduct. An intervention under these circumstances would require a lot of courage. Moreover, this was the finals. His interference could affect who the final champions would be.

He didn’t want to make an intervention. He felt like if neither of them were deliberately trying to avoid the other, the two should soon meet, but this had already lasted for three minutes.

Three minutes wasn’t that long, but on the Glory competitive stage, three minutes of nothing was enough to extinguish a lot of enthusiasm from the crowd. The excitement for this fight was crumbling by the second. The Zhou Zekai fans had stopped cheering at this point, instead choosing to mock and deride Ye Xiu. In their eyes, Zhou Zekai was not at fault. On the other hand, Ye Xiu’s detour at the beginning looked to be the reason. Former versus current number one? What a joke. Anyone who had been hyped for that was truly blind.

“Too naive.” The pro players heard the derision from the crowd and disagreed with it, especially the older pros.

How could Ye Xiu be avoiding the opponent? Especially on the competitive stage, avoiding the opponent wouldn’t result in anything. Did you think this was the online game? You couldn’t avoid a fight forever.

Victory would be decided one way or the other. The two would have to fight. It was just that three minutes of nothing was indeed quite strange.

“Do you think it’s a coincidence?” Everyone was asking each other. They were wondering if it was all just a coincidence.

The majority of the answers was “No”.

“Look at it from a bird’s eye view and pay attention to Ye Xiu’s positioning,” Zhang Xinjie said.

The projection technology didn’t show the match from this view, but the large screen in the stadium displayed it. Apart from the projection technology, the crowd also had a large screen displaying a live broadcast. Besides an exciting live atmosphere, the stadium provided an additional viewing experience that those sitting in front of their computers or TV couldn’t get.

A bird’s eye view had always been an advantage that the live audience had over the viewers watching from home.

And this bird’s eye view revealed the secret behind these three minutes of nothing.

Chapter 1582 - Web

Positioning.

Zhang Xinjie reminded everyone, and so everyone took a look at Lord Grim’s position.

Because the map cave was an enclosed space, the bird’s eye view showed two layers. The cave ceiling was depicted as a translucent layer that overlapped with the ground underneath. For normal viewers, it was easy to get confused, but the pro players had no trouble distinguishing between the two layers. After finding Lord Grim’s position through the bird’s eye view of the map, everyone quickly realized what they should be paying attention to.

The dripstone surrounding Lord Grim.

The pro players quickly understood the reason why Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai had yet to encounter each other.

Luck was a part of it, but the foundation for this luck was purposefully constructed by Ye Xiu. Lord Grim had been taking advantage of the surrounding dripstone to hide himself. It wasn’t as simple as just hiding behind a piece of dripstone. He was carefully keeping track of what sort of cover the surrounding dripstone could provide him. As a result, the surrounding ten units of dripstone formed a sort of net that blocked the enemy’s vision. Lord Grim would always move towards the area in the net that provided him the most cover.

Under this protection, if Zhou Zekai wanted to find Lord Grim, his Cloud Piercer would need to fortuitously be in a few specific positions. However, what was more depressing for the viewers was that Ye Xiu clearly knew where these positions were, so he would constantly be adjusting his positioning.

After recognizing this point, Zhang Xinjie turned to look towards his teammate, Qin Muyun.

Qin Muyun understood his vice-captain’s intent and slowly shook his head: “I wouldn’t be able to do it.”

Qin Muyun was a player with exceptional talent as positioning, but he didn’t hesitate to reach this conclusion. He wasn’t able to move around like Ye Xiu could in this map.

“This sort of positioning requires a lot of experience to do,” Han Wenqing explained why Qin Muyun wasn’t able to do it.

“What about you, captain?” Song Qiying asked.

Han Wenqing stared blankly for a moment before shaking his head helplessly: “I wouldn’t be able to do it as meticulously as him.”

Experience. Han Wenqing didn’t lack experience. Positioning was a fundamental part of Glory, and after so many years of playing Glory, his fundamentals couldn’t be lacking either. Experience alone wasn’t enough to do what Ye Xiu was doing though. Ye Xiu’s positioning required careful calculations, and that wasn’t Han Wenqing’s strong point.

“What about you, Wang Jiexi?” Zhang Xinjie asked the person next to him.

“Hard to say,” Wang Jiexi shook his head. He understood how Ye Xiu was positioning himself, but unless he was there himself, he couldn’t be certain.

“There’s no bird’s eye view while playing,” Wang Jiexi pointed out where the difficulty lay. This made many of the players, who thought that they could do it too, wake up from their glee.

“But so what if he can do it?” No one knew who asked the question, but there was no lack of spite in it. This person was right, though. So far, it hadn’t seemed to amount to anything.

What was Ye Xiu planning?

They began trying to figure out Ye Xiu’s intentions. However, they weren’t the first to figure it out because they didn’t know what the two teams had planned out before the match.

On the sidelines, Samsara’s Jiang Botao noticed Ye Xiu’s actions and quickly realized his goals.

Finish him off in a burst of energy!

Samsara’s Zhou Zekai had come onto the stage with this goal in mind. Samsara wanted to try overwhelm Happy mentally.

But Ye Xiu used this sort of evasive positioning to destroy their plans.

Three minutes. The two sides hadn’t even crossed blows yet, but even if Zhou Zekai won in the end, the momentum that Samsara had wanted to ride all the way through the group arena had already been put to a stop.

Only the two opposing teams could understand the subtlety in Ye Xiu’s actions. The current Happy looked calm and relaxed. As for Samsara? It was as if a knife had stabbed through their hearts, their spirits dampened.

“As expected of Ye Xiu.” Jiang Botao had no choice but to accept the outcome. They had sent Zhou Zekai out first to put mental pressure onto Happy, but Ye Xiu had already dispelled it. Next, they would just have to wait and see how the battle would turn out.

Lord Grim continued to wander around, using the same positioning tactics. During these three minutes of avoiding, Ye Xiu became more and more familiar with the map, and Lord Grim began to move a lot faster. But for a moment, it didn’t seem like he would be encountering Cloud Piercer any time soon.

Just when everyone was wondering how long this grind would last, they suddenly heard a gunshot.

Without any warning, Lord Grim raised his umbrella and fired a shot into the air.

The sound of the gunshot echoed through the cave. Zhou Zekai clearly heard it. Cloud Piercer stopped, turned around, and then headed towards the direction of the sound.

How precise!

The crowd cheered. The gunshot had broken through the previous silence, invigorating everyone’s spirits again.

Cloud Piercer was already moving toward the direction of the gunshot.

Lord Grim didn’t move though. He simply stood there, looking around.

Most people just thought that Ye Xiu was taking the initiative to lure Zhou Zekai here. Right now, he was looking around to find his target.

They weren’t wrong. Ye Xiu was indeed doing this, but there was an even deeper level.

With how Ye Xiu positioned himself, he knew exactly which spots Cloud Piercer could come from. As a result, when he looked around, he was only paying attention to these few spots. He was ready to attack the moment Cloud Piercer appeared.

Some of these spots were farther than others. The farthest one could be considered mid-range. Ye Xiu hadn’t fired the gunshot at any random moment. He had specifically picked this location. At this position, when he and Zhou Zekai finally found each other, the two would be at a relatively close distance, which was more advantageous for his unspecialized.

These three minutes of avoiding Zhou Zekai hadn’t just been to get rid of the psychological pressure from Samsara, but also to pull the snake from its hole and seize the initiative.

Cloud Piercer appeared!

Of the several possible spots, Cloud Piercer rushed out from one that was neither the farthest nor the closest.

Bang bang!

Two gunshots. Ye Xiu had carefully thought up plans for each of the several spots. As soon as he saw Cloud Piercer, he immediately attacked. After firing twice, Lord Grim rushed out. But suddenly, the glimpse of the gray windbreaker that he had seen disappeared from his sight….

Zhou Zekai had seen Lord Grim, but he didn’t immediately attack. Cloud Piercer seemed to be in a hurry, quickly dashing past that spot. He had only appeared for an instant before disappearing.

Ye Xiu had tried to seize the initiative, but Cloud Piercer was unexpectedly already gone.

Chapter 1583 - Fake Shield

The average viewer wasn’t able to catch this subtlety. From what they saw, the two had finally come across each other. Ye Xiu made the first move, while Zhou Zekai nimbly evaded it.

On the other hand, the pro players also knew that Ye Xiu had tried to create an opportunity through careful positioning. However, the only ones who truly understood the subtleties within this interaction were Ye Xiu and Zhou Zekai.

Two shots!

The moment they saw each other, Ye Xiu fired two shots at him before he could even react.

Zhou Zekai didn’t only possess outstanding mechanic prowess. He wouldn’t become arrogant because people were calling him the number one player in Glory, but he wouldn’t be too modest, either. Modesty and arrogance could both lead to errors in judgement.

Zhou Zekai was confident in himself and could notice the discrepancies in a situation.

His opponent had fired two shots before he could react!

This wasn’t a coincidence.

This was the conclusion that Zhou Zekai reached. He didn’t have a bird’s eye view like the pro players spectating the match, so he didn’t know about Lord Grim’s tactical positioning. However, he was able to use his own way to determine that “Ye Xiu had the initiative.”

As a result, Cloud Piercer didn’t stop to counterattack. Without even the slightest bit of hesitation, he dashed right by.

As for Ye Xiu, after firing two shots, he immediately lost his target.

What a guy!

Ye Xiu internally praised him.

Through that single exchange, Zhou Zekai was able to get a clear grasp on the situation. The title of Glory’s number one player wasn’t purely subjective. Zhou Zekai’s mechanical prowess, intuition, awareness, and mentality were outstanding even within the pro scene. Ye Xiu understood this point clearly.

Because it wasn’t as if he was unfamiliar with Zhou Zekai. Starting from Season 5, apart from his year of retirement in Season 9, the two had fought countless times on stage. He understood Zhou Zekai’s capabilities and how hard he was to deal with.

Relying on a single carefully thought out positioning to seize the initiative and win the match? The thought hadn’t crossed Ye Xiu’s mind. However, he was still caught off guard by the outcome. He hadn’t thought that the opportunity he had created would disappear so quickly. All of the plans that he had prepared instantly fell through.

But the experienced Ye Xiu couldn’t be intimidated so easily.

Change directions!

Lord Grim had initially planned on rushing towards Cloud Piercer right after firing those two shots, but with his plans having gone awry, he turned around and quickly moved away to widen his vision. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer immediately appeared in his sights from a different angle.

Bang bang bang bang!

Sparks flew.

Such dense gunfire couldn’t be produced by Lord Grim’s unspecialized. This sort of burst could have only been done by a Sharpshooter!

Wildfire in his right hand, Shattered Frost in his left.

The gray windbreaker on Cloud Piercer flapped as he moved.

Ye Xiu’s movements had instead given Zhou Zekai the initiative. This scene was eerily similar to the previous scene where Cloud Piercer had stepped into Ye Xiu’s trap.

Zhou Zekai didn’t completely understand Ye Xiu’s tactical positioning, though, so this wasn’t returning a tooth for a tooth. These two top players were simply taking advantage of the terrain.

Ye Xiu had done it through careful observation and precise calculations.

As for Zhou Zekai? Samsara had chosen this map, so how could he not be familiar with it?

Gunfire roared.

Ye Xiu was at gunpoint. That was exactly the situation that Ye Xiu now faced.

Shua. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened. The bullets struck the canvas like a tempest, causing it to shake uncontrollably.

The gunfire was too fierce!

The stadium screen as well as the broadcast picked out data on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

The durability.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had a durability of 23. For a Shield, this was a very low number. Because of how Shields were used, its durability should be much higher than other weapons.

A durability of 23 was the durability of a normal weapon. The umbrella could transform into a Shield, but its durability didn’t change.

How low of a durability was it for a Shield? Using a comparison was best.

Glory’s lowest-level shield, a Level 5 Wooden Shield, had a durability of 20, which wasn’t far from the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s.

In the Heavenly Domain, many Knight players had the Level 70 Purple shield, “Drenched Thorn,” which had a durability of 85.

And the strongest shield in Glory, the “Sighing Wall” owned by Tiny Herb’s Knight Angelica, had a durability of 135.

A high-level shield with a durability of 23? There was no shield with a durability lower than that.

The stadium screen had displayed the umbrella’s durability because Cloud Piercer’s fierce assault was causing its durability to rapidly decrease.

22, 21…

The number was decreasing at a visible speed, showing just how powerful Cloud Piercer’s offense was.

“Run!!” Chen Guo shouted anxiously from Happy’s bench. The durability on the umbrella wasn’t just for the shield form, but for the umbrella as a whole. If this continued, its durability would soon drop to 0, and when the durability of an equipment dropped to 0, it would be destroyed and become useless.

20, 19…

After just a few seconds, the durability on the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had dropped by 4. Facing Cloud Piercer’s burst, the shield appeared frail and weak.

But Lord Grim didn’t run.

During these few seconds, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim continued to hold up his umbrella shield.

It wasn’t that he didn’t want to run, but that there was nowhere to run to!

By widening his vision, Ye Xiu wanted to seize the initiative again, but Zhou Zekai already knew where Lord Grim would likely appear from, and now, Zhou Zekai had the upper hand.

He was just one step faster.

Ye Xiu could only defend against the attacks. There was currently nowhere closeby for Lord Grim to take cover.

As a result, his only choice was to prop up his shield.

For the durability on his shield to be decreasing so rapidly, this sort of dense gunfire couldn’t be avoided through just movement.

There was nowhere to retreat, nowhere to hide, and his umbrella shield wouldn’t be able to last much longer.

Then, his only choice was to push forward and advance under this barrage of bullets!

Charge!

The shield form was considered a Priest weapon, thus, using a Knight’s Charge wasn’t a problem.

Amidst a hail of bullets, Lord Grim charged towards Cloud Piercer.

Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer move horizontally in an attempt to find an angle where he could directly shoot Lord Grim behind his umbrella shield.

As Cloud Piercer moved, his guns stayed steady.

In an instant, he had found the angle, and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella hadn’t moved to adjust to his movements.

Fire!

Bullets flew behind the Myriad Manifestaions Umbrella.

But there was no one there!

Chapter 1584 - Gunshot

Using the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s large canvas to hide Lord Grim’s movements was a trick that Ye Xiu liked to use. There was no way Team Samsara wouldn’t know about it.

Knowing about it and playing against it were two entirely different matters. When Lord Grim held up his umbrella in front of him and used Charge, Zhou Zekai had recognized this possibility. He had observed that Lord Grim should still be behind his umbrella. After all, his umbrella was mid-Charge!

Yes, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was still mid-Charge!

But when Cloud Piercer moved horizontally so that he could attack Lord Grim unobstructed, Lord Grim was gone.

Zhou Zekai was confused for a moment, but he quickly figured out what had happened.

Spirit Guidance!

This was the Exorcist’s Spirit Guidance. Ye Xiu used this skill and threw out his umbrella to make it seem like he had used Charge.

In theory, any Priest class could do this, but no one ever did because no one had a shield that completely covered them like the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Even Zhou Zekai wasn’t able to keep up with the endless skill combinations from the unspecialized. Figuring out that it was Spirit Guidance so quickly was already very impressive.

Lord Grim wasn’t there. Where was he?

Cloud Piercer used Random Firing as he searched his surroundings. Bullets flew in all directions, creating a protective net around himself. Zhou Zekai had unexpectedly adopted a defensive stance.

However, he wasn’t able to locate Lord Grim. He had searched everywhere around him, but no one was there.

How?

How did Lord Grim run so far away in such a short amount of time?

Shadow Clone Technique? Teleport?

There was no shadow clone left behind, but it wouldn’t have been possible anyways. Because his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had been thrown out with a Spirit Guidance, Lord Grim could only use Priest skills. Spirit Guidance wasn’t discarding the weapon. The thrown weapon was still considered equipped even if it wasn’t in the user’s hands. Thus, Lord Grim was stuck as a Priest, and Priest classes didn’t have instant movement skills.

There was only one possibility!

Cloud Piercer leapt to the side. While in the air, he turned around and fired two shots towards the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. A change had already occurred over there. The moment Cloud Piercer turned around to search his surroundings, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella retracted, and Lord Grim appeared. Then, he lifted his umbrella and sprinted towards Cloud Piercer.

Everyone except for Zhou Zekai saw this change.

Yes, it had indeed been Spirit Guidance. Zhou Zekai had guessed correctly. Lord Grim had feigned a Charge by using Spirit Guidance.

Priest classes didn’t have instant movement skills. What Ye Xiu used wasn’t a skill but simply basic movement. He used his stamina to sprint.

He hadn’t moved far, maybe two or three steps. However, with these two three steps, he just happened to be outside of Cloud Piercer’s vision. When Cloud Piercer moved to an angle behind the umbrella, Lord Grim had moved to an angle in front of the umbrella.

It looked like two kids playing a game, but even the normal players knew what terrifying skill was needed to pull it off.

The angle of the umbrella, the timing of the sprint, and the timing for stopping the Spirit Guidance. All of these details were crucial, and the slightest misstep meant failure. Connecting all these parts together was already very difficult, but Ye Xiu had done it all perfectly. It was through this perfect execution that he was able to catch Zhou Zekai off guard.

The moment Zhou Zekai realized what Ye Xiu had done, he had Cloud Piercer leap to the side to dodge. But it was too late. With a Shining Cut, Lord Grim instantly closed the distance, faster than Cloud Piercer could shoot.

Blood splattered into the air.

The Shining Arc cut Cloud Piercer. His guns were aimed in the wrong direction.

Bang bang bang bang!

Cloud Piercer’s dual guns still went off. He wasn’t able to stop himself from firing in time.

But he immediately responded to the current situation, Knee Strike!

Cloud Piercer sent a Knee Strike towards Lord Grim. This skill had a knockback effect, which would help pull apart the distance between them. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim dodged to the side. At the same time, his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella split into two swords, creating two intertwining arcs of light.

Cross Slash!

It was a low-level Assassin skill, which had different effects depending on the weapon. When two swords were used, the swords criss cross, cutting off the target’s movement options.

However, when these intertwining arcs of light flashed out, an opening appeared.

Bang bang bang bang…

Gunfire continued to echo. And just like this, Cloud Piercer was able to make his way past Ye Xiu. After Cloud Piercer had been sliced by the Shining Cut, he was still able to pull away from Lord Grim.

Aimed in the wrong direction?

Unable to stop himself from firing?

Anyone who had these thoughts was gravely mistaken.

Zhou Zekai hadn’t made a mistake. He had been aiming toward where the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had previously been. Miss?

His goal wasn’t to attack. If his Random Firing from before had been him playing defensively, then his Cloud Piercer was currently playing the run-away game. He hadn’t fired his dual guns to attack, but rather to use the recoil to help him move.

Zhou Zekai was using Aerial Fire!

People still didn’t realize it even after Cloud Piercer pulled away from Lord Grim. They thought that Zhou Zekai had done something miraculous, when in reality, it was simply a result of his immediate response to not finding Lord Grim during his search.

Cloud Piercer had pulled away from Lord Grim, but it was no more than three body-lengths away. After Lord Grim’s Cross Slash missed, he readjusted himself and attacked again with Teleporting Stab!

In Happy’s match against Tyranny, Ye Xiu had chosen to put Flickering Stab on his Assassin weapon form, giving everyone a deep impression. This time, he used a similar skill to Flickering Stab: Teleporting Stab!

The distance was instantly closed!

But this move wasn’t considered a teleport.

No matter how fast it was, Lord Grim still had to turn around and take a step. It was just that it was all done extremely fast.

But Zhou Zekai was faster!

Before the Flickering Stab could be completed, a pitch-black muzzle was already aimed towards Lord Grim’s head.

The body of the gun was very long. It wasn’t a revolver.

Sharpshooter Level 70 skill: Thunder Snipe.

He had actually used Thunder Snipe at such a close range!

The crowd was in chaos. The Zhou Zekai on stage and the Zhou Zekai off-stage were like two different people. Off-stage, he was silent and invisible. But on-stage, he was always so flashy.

Bang!

Chapter 1585 - Despair and Hope

The open gunfire seemed to be right on Lord Grim’s forehead. It was true that long-range attacks were at a disadvantage at close range, but at such close range, shots could be fired with extreme accuracy. Dodging would be impossible, something that no one could do.

Poof!

The bullet broke through the skull, and the sound of it entering the flesh was exceptionally clear. Lord Grim’s head exploded with blood.

Just from the power and movement of this attack, those watching felt that it wouldn’t be unfair if this one attack was able to directly kill him. But this was a game, after all, and everything had to follow the rules of the game. Lord Grim’s head was still there even after being hit, but the sharp drop in his health was unavoidable. Cloud Piercer, as the Great Gunner, had an extremely high attack stat to begin with, and as a headshot, the damage was doubled. This one attack took one-third of Lord Grim’s health, enough to hurt the heart. With the skills available to an unspecialized, who knew how many attacks would need to land in order to do that kind of damage to the opponent.

He can’t go on?

At this moment, even Happy’s most loyal of fans couldn’t help but wonder. Even though the two hadn’t exchanged blows for too long, even though Lord Grim’s health was far from depleted, the might that Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer demonstrated onstage could generate this kind of despair.

A Thunder Snipe unleashed at close-range. Such an unthinkable thing spread despair offstage, and all those who stood opposed to Samsara felt it.

Not only did this one attack deal so much damage, the momentum carried by this powerful shot affected the character’s balance. The head that remained amidst the blood jerked back, as though punched, and it carried the rest of the body with it.

But, he didn’t fall!

Lord Grim’s right foot stepped back, supporting the rest of this body.

Perhaps most people wouldn’t have noticed this detail, but this was a powerful demonstration of Ye Xiu’s skill. A snipe at this distance couldn’t be avoided, but stepping back in time to support the rest of the body required reaction and response to the extreme. With this step, Lord Grim stabilized himself in the fastest way possible, and from here he could counterattack in the shortest time possible. After all, no matter how fierce or destructive, Thunder Snipe was only one attack. To switch the long gun for the revolver again, the character still needed to move, and this short span of time was a window for Ye Xiu to counterattack. Without this step backward, he would have no way of seizing this opportunity.

Amidst despair, hope arose. But only experts would be able to detect this kind of hope. Before this hope could spread to everyone, another wave of despair came crashing down.

Ka…

A light sound, clear, crisp, but uncommonly powerful.

Thunder Snipe… bullet reload?

No one dared believe their ears. Glory’s Thunder Snipe only had one shot. Firing again required the skill to come off cooldown. But now, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer, right after using one shot, was already reloading a second shot? Where did his skill cooldown go?

Skill cooldown?

As soon as they thought of this game terminology, a number of players reacted.

Dual Load!

This Sharpshooter skill could allow a skill that was currently in cooldown be ready for immediate use. Zhou Zekai must have used this skill. That was why, right after using a Thunder Snipe, it could be immediately be reloaded, because he used Dual Load to end the cooldown.

Bang!

The gun fired again…

It was over. It was really over.

If what happened before could only be called a subconscious feeling aroused in the heart, then this time, this second consecutive Thunder Snipe, dragged everyone down into despair for good.

The gun’s muzzle spat out fire. No one could even see the bullet fly out, because it was too fast, too close. The bullet would hit, blood would spatter, wasn’t that how it went?

Clang!

No blood. What came with the sound was a brilliant flash of sparks, sparks generated from the friction of a metal collision.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was lifted in front of Lord Grim’s chest. The sword pulled from the center of the umbrella was still trembling after the sparks faded.

Sword form, Guard!

The stadium was in an uproar.

Those in front of their televisions were in an uproar.

He’d actually used the Blade Master’s Guard, to block Cloud Piercer’s Thunder Snip? At this close range?

What kind of eyesight? What kind of control?

No one could answer this question. All that they knew was that the two people currently onstage were accomplishing the superhuman.

If Lord Grim’s step back was a hope that not many detected, then this time, using a Guard to block a Thunder Snipe, was a clear scene that brought clear hope, hope that could burn away the despair that Zhou Zekai wrought.

It wasn’t over!

It was far from over!

Only a bastard would think it was over!

Those that supported Happy and Ye Xiu almost wanted to cry. This feeling of surviving despair was too wonderful, this feeling of hope was too wonderful.

At this time, the amount of time these two had spent attacking each other could be counted in seconds. But the rise and fall in emotion that it gave the viewers was just this intense.

But even after successfully blocking the Thunder Snipe, Lord Grim’s situation couldn’t be called stable. The momentum from the first shot that had hit his head hadn’t been completely dissipated, and although the Guard absorbed the attack’s damage, it couldn’t completely dispel the momentum from this powerful Level 70 attack.

Step back, step back nonstop.

Ye Xiu didn’t use backward rolls, the simplest and most effective way of dispelling momentum. He chose to use this more complex method, whose rhythm was harder to grasp, because he didn’t want Cloud Piercer to leave his sight. An opponent like Zhou Zekai, even the short moment in a roll when his eyes would leave him was enough of an opening for him to seize.

And while stepping back, Ye Xiu counterattacked.

Bang! Gunshot.

The blade used for the Guard was already slid back into the umbrella. Raised parallel to the ground, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella turned back into gun form, and fire spat out of the tip. This counterattack against the Great Gunner was also a Gunner shot, an accurate close-range shot, Stun Bullet!

But the distance between the two characters right now was still larger than it had been when Zhou Zekai had used his first Thunder Snipe.

Cloud Piercer was moving backward from the recoil, Lord Grim was moving backward from the impact of the attack. Even though Ye Xiu’s shot was very fast, but distance still gave Zhou Zekai the space to react.

Twist the body, holster the gun!

This rifle that would not come off cooldown so quickly again was put away, and Cloud Piercer once again lifted his twin revolvers.

He twisted his body to avoid the Stun Bullet, activated Speed Firing, and the bullets flew outward.

But in this moment, Ye Xiu had already completely regained control of Lord Grim’s movement.

Collapsing Mountain!

The gun was put away and the sword came out once again, not the tachi hidden in the umbrella stem, but the broadsword formed from the eccentric folded shape of the umbrella’s surface. With burning killing intent, flying right past the bullets that Cloud Piercer shot, fall!

Chapter 1586 - Ten Years, Samsara

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in broadsword form wasn’t bright, and its shape was so strange that it was laughable. But when it came plummeting down, carrying a strong gust of wind, even Zhou Zekai couldn’t laugh.

Ye Xiu didn’t dodge, didn’t retreat. Just like this, he met the attack head on. Under the rain of bullets, Lord Grim slashed forward with a Collapsing Mountain.

With Zhou Zekai’s level of control, he could easily change the angle of Cloud Piercer’s attack to land many shots upon Lord Grim’s body. But so what?

He could damage Lord Grim, but he couldn’t stop the fall of Lord Grim’s Collapsing Mountain. In terms of attack priority, long-range attacks were no match for close-range, this was a design that Zhou Zekai couldn’t change. Even if he could use the Level 75 Thunder Snipe and blast Lord Grim’s head again, he couldn’t force Lord Grim back.

Ye Xiu understood this point extremely clearly. To defeat a long-range class, he could only advance, and could not retreat. Whether facing an ordinary gamer in Glory’s Arena, or the number one Great Gunner Zhou Zekai, it was all the same.

And so, he didn’t retreat.

And so, he maintained his forward-facing attack stance.

He did so when faced with the Thunder Snipe.

He did so when faced with the rain of bullets from Speed Firing.

The Collapsing Mountain came down, and Zhou Zekai had no choice but to dodge. Cloud Piercer hurriedly retreated, at the same time lifting his gun and firing toward the midair Lord Grim.

He chose to dodge, but he didn’t give up on attacking.

But Lord Grim suddenly changed direction in midair, plunging downward with a speed that shouldn’t have been possible with a Collapsing Mountain.

Ye Xiu had anticipated early on that Zhou Zekai could dodge to the side and attack at the same time, and so he began making midair adjustments as soon as he jumped up for the Collapsing Mountain.

Collapsing Mountain cancel, Falling Light Blade!

A broadsword could use Falling Light Blade as well. The form wasn’t as light or graceful as it would be with a lightsaber or tachi, but it carried greater momentum and pressure.

With this change, Lord Grim’s path skewed toward Cloud Piercer, and Cloud Piercer, who was currently jumping back to avoid the Collapsing Mountain, could not easily change direction again.

But the current controller of Cloud Piercer was Zhou Zekai, that Zhou Zekai who was said to be able to do anything onstage except heal. He was actually able to react fast enough to keep up with Lord Grim’s swift change from Collapsing Mountain to Falling Light Blade. The bullets he fired from the gun he just lifted were knocked away by the Falling Light Blade, but then he was already moving. Characters in midair especially relied on recoil to adjust their movement.

This whole process took less than a second, yet the two of them fought with so many changes, so many inputs. What level of technique was this?

The broadcast wished to show stats of the two players’ handspeeds, but by the time they displayed this data, that moment had already passed. They just couldn’t catch up to the battle rhythm. All of this had happened in the span of time Cloud Piercer took to jump back once.

Cloud Piercer landed, and immediately looked for a direction to roll. Even though he had adjusted his aim precisely, he could only damage Lord Grim, it wouldn’t impact his skills very much. Immediately after, Lord Grim landed, and the force from the Falling Light Blade expanded. Cloud Piercer, who had started rolling, couldn’t avoid all of the damage, but he was able to dispel the effects of the attack with the greatest speed. When his roll was halfway through, two muzzles were already pointing at Lord Grim from the ground. This kind of attitude was very similar to Ye Xiu’s mindset when he stepped backward after the Thunder Snipe to stabilize himself. At any moment, both of them were working hard to find an opportunity to attack. In a situation where only half a step of retreat was necessary, no one would retreat any further, not even an inch.

Gunshot!

Gunfire burst forth from the muzzles of the revolvers. At this moment, Cloud Piercer and Lord Grim were already within melee range of each other, but even in this kind of small space, Lord Grim actually didn’t have control over the situation. Cloud Piercer was supposed to be better at long-range, but his gunshots didn’t stop. It was as though he carried two knives in his hands, that spitting fire and those nonstop bullets serving as sharp blades, accurately slicing any enemies that dared approach!

At this point, he had already broken past the idea of Gun Fu. This wasn’t a combination of taijutsu and gunfire. Zhou Zekai’s gunfire had become a form of taijutsu, thanks to his extreme control, taking precision to the limit.

“Too strong!!” In the broadcast, Pan Lin couldn’t hold himself back, forgetting himself as he shouted. Because he believed that he was far from the only one who had fallen into the craze of this moment. The entire Glory world was probably trembling from this scene. Long-range, short-range, two completely different kinds of classes, but under Zhou Zekai’s control, this wall built into the game was actually broken. His Cloud Piercer danced with his gunfire like a close-range class. Wildfire, Shattered Frost, they spat out not individual bullets, but a tight and continuous stream. They were the searing and deadly blades in Zhou Zekai’s hands!

“Brilliant, beautiful, unbelievable!!” All sorts of praise tumbled from Pan Lin’s mouth. “This is the summit, this is a revolution, I think that even Ye Xiu would have to admit this point.”

“Yes! Worthy of being Glory’s number one!” Li Yibo hurriedly broke in before Pan Lin could steal away all the words and spotlight. But would someone misunderstand? Would anyone not know the person about whom Li Yibo was talking? Of course not. The person he was talking about was of course Zhou Zekai, only Zhou Zekai, the Zhou Zekai who could break through the very fundamentals of Glory’s design through sheer skill.

The number one in Glory was him!

Li Yibo directly gave this conclusion. Facing Ye Xiu, the Ye Xiu who repeatedly surprised and humbled them, Li Yibo still dared to declare this without hesitation. All of those lessons and experiences from before, he no longer remembered them. In their eyes, there was only the sheer strength that Zhou Zekai displayed. A thousand troops and ten thousand horses couldn’t stop him, how could a mere Ye Xiu?

Yes, a mere Ye Xiu.

Right now, everyone saw nothing but Zhou Zekai’s stunning, jaw-dropping performance. Ye Xiu? Or a wooden dummy? A scarecrow? It didn’t matter. He was just a backdrop, a not-too-bad backdrop, serving to augment the protagonist.

Too powerful, too brilliant, too beautiful, too unbelievable, the summit, a revolution!

Pan Lin said that even Ye Xiu would have to admit this point.

Yes, Ye Xiu very much admitted it. It was indeed very powerful, very brilliant, very beautiful, very unbelievable.

But the problem was, this kind of incredible power, brilliance, beauty – he had already experienced it ten years ago!

Ten years ago, he had experienced it all.

If not for an accident, this brilliance should have stepped onto this stage ten years ago.

Ten years, samsara*.

Chapter 1587 - Glory’s Greatest

This confrontation had everyone on the edge of their seats. Even neutral viewers who were indifferent to both teams felt exceptionally anxious right now.

But the most anxious were still those audience members directly affected by the atmosphere of the audience, as well as the players of the two teams who’d been sitting in the player areas for a while now. When Zhou Zekai broke through the class design barrier and controlled Cloud Piercer to wield his bullets like swinging blades, the stadium had gone wild. Countless people had jumped up, cheered, hollered! Samsara’s power reached its peak, and even the Samsara players on the sidelines had burst into smiles.

They were very strong, strong enough to directly push Zhou Zekai into number one, but they weren’t blindly confident. Competition had wins and losses, and even Zhou Zekai couldn’t win every single match he was in. Zhou Zekai had stumbled in front of seemingly weak opponents before. And the opponent he now faced was Ye Xiu, the Glory Textbook, the former number one.

It wasn’t until Zhou Zekai demonstrated this absolutely powerful stance that the Samsara players allowed themselves to relax, revealing smiles that anticipated victory.

They relaxed, but Happy grew even more anxious.

To be able to use gun attacks as close combat attacks, the ferocity that Zhou Zekai demonstrated was clear and earthshaking. Any Glory fan could feel it.

In this moment, Chen Guo hoped she was wrong. She hoped that her judgment would once again became a joke, because her skill level wasn’t high enough.

But when she looked at everyone else, Wei Chen, Fang Rui, the shock written on their faces was the same as hers.

Unfortunately, this time she wasn’t wrong. Unfortunately, Zhou Zekai was truly strong enough to shock everyone present.

But Chen Guo refused to give up, she continued to search everyone’s faces for some reassurance, one after another. But nothing, there was nothing, everyone’s faces were grim, it was like one punch after another telling Chen Guo that there was nothing optimistic about this situation. She looked around in a large circle, all the way until she saw Su Mucheng, sitting on her other side.

And here, she saw an expression different from everyone else’s.

There was shock, yes. But aside from that, she didn’t seem as grim as everyone else. In Su Mucheng’s expression, Chen Guo saw a sort of… grief?

Was Su Mucheng already feeling grief for Ye Xiu’s imminent defeat? This person, who knew Ye Xiu better than anyone else, did she have a clearer prediction of the situation than everyone else?

“He hasn’t lost yet!” Chen Guo suddenly said. Even though the situation wasn’t looking good, as long as Lord Grim still had a drop of blood left, she would hope a miracle.

“Ah?” Su Mucheng responded automatically, as though she’d been lost in thought and was suddenly jolted awake. Her expression instantly became very calm.

“Yes, he hasn’t lost yet,” she said to Chen Guo. After recovering, her face now brimmed with energy, with the unwavering trust in Ye Xiu that she always had.

“He won’t lose!” Chen Guo said firmly. “Hasn’t lost yet” became “won’t lose.” This was a wish, a hope, a trust.

But there really weren’t many who could do the same.

In the live broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo already declared Ye Xiu’s death, and were going back and forth discussing Zhou Zekai’s deadly skill.

“Because of this, Glory might have to undergo a massive rebalancing in the next update,” Pan Lin chuckled. His tone was carefree, as though there were no tension in the battle in front of them right now. In his mind, this battle had already ended.

“Yes, this really is a game-changer. Compared to forcing the Alliance to change its rules, forcing the Glory developers to change the game’s design is much more drastic,” said Li Yibo.

“Yes yes, he really is too strong.” Pan Lin had used this phrase “too strong” countless times by now.

Yes, too strong.

But “too strong” didn’t mean invincible. It was only “too strong,” not “the strongest”!

The bullets traced blade-like paths in the air, and amidst it all, Lord Grim suddenly tilted his body. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in his hands came apart into two pieces, tonfa form, and at the same time his body trembled!

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Lord Grim didn’t dodge, instead suddenly using this skill. Instantly, countless bullets landed directly upon his chest, as though many slashes were cutting into him again and again. Blood spurted, Lord Grim continued to step forward. He charged through the blood filling the air, his umbrella again shifting to another Fighter class weapon, the claw, and his right hand swiftly thrust forward.

Cloud Body, Strangle!

Cloud Piercer hurriedly retreated.

It might have been a step backward or a jump backward, but no one would know. Because this Cloud Body, this Strangle had come so quickly, so suddenly, Zhou Zekai had made the inputs, but Cloud Piercer didn’t have the chance to display the movement. Lord Grim’s right hand was already tightly gripping his throat.

Everyone was stunned.

How had the elegant and game-changing Great Gunner been caught by a crude Strangle just like that?

But, this didn’t affect his attack, did it?

Everyone could see that although Lord Grim had rushed forward to seize Cloud Piercer, Cloud Piercer’s twin revolvers were still tightly pressed against Lord Grim’s body.

Strangle could restrict the opponent’s movement, but not their attack. Right now, Zhou Zekai didn’t even need to aim in order to fire like crazy. In this moment, how much of Lord Grim’s health could he destroy?

Peng!

A dull sound. A gunshot?

No, it was Lord Grim bashing his head directly against Cloud Piercer’s. Immediately, blood began streaming down his forehead.

Headbutt!

A Brawler skill. Only the street-dwelling Brawlers would use anything as weapons in a scuffle, even their own heads. This was how they survived the violent street life.

Zhou Zekai’s vision swayed, but even so, Cloud Piercer’s revolvers were still steady, and the sound of gunshots was as strong as ever. But Lord Grim’s knee was already connecting with Cloud Piercer’s abdomen, the force of the impact bending his entire body in half.

Knee Attack!

Under the effect of this half-grab skill, Cloud Piercer finally had no way of maintaining his posture. When his body bent, his arms naturally came down, and his bullets swept the ground.

Then, there was an Elbow, coming down heavily upon the back of Cloud Piercer’s lowered head. As Cloud Piercer crumpled downward, Lord Grim’s other hand was already forming a fist, and an Uppercut sent him back into the air.

Strangle, Headbutt, Knee Attack, Elbow, Uppercut…

They were all Brawler skills, and aside from Headbutt, the other four were all sub-Level 20 skills. Yet the combination of these attacks managed to break Zhou Zekai’s remarkable technique.

Those shouting and cheering earlier now seemed as though a fist had been shoved in their mouth, rendering them speechless.

Chen Guo was excited.

No wonder this was Ye Xiu. As expected of Ye Xiu. This was the Ye Xiu that never let her down.

“Amazing!” she shouted.

“It is.” Su Mucheng smiled gently. Just like how she wasn’t too panicked before, right now she didn’t seem too excited.

When she had seen Zhou Zekai’s exceptional technique earlier, she had indeed gotten somewhat lost in thought.

She thought of her now-deceased older brother Su Muqiu, also using a Sharpshooter, also possessing incomparably elegant skill and technique.

At the same time, she couldn’t forget that shock when his Sharpshooter Autumn Tree had been sent sprawling to the ground by Ye Xiu’s One Autumn Leaf.

“Fuck!”

That was the only time Su Mucheng had ever heard Su Muqiu swear. For someone like him with such beautiful technique to lose like this, he was surprised, flustered, and exasperated.

“Could your fighting be any cruder?”

Su Mucheng still remembered the mockery that Su Muqiu had often thrown at Ye Xiu. The two of them had never gotten tired of fighting back and forth, using all sorts of classes and all sorts of characters.

Su Muqiu had even specifically gotten a little notebook to write down the win-loss record between the two of them. He gave it to Su Mucheng to take care of.

“Don’t look!” Ye Xiu had wanted to see it, but he never got permission.

“We’re basically tied, there’s nothing to look at.” That was what Su Muqiu always said, but Su Mucheng, as the one holding the notebook, of course knew that Ye Xiu was always in the lead. They had that youthful spirit of always wanting to outdo the other. Su Muqiu certainly wasn’t keeping track of the win record because he wanted to display his failures. But unfortunately, in the end, he had been unable to tie the score.

The notebook had been taken away with the rest of Su Muqiu’s belongings, but Su Mucheng would sometimes think, if they had managed to continue playing, play all the way until now, play for these ten years, then what kind of record would that notebook hold?

Who was Glory’s greatest?

Everyone had an answer in their heart, and because of emotional bias, this answer would never be universal. Ye Xiu, for example, always felt that if Su Muqiu were still alive, he would definitely be Glory’s greatest player. This thought was tangled up with feelings of loss and regret toward the one who had passed away.

But in Su Mucheng’s heart, the greatest was Ye Xiu. Even though she also missed Su Muqiu, she still believed this, because this was what her brother told her: Ye Xiu, the greatest.

So, in this attention-catching match between Glory’s number ones, from the very beginning, Su Mucheng had had an answer in her heart. No matter what the result was, her answer wouldn’t change.

As soon as he was sent into the air by the Uppercut, Cloud Piercer was already readjusting his aim. Zhou Zekai’s reaction was both fast and accurate. While in midair, he couldn’t see Lord Grim at all, but based on his experience and awareness, the dual revolvers in Cloud Piercer’s hands fired down shot after shot.

Bullets rained down, that was truly the only way to describe it. The bullets that came out of his guns were all aimed in different directions, with a slight adjustment in angle after every shot. The bullets instantly poured out, covering the maximum possible area.

But, so what?

Ye Xiu ignored them entirely. Lord Grim’s chest remained upright as he welcomed the bullets that rained down, and continued to attack!

Because the distance was close enough, because the two characters were almost right on top of each other.

Even if Zhou Zekai could rely on his exceptional technique to turn Cloud Piercer’s bullets into blades no matter what, he couldn’t change the fundamental design of the game.

The priority of long-range attacks couldn’t compare to that of close-range. Turning firepower into bladework, no matter how beautiful it was, it couldn’t control a situation as solidly or securely as true close-range attacks.

This was the most basic of principles.

Or, in other words, this was the crudest of principles.

Chapter 1588 - Simple and Clean~~~

All the cheers and screaming stopped. Only the sound of the fight between the two characters remained. The viewers watching at home wanted to know what exactly had happened, but the commentators, who had been talking excitedly just before, had suddenly quieted down. It seemed like the only thing that could be heard from them were coughing sounds?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were on the verge of tears. The two felt like they had been thrown onto the

What could they say?

What did they still dare to say?

Even if the two had a million things to say about the current situation, they couldn’t put the words together. The embellishment that the two had blurted out just a moment ago was like a whip. After twirling the whip in a circle, they had winded it around their own necks. The harder they pulled, the harder it became to say anything.

The commentators were supposed to be neutral, without any bias for either side. They hadn’t been excited because they wanted Samsara to win, but rather because Zhou Zekai’s stunning play had excited them. If such stunning and beautiful playing couldn’t win, then how could the heavens be fair?

The two had said those words because of this belief. Otherwise, the countless time that Ye Xiu had slapped their face would have reminded them to be cautious. How else could they have gotten excited and predicted the outcome even when the other side had more than half his health left?

In that instant, they had indeed thought that Zhou Zekai was invincible.

In that instant, they had forgotten that there was no such thing as absolute victory in a match.

In that instant, they had forgotten that the match wasn’t over until the last drop of blood flowed.

It had been the case before, and it always would be.

However, breaking Zhou Zekai’s breathtaking four-step Gun Fu didn’t mean that Ye Xiu had won either. Cloud Piercer was still in the lead by a considerable amount of health!

Even if Ye Xiu had seized the initiative, Zhou Zekai’s might was no less than before.

For the average player, an airborne character was the sign of someone about to get thrashed. However, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer continued to attack while in the air. A rain of bullets descended, making it feel as if whatever was beneath it was a lamb in a tiger’s den. Ye Xiu didn’t seem to see it though. Lord Grim tanked the bullets and continued his attacks.

A trade?

Lord Grim had less health. A trade didn’t seem to be wise though.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo thought the same thing, but remained silent. They were too afraid to try and guess Ye Xiu’s intentions.

Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash, Wave Wheel Slasher!

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly transformed from a Fighter weapon into a Swordsman weapon. Three slashes one after the other. Light filled the sky as Cloud Piercer tumbled through the air. Even Zhou Zekai had no way to steady his character facing such fast successive attacks. Cloud Piercer’s shots began to miss their mark. The rain of bullets seemed to have split apart from the three bright sword lights, and Cloud Piercer was locked into place by the Wave Wheel Slasher, magic rendering him apart.

Vision!

Zhou Zekai understood that this was the key point. He could only make the appropriate response if he could grasp the opponent’s movements.

However, Lord Grim followed close on his heels. In an instant, he moved into a dead angle where Cloud Piercer wouldn’t be able to see him. Vanishing Step. This difficult and complicated technique was already second-nature to him. As soon as he saw his target airborne, he would use this technique out of habit to continue the combo.

Even in the pro scene, there were many players who were helpless against Vanishing Step, but Ye Xiu wasn’t so naive to think that Zhou Zekai would be one of them. He recognized Zhou Zekai’s skill clearly. Whether it worked or not, he had to at least try. It was an ideology that both of them agreed on.

Zhou Zekai wasn’t able to see his target, but by process of elimination, he had a rough idea of Lord Grim’s position. Cloud Piercer wasn’t able to turn his head towards that direction, but his hands were more nimble than his head. The trustworthy guns in his hands, Wildfire and Shattered Frost, instilled fear into anyone who saw them, the guns of the Gunner King!

Fire burst out.

This time, he wasn’t spreading out his attacks to cover more area. He was aiming precisely towards his dead angle.

Bang bang bang bang.

Bullets descended.

The distance was too close, and Ye Xiu didn’t have time to react to it. However, he had never intended on dodging. Bullets could hurt him, but they couldn’t stop him from attacking .The transforming Myriad Manifestations Umbrella struck Cloud Piercer repeatedly. Because of these destructive hits, the once precisely aimed gunfire once again becams scattered.

“Zhou Zekai’s situation isn’t looking good!!” Pan Lin finally braved it out and spoke, once he saw that Ye Xiu had the upper hand.

“Mm, he…” Before Li Yibo could finish his sentence, he shut his mouth and stared with wide eyes. Lord Grim’s combo had made Cloud Piercer lose his aim. His bullets no longer followed a straight path, but rather an arc.

“Curve Firing!” Pan Lin shouted.

Curve Firing wasn’t a technique, but rather a Sharpshooter skill. Of the four Gunner classes, Sharpshooters emphasized firing technique. Many of their skills were buffs. For example, Rapid Firing and Burst Firing. For a period of time, the skills gave the user increased firing speed or critical hit chance. Curved Firing made the bullets curve. How much the bullets curved was set by the system by default, but the user could manually control it too.

Zhou Zekai had Cloud Piercer use Curved Firing while in an airborne state. Despite losing control of his aim due to Lord Grim’s attacks, many of the curved bullets still headed towards Lord Grim. Zhou Zekai had taken into consideration the fact that Lord Grim would be comboing him, so he used Curved Firing as a counter. He wasn’t so godly that he could accurately calculate the trajectories of all of the bullets, but with so many bullets being fired, some of them were bound to hit.

It hadn’t been easy for Pan Lin and Li Yibo to resume their commentating, but now they had been stopped in their tracks again. Today’s situation was looking grim. No matter which side they talked about, they would immediately be slapped in the face. The two wanted to cry. What should they do? It wasn’t like they could stay silent, no?

The two were quiet, but the crowd wouldn’t be.

Those curved bullets flew around like wild bees, completely unpredictable. Ye Xiu could only try his best to dodge them, but many of them still landed. However, Curved Firing only affected the trajectory. It didn’t increase the damage or have any other effects. As a result, Lord Grim could still continue his attacks.

Sky Strike!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear and swung upwards towards the falling Cloud Piercer. Just when it looked as if it was about to hit, Cloud Piercer’s dual guns suddenly turned towards him and fired two shots.

The recoil made him move away slightly, and this slight displacement was enough for Lord Grim’s Sky Strike to miss.

The skilled are bold!

Zhou Zekai could have obviously done it earlier, utilizing the recoil to adjust himself while in the air, but he didn’t because he knew that Ye Xiu would certainly have countermeasures. He had intentionally waited for Ye Xiu to act first before doing this at the very last moment, so Ye Xiu wouldn’t have time to readjust his attack. Finally, Cloud Piercer was back on the ground. Cloud Piercer landed and rolled, but before he could get up, he saw a grenade out of the corner of his eye.

Boom!

The grenade exploded, and Cloud Piercer was thrown to the side. Cold light flashed. Lord Grim used Shining Arc to close the distance, Cross Slash, Upwards Slash… Cloud Piercer was in the air again.

He wasn’t able to dodge it?

Samsara’s fans felt a blow to their hearts. They watched as their ace player used everything at his disposal while taking a beating, yet still fail to escape.

Bang bang bang bang…

Gunfire sounded again. Zhou Zekai refused to give up, but everyone had noticed long ago that his attacks had no effect on Lord Grim’s offense. Lord Grim simply took the hits and continued attacking.

“This… isn’t good, right?” Pan Lin carefully expressed.

Li Yibo didn’t even follow up. The fight between the two number ones was truly too high-level for them. They talked about this, but it was wrong. They talked about that, but they weren’t sure. At this point, he and Pan Lin basically existed to get their faces slapped. It was too humiliating.

Unfortunately, the one to suffer the most would be Pan Lin. After all, Li Yibo was considered an invited guest. His status was slightly higher, so while it might be okay for Li Yibo to not say anything, it was not okay for Pan Lin. Pan Lin could only brace himself and blabber away.

“He has no way to force Ye Xiu back…” Pan Lin’s voice was like a mosquito.

And this time, he was right. Ye Xiu couldn’t be forced back. Lord Grim continued to attack. He wasn’t afraid of this sort of competition. Zhou Zekai understood this point too, and he hadn’t been hoping that he could force Ye Xiu to retreat because he understood Ye Xiu’s thoughts: the priority of close-ranged skills was far higher than long-ranged skills.

Zhou Zekai hadn’t forgotten this kind of basic knowledge. He didn’t think his bullets could compete with close combat from an unspecialized. Everyone else had been cheering excitedly because it had seemed like Zhou Zekai had broken the seemingly unshakeable barrier between close-ranged and long-ranged classes. However, Zhou Zekai knew clearly that it was because he had no other choice. Lord Grim had been too close to him.

It wasn’t good for Sharpshooters to get closed in on.

It was logic that even a noob in Glory would know. But everyone had believed in him because he was Zhou Zekai, and there was nothing he couldn’t do apart from healing. That was why although it was common sense that the situation had been unfavorable for a Sharpshooter, it shouldn’t be a problem for Zhou Zekai. Even if his opponent had closed in, the one to be taught a lesson would be the opponent.

In reality, it had indeed been the case numerous times. Even when Zhou Zekai’s opponents were able to close, they would often be the ones who lost.

Zhou Zekai didn’t become arrogant though.

Others could believe that his Sharpshooter was invincible even in close combat, he himself couldn’t.

It wasn’t good for Sharpshooters to get closed in on!

Zhou Zekai, the current number one player, hadn’t overlooked this logic that even a noob understood. When he played, he would still follow this principle. After being closed in on by Lord Grim, he had been trying to get away. However, while running away, he wouldn’t miss an opportunity to injure his opponent. That was why he had used Thunder Snipe earlier and given Cloud Piercer a nearly 33% health lead.

With this lead, Zhou Zekai began to use Gun Fu to fight because at that time, he had decided to trade blow, trade health for health.

In other words, the thought that he could completely suppress Ye Xiu with Gun Fu hadn’t even crossed his mind. The reason that he had used Gun Fu was to trade.

Trading meant that I hit you, and you hit me.

The Gun Fu was like this, and it was the same afterwards even when Ye Xiu seized the upper hand. However, Zhou Zekai never let go of any opportunities to injure Lord Grim. By relying on this sort of accumulation of damage along with Cloud Piercer’s health lead, even in these disadvantageous trades, he would be the one to win in the end. Zhou Zekai was certain of it.

As for all that flashiness? That was just a service to the plain and simple Glory principle: the one with more health bullied the one with less.

Chapter 1589 - Trade

Those who supported Ye Xiu or those who worried for Zhou Zekai didn’t quite understand the current situation. From start to finish, the only ones who remained unaffected were Team Samsara and Zhou Zekai’s teammates.

Because they understood Zhou Zekai’s personality and play style. Their captain, who was considered the number one player in Glory, was never arrogant. Fighting close-ranged as a long-ranged class? That would be the epitome of arrogance. How could their captain entertain such a useless thought? If Zhou Zekai decided to play in such a way, that simply meant it was necessary. So that’s what he did.

Cheers and screams were fine. After all, it was indeed an incredibly beautiful display of skill.

But if you had to say that it was the pinnacle of Glory or a revolution, that would be nonsense.

Even Samsara snorted disdainfully at Pan Lin’s word choice, and then when Ye Xiu slapped him in the face, they rejoiced at his misfortune.

Because they were the same as Zhou Zekai. Playing like this would be exciting for the viewers, but it wouldn’t be enough to suppress an expert like Ye Xiu.

As a result, they had never thought that Ye Xiu would be beaten down by Zhou Zekai in this way. What they saw was a trade. With Zhou Zekai having the health lead, he was trading with Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Even though Ye Xiu had the upper hand in these trades, the outcome of these trades lead towards Zhou Zekai’s victory.

The battle continued.

At a rapid pace.

The average viewer didn’t understand the reality of this situation. The pro players wouldn’t make this mistake though. Quite a few of them had begun calculating the DPS from both sides to determine who the winner would be.

Zhou Zekai would win.

Zhou Zekai would win.

Zhou Zekai would win.

This was what Zhang Xinjie, Yu Wenzhou, and Wang Jiexi concluded.

The others, who hadn’t yet reached a conclusion, stopped calculating. If those three all agreed, then what was there to argue about? Right now, Zhou Zekai would win without a doubt.

“But it’s risky,” Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin said.

Everyone nodded their heads.

Zhou Zekai would win at this rate, and he had it under control at the moment. However, he was playing against Ye Xiu’s unspecialized, who had the upper hand in these trades. The slightest mistake could mean disaster. Until the very end, it was hard to say who exactly would win.

“But looking at Samsara, it seems like they’re not worried at all!” Yu Feng said.

The pro players had special VIP seats, facing the stage directly. They were situated quite close to the two competing team’s seats, so they could see the expressions on each team’s players.

On Happy’s side, there was quite a bit of commotion going on there. Their expressions were heavy. They clearly realized where the issue lay,

As for Samsara, everyone there was quite relaxed. There would occasionally be a few whispers here and there, but it just seemed to be casual chatter.

“Zhou Zekai isn’t being completely dominated. Through his attempts to escape, he’s restricting Ye Xiu and giving himself opportunities to seize the upper hand,” Zhang Jiale suddenly said.

“Yes,” Han Wenqing affirmed.

“Ye Xiu’s situation is probably worse than we think,” Chu Yunxiu said.

“If you ride a tiger, it’s too hard to get off. It’s kind of giving off this feeling, isn’t it?”

“Yeah.”

“Zhou Zekai isn’t letting a single drop of water slip through.”

The pro players unanimously agreed. Ye Xiu’s situation wasn’t like what the average viewers thought. After breaking through Zhou Zekai’s Gun Fu, Ye Xiu wasn’t completely dominating the fight. The current situation was the same as the previous situation against Zhou Zekai’s Gun Fu, different methods to achieve the same goal. With Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer having the health lead, Ye Xiu couldn’t let go of the opportunity to fight him at close-range. No matter what, he had to stick close to him. When Zhou Zekai tried to escape, he had to stop him at all costs, and Zhou Zekai would use this opportunity to deal heavy damage and trade with him. This was what the pro players had concluded. From a certain perspective, Zhou Zekai held the initiative.

If you ride a tiger, it’s hard to get off.

It was indeed the case. Ye Xiu probably knew that he wouldn’t be able to win if he continued trading like this, but what could he do? If he let Cloud Piercer escape and widen the distance between them, he would be in an even more disadvantageous position.

The battle continued, and the two characters were both losing health. Cloud Piercer was losing health faster, while Lord Grim was losing health slower. In the end, the unspecialized Lord Grim had the advantage in close combat. Only Zhou Zekai could trade with Ye Xiu in this situation. By relying on his health lead, his health was still higher than Lord Grim’s even if he was losing health faster. As more time went on, this difference in health became more apparent. The viewers slowly began to notice it, and soon, sounds of discussion and doubt unfolded. They had thought that Zhou Zekai was in a terrible spot, but from the looks of it, if this continued, he would… probably win?

“Although Cloud Piercer is losing health rather fast, it looks like… it won’t ever be lower than Lord Grim’s?” Pan Lin carefully said.

“This is because of the early advantage that he obtained before!” Li Yibo finally spoke. He was quite confident in his words. He had seen the critical strike from the Thunder Snipe. The past was the past. It couldn’t be changed, no?

“If this continued, Ye Xiu will… will…” Pan Lin stuttered. He was just too afraid of saying the word “lose”.

“We can’t relax until the end,” Li Yibo said. Pan Lin couldn’t help but glance at him. Was this really the same person, who had been fighting with him to proclaim Zhou Zekai the winner?

“Red health!” Pan Lin shouted.

Red health meant health below ten percent. Although it didn’t affect a character’s stats, whether it was a normal player or a pro player, red health was usually a signal for danger.

Lord Grim was at red health. Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer still had 22% of his health left. Ye Xiu had closed the initial gap by a considerable amount, but it wasn’t enough! Judging from their previous trades, Lord Grim’s 10% could trade for approximately 15% of Cloud Piercer’s health, about a 1 to 1.5 ratio. On the pro stage, this figure was already very impressive. If it was any other occasion, this ratio would be unlikely.

However, for this fight, this ratio wouldn’t be enough to catch up. In the end, using a 1 to 1.5 ratio to beat a 22% health opponent with 10% wasn’t going to happen.

But…

That 1 to 1.5 ratio was an average. There were many back and forths, and not every exchange would result in this ratio. Sometimes, it would be higher. Ye Xiu needed it to be higher in order to win.

Not everyone had these numbers, but just looking at the health, even a noob knew that Ye Xiu wasn’t in a good position.

The audience could stop and discuss it, but the ones playing couldn’t. 22% against 10%? In the blink of an eye, the 22% became 19%!

A 1 to 2 trade!

The audience wasn’t too perceptive. After all, they weren’t precise enough to calculate the numbers. However, the pro players were more acute. Ye Xiu wanted to use this final moment to burst down Zhou Zekai?

Gore Cross!

Predicting where Cloud Piercer would land, Lord Grim rushed forward to use Gore Cross to trap him. Sword light overlapped, forming a cross shape.

Bang bang bang bang!

Gunshots. Cloud Piercer never seemed to stop firing. As soon as he encountered Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, Cloud Piercer never stopped to rest. Shooting to attack, shooting to borrow the recoil, shooting to fight at close combat.

This time, the bullets formed a star, creating a ripple in the Gore Cross. Cloud Piercer’s attacks had unexpectedly hit Lord Grim’s cross.

Long-ranged attacks had far lower priority than close-ranged attacks, so it wouldn’t be able to stop the Gore Cross. However, with so many bullets hitting, it would displace it somewhat.

Sword light streaked across, hit!

There was only one streak of blood. The horizontal slash of Lord Grim’s Gore Cross had hit, but the vertical slash had missed.

The skill consisted of two simultaneous slashes, but through precise maneuvering, Zhou Zekai was able to dodge one of them.

The crowd clapped and cheered wildly. Everyone loved to see these kinds of spectacular plays.

But the pro players, who knew about the subtleties of this fight, didn’t think it was necessary. Cloud Piercer had double Lord Grim’s health. He had so much room to work with. It was easier to make a mistake doing extremely precise inputs like what Zhou Zekai had done, and a mistake could give Ye Xiu a chance to turn things around.

“Why doesn’t he rush him down?” Void’s Yu Ce said.

“It’s better to be cautious. Don’t forget that Lord Grim can heal,” Zhang Xinjie said.

“Heal? He can’t health that much, can he?” Tiny Herb’s healer, Yuan Baiqing, said. With how the two were fighting, long cast time skills couldn’t be used. As a result, the only instant that Lord Grim’s unspecialized could do was a “Small Cure”.

Everyone immediately remembers that Ye Xiu could add other healer skills onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Such as “Great Cure” or “Holy Cure”.

Although these would be at most level one, instant heals healed a lot of health, but had extremely long cooldowns. Even at level one, with both players at such low health, it could be enough to save him.

“Is he planning on healing?” The pro players started getting nervous. They realized that the battle would be decided here.

Chapter 1590 - Attack

It was the final moment. There was no room for mistakes. Usually, players would lean towards caution. Success second, no mistakes first. It might not look too flashy, but those who understood Glory knew from experience the thrill of it.

Cloud Piercer had 20% of his health left, while Lord Grim had less than 10%.

With this health difference, most people wouldn’t consider it a desperate situation, but rather an advantageous one for Cloud Piercer.

That wasn’t what the spectating pro players thought though because they had thought of how Ye Xiu could win this match. Thinking back of their experiences with Ye Xiu, they analyzed how much health he would have if he used Small, Great, and Holy Cure back to back.

4%? 5%? 6%? Higher?

For a specialized healer, the amount of health healed would be a joke to them. But at this moment, it could be what saved Ye Xiu. With Lord Grim’s advantage over Cloud Pierce in close combat, a few extra percent in health would likely be enough for him to win.

“If you ride a tiger, it’s hard to get off. It looks like Zhou Zekai’s the one in trouble!” Huang Shaotian said. He spoke as if it was set in stone that Lord Grim would heal his health.

“Maybe not?” Some of the pro players were trying to think of other possibilities.

“With how crafty and despicable that guy is, it’s probably going to happen,” Zhang Jiale nodded his head.

“He’s been holding back, waiting for the very last moment to decide this match with one move. Doesn’t it feel similar to that one play? What was it? Right, it was when Cloud Piercer dodged Lord Grim’s Sky Strike. Zhou Zekai had waited until the very last moment before dodging so that Ye Xiu wouldn’t be able to react in time! Don’t you think it’s kind of similar?” The more Huang Shaotian talked, the more excited he became. As for that “one play”, he had just been referring to a small little detail in this fight. No wonder he remembered it so clearly.

“When is he planning on acting?” No one answered him. Huang Shaotian didn’t seem to care and continued on.

The two were still fighting, their health bars dropping. A short while later, Cloud Piercer’s health had dropped to 14%, while Lord Grim’s health had dropped to 5%. A single high damage skill could remove that last 5%, but with both sides being cautious, no such opportunity was given. Their health continued to slowly decline bit by bit. Just watching it made people sit on the edges of their seat.

Isn’t it about time he healed?

People like Huang Shaotian and Zhang Jiale were certain that Ye Xiu would heal. They felt like it was about time. 5% health was too dangerous. Cloud Piercer could kill him easily in one combo. Was there any need for him to slowly grind away at Lord Grim until death?

Yes! There was no need!

Zhou Zekai had been playing cautiously the entire time to the extent that he would even go so far as to dodge half of a Gore Cross. His opponent only had 5% of his health left, while his Cloud Piercer had 14%. He suddenly rushed forward!

“He’s going to rush him!!” Wu Yuce shouted.

When Lord Grim had 10% of his health left, Wu Yuce had already felt like Zhou Zekai could just rush him down, but with everyone talking about those instant heals that Ye Xiu could use, it was quite easy to understand why Zhou Zekai would rather be a bit more careful.

Rushing down the opponent would come at the sacrifice of a large amount of his health. If he wasn’t able to kill off Lord Grim and Lord Grim healed himself to survive, he would be in deep trouble.

Not rushing down Ye Xiu at that time showed how clear-minded Zhou Zekai was. He was the same as the spectating pro players. He had considered these possibilities. It wasn’t as difficult as guessing what skills Ye Xiu could choose to use. Healing was its own entity, and no one would forget that Lord Grim could heal. In this situation, healing would be immensely effective. The pro players had realized it, and Zhou Zekai did too. As a result, he played more cautiously. It was only when Lord Grim had 5% of his health left did Zhou Zekai choose to rush him down. He was confident that with this health difference, he could take down Ye Xiu in one combo and not give him an opportunity to heal!

Ye Xiu was waiting for the right moment to heal. Zhou Zekai was waiting for the right moment to rush him.

Huang Shaotian, Zhang Xinjie, and many other pro players felt like it was time for Ye Xiu to heal, but Zhou Zekai had picked this moment to make the first move!

“Ai!” Huang Shaotian gave a deep sigh.

He was a master opportunist. Both players wanted to seize this opportunity, but in the end, Zhou Zekai had seized it first. Was it over?

Not yet!

Cloud Piercer twisted his body, ready to fire. Suddenly, he saw a flash of cold light. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella thrust towards him.

Dragon Tooth!

Zhou Zekai had no choice but to dodge. Dragon Tooth stunned, which would disrupt his rhythm.

Cloud Piercer twisted his body, dodging the Dragon Tooth. His body was moving, but his two guns aimed true as they fired towards Lord Grim. The Dragon Tooth hadn’t affected his rush.

Bullets flew out, but Ye Xiu seemed to have predicted it. Lord crouched. At this close of a distance, he was unexpectedly able to dodge the bullets. Then, he unsheathed the handle of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and used the Berserker skill: Colliding Stab!

Charge!

The two were only three steps away. For normal players, it was a distance impossible to dodge the attack. However, Ye Xiu was facing Zhou Zekai, the most extraordinary in Glory. Three steps were the same as zero steps for normal players, but for Zhou Zekai, it was more than enough.

Dodge!

The instant Ye Xiu unsheathed his sword, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer reacted. In a high-level confrontation like this, neither of them would just be standing still exchanging blows. The two were constantly moving. All of their attacking, defending, and dodging were done while moving. Cloud Piercer dodged the Dragon Tooth, while also taking the next step. When Lord Grim had used Colliding Stab, he had already taken half a step. He would dodge it.

But he didn’t!

Zhou Zekai had unexpectedly made an error in judgement. The attack distance wasn’t three steps. The area covered by the strike was far greater than Zhou Zekai had expected.

Because the Colliding Stab hadn’t come from the tachi unsheathed from the umbrella. The tachi had only been unsheathed halfway before retracting. Lord Grim had kept the same stance after using Dragon Tooth and then followed with a Colliding Stab.

As a result, the distance of three steps was in fact zero steps. Because when the Dragon Tooth came out, the umbrella had completed those three steps. All it did next was switch forms. The tachi had been a feint. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had transformed into the strange greatsword form. The canvas of the umbrella was considered the blade of the greatsword. As a result, the greatsword was ridiculously big, and the area covered by Colliding Stab was much bigger as a result.

Hit!

Cloud Piercer had been hit by the Colliding Stab. This skill didn’t only have a knockback. The sword pierced through the target, flying out along with the target.

Bang!

Cloud Piercer crashed into a stalactite. There was nowhere for him to retreat to. Lord Grim closed in. At such a close distance, all Zhou Zekai could see was Lord Grim’s emotionless face.

Not good!

Zhou Zekai had realized that the situation was bad. They were too close, so close that even a class with a close-ranged weapon like a Blade Master would feel uncomfortable let alone a long-ranged class. At such a close distance, only punches and kicks could be performed. In other words, Fighter skills!

Bang!

Headbutt, another Headbutt.

Head against head, for a second time!

A punch to the stomach soon followed. It wasn’t even a skill, but a normal attack.

Lord Grim’s offense had begun. Zhou Zekai obviously wasn’t going to just sit and let Lord Grim hit him. Cloud Piercer used Knee Strike!

Knee Strike was a low-level Sharpshooter skill. It used the knee to strike the opponent. It was similar to the Brawler’s Knee Attack. The attack didn’t have grab priority, but it had Super Armor. It meant that only a grab skill could interrupt it. As a shared low-level Gunner skill, it was considered a godly skill for Gunners in getting out of close combat.

But the moment Cloud Piercer raised his knee, Lord Grim grabbed his leg and then threw Cloud Piercer onto his shoulder before slamming him back into the stalactite.

Grappler skill: Receiving Throw. It was a dismantle skill, a grab that ignored Super Armor.

A sudden shift. Everyone was dumbstruck, including the spectating pro players.

Heal?

That was their own wishful thinking? Lord Grim hadn’t bothered to heal. When his health dropped to 5%, Zhou Zekai rushed at him. As for Ye Xiu? He did the same! Ye Xiu also decided to rush at Zhou Zekai.

Rush down the opponent when you only had 5% of your health left?

It didn’t seem logical. Rushing down the opponent at that health? That was suicide. When rushing, the amount of damage taken was often more than the amount of damage dealt. Trying to kill the opponent relying on such low health would be rude.

Cloud Piercer had a lot of health left. That was why Zhou Zekai rushed at Ye Xiu!

Lord Grim had little health left. Ye Xiu had unexpectedly done the same?

Inconceivable. But that was what he did. Now, Cloud Piercer was pinned to the stalactite, with no room to run.The Gunner King was like the stuffing in a dumpling, squeezed together by the wonton wrapper, trapped and unable to escape.

The 14% health was peeled off layer by layer, but was it enough?

Lord Grim could only use Fighter skills. Among those, skills like Qi Bullet were unsuitable and useless to him in this situation.

He had only had a few low-level skills that he could use, yet he needed to finish off Cloud Piercer in one go.

Punch, kick, knee, elbow, head…

Lord Grim used every part of the body that he could use to attack.

13%, 12%, 11%…

Right now, everyone wasn’t thinking about what Zhou Zekai could do, but rather whether Ye Xiu could continue this combo until the end.

The broadcast was clever. The broadcast team quickly figured out where the key lay and immediately pulled out Lord Grim’s skill tree to show everyone his cooldowns.

The umbrella was in its Fighter weapon form. All other class skills were gray, unable to be used. Among the Fighter skills available to Lord Grim, there was a big red question mark. It was the bonus skill on his Claw form. It wouldn’t appear in the skill tree. However, everyone knew that Ye Xiu had chosen to add Headbutt.

All of his skills were low-level, so the cooldowns weren’t long.

Even so, was it possible for him to chain these skills long enough to finish off Cloud Piercer?

“It’s not enough…” Someone said. Pan Lin and Li Yibo obviously wouldn’t dare to come to this conclusion. These two were too afraid of making any remarks towards Ye Xiu.

It was Han Wenqing who said it. He was the expert at close combat and also a Fighter class. His judgement was naturally very reliable.

“It’s probably just by a bit,” Wang Jiexi said.

Would this tiny bit be enough for Zhou Zekai to turn it around?

Everyone’s gaze returned to the stage. They would know soon enough. Lord Grim’s Fighter skills would soon all be on cooldown. He would only be able to use normal skills or other class skills. He wouldn’t be able to keep up an inescapable combo.

Zhou Zekai couldn’t see Lord Grim’s skill tree, yet he seemed to see it more clearly than any of the ones who could see it. He immediately saw the opening and seized it.

Roundhouse Kick! Cloud Piercer spun around with a kick, but Lord Grim had already activated Cloud Body and jumped out of the way.

Cloud Piercer jumped up, pulled out his gun, and fired wildly!

Lord Grim’d body flickered. The distance of three steps was instantly closed.

Blade out, blade in.

Assassin skill: Teleporting Stab.

Cloud Piercer’s health dropped to zero.

“Nice try. You were close :)” Ye Xiu typed into chat with a smiley face.

Chapter 1591 - Establishing Dominance

Lose? Win?

Samsara’s fans were in a daze. Happy’s fans were in a daze. Unlike the pro players, they hadn’t fully grasped what had just happened. Their judgement had been very simple: whoever had more health was winning.

Of course, this sort of judgement wasn’t wrong. Yes, whoever had more health was winning. The end outcome of the battle could be considered a reversal from Ye Xiu. It was just that the reversal had been too quick. In the previous second, the two characters seemed to be evenly matched. Suddenly, Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer was pinned to a stalagmite, seemingly powerless. Then, just when he was finally able to escape, a silver blade went in and a red blade came out, marking the end of the battle.

How could it be?

How could it be?

Samsara’s fans were at a loss. Happy’s fans were also at a loss. They had thought that they would lose this fight. Getting Zhou Zekai’s Cloud Piercer down to such a low amount of health was still an acceptable result though.

This sort of thought was just them comforting themselves. Whether it was the confrontation between the current and former number one, or Ye Xiu’s legendary 1v1 win streak, none of Happy’s fans wanted to see Ye Xiu lose. As for whether it was good or bad for the group arena as a whole, this sort of rational reasoning wasn’t something that fans gave consideration to.

But contrary to their expectations, they had won.

Just like they had hoped, Ye Xiu had won. Just before, they had been constructing mental barriers, coming up with a reason to comfort themselves. All of a sudden, everything was flipped on top of their heads. Everyone was in a daze for a long time, all the way until Zhou Zekai left the player booth. Reality finally sunk in. The fans gathered at the away team seats began to cheer.

How did he win?

They didn’t know, but it wasn’t important. Ye Xiu had won, so let’s celebrate first! They could always go back and slowly analyze it at a later time.

The audience could take on this mentality, but the commentators, Pan Lin and Li Yibo, couldn’t. There was no later in a live broadcast. The two had to discuss the sudden reversal from Ye Xiu.

As a result, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella during that reversal became the focus of the discussion.

“The Dragon Tooth had closed the distance beforehand, so when Colliding Stab was used, it came out at point blank range.”

“The greatsword form of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella is truly gigantic. The area covered by Colliding Stab is quite large, making it quite difficult to dodge!”

“Look, the moment Colliding Stab came out, Lord Grim pulled out the tachi from his umbrella’s handle. This small movement misled Zhou Zekai into misjudging the attack.

“Yes, yes. What an elaborate scheme!”

The two spoke back and forth, not at all stingy with their praise. The two were even thinking of the future. Whenever Ye Xiu was in a 1v1, they should just immediately start out by declaring Ye Xiu’s victory. Then, wouldn’t anything they said after that be untouchable?

Through this evaluation, the two were able to move past the reversal. But for the pro players, while this feint was very important, it wasn’t as simple as that.

Ye Xiu. Zhou Zekai. The two players with the title of number one were very similar to each other in many ways. Just take how they played. Compared to normal players who cared strongly about hand speed, the deepest impression that these two players gave wasn’t speed but precision.

The two were exceptionally precise. Because of this precision, the two frequently made plays with little room for error. Zhou Zekai was able to perform such an impressive display of Gun Fu because of this precision. Ye Xiu dared to rush down Zhou Zekai despite only having 5% of his health remaining because of this precision.

Apart from precision, their decision-making and intuition were similar. When either of them took control, it was extremely difficult for the opponent to find an opening to counterattack.

At the end of the battle, Lord Grim had pinned Cloud Piercer against a stalagmite and fought at close combat. Was there no such opportunity before? No!

He had intentionally saved this move for the very end at the deciding moment. Everyone was shocked at his decision to rush down Zhou Zekai with only 5% health remaining on Lord Grim. But in reality, Ye Xiu hadn’t been looking at his own health, but rather Cloud Piercer’s 14%. As they traded blows, he knew that Zhou Zekai was waiting for an opportunity to finish him off in one combo. He was the same.

But his Lord Grim could also heal. The three instant cast heals could be added onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. However, during this entire battle, he had never used any of them. It was hard to not be suspicious. The spectating pro players had been certain that he was saving these heals for a final explosive burst. They thought that he had chosen not to use these heals before because he had been waiting for the right opportunity. When their health dropped low enough, he would heal, and Zhou Zekai wouldn’t be able to react in time.

The pro players had been partially correct. Ye Xiu had been waiting for the right opportunity. However, he wasn’t waiting for an opportunity to heal. Instead, he had been waiting for an opportunity to counterattack, waiting until Cloud Piercer’s health was low enough for him to kill him in one combo. He had also been waiting for Zhou Zekai to rush him down.

When performing a rush, attacking the opponent would be the priority, while defense would be secondary. Ye Xiu had been watching Cloud Piercer’s health carefully. He seized the moment Zhou Zekai decided to rush at him and counter-rushed him.

The two were fighting at close-range, and a Sharpshooter couldn’t compare to an unspecialized in close combat. And this time, Ye Xiu wasn’t going to give him any opportunity to trade. He would wipe out that 14% in one go.

Everyone saw what happened afterwards. Lord Grim completely suppressed Cloud Piercer. Apart from taking some damage when forcing the Colliding Stab, Cloud Piercer was unable to do anything. An opening had appeared because Lord Grim wasn’t able to continue his combo, but Ye Xiu had been ready. Cloud Piercer was only hit away from death. With a teleport, Lord Grim gave the final fatal strike.

What the pro players saw wasn’t just technical prowess, but their control over the pace of the fight.

Ye Xiu had won, a very close win, but if you considered how he had taken such a massive amount of damage from the Thunder Snipe at the start and then made a comeback from a disadvantageous position, he had been the one with a stronger grasp over the pace of the fight.

Of course, Lord Grim’s class as an unspecialized and his transforming Myriad Manifestations Umbrella contributed greatly towards this achievement. If he wasn’t an unspecialized, without the possibility of healing, Zhou Zekai wouldn’t have waited until Lord Grim only had 5% health before trying to rush him down. If Lord Grim couldn’t heal, Zhou Zekai would have likely rushed him down to decide the fight when Lord Grim had over 10% of his health left.

In the online game, in PvP, if the winner relied on a class advantage or an equipment advantage to win, the loser would often spite the winner for having an unfair advantage.

But on the pro stage, everyone would exploit the slightest of advantages to win. Ye Xiu was no different. His unspecialized and his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella gave other pro players a huge headache. They really wanted to be like the in-game players: if you didn’t have that stupid umbrella or if you weren’t playing a broken class, I would have won.

But then again, when Ye Xiu had been using a Battle Mage, hadn’t they been getting slapped left and right as well?

The pro players applauded. It had been a spectacular fight. The winner showed terrifying skill, but the loser did as well. When watching a match, they often pretended as if they were the ones playing. Their expressions were grave. Clearly, none of them dared to say that it might have gone differently if they had been the ones playing.

Game two of the finals. The first round of the group arena had ended. In Samsara’s home stadium, Happy had won the first round. Ye Xiu continued his legendary win streak, and this time, he had defeated Zhou Zekai, the number one player. With this win, he shut up the haters, who argued that his win streak was because he was avoiding those ace players in the group arena.

Even Zhou Zekai had lost against him. If that wasn’t enough to legitimize his win streak, did he need to play 1v2s?

The Samsara fans in the crowd were silent. Their ace, the god in their eyes, had lost? He had come out specifically to play against Ye Xiu, coming out full force, yet he had lost?

Samsara’s fans weren’t used to this. For a moment, they were having trouble accepting reality to the point of even forgetting to give a consolation applause to the loser. In their eyes, there were only cheers and praise for Zhou Zekai. Consoling him as the loser didn’t feel right…

“Then, it’s my turn.” At Samsara’s bench, Jiang Botao got up and went to welcome Zhou Zekai back.

“Mm.” Zhou Zekai nodded his head. He was always quiet, so it was hard to tell what he was feeling.

“4% health, huh. He’s probably going to heal now…” Jiang Botao muttered as he walked towards the stage.

The atmosphere in the stadium was heavy. Samsara had forgotten to console Zhou Zekai, who had lost. They had also forgotten to cheer to give their Jiang Botao encouragement. They were still trying to take in the fact that Zhou Zekai had lost.

But Jiang Botao didn’t appear to be concerned.

4%.

Lord Grim only had a few drops of health left. From the perspective of the group arena as a whole, Zhou Zekai’s loss wasn’t bad. It was just that because of how important the fight had been to the audience, because Zhou Zekai had gone first to play against Ye Xiu, because it was a challenge that Zhou Zekai had taken the initiative to put out.

In the end, he lost.

It made Samsara’s fans feel embarrassed and ashamed…

Zhou Zekai had never given them these feelings before. There were even a few girls out in the audience who burst out into tears.

But Zhou Zekai’s teammate, Samsara’s vice-captain Jiang Botao, wasn’t affected by the atmosphere. He walked calmly onto the stage and into the player booth.

The characters loaded. The map loaded. The match began.

“Hello, senior! I’m coming!” Zhou Zekai had been silent, but as soon as Jiang Botao went onto the stage, he greeted Ye Xiu enthusiastically.

“Coming to surrender?” Ye Xiu replied.

“No way,” said Jiang Botao, “I’m here to experience how fearsome you seniors are.”

Chapter 1592 - Healer

The exchange between Ye Xiu and Jiang Botao before the match began hadn’t been broadcasted or recorded, so only those who’d been onstage at the time knew that Jiang Botao’s message was a callback to what they’d said earlier. The audience didn’t know anything about it, so they just treated it as a polite challenge.

But Lord Grim only had 4% health left. For a Spellblade, most Wave Formation attacks would be enough to knock out that much health. From the very beginning, this faceoff would be a very lopsided one.

But Happy’s supporters didn’t lose faith. Those who thought that a match was already over at low health, why not go talk to last match’s Lin Jingyan!

It wasn’t just Happy’s supporters, either. Even Pan Lin and Li Yibo clearly had a lot of faith in Ye Xiu right now.

“Lord Grim still has 4% health,” said Pan Lin.

“Yes. With Jiang Botao’s Spellblade, one Wave Formation could probably take him out,” said Li Yibo.

No matter what, this was the situation. It wouldn’t be wrong to explain it.

“Let’s see what Ye Xiu will do,” said Pan Lin.

Heal, of course… That was what Li Yibo thought, but he didn’t voice the thought. What if that guy didn’t heal?

“Heal, this guy’s definitely going to heal again.” Among the pro players, countless people were already pointing it out.

“He always does that, the same old thing!”

“Having this kind of character appear in the group arena is so broken, the Alliance should do something about it.”

Someone coughed. It was Tiny Herb’s Xu Bin.

Lord Grim was able to heal by relying on the low-level skills of the Cleric and Paladin classes. The low-level skills of these classes weren’t limited to just unspecialized, though. The other Priest classes, the Knight and Exorcist, could learn them too. And reality showed that the players of these two classes wouldn’t pass on this kind of opportunity. In particular, the Cleric’s Small Cure and the Paladin’s Recover were practically a necessity for their classes. Healing during a solo battle wasn’t patented by the unspecialized Lord Grim, it was something that these two classes often did as well. Defeating an opponent during the group arena and then hiding at the start of the next battle to heal was commonly done when it came to them.

But their presence was far weaker than that of Ye Xiu and Lord Grim. Xu Bin’s cough didn’t catch much attention, and the other players were all rising in rebellion to denounce this kind of practice. They completely overlooked the fact that they were attacking more than just Ye Xiu.  ( B oxnovel.c om )

Xu Bin felt incredibly awkward. If he jumped up now to say something, wouldn’t that just be the same as eating these attacks? Helpless, he could only maintain his silence, pretending that he had nothing to do with this. As he looked around, he couldn’t help but see someone else wearing a similarly awkward expression, looking like he wanted to distance himself.

The two of them met eyes, reaching a tacit mutual understanding.

Xu Bin, Knight player.

Tian Sen, Exorcist player.

Both were Priest classes, group arena healers that everyone was now attacking for being dirty, shameless, sneaky, foul, cheating, undignified, unoriginal…

“He’s definitely going to heal, is that even a question? Look at how he’s scurrying around so sneakily, he’s looking for somewhere to hide, right? How much is he planning to heal? All the way?” Finally, the topic had one single target again. Just in time, Huang Shaotian turned the conversation subject back to the ongoing match.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was currently moving, not toward the center road, and not circling around. Just like Huang Shaotian had said, he looked like he was searching for a place to hide and heal up for all eternity.

“Look, he’s about to heal right now!”

“He’s healing!”

“He’s really healing!”

“Small Heal!”

“Fuck, just like we thought, he’s just that disgraceful! Of course he heals!” Huang Shaotian rattled on, far noisier than the broadcast commentator Pan Lin. How could Pan Lin dare use this kind of mocking speech to criticize Ye Xiu!

“Shame on him!”

“Yeah!”

“So unfair!”

“We have to change the competition rules.”

As the discussion progressed, Xu Bin and Tian Sen, as well as the other Knight and Exorcist players, all lowered their heads. Even though they knew that everyone was talking about Ye Xiu and had just forgotten about them for the moment, they simply had no way to face this calmly.

“He’s still showing off in the chat, he thinks he’s so honorable!” Huang Shaotian continued to shout.

At the moment, Ye Xiu had just sent a message in the chat: “Are you at the center yet? Hold on, I’m healing first.”

Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had just arrived at the center of the map without seeing Lord Grim. He’d already been thinking that Ye Xiu might heal, and with this message, the other player made it very clear. He was very straightforward, very confident. He just told him directly.

But Jiang Botao wasn’t just going to wait there! If he waited for Ye Xiu to voluntarily show up, then he’d probably be waiting until Lord Grim was completely reborn.

Jiang Botao controlled Empty Waves to move forward, toward Lord Grim’s spawn point. Along the way, he changed his path constantly, adjusting his view. Because he’d watched the previous match from off-stage, he knew that Ye Xiu had ways of covering himself. Fortunately, Samsara had chosen this map and so they were more familiar with it. After seeing Ye Xiu’s tactic earlier, as long as they paid attention, it wouldn’t have much effect against them anymore.

Jiang Botao was now on guard against this tactic as he controlled Empty Waves to move forward, but he didn’t discover anything. Soon, the dripstone along his path had all been carefully sifted through, and the only remaining possible places for Lord Grim to hide were in front of him. There were three stalagmites, standing in a triangle, relatively close together. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was probably right behind one of them.

Jiang Botao didn’t let Empty Waves approach to investigate. When the distance was close enough, he quietly lifted his sword and began to cast.

The short sword Divine Chain rippled,

Over here!

Jiang Botao didn’t wait for Lord Grim to appear. Empty Waves lifted his sword and swung it, releasing a Waltzing Wave Formation that circled around toward that stalagmite.

The stadium was silent.

By this point, Samsara’s fans had basically recovered from the emotions of Zhou Zekai’s defeat, but seeing their vice-captain bravely fighting onstage right now, they couldn’t reward him with applause.  ( B oxnovel.c om )

Because, with the omniscient view, they could see that behind that stalagmite wasn’t Lord Grim, but a Goblin that he had summoned.

“Little Lu did you see that? If you’re too simple and naïve, you’re no match for Ye Xiu…” Seeing this scene, Huang Shaotian sighed and gave this lesson to his junior sitting next to him.

“Simple and naive? You’re talking about Jiang Botao?” When Misty Rain’s Li Hua heard this, he couldn’t help but interject, surprised.

“Of course not, I’m just using an example. That guy definitely isn’t,” said Huang Shaotian.

Jiang Botao, Season 6 debut. After joining Samsara, he began making a name for himself. Under Zhou Zekai’s light, the Samsara players all seemed less eye-catching. But as opponents that had interacted with him onstage, everyone was clear that Samsara’s Jiang Botao was not an easy character to deal with. At the very least, simple and naïve definitely was not a phrase that could describe him.

Chapter 1593 - A Senior’s Fearsomeness

Electric Wave Formation, Waltzing Wave Slash.

The weakest summon, the Goblin, couldn’t resist these two powerful attacks, but so what? The viewers could clearly see that Lord Grim wasn’t inside the Electric Wave Formation’s range. By the time the lightning struck the Goblin, Lord Grim had finished forming the hand seals for Shadow Clone Technique, launching a sneak attack from Empty Waves’ side.

But!

After drawing out a Waltzing Wave Slash, Empty Waves’ Silver weapon, Divine Chain, didn’t stop and headed directly towards his side. Killing intent emanated from the edge of its blades as it tore through the air. A Wave Wheel Slasher flew directly towards Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu was caught off guard. His Lord Grim had only just landed when the Wave Wheel Slasher arrived. There was no time for him to dodge. Guard? Parry? It would be useless. Wave Wheel Slasher was a skill with grab priority. Even if he tried using his shield to block it, the Wave Wheel Slasher would still tear aparts its defenses, locking him in place and dealing damage. A Dismantle skill could work, but Dismantle skills required the proper timing. Using it now would be too late.

There was unexpectedly nothing he could do?

All of the viewers including the pro players thought that the Wave Wheel Slasher was inescapable. Suddenly, Lord Grim swung his arm, sending out a flash of sword light. Magic waves specific to Spellblades swirled around the light. It looked exactly the same as Empty Waves’ slash. It was also a Wave Wheel Slasher. Wave Wheel Slasher against Wave Wheel Slasher.

The two streaks of sword light intertwined.

In a collision between two of the same skills, the outcome would be decided based on attack power as well as factors such as timing.

Lord Grim’s attack had been hasty, and the magic emanating from his sword couldn’t compare to a true Spellblade’s. The Level 20 Spellblade class advancement skill “Killing Intent Wave” specifically buffed wave skills. Unspecialized could not learn class advancement skills, so his wave skills would naturally lose to a Spellblade’s.

Lord Grim lost the priority battle. The undulating magic swallowed him, forcing Lord Grim to stagger back. However, the imprisonment from the Wave Wheel Slasher was shattered by the collision. Lord Grim’s Wave Wheel Slasher fell short compared to Empty Waves’, but it couldn’t be considered useless. It had nulled Wave Wheel Slasher’s grab effect, achieving Ye Xiu’s goal. After staggering back two steps, he immediately steadied himself and rushed forward again.

Although Spellblades were part of the Swordsman superclass, their strengths lay in mid-ranged combat. Close combat wasn’t their class’s expertise. The moment Empty Waves swung out a Wave Wheel Slasher, Jiang Botao had Empty Waves step to the side to pull away. Lord Grim was able to negate his Wave Wheel Slasher’s grab effect, but the shockwave still pushed him back two steps. Even though he was able to immediately steady himself and rush back, Empty Waves had already followed with his next attack. A streak of scarlet fire roared towards him, a Flame Wave Slash.

Fire Wave Slash was the strongest of the Wave Slashs and had the strongest knockback. Forcing your way through it wasn’t possible. It wasn’t just flames. It also contained powerful undulating magic.

Unable to get past it, he could only dodge. However, Ye Xiu knew that this attack was just the beginning.

Fire Wave Slash, Ice Wave Slash, and Light Wave Slash. These three Wave Slashs containing fire, ice, and light were often used together. This combo was nicknamed “Three Fold Wave”. The Fire Wave Slash had already put Ye Xiu in a fluster. How could ice and light not follow?

And the ice and light quickly followed!

Lord Grim turned and used the Assassin skill, Shining Cut. Cold light flashed as the Fire Wave Slash brushed past him. When he looked towards Empty Waves again, as expected, it was the “Three Fold Wave.” The second Light Wave Slash had arrived next.

As the name implied, Light Wave Slash was extremely fast, but Jiang Botao had underestimated the speed of Lord Grim’s movement skill. The Light Wave Slash flashed past him, missing Lord Grim!

Thunderous applause.

Ye Xiu didn’t know, but the viewers watching did. The Waltzing Wave Slash from before hadn’t hit the Goblin behind the stalactite, instead circling around it before returning like a boomerang. To dodge the Light Wave Slash, Lord Grim had used Shining Cut. However, although he was able to dodge the Light Wave Slash, the Waltzing Wave Slash had looped around, striking him in the back.

Lord Grim lost his balance and stumbled forward.

Naive? Pure?

Sure enough, none of those traits had any relation to Jiang Botao. How could a naive and pure person set up such a tricky and crafty trap?

Ice Wave Slash!

The third wave of the “Three Fold Wave” swept towards the stumbling Lord Grim. Jiang Botao had calculated how he would follow up and was about to go through with it, when he saw Lord Grim suddenly raise his umbrella. With a whoosh, the umbrella opened. Lord Grim used his shield to block the Ice Wave Slash.

Jiang Botao felt a tremble in his heart. He had calculated the distance and timing of these consecutive Wave Slashs. Even a machine wouldn’t have been able to react in time. For Ye Xiu to do so, he must have been prepared ahead of time.

The thought flashed through his mind. The Ice Wave Slash hit the canvas of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. The shards of ice seemed to come alive, shooting back towards Empty Waves.

He really was ready for it!

This wasn’t just a block, but a skill: Shield Counter!

Shield Counter absorbed and reflected damage depending on the level of the skill. Lord Grim’s Shield Counter could only be level one, so the reflected ice shards was very sparse. However, the speed of the ice shards was no less than before. Jiang Botao had wanted to chain together his attacks, so he positioned Empty Waves as close as possible to Lord Grim. But that only made it more difficult for him to dodge the reflected Ice Wave Slash now.

The reflected damage from a level one Shield Counter was insignificant, but the threat from Ice Wave Slash wasn’t the damage but rather its Freeze effect. The Freeze effect would be drastically reduced from the Shield Counter, but it still couldn’t be ignored and had to be dodged.

Spellblades wore plate armor, so their movements were slow. Dragged down by the heavy weight of his armor, Empty Waves was just barely able to dodge the ice shards, but by this time, Lord Grim had closed in.

With a bang, Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella struck Empty Waves’ armor. Knights also wore plate armor. With their heavy weight, the knockback from a Charge could send a Spellblade flying. But Lord Grim’s Charge was much weaker. Against a plate armored Spellblade, all it could do was send the opponent stumbling back a few steps.

But this was what Ye Xiu wanted. He wanted to take the initiative, not send Empty Waves flying away.

“What do you think? Have you gotten a taste of this senior’s fearsomeness?”

As he typed, Lord Grim rushed forward. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear, stabbing towards Empty Waves’ head.

Jiang Botao didn’t have time to reply back to Ye Xiu’s message. Empty Waves held up his weapon, Divine Chains, in an attempt to parry the Dragon Tooth. Suddenly, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed. The canvas retracted, and the parry missed. All that remained in Jiang Botao’s sigh was the muzzle of a gun.

Boom boom boom!

Three Anti-Tank Missiles fired. How could Empty Waves dodge something at point blank distance? Blast after blast, Empty Waves was swallowed by smoke and light.

Flash!

A sword was unsheathed. Two streaks of light followed, creating a cross in the air.

Empty Waves was still inside the smoke and light from the explosions. However, he was able to swing his shortsword, Divine Chains, downwards from the previous parry position. Ghost Slash!

Ghostblades and Spellblades primarily dealt magic damage. As a result, when one class used the other class’s skills, the skills were quite powerful. This Ghost Slash collided with Lord Grim’s Gore Cross.

Ghost Slash had a blow-away effect and impressive attack priority. The slash shattered the sword light from Gore Cross, and Lord Grim was forced to jump back to avoid the blow.

The Divine Chains swung back up, using a Spellblade skill: Earth Wave Slash*.

The earth was swept up as it headed towards Lord Grim. By this time, the flames from the explosion had yet to completely disperse. From Jiang Botao’s screen, only a fuzzy haze could be seen, but even so, he was able to push out two attacks.

With a turn, Lord Grim dodged the Earth Wave Slash. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella swung horizontally, while changing forms into a scythe, a Priest weapon. Using an Exorcist skill “Hook”, it went straight for Empty Waves’ throat.

Jiang Botao’s vision had returned to normal. He rolled on the ground, dodging the attack. He slashed upwards with his sword, counter attacking with a Storm Wave Slash.

The two began fighting back and forth. Lord Grim had too little health. Even though he had been furiously healing himself at the start of the match, he wasn’t able to heal too much. No one had expected him to win this fight. It was just a question of how much damage he was able to deal to Jiang Botao. In the end, he was able to take down 24% of Empty Waves’ health before falling.

Using 4% health in exchange for 24% was a very good result. Happy was happy. They got up and welcomed Ye Xiu down from the stage. Of course, in reality, their applause was mainly for Ye Xiu’s win in the first round against Zhou Zekai. That had been a huge boost to their morale. Ye Xiu had been in the player booth the entire time, so he didn’t know. However, the others remembered how quiet the stadium had been when Zhou Zekai lost.

Mo Fan was Happy’s second player for the group arena. He clapped very mechanically alongside everyone else, waiting for Ye Xiu to come back before heading onto the stage.

“Be careful, that guy’s got a very black heart,” Ye Xiu reminded.

No one knew if Mo Fan heard him or not, but he was on his way towards the stage now. On the side, Fang Rui booed at Ye Xiu: “Is there anyone with a blacker heart than yours?”

“Of course not! Boss is the best at everything!” Steamed Bun replied back for Ye Xiu.

Chapter 1594 - Young Growth

Both sides had sent out their second player in the group arena, but the atmosphere in the stadium seemed to have paused at the first matchup. When Mo Fan walked towards the stage, the crowd members in the away team seats clapped wildly, but because the Samsara fans were still downcast, the overall atmosphere felt rather oppressive. No boos or taunts were thrown towards the opposing side.

The atmosphere in the stadium could affect how a player performed, especially more emotional players. For them, the more intense the crowd, the more exhilarating it was. It didn’t matter if the cheers were aimed towards them or the other side, the cheers could help ignite their fighting spirit all the same.

The atmosphere in Samsara’s stadium was abnormal. It was only the second player in the group arena, but because of Zhou Zekai’s defeat, the crowd seemed to be dispirited and cold.

However, this ice-cold atmosphere seemed to be far more comfortable for Mo Fan compared to the past. His footsteps were light and quick as he walked towards the stage.

The match soon began, and the two characters loaded in.

The map wasn’t a random map, so the group arena lineups were predetermined. Jiang Botao knew who his next opponent would be.

But while Mo Fan’s Deception loaded into the map, Jiang Botao was in a similar mood as the crowd. He was still thinking about the previous match and was having trouble readjusting his mindset.  ( B oxnovel.c om )

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim only had 4% of his health remaining from his battle with Zhou Zekai. However, with that 4%, he was able to take out 24% of Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves. This was not a good outcome.

But if you considered that Ye Xiu had healed at the start and his true health wasn’t really 4%, it wasn’t too bad.

But he couldn’t seem to forget how he had believed that he had seen through Ye Xiu, but in reality, he hadn’t, and Ye Xiu was still able to get off a combo on him.

Even though he was able to quickly stabilize his footing again, he had indeed experienced Ye Xiu’s fearsomeness.

He hadn’t looked down on Ye Xiu. At the start of the fight, there had been a psychological battle. Jiang Botao’s words hadn’t been fierce. There was no unadorned ridicule. He had used a rather passive-aggressive method to get at his opponent. This was because he knew that to these experienced old players, that sort of unadorned trash talk wouldn’t faze them. On the contrary, the seemingly more careless but sincere remarks were more likely to tilt them.

Jiang Botao wasn’t the first on Samsara to go up, but before the match had started, he had talked with Ye Xiu quite a bit.

It didn’t seem like he was trying to provoke Ye Xiu. He just seemed to be calmly stating a fact. However, Ye Xiu exposed his intentions to teach them a lesson. Jiang Botao’s calm and collected provocation had clearly succeeded.

He had wanted to trigger this sort of mentality from Ye Xiu. That way, when he faced Zhou Zekai, he might play more rashly and become distracted by Jiang Botao’s words. Even if he won against Zhou Zekai with this mentality, when he faced Jiang Botao, he might play poorly from being too excited…

In short, Jiang Botao’s goal was to break his concentration.

However, it ignited Ye Xiu’s fighting spirit instead. Then, he beat Zhou Zekai and fought against Jiang Botao well enough to display his “fearsomeness”.

Jiang Botao was at a loss. He wasn’t sure if his mental attack had worked or not.

If the skill gap had been wide, then this sort of mental attack was useless. But Ye Xiu was facing Zhou Zekai! There wasn’t a wide skill gap.

That was why Jiang Botao was rather inclined to believe that Ye Xiu hadn’t been provoked by him in the end.

Was the attitude that Ye Xiu displayed just in order to make me overly optimistic?

This was the “fearsomeness” that Jiang Botao experienced. The subtleties in this psychological battle couldn’t be completely uncovered in just a few minutes. The psychological battle was no less fierce than the battle on stage.

Loading complete!

When these words popped up, the scene instantly shifted to his character’s view. The countdown finished, and Jiang Botao immediately refocused.

Ye Xiu? Who? What did he do? No idea!

His opponent was Mo Fan. What he needed to do was beat him, that was all.

Jiang Botao’s attention quickly returned to the match, to the opponent he would be facing next, to Happy’s Mo Fan.

A quiet, persistent, patient, and explosive player.

He played rather unorthodoxly, but what was more astonishing was that after an entire season, these unorthodox traits still remained. Jiang Botao was very curious to how Happy practiced. Had there been any guidance for this rookie?

Could they all be self-made geniuses? But Happy didn’t only have one rookie though. The others weren’t as unorthodox as him.

Unless Happy told him the answer, thinking about it was pointless. Knowing the reason wasn’t important anyways. As long as he could see what condition his opponent was in, that was all that was needed.

Empty Waves began to move, going straight towards the center. At the same time, Jiang Botao typed out in the chat: “Straight to the center? Going around? Thanks.”

No response. Jiang Botao wasn’t surprised. Up until now, no one had seen Mo Fan say anything during a match, let alone respond to trash talk.

Jiang Botao hadn’t expected any response from Mo Fan, and reality proved that he was right.

Empty Waves quickly reached the center of the map. The center of the map had a huge stalactite that connected the ground and ceiling.

Before Jiang Botao got close to it, he looked around, and sure enough, Mo Fan’s Deception had taken a roundabout path.  ( B oxnovel.c om )

Mo Fan would circle around 9 times out of 10 to set up an ambush, and it looked like this time was no exception.

But this was Samsara’s map. When choosing a map, the map should be advantageous to your side but disadvantageous to the other side. The map should help the players on your side perform, while restricting the players on the other side. That was how a map should be picked.

Mo Fan’s playstyle was restricted by this map. Seeing that the other side hadn’t gone straight towards the center, Jiang Botao had Empty Waves find a spot and wait there quietly.

There were three stalactites in his immediate surroundings. The closest one was still a distance away. If Mo Fan wanted to ambush him from there, he would still be able to react in time. By positioning himself here, he seemed to have shut down Mo Fan’s preferred methods.

“Would you like my coordinates?” Jiang Botao had finished finding a spot. He continued to check his surroundings and tried to communicate with Mo Fan.

Mo Fan spoke more in the game than in real life, but when playing in a match, he didn’t like to talk with his opponent, especially if it was to respond to this sort of useless chatter.

I don’t need your coordinates because I already see you…

Deception was hidden behind one of the three stalactites close to Empty Waves.

It wasn’t easy to ambush him at this distance, so Mo Fan patiently waited.

But Jiang Botao didn’t move.

In these circumstances, if Jiang Botao didn’t move and he didn’t move, he would be the one penalized. Mo Fan had made this mistake before, and he still remembered it clearly.

He checked the time and made sure that the other side wasn’t going to move. Mo Fan was helpless. He could only act.

Deception peeked out his head from behind the stalactite.

Jiang Botao had been checking his surroundings the entire time. Suddenly, he noticed a flash of cold light from one of the stalactites. Deception had thrown a Shuriken towards him.

Empty Waves dodged it and then quickly moved forward, swinging his Divine Chains. Jiang Botao didn’t think a simple swing of his weapon would hit Deception, who only had a small part of his body exposed. As a result, when he swung his Divine Chains, he used Waltzing Wave Slash to curve his attack.

Deception pulled back and then took out his ninjato. He stabbed it into the stalactite and then leapt onto it.

Jiang Botao couldn’t see what Deception was doing, but he also wasn’t charging in. After all, Spellblades were a mid-range class.

Empty Waves moved laterally to expand his vision.

At this distance, Empty Waves could see Deception above. Mo Fan’s attempt at a sneak attack was like child’s play. Mo Fan had completely overlooked the characteristics of his opponent’s class.

But no one had expected Deceptions to move along with Empty Waves. Empty Waves moved to the side to widen his vision, while Deception also circled around to keep himself hidden.

He had predicted what Jiang Botao would do!

At Happy’s player bench, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and the others gave off smiles of gratitude.

Mo Fan was becoming more and more like a pro player. For example, predicting what the opponent would do based off of the opponent’s strengths.

He had been trained in an unorthodox way. His playstyle was unique to him, but his thoughts, his intuition, and his approach towards the game was becoming more and more like a pro players’.

He was playing the game like it was a competitive match rather than like his former scrap-picking days. With this change in perspective, he was gradually forming his own way to better utilize his strengths to win.

The more time went on, the less Ye Xiu worried about Mo Fan’s future. Mo Fan might not like talking to others, but that didn’t mean he refused to change. He had his own way of doing things. It might be slower than if he listened directly to his advice, but what he found in the end would definitely be the most suitable and the best for him.

“It’s good to be young!” Wei Chen suddenly sighed. He had also seen Mo Fan’s quiet growth and hated how he wouldn’t have the same opportunity as him ever again. If not, no matter how difficult it was, he would certainly try his hardest to break through and improve.

Growth was the domain of the young!

Chapter 1595 - Calm Terror

Waltzing Wave Slash, missed.

There was not a soul in sight.

The others on Happy were gratified seeing Mo Fan’s read on Jiang Botao, but this alone wouldn’t be enough to baffle him. Mo Fan had learned to make decisions according to the opponent’s class. How could an even more experienced player like Jiang Botao not be able to either?

Deception was a Ninja. Ninjas could use their ninjato to climb up walls, and no pro player would ever overlook this ability when playing against a Ninja. Because Empty Waves was a certain distance away from the stalactite, he could see the majority of it. When he moved to the side to take a look from a different angle, he also moved forward, which allowed him to see the entire height of the stalactite.

But there was nothing below or above.

Jiang Botao reacted at lightning speed. Empty Waves immediately went back to his previous position.

Deception was instantly exposed. Empty Waves slashed upwards, sending a Light Wave Slash towards him. The slash came out at the speed of light, tearing through Deception. Poof!

“It’s a Shadow Clone Technique!!” Pan Lin shouted as if he were crying out in surprise in place of Jiang Botao. In reality, with their omniscient view over the battle, they had already known this would happen. As Mo Fan’s Deception circled around to prevent Empty Waves from seeing him, he also used a Shadow Clone Technique. The shadow clone remained hanging on the stalactite, while the real body dropped to the ground and then disappeared.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Deception had used Underground Tunneling Technique to hide and then strike at the right opportunity.

Hua!

Deception drilled out of the ground, earth still crumbling away from him, as he aimed straight for Empty Waves’ throat.

But by this time, Empty Waves had retracted his Divine Chains, Guard!

Ding!

Their weapons collided. Empty Waves used the impact to slide backwards. He was even able to react to such a sudden Underground Tunneling Technique?

Earthquake Sword!

Empty Waves threw out an Earth Wave Slash. It was too close, too fast, and this time, Mo Fan wasn’t able to react in time. Deception was hit by the attack.

It wasn’t that Jiang Botao’s reaction speed had been godly, but rather that he had been ready. He had seen through Mo Fan’s plans. The Light Wave Slash had simply been a bait.

After Earth, Fire and Ice! Two successive wave slashes one after the other. However, when the ice crystals swept over, all that was frozen was a straw dummy.

Substitution Technique!

Mo Fan had used a Ninja skill to escape this combo. This was why the “Three Fold Wave” was always “Light, Fire, Ice” in that order. Otherwise, the combo could be broken. Earth Wave Slash didn’t have the same speed as Light Wave Slash. As a result, there was an opening between the following Fire and Ice Wave Slashs, which Mo Fan seized, using a Substitution Technique to escape.

Substitution Technique teleported the user to a random location, so Mo Fan didn’t know where he would end up at himself. It would naturally be even more difficult for the opponent to follow since there was no logic behind it.

Mo Fan had taken advantage of this randomness multiple times in the group arena against Tyranny. He gambled again and again, and in the end, he was able to beat Tyranny’s Qin Muyun.

That fight had left a deep impression on many people. And now that Mo Fan had used Substitution Technique again, their first thought was that it wasn’t to escape but rather to attack!

Jiang Botao also realized this point. Empty Waves didn’t just stand there stupidly. He looked all around him, swinging his sword in a circle.

Magic burst from his blade, covering all of Empty Waves.

Nebula Wave Slash, the Level 75 Spellblade skill.When used, the magic would be shaped randomly. But the magic could also be controlled by the user. One way was to have it spread around 360 degrees. This skill was extremely flexible, allowing the user to use it in surprising ways. After this skill came out, it became hugely popular among Spellblade players. Spellblades mainly added points into their Wave Slashs or Wave Formations. However, the Nebula Wave Slash was so fun and useful that even players who specialized in Wave Formations would spend their skill points to learn and level it.

Pro players obviously wouldn’t learn it just because it was fun. Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves specialized in Wave Slashs. As a result, he had spent a lot of effort coming up with ways to use this skill.

Mo Fan really had used the Substitution Technique to attack. He didn’t want to repeat the same strategy as before, but he simply realized the fact that the Substitution Technique’s random teleport could catch the opponent off guard. He was just taking advantage of it right now.

He threw a Storm Shuriken towards Empty Waves and rushed forward to close in. But then, he saw Empty Waves turn in a circle, creating a protective barrier around him with a Nebula Wave Slash.

Shua!

The fast and powerful Storm Shuriken was blocked by the Nebula Wave Slash and deflected to the side. The priority of Nebula Wave Slash wasn’t low, having properties of both offense and defense. For a moment, Mo Fan wasn’t able to find any openings.

When Jiang Botao turned and used Nebula Wave Slash, he had located Deception. The Nebula Wave Slash appeared to be a complete circle, but after Jiang Botao found Deception, he immediately made some slight adjustments. In the end, the Nebular Wave Slash formed a large crescent moon. His shortsword, Divine Chains, swung towards Deception. Instead of spreading outwards, the magic swept towards that direction.

The AoE covered at least five or six body lengths. The magic wave was neither concentrated nor dispersed. It was like a wall that was pushing towards Deception.

Dodge?

Dodge where?

Up? Down? Left? Right?

In the end, Jiang Botao was able to turn the Nebula Wave Slash into a gigantic AoE attack. Deception’s escape routes had been sealed, and his escape tools, Shadow Clone Technique and Substitution Technique were on cooldown.

But Mo Fan didn’t just sit there doing nothing. Deception immediately retreated backwards. The Nebula Wave Slash was shaped like a crescent moon, which meant that there was more room to escape from the sides. Deception wanted to take advantage of this point.

But as the Nebula Wave Slash expanded, it quickly patched up these openings on the side. The magic was densely weaved together with no openings. This time, Mo Fan was helpless. The retreating Deception was swallowed by the Nebula Wave Slash…

Everyone looked towards Deception’s health… but they discovered that the powerful Nebula Wave Slash didn’t deal as much damage as everyone had expected.

This Level 75 skill had a very high base damage, but because of how spread out it was, the damage was reduced considerably.

Loud thunder, but only small drops of rain…

That was the feeling this attack gave off. Some people felt disappointed. Some people saw this attack as nothing more than the start of a combo.

Empty Waves got up and gave chase, sending out Wave Slash after Wave Slash, magic slash after magic slash striking Deception. The combo meter soared as Deception’s health plummeted. There was unexpectedly nothing Mo Fan could do. Empty Waves didn’t only include the unbreakable “Three Fold Wave”, but also many other Wave Slash skill. Even so, Mo Fan wasn’t able to find an opening to escape?

Escaping was what Mo Fan was best at. In terms of escaping, Mo Fan was number one even in the pro scene.

But right now, his Deception had unexpectedly been completely locked into place by Empty Waves.

By Empty Waves, a Spellblade!

This was worthy of astonishment.

Although Spellblades were Swordsman, they were considered a mid-ranged magic class. There were two ways to play Spellblades. The first was to specialize in Wave Formations, larger AoEs and strong CC. The other way was to specialize in Wave Slashs, stronger DPS but weaker CC. Their mid-range meant that they didn’t have the same oppressiveness as close-ranged classes.

However, Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves had linked together his Wave Slashs so tightly that not even a master at escaping like Mo Fan was able to get away.

How is he doing it?

Those familiar with Spellblades were in awe. They couldn’t see the reason. They could only be in awe at Jiang Botao’s skil. No wonder he was the number one Spellblade. He could do what others couldn’t.

As for the pro players, they quickly discovered the secret.

Prediction and positioning!

Whenever Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves used a Wave Slash, he would never be in the same spot. He was fully putting to use the characteristics of every Wave Slash, searching for the most suitable position to send his attack where he wanted it to go, striking Deception and continuing the combo.

Every attack was a read. This was because Mo Fan wasn’t just doing nothing. He was trying to find an opening, and ever struggle from Deception was read perfectly by Jiang Botao.

“No, he isn’t just reading him…” Ye Xiu said.

“He’s constantly putting out bait. Every attack he makes leaves what seems like an opening, but this opening will quickly be patched up by his next attack. Mo Fan is too sharp. His reactions are too fast. The moment he sees the opening, he immediately goes for it. However, by then, Jiang Botao has already patched it with another attack, which then leaves another opening… it’s a strategy that works against Mo Fan specifically. He’s taking advantage of Mo Fan’s strengths, rather than his weaknesses. That guy’s quite terrifying.” Ye Xiu said.

“It never feels like he’s that great of a player though…” Chen Guo said.

“Because he’s too calm.” Ye Xiu said.

Chapter 1596 - Vice Captain's Song

In recent years, Jiang Botao’s placings in the All-Star rankings were quite high. Everyone felt like he was an amazing player, but whenever people were asked to say what specifically was amazing about him, nine times out of ten, they wouldn’t be able to answer back. They had that feeling in their heart, but they didn’t know how to describe it in words.

Even Team Samsara themselves couldn’t seem to find the right words to describe their vice-captain. In the end, his fame seemed to simply be because he was the vice-captain of a championship team.

And now, Ye Xiu had given him high praise: terrifying!

A calm terror!

Chen Guo couldn’t immediately understand what Ye Xiu meant by that. She really wanted to drag Ye Xiu over and explain it more clearly, but right now, Mo Fan’s situation was more concerning.

A calm terror… it wasn’t important that she understood it. What was more important was whether Mo Fan could.

A 27 hit combo!

This was the number on the combo counter. It was extremely eye-catching. Even a close-ranged class would have difficulty pulling off this long of a combo. Spellblades had it somewhat easier to get a high-hit combo since their wave swords counted for several hits, but a 27 hit combo in one breath wasn’t easy at all.

Spellblades were Swordsman, but unlike Blade Masters and Berserkers, their strikes didn’t feel like strikes. For those classes, combos were an important metric to measure a player’s skill. On the other hand, Spellblades were more similar to Mage classes like Elementalists and Witches. Although they could also combo, no one measured an Elementalist’s skill based off how long their combos were. It would almost be forcing the Elementalist into doing something they shouldn’t be doing.

As a result, if these types of Mage classes ever put out long combos, it was mainly a sign that they were crushing a noob. However, this was the Glory championship finals, a battle between the very best players. No matter how new or how much of an underdog Happy was, to reach this step, it was impossible for them to be noobs.

There were no noobs in the finals. Mo Fan may be a rookie, but he was undoubtedly a troublesome opponent. Even so, Jiang Botao was able to get his Spellblade to perform such a long combo against this sort of opponent on the finals stage!

This obviously wasn’t him crushing a noob. It was an unprecedented display of brilliance. When the combo reached 30, the crowd went wild. After Zhou Zekai lost to Ye Xiu, Samsara’s fans seemed to be unable to accept it and became dispirited. But starting from that Nebula Wave Sword, their spirits reignited. With each hit, their spirits rose to new heights. When the combo counter hit 30, a Spellblade performing a 30-hit combo, their blood was boiling!

Cheers, applause, the entire stadium was filled with shouts of Jiang Botao’s name. The silence had finally been broken, and the one who did it was Jiang Botao, Samsara’s vice-captain.

The crowd suddenly started to sing. No one knew who started it, but the person wasn’t able to get the whole crowd going. It didn’t seem like many people knew the song. Even the fans singing it weren’t in unison. It was a mess of noise, and the song lyrics were unclear. Their unfamiliarity with the song leaked in every way it could. Even so, they continued to sing and sing. Suddenly, a powerful and united chant began to reverberate in everyone’s ears as if the entire song had been a build up for this chorus.

When you’re in joy, that’s when he strikes.

When you’re in joy, that’s when he strikes.

…

Those who couldn’t sing, those who didn’t know the lyrics, when this phrase came, the entire stadium seemed to echo with this chant, again and again.

This was the song of Samsara’s vice captain. Even the fans weren’t familiar with it. When they sang it, not many fans knew it. In fact, very very few fans knew it. This was because their team had Zhou Zekai, and all the flashy stuff was done by him. Numerous songs had been composed for Zhou Zekai, but the fans hadn’t forgotten about their vice-captain. Even though he wasn’t a flashy player, just like their song said: when the opponent’s feeling happy, their vice-captain strikes. They would always remember this point clearly.

Like today.

Their Zhou Zekai had unexpectedly lost. The fans didn’t care what exactly their opponents were feeling, but in any case, they believed that their opponents would definitely be in glee seeing Zhou Zekai’s defeat.

The crowd had become depressed a result. But at this moment, their vice-captain stood up, executing a rarely-seen high-hit combo from a Spellblade, awakening the crowd and burning down their opponent’s delight.

Their vice-captain didn’t disappoint them. They had been so downtrodden that they had forgotten to put their hopes onto him, yet he still stood up and gave them the support they needed.

It was because he was always so reliable in these crucial moments that Jiang Botao became so popular. Placing high on the All-Star rankings wasn’t that easy. It showed that he truly had support from a huge number of fans.

“You can do it!”

“You have to win!”

“We are the champions!”

The chant ended, and the cheering began again. Samsara’s home crowd had recovered, and the Happy fans in the away team seats were once again surrounded in enemy territory.

Mo Fan wouldn’t know about any of this. Even if he knew, he probably wouldn’t have any reaction. He definitely wasn’t the “you” in the song, he hadn’t been in joy.

30 hits!

Mo Fan hadn’t been able to escape. He had tried to search for openings, but his opponent would always patch those immediately. Mo Fan could faintly feel something. But even though a 30-hit combo sounded long, in reality, it was only a matter of seconds. He didn’t have time to think carefully about what that feeling was. Suddenly, the attacks stopped.

Spellblade skills were strong, but also had relatively long cooldowns. After this combo, an opening soon appeared because he didn’t have any suitable skills to continue it.

Dodge?

Charge?

These two thoughts flashed through Mo Fan’s mind.

Charge!

Empty Waves was in front of him, four and a half steps away. For a Ninja, this distance was negligible. Running and then re-establishing an offense might not get him this sort of opportunity.

Deception rushed out, forming hand seals.

Ninjutsu – Ground Shrinking Technique!

Four and a half steps became two steps. Deception had closed in onto Empty Waves. However, all he saw was the cold light from Empty Waves’ Divine Chains. It wasn’t magic, but a sharp sword light.

Moonlight Slash!

With a flash of light, Deception was launched into the air. Naturally, the second part of the “Dual Moon Slash” followed, Full Moonlight Slash.

Full Moonlight Slash’s Blow-Away effect pushed Deception away, giving Empty Waves space to swing his sword again.

Wave Wheel Slasher!

The waves of magic locked Deception into place…

That four and a half steps of distance hadn’t been an opportunity, it had been bait. His set-up hadn’t worked on Ye Xiu, but he didn’t lose confidence in himself. Facing Mo Fan, he calmly made these arrangements. His utilization of Mo Fan’s strengths and weaknesses became the core of his set-up. Mo Fan seemed to have stepped into a quagmire. The more he moved, the deeper he fell.

Earth Wave Sword!

Empty Waves slashed again with his sword, sending an Earth Wave Sword at Deception. Peng! Purple smoke suddenly spread out, engulfing Deception and the Earth Wave Sword.

Ninjutsu – Smoke Bomb!

Jiang Botao reacted quickly. His Earth Wave Sword had missed. He couldn’t see where Mo Fan was, and he didn’t know whether Mo Fan would run or attack him. As a result, he had Empty Waves retreat. First, open up some distance between them. Then, he saw a figure dart out from the purple smoke from where the Earth Wave Sword had swept towards.

Shadow Clone Technique?

Deception had been in the air when he threw out the Earth Wave Sword. To dodge the attack, he could have only used a skill.

Ghost Slash!

Jiang Botao had been ready. He swung his Divine Chains, using a Ghost Slash straight towards Deception, sending him flying. But then, one, two, three…

Deception after Deception rushed out from the purple smoke, while the sword light from his Ghost Slash was still moving.

It wasn’t Shadow Clone Technique. It was Shadow Dance!

Jiang Botao couldn’t help but be surprised. He knew that there was an opening before the Earth Wave Sword would arrive when Wave Wheel Slasher ended. If Mo Fan took advantage of the opening well enough, he could dodge it. But Mo Fan had actually been able to use Shadow Dance during this tiny opening.

Ninja hand seals could be considered as a cast time. It was just that the cast time depended on the player’s hand speed. Using Shadow Dance with such a tiny opening was truly brave, yet to actually succeed showed how frightening his hand speed was.

What was more amazing was that… Shadow Dance succeeded, but he didn’t hurry to attack. He first sent out a bait to lure him into attacking. Then, while he was still in the attack’s ending lag, he attacked.

Wasn’t this what he had just been doing to Mo Fan? This punk… a tooth for a tooth so fast?

For a moment, Empty Waves was surrounded by shadow clones. For a Spellblade, it wasn’t easy to deal with attacks from all sides. Empty Waves swung his sword, using normal attacks to parry and block what attacks he could. An opening! He raised his sword, Waltzing Wave Sword!

This Waltzing Wave Sword’s arc was extremely large. As soon as it came out, it started to curve, dispersing the Deception shadow clone to his side. It didn’t stop there, continuing its arc towards the next one!

Jiang Botao’s Waltzing Wave Sword was used adeptly. He had it go around him. After it hit a target, its power would decrease, but it would keep going, hitting target after target.

In an instant, the Waltzing Wave Sword went in a large arc, destroying three of Deception’s shadow clones. A huge hole was created in the encirclement. Empty Wave swung his sword again, a Fire Wave Sword opening a path as he rushed out!

But Mo Fan refused to let him go. He cancelled his Shadow Dance and intercepted Empty Waves, Ninjutsu – Exploding Flame Dragon!

Boom!

Two balls of fire erupted.

The Fire Wave Sword’s burst was extremely strong, sending Deception flying far away. But at the same time, Empty Waves was also hit full force by Deception’s attack.

Exploding Flame Dragon. A Level 75 Ninja skill. Even when matched against the Spellblade’s most powerful wave slash, its damage wouldn’t lose out.

Chapter 1597 - A Good But Unsustainable Game

Mo Fan suddenly went aggressive. To outsiders, it seemed to simply be a different choice due to the circumstances, a change in tempo. But to Happy, it was another breakthrough for Mo Fan.

Mo Fan had grown as a scrap picker. His instinct was to prioritize his survival, now and in the past. His entire play style revolved around survival.

In his previous matches, there were times when he rushed his opponent, but this sort of blow for blow combat was mostly out of helplessness. However, his decision to trade Exploding Flame Dragon for Fire Wave Slash was a proactive choice. This was a step forward towards his future.

Turn around and go again!

The moment Deception touched the ground, he immediately turned around to attack again. He threw a Shuriken to open up a path and quickly formed hand seals.

Ninjutsu – Hundred Streams

Hundreds of streams of water rushed towards Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves, but the distance was a bit far. Empty Waves was able to dodge it with ease. However, in that time, Deception turned into a blur and suddenly appeared in front of him.

Ninjutsu – Flickering Pursuit!

Ninjutsu – Bird Fall!

Annihilation!

Attack attack attack! Mo Fan suddenly became extremely aggressive. It was as if he had become a different person. Even if it could be considered a breakthrough, it felt rather exaggerated.

Undaunted by dangers, he attacked furiously.

At this point, even his teammates on Happy felt surprised at Mo Fan’s sudden shift in mentality, let alone Jiang Botao.

Deception weaved forward, backwards, to the side, from above, from below, all around Empty Waves, searching everywhere he could for an opening to attack. Empty Waves seemed to be at a loss. Jiang Botao was clearly caught off guard.

Samsara had obviously studied their opponents in the finals, and stand-out players like Mo Fan, who had clear and defined playstyles, were relatively easier to grasp. In the first game in the finals, Mo Fan hadn’t given them much trouble. It had only been three days since then, yet it was almost like he was a different person. They had never seen him play this way in the finals, in the semifinals, in the regular season. It just had to be now!

“Nice! Beautiful!!!” Chen Guo cheered.

“Yeah, good job!!” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

What he saw wasn’t just Mo Fan doing what he had never done before. What he saw was Mo Fan’s purpose and goal.

For someone like him who prioritized survival, why would he suddenly charge in aggressively all of a sudden? Because he noticed that Jiang Botao’s Empty Waves currently had no skills available to use. Spellblade skills were powerful, but their cooldowns were long. Not caring about combos was hard for normal players, but for pro players, it was worse for a Spellblade to overuse their skills to continue a combo.

To produce a combo, attacks needed to be chained together fast enough. However, for Spellblades, if they tried to chain their skills together that fast, their cooldowns wouldn’t be able to keep up and soon, they would have no skills left to use.

To guarantee that there were always skills that could be used, classes like Spellblades could not pursue these types of long and flashy combos.

Jiang Botao had performed this type of combo in this match though. The spectators had been in awe watching it, even singing their vice-captain’s song. However, the pro players knew what this thirty-hit Spellblade combo would entail. Mo Fan had caught on, choosing to rush down Jiang Botao, doing what he didn’t like to do.

Jiang Botao hadn’t expected this to happen. He had performed that combo in order to stir the crowd. How could he not know that their fans were downcast after Zhou Zekai’s defeat?

If he could take out Ye Xiu beautifully, he could boost their morale. Unfortunately, he failed. Instead, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim used his 4% to take out his 24%. The crowd’s morale sunk even lower.

As a result, when he fought against Mo Fan, he did a risky Spellblade combo.

The reason that he took this risk was because he reckoned that Mo Fan wouldn’t seize the opening that came afterwards. That player would always play his own way, refusing to interact with his opponent, regardless if it was for better or for worse.

But he was wrong. Not only did Mo Fan take advantage of the opening, he was very decisive, staking everything on it.

Mo Fan still hadn’t opened up to interacting with his teammates, but he had opened a new page on the stage.

Mo Fan went all out, showing a fighting strength that he had never shown before. Jiang Botao did his best to defend.

He’s playing beautifully!

Ye Xiu agreed with Chen Guo. But… beautiful wasn’t enough.

Mo Fan had taken advantage of the opening, but he wasn’t able to fully utilize it. He knew that Jiang Botao didn’t have many skills he could use, but he also couldn’t finish the battle here. Jiang Botao just needed to defend himself until his skills came back off cooldown, but did Mo Fan have a way to fight his opponent once those skills came off cooldown? Could take it another step and adjust his mentality to hold on to his current advantage?

It looked like he didn’t…

In the end, he lacked experience.

Mo Fan was able to seize this opportunity, but he wasn’t able to fully take advantage of it. He could burst, but he didn’t have the control to maintain a drawn-out offense.

To do the latter, he needed to have a deeper understanding of his opponent and his opponent’s class.

Happy had, of course, analyzed Jiang Botao. At this point, Mo Fan had a good understanding of every class in Glory, but for right now, it wasn’t enough.

He had created an advantageous situation for himself, but he didn’t have the experience to maintain it. It was unfortunate, but it showed hope for the future.

He lost.

In the end, Mo Fan lost.

Jiang Botao had only been caught off guard for an instant. He quickly regained his footing. Even though he hadn’t been able to retaliate much, he was able to stabilize the situation. Then, once his skills came off cooldown, he started his counterattack. In the end, he was able to gain back the upper hand and beat Mo Fan.

However, Empty Waves only had 11% of his health left. This outcome was far worse than Jiang Botao had expected. He had thought he had complete control over the battle, but he had been caught off guard by Mo Fan’s sudden outburst. The lead that he had was reduced to just 11%. It hadn’t been easy for him to reinvigorate the crowd, but unfortunately, most of his efforts had been ruined by Mo Fan’s counterattack. Luckily, he was still able to win in the end. The Samsara fans didn’t feel that their singing had been for nothing. Their vice-captain didn’t let them down, so their mood was much better than before.

Mo Fan left the stage amidst congratulatory applause. Usually, his non-interactive playstyle was frequently met with boos in away team stadiums. Today, he had shown a surprising amount of aggression. For a moment, Samsara’s fans couldn’t find anything to pick at. Instead of booing, they applauded his performance.

Mo Fan never cared though. He quietly walked back to his team.

“Nice job!” Everyone on Happy exclaimed.

Mo Fan looked at the stage and at the screen.

11%. It was a small difference. Just a bit more and he could have won. No matter how well you played, what was the point if you lost?

Mo Fan wasn’t happy with the result. As he walked back to his seat, he clenched his fists tightly, staring intently at Jiang Botao’s 11% health Empty Waves.

“Keep up the good work. There will be more chances in the future,” Su Mucheng waved her hands towards Mo Fan and said.

Mo Fan stared blankly at her. Before he could nod his head, Su Mucheng turned around and headed towards the stage. She was Happy’s next player.

The Samsara crowd had returned to their usual state, cheering excitedly for their team. Even though Empty Waves only had 11% health left, they had hopes for Jiang Botao. The fans at the away team seats cheered for their team, but the shouts from Samsara’s fans drowned them out.

Su Mucheng wasn’t as expressionless as Mo Fan. She wore a smile on her face as she walked onto the stage.

Su Mucheng was Happy’s third player in the group arena. She would be playing against Jiang Botao. The match began.

Dripstone Cave. For Sharpshooters, it provided them space and cover. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was a Gunner as well, and she could take advantage of the space as well. Because she was longer ranged, it wasn’t as good for her as it was for a Sharpshooter, but in general, the map was favorable for Su Mucheng.

There was no way to choose a perfect map that would make it difficult for every opponent. After all, there would be class overlap between teams. Both teams could have players with similar play styles as well. When it was advantageous for one team, it could also be advantageous for the other team. When choosing a map, you could only do your best.

In today’s match, Su Mucheng was Happy’s winner. When the battle began, she immediately headed for the center of the cave.

Samsara’s Jiang Botao took his time though, seeing what the circumstances were. With only 11% of his health remaining, he decided not to go straight for the center, instead choosing to circle around from the left.

Su Mucheng gradually approached the center of the map. She naturally didn’t see any traces of him. She didn’t continue forward, instead stopping immediately.

She didn’t lean to the left or right. She centered herself at the center and lifted her handcannon.

She looked ahead, to the left, and to the right. For other classes, the purpose of having a wide field of view was to find the opponent earlier. However, for Launchers, their attacks could be launched from afar.

It didn’t matter what route Empty Waves took. It seemed like he wouldn’t be able to escape from Dancing Rain’s artillery fire.

The broadcast cut the screen into two. One part showed Dancing Rain’s point of view, while the other showed Empty Waves’.

The dripstone was sparsely scattered throughout the cave. Trying to move completely hidden was impossible, and it didn’t look like Empty Waves was trying to hide himself. He simply went along a straight line. What was the point of circling around then? Many members of the crowd couldn’t help but ask.

Chapter 1598 - Still One Eye

The commentators analyzed Empty Waves’ movements from different angles. Once Ye Xiu had left the stage, Pan Lin and Li Yibo felt a huge weight off their chests. Their discussions became more colorful and vivid. As the distance between the two players grew nearer, the small screen showing Su Mucheng’s perspective grew larger.

Where was Empty Waves moving to? The viewers knew, but would Su Mucheng be able to tell?

What was the secret behind Jiang Botao’s movements?

Everyone was trying to figure it out! Empty Waves rushed out from a stalagmite and appeared in Su Mucheng’s view.

Secret?

The discussion between Pan Lin and Li Yibo stopped. The two had been chatting, thinking up all sorts of possibilities. The one possibility that they hadn’t talked about was that there was no ulterior motive behind Jiang Botao’s movements…

How could they say that!

The two had the same thought. If they said north, when it was actually south, how could they show their faces? Ye Xiu was an exception. Facing Ye Xiu, they would try not to make any predictions, but they couldn’t do that with everyone. There wouldn’t be any commentary then.

“Hurry up and talk!!”

The two characters had encountered each other, but the commentary had suddenly stopped. The director wasn’t happy at all and yelled at them.

Talk? Fuck off!

Pan Lin cursed inwardly, but he had to talk.

“What a surprise… Jiang Botao… just let Empty Waves appear in Su Mucheng’s view…” Pan Lin said powerlessly.

The ones most surprised were him and Li Yibo. All of their previous analysis had been wrong.

“What is he thinking?” Even Li Yibo didn’t pretend like he knew and simply stated the truth.

“We can only wait and see,” Pan Lin remarked, and then the two went silent again.

As soon as Empty Waves appeared, Dancing Rain aimed her cannon at him, but didn’t immediately fire at him.

Dancing Rain had the range to attack him. However, the farther away the target, the more time there was for the target to dodge. It was hard to guarantee that she would hit him. Su Mucheng didn’t feel like her attacks would be much of a threat at this distance. She was better off just doing nothing.

Empty Waves didn’t rush towards her either. He continued to circle around as if it was just another day in the park.

He had already been exposed. What was the point of circling around?

Su Mucheng turned, following his movements. Soon, everyone noticed a peculiarity. Whether it was closeby or far away, the dripstones were arranged neatly along a jagged line.

Empty Waves took cover behind these dripstones. The logic behind this positioning was the same as when Ye Xiu evaded Zhou Zekai in the first fight of the group arena. Sure enough, Samsara had also discovered this method.

Su Mucheng immediately had Dancing Rain rush out, changing her angle to find Empty Waves.

None!

Empty Waves was nowhere to be seen. Which stalagmite was he hiding behind? Su Mucheng wasn’t sure.

The spectators could see his location clearly. When Empty Waves escaped from Su Mucheng’s line of sight, he immediately began to move inwards to get closer to Dancing Rain. He was aiming for three stalagmites, each one taller than the other. It would allow him to close in without being seen.

If she moved just a bit more to the side, she would find him!!

The Happy fans were praying anxiously. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was just one step off…

Step!

Dancing Rain finally took that awaited step, widening her vision. However, Empty Waves had already moved from the shortest stalagmite to the next shortest one and was now onto the tallest one. With this switch, Su Mucheng’s line of sight was blocked by a stalagmite.

Jiang Botao was predicting her movements and acting accordingly!

Everyone could see this. Jiang Botao hadn’t taken advantage of the map too much in his previous two fights. As a result, everyone had overlooked the fact that Samsara had chosen this map. This time, he utilized the map to the fullest, efficiently closing the distance between Empty Waves and Dancing Rain. The distance between the tallest stalagmite and Dancing Rain was completely within the attack range of a Spellblade. Spellblades wouldn’t fear Launchers in a confrontation at this distance.

He reached it!

Thunderous applause followed. Jiang Botao reached his goal just as they had expected. As for Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain? It seemed like she was still carefully investigating Empty Waves’ whereabouts.

He can attack!

Everyone thought.

Then, they saw Su Mucheng’s camera suddenly turn around. Dancing Rain stepped to the size and open fired!

Boom boom boom!

The first to attack was unexpectedly Dancing Rain. Three Anti-Tank Missiles fired. With a bang, a Stinger burst apart like fireworks in the air.

Then, a roll!

Boom boom boom!

Three consecutive explosions. Empty Waves swung his sword, intercepting the three Anti-Tank Missiles with a Fire Wave Sword! This was the reason why Spellblades didn’t fear Launchers at this distance. Their wave swords had a higher priority than Launcher artillery shells. A collision between their magic and the Launcher’s artillery shells would result in an explosion, and their magic would still continue along its original trajectory!

Hu!

The Fire Wave Sword continued to sweep towards Dancing Rain, who rolled away to just barely dodge it.

Bang!

The Stinger split apart in the air. Eight missiles rained down. Spellblades could use their wave swords to intercept these missiles, but these missiles were spread out like an angel scattering flowers. It wasn’t possible to intercept them all with one swing. As a result, Empty Waves dodged to the side. Dancing Rain got up from her roll and then set-up a Mounted Gun.

Light filled Jiang Botao’s screen. A Laser Beam shot towards him. The two were fighting at mid-range. The Laser Beam moved faster than anyone could react. Jiang Botao had expected there to be a follow-up to the Stinger and was planning on continuing to dodge, but the Mounted Gun had strengthened Laser Beam. Even though he predicted correctly, he wasn’t able to dodge it.

“With so little health, why bother making it so complicated!”

Su Mucheng typed out. The 11% health was instantly obliterated under her Launcher’s heavy firepower.

The crowd was dumbfounded.

Jiang Botao had circled around and avoided being seen by Su Mucheng. Empty Waves successfully got into range. Everything seemed to be going smoothly. But how did it become Su Mucheng making the first move? It had only been an instant, and Empty Waves was dead?

The viewers couldn’t understand. Too many people couldn’t understand. Jiang Botao himself didn’t understand either.

Had he exposed an opening?

No…

After casually walking out into view, Jiang Botao had seen Dancing Rain’s position. The route that he had chosen to follow afterwards would allow him to hide from Dancing Rain no matter what she did. Yet Su Mucheng had been the first to draw first blood, putting him on the backfoot. His movements had been completely seen through. How did she do it? Instinct? Or did she guess it?

Happy hadn’t chosen this map, so how could they have such a strong understanding of the map?

He truly didn’t understand why he had lost!

Jiang Botao tried to struggle. But with only 11% health, it wasn’t enough. Being able to survive for so long was thanks to his class being a Spebllade. Plate armor offered high defense.

He fell…

Empty Waves died. His ghost floated up, and his screen turned gray. Jiang Botao stared blankly at the surrounding battlefield as his ghost floated higher and higher.

Suddenly.. Jiang Botao saw something floating above that stalagmite. It seemed to be some sort of spinning round object…

That’s… Electronic Eye…

Jiang Botao was speechless. He hadn’t thought that Dancing Rain would bring along this skill.

Electronic Eye was a Mechanic skill. The user could see whatever the eye saw. This was the skill that Su Mucheng had placed on her weapon. Everything was answered.

He had carefully observed Dancing Rain, calculated a route, and made predictions. It turned out that a simple Electronic Eye had ruined all of his plans. Dancing Rain might not be able to see him, but the Electronic Eye could.

The broadcast had finally found the reason as well. A replay was performed from the Electronic Eye’s perspective. It wasn’t as clear as a character’s point of view, but it was clear enough to see Empty Waves’ movements. Su Mucheng had grasped Jiang Botao’s intentions very early on, but she calmly went along with it. She waited until the final moment to get the first attack off before Jiang Botao, cleanly sweeping away the rest of his health.

Jiang Botao walked down from the stage.

The Samsara fans had been hoping that Jiang Botao would be able to deal a lot of damage to Su Mucheng like what Ye Xiu had done to him, but instead, Su Mucheng finished him off cleanly. It was rather disappointing, but when they thought of Jiang Botao’s brilliant performance in the previous fight, their moods instantly lifted. Both sides were now at their third player. Su Mucheng had won with 100% of her health intact. The match was completely even. However, the Samsara fans had complete confidence in their next players.

Lu Boyuan!

An All-Star, the number one Grappler in Glory, got up and walked towards the stage.

Applause was sent towards Jiang Botao.

Applause was also sent towards Lu Boyuan.

We are the champions!

Samsara’s fans roared.

Chapter 1599 - Extremely Far versus Extremely Close

Lu Boyuan had once given an amazing performance in the Season 8 finals between Samsara and Blue Rain. He had been a huge reason for Samsara’s first championship trophy. After that year’s finals, Lu Boyuan’s fame soared. In the All-Star voting the next year, he placed thirteenth, replacing the previous All-Star Grappler player, Li Yihui, a former Tiny Herb and current Team 301 player. From then on, Lu Boyuan stood at the peak of his class. As for Li Yihui, he had once been an All-Star as well, but because of the transfer, he quickly disappeared from everyone’s sights. The title of number one Grappler became uncontested.

This season, Lu Boyuan had successfully entered the All-Stars again. Although it wasn’t high, only 22nd, anyone who made it into All-Stars was one of Glory’s most popular players. Moreover, Samsara had invited another top player, Sun Xiang, into the team, along with a legendary character like One Autumn Leaf to accompany him. As a result, there was a lot of competition within Samsara’s fan base for who got the votes. Lu Boyuan squeezing into the ranks of the 24 All-Stars wasn’t easy. If he was less skilled or less popular, the other stars on Samsara might have taken away the spotlight from him.

Zhou Zekai, Sun Xiang, Jiang Botao. These three Samsara players placed above tenth on the All-Star rankings. Their 4th All-Star, the 22nd Lu Boyuan, was put as Samsara’s third player in the group arena.

The crowd cheered and clapped, showing how popular he was. The players on Samsara were making their existence known one after the other to let everyone understand that they weren’t just a one-man team.

The match began amidst the applause. Because of Su Mucheng’s perfect victory in the last fight, both sides were at full health. Dancing Rain had used up a bit of mana, but it was more than enough to last another 1v1 fight. There was practically no difference in their conditions going into the fight. On the other hand, their classes were as different as they could be.

This main difference was their range.

Launchers had the longest range out of any class. As for Grapplers? Even among the Fighter classes, Grapplers had 2/3 the attack range of Strikers, who specialized in close combat. Not only did they need to land a hit on their opponent, they needed to grab their opponent. In order to deal damage to their opponents, they needed to be at point blank range.

The atmosphere in the stadium was quite good. On the other hand, the commentators, Pan Lin and Li Yibo, were in a not so good mood. Their faces had been slapped too hard. They still talked about the battle between the longest range and shortest range classes, cleverly shifting the topic to a discussion between classes rather than a discussion between players. That way, there would be no way for their faces to get slapped. It was a safe plan.

Soon, the two characters met at the center of the cave.

Su Mucheng didn’t hesitate. Dancing Rain immediately fired at him. Lu Boyuan didn’t hesitate either and dodged.

Facing heavy gunfire from a Launcher, it would be hard for him to force his way through. However, Lu Boyuan didn’t plan on doing that. After locating Dancing Rain, he began to survey his surroundings. When Dancing Rain started shooting at him, he had already planned out a route in his head. His Chaotic Cloudy Mountain quickly hid behind a stalagmite.

Stalactites and stalagmites were scattered around Dripstone Cave. In the previous fight, even though Jiang Botao was finished off by Su Mucheng with one combo, he had showed a deep understanding of the map. If not for Su Mucheng’s “Electronic Eye”, it was hard to say how that fight would have turned out.

Jiang Botao had utilized the map well, and Lu Boyuan wouldn’t be any less familiar with it than him. However, compared to Jiang Botao, he knew about Su Mucheng’s “Electronic Eye”, so he was naturally on guard against it. “Electronic Eye” was a small robot about the size of a ping pong ball. If it just floated in the air the entire time, it wouldn’t be too hard to notice, but in the last match, Su Mucheng had the Electronic Eye drop down to a certain spot, making it much harder to see.

The broadcast also knew that Su Mucheng had this skill up her sleeve, so they kept a close watch by displaying her point of view as the main viewpoint. Before, they had only given a smaller screen in the corner. As a result, they hadn’t noticed the Electronic Eye interface until the replay.

This time, the broadcast was mindful of it. However, Su Mucheng hadn’t used Electronic Eye, even when Lu Boyuan hid behind the stalagmite. She didn’t hurry and send out the Electronic Eye to scout around. Instead, Dancing Rain moved to the side to see if she could find Chaotic Cloudy Mountain from a different angle.

With a turn, she was able to see half of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s body. Dancing Rain immediately started shooting. Lu Boyuan had been paying attention to her though. He shrunk back and retreated. Dancing Rain continued to fire as she pulled away. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had retreated quickly, but Dancing Rain had promptly followed after him. Soon, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain circled halfway around the stalagmite. On the other hand, for Dancing Rain to circle around that far, she would have to cover much more distance. If the two decided to spin around this stalagmite, Dancing Rain’s radius would be ten times that of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s. How was she going to keep up?

As a result, Dancing Rain stopped. She aimed away from Chaotic Cloudy Mountain and fired.

The flames from the explosion burst forth in front of the stalagmite. Su Mucheng wanted to use the AoE from Launcher attacks to hit him. Even though her attacks wouldn’t directly hit Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, they would still deal some damage. Unless Lu Boyuan wanted to just sit there and take damage, he would certainly expose himself sooner or later.

Su Mucheng’s plan was quite good, but it had been within Lu Boyuan’s expectations. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t stick close to the stalagmite. He was using it more as a way to block Su Mucheng’s line of sight rather than to block her attacks.

How much of Su Mucheng’s vision was blocked depended on the distance between them. Lu Boyuan had a good grasp of this dead angle for Dancing Rain’s previous position. He was using the dead angle to hide and move. Amidst the explosions, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had used the dead angle to get behind a different stalagmite.

However, the viewers noticed that Su Mucheng had finally used Electronic Eye. She didn’t use it to scout ahead but to circle around that stalagmite. That stalagmite blocking Su Mucheng’s vision was also blocking Lu Boyuan’s vision. She took advantage of that fact and quietly advanced as she attacked.

Soon, the Electronic Eye got behind the stalagmite. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had already left. The Electronic Eye circled around two times, locating the next stalagmite that Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was hiding behind.

Dancing Rain continued to move silently, but her movements had clearly quickened. This time, when she sent out the Electronic Eye, she didn’t have it scout ahead. Instead, she had it take a different path than Dancing Rain to get a more comprehensive view of her surroundings. As a result, the stalagmites no longer blocked her vision. Su Mucheng had a complete grasp of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s location.

Lu Boyuan once again tried to use Dancing Rain’s dead angle to get to another stalagmite. A crosshair lit up at his feet. By the time he noticed it, it was too late. A Heat-Seeking Missile crashed to the ground, and the ensuing mushroom cloud engulfed him. Dancing Rain came out from behind the stalagmite, her cannon aimed at the mushroom cloud, ready to shoot. Suddenly, a formless power grasped onto her, and she was sucked into the mushroom cloud.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

Su Mucheng had figured out what it was.

The mushroom cloud dispersed. Qi was swirling around the palms of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s palms. From his stance, wasn’t that the Qi Master’s “Cloud Grasping Fist”?

In the previous fight, Jiang Botao’s plans had been ruined by Su Mucheng’s Electronic Eye. In this fight, Su Mucheng’s plans were ruined by Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s Cloud Grasping Fist.

The crowd erupted into cheers. Samsara’s fans had been worried for Lu Boyuan because they thought that Su Mucheng had complete control over the situation. They hadn’t expected a sudden reversal. How did he do it?

The stadium’s electronic screen did a replay, showing what Lu Boyuan had done.

When the Heat-Seeking Missile descended, Lu Boyuan had no intentions of dodging. He immediately activated Reinforced Iron Bones. Even though this Heat-Seeking Missile dealt heavy damage to him, because of his Super Armor, he wasn’t sent flying away. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain used the explosion as cover for his Cloud Grasping Fist. No matter how many eyes Su Mucheng had, she couldn’t have known about Chaotic Cloudy Mounatain’s counterattack. Lu Boyuan had predicted that Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain would expose herself in order to make follow-up attacks. Sure enough, Dancing Rain came out from hiding. He immediately grabbed her, and in the blink of an eye, Dancing Rain was pulled in front of Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. The distance between the two sides was now zero!

Spinning Throw!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s movements were incomparably fluid. After pulling Dancing Rain in front of him, he grasped onto her firmly, twisted his body, and threw her into the air. At the same time, he also jumped into the air upside down. His legs wrapped around Dancing Rain’s neck.

Aerial Twist!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain flipped around, sending Dancing Rain crashing to the ground. The Grapplers’ relentless tossing had just begun.

Chapter 1600 - Tank

Spinning Throw, Aerial Twist!

Two skills in quick succession. Dancing Rain’s health dropped in chunks like an elevator going down. However, the combo counter was only two.

For combos, Grapplers were in an even worse situation than spell-based classes like Elementalists, Witches, Spellblades. This was because of how grab skills worked. Other classes could rely on their experience and instinct to find a way to break out of a combo. But since Grappler grabs could not broken out of, if Grapplers could combo, then there would be no counter play.

Long combos were very difficult to pull off with spell-based classes like Elementalists and Witches. However, long combos were impossible for Grapplers. Let alone against a pro player, Grappler combos were extremely limited even against a motionless sandbag.

As a result, when looking at a Grappler, statistics on combos were completely ignored. Using a DoT attack to increase the combo count wasn’t considered a combo, and chaining together skills couldn’t be done by Grapplers. Grapplers had to rely on reads to perform inescapable combos that the system didn’t count.

Aerial Twist!

Dancing Rain was ruthlessly thrown towards the ground. It was hard not to think of the character as the player. It was as if Su Mucheng had been thrown towards the ground headfirst. Thinking of how Su Mucheng’s beautiful face would look like afterwards, even the Samsara’s fans couldn’t help but sigh.

Lu Boyuan obviously didn’t care. As soon as Chaotic Cloudy Mountain landed on the ground, he rolled and then stood up. As for Dancing Rain? Knockdowns from grabs could not be Quick Recovered. She could only wait until her face slammed into the ground. However, Dancing Rain didn’t immediately stand up. She lay on the ground and turned, aiming her cannon at Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

Boom!

Light flashed.

Su Mucheng’s response showed her experience against Grapplers. No matter how she got back onto her feet, her opponent would have a way to counter it. She had to attack first or use some other method to disrupt him before he reached her.

Su Mucheng had experience playing against Grapplers, but Lu Boyuan had taken her experience into consideration. Light flashed. A missile shot out, but Chaotic Cloudy Mountain suddenly dropped down.

You think I can’t hit you if you stay flat on the ground? How could Glory have such a huge flaw? Ground sweeping attacks were meant for these situations. Even basic attacks had a ground sweeping effect if they landed. Lying flat on the ground and not getting up wasn’t an invincible buff.

Elbow Drop!

Dancing Rain wasn’t getting up, so Chaotic Cloudy Mountain might as well get down to the ground too. His elbow went straight for Dancing Rain’s throat.

Su Mucheng had been waiting for Lu Boyuan to attack. Dancing Rain rolled to dodge the strike. Suddenly, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain stretched out his arm. Elbow Drop was cancelled, and his hand grabbed onto her. One Hand Grab.

Dancing Rain was suddenly pulled back. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain fell to the ground, but Dancing Rain was dragged back to the ground as well. In one fluid movement, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rolled and got up. On the other hand, because Dancing Rain was knocked down by the skill, she was slightly slower.

This was the foothold that Grapplers needed to continue their attacks after grabbing an opponent. As for the side that was grabbed, breaking out from this hold was the key to taking back the initiative.

And this was much more difficult for long-ranged classes like Launchers. As a class that was extremely bad at close combat, having a Grappler close in meant that she was already halfway to losing. Su Mucheng needed to bring back victory from defeat.

Roll!

Dancing Rain immediately tried to get up. This wasn’t the smartest choice, but on occasion, choosing the bad option could catch the opponent off guard, making it a good option.

But unfortunately, Lu Boyuan wasn’t caught off guard.

After Chaotic Cloudy Mountain got back onto his feet, he immediately locked onto what choices Dancing Rain could do to get up. Lu Boyuan never overlooked the options that seemed bad and that no good player would choose to do.

Ground Toss!

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain planned on pinning her back to the ground. Just when he was about to grab Dancing Rain’s head, he suddenly heard a loud boom. Fire and smoke flashed from beneath Dancing Rain, immediately sending her to the left. She had used the recoil from her shot to bounce away.

He missed!

He missed his grab. He immediately rushed forward to try again, but the moment Dancing Rain dodged the grab, she aimed her cannon towards him.

Boom boom boom!

Three Anti-Tank Missiles at such a close range. These three missiles aimed towards three different points. It could be seen that she had complete mastery over this low-level skill.

Dodge!

Lu Boyuan had been ready for an attack, but the AoE covered by these three missiles had been outside of his expectations. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain tried to dodge, but he was still hit by one of them in the end. The explosion pushed him back.

He had been wary of her attacks, yet he still hadn’t been able to dodge in time. This time, Su Mucheng had blocked Lu Boyuan through pure technical skill. At this distance, Lu Boyuan wasn’t able to keep up.

With one of the missiles hitting, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain lost the initiative. The distance between the two sides started pulling apart, and a distance of two or three steps was already too far for Chaotic Cloudy Mountain to grab Dancing Rain.

Dancing Rain hadn’t completely gotten back onto her feet, but she was still able to leap back. The distance of two steps became four steps. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had finally steadied himself and immediately rushed forward. But then, Dancing Rain’s cannon flashed again.

I can’t back down!

If he were ten or twenty steps away, Lu Boyuan might not have forced it. But the two sides were only three or four steps away. Even though he couldn’t grab her at this distance, it was still favorable for him. He couldn’t use Grappler skills, but Launchers were greatly restricted too. Their weakness of a slow firing speed was fully exposed, and there was no threat of combos from them.

Forward!

Lu Boyuan didn’t hesitate. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain dodged. He had his body sway left and right irregularly as he charged forward to meet the attack.

This wasn’t a read. At the same time, Su Mucheng had no way of reading his irregular swaying either.

This was a gamble!

At this distance, it was impossible for Chaotic Cloudy Mountain to react once the artillery shell was fired. Dancing Rain didn’t have time to make any precise calculations either.

One attack!

Everything depended on this one attack.

If this attack hit, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain would be forced back and the distance would widen even farther.

If the attack missed, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain would close the distance, and Dancing Rain would once again be within his grab range.

Would the attack hit?

The entire stadium went silent. Everyone watched as Chaotic Cloudy Mountain swayd left and right as he ran towards Dancing Rain. Dancing Rain aimed steady, yet there was no pull of the rigger. Although she was also retreating, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain moved much faster than her. She would soon be caught, yet she seemed to be waiting. What was she waiting for?

Close! Reach out!

Lu Boyuan hadn’t expected Su Mucheng to not do anything. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had closed in, his hand reaching towards her. Even if she attacked now, he should still be able to grab her, right?

Probably… right?

Just before he grabbed onto her, her cannon suddenly lit up with a bright blue light.

Not good!

Lu Boyuan realized it, but it was too late.

There was no explosion. It was just a sudden release of energy.

The artillery shell flew out slowly, but it was flashing with blue light, crackling like lightning.

X-1 Extruder!

At the last moment, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain used X-1 Extruder. It was a rare Launcher skill with CC.

Was this a read? A set-up?

No.

It was another show of technical prowess!

X-1 Extruder gave off light when used that warned the opponent. It also moved rather slowly. If she had used it immediately, even at a distance of three or four steps, Lu Boyuan would have easily dodged it. If it missed, Su Mucheng wouldn’t have a second chance.

Launchers had low attack speed. This attack speed wasn’t referring to how fast the missiles flew, but rather the amount of time it took for them to reload and shoot again. Whether it was a basic attack or a skill, it required reloading. Launchers were slow because of this reloading process. No matter how fast your hands were, it wouldn’t matter. The only way to speed up this reloading process was by wearing equipment that increased attack speed.

Launchers couldn’t combo at such a close distance because of this reason. Once they fired a shot, by the time they fired the next one, the opponent would have already closed in. As a result, there was only one chance.

Su Mucheng let Chaotic Cloudy Mountain get near her. She waited until he was about to grab her before launching an X-1 Extruder.

Attack speed couldn’t be changed through faster inputs. However, the input was what gave the command to use the skill. The faster the command was completed, the earlier the skill would be used.

An X-1 Extruder one step away.

Su Mucheng relied on this daring move to strike Lu Boyuan.

There was nothing Lu Boyuan could do. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was immediately sucked into the X-1 Extruder and then sent flying away. He could only watch Dancing Rain move farther and farther away. The effects of X-1 Extruder could not be disrupted.

Chapter 1601 - True Assault

For both Lu Boyuan and Su Mucheng, distance was their advantage. Distance would be what decided the win.

Seeing Chaotic Cloudy Mountain getting blown farther and farther away from Dancing Rain, all of the Samsara fans felt their hearts sink.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain set up a Mounted Gun again. She had used this Level 75 Launcher skill to great effect countless times in the playoffs.

This skill restricted her character’s movements but greatly increased her attack power. It represented a powerful assault with the intent to fight a bloody battle with the opponent.

X-1 Extruder’s final landing position was at the perfect firing line distance for Su Mucheng. When the X-1 Extruder exploded, the artillery barrage from Mounted Gun arrived. Launchers were most threatening when their targets were at their firing line, and it had already been shown that Su Mucheng’s firing line was very flexible. It wasn’t just a single dot or a line. It encompassed an area. Whether you moved forward, backward, left, or right, you would still be inside.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was engulfed by the artillery fire. His zero-distance close-ranged character wasn’t able to counterattack. He could only run away and dodge.

( novelfull.Com )   But where should he run to? Should he go forward or backwards?

This was the trickiest part about Su Mucheng’s firing line.

You could go forward, but you wouldn’t know if you could get close to her under such a heavy barrage without dying. You could go backwards, but you wouldn’t know if you could actually retreat far away enough to a safe place.

Long distance was the domain of Launchers. It wasn’t something that Grapplers could touch.

He was trapped inside Su Mucheng’s desired firing line.

Lu Boyuan didn’t get discouraged.

Advance? Retreat? He found a third option, an option that was only possible in this map.

Sprint, jump, roll.

It was hard to move around amidst the barrage of artillery shells, but he was still moving. He wasn’t locked into place by Dancing Rain’s assault. The stalagmite up ahead was his goal. He wanted to run over there and take cover. Once he was able to catch his breath, there would be more opportunities laying in wait.

Lu Boyuan acted on his plans. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rushed towards that stalgamite.

Su Mucheng quickly saw what Lu Boyuan intended. It seemed like Dancing Rain would need to make adjustments to keep up pressure after Chaotic Cloudy Mountain reached the stalagmite.

But Su Mucheng didn’t make any.

Dancing Rain continued to use her Mounted Gun and the buffs it provided.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s health dropped rapidly, but he wouldn’t die before he reached that stalagmite. Did Su Mucheng have a way to burst him down?

It was hard not to think of this question. Even though Su Mucheng was a high DPS class, she didn’t brute force things. She would often set up subtle traps that were only understood after being caught inside.

( novelfull.Com )   Pan Lin and Li Yibo looked at one another. They wanted to say something, but were too afraid to say it, fearing that their faces would get slapped. They didn’t dare make any predictions for any of the players today, let alone someone like Su Mucheng who was so close to Ye Xiu. Just this relationship alone scared them.

“Let’s wait and see.” The two called for everyone not to ask them and instead wait to see it for themselves.

And so everyone watched.

The Samsara fans were worried and anxious. The Happy fans were filled with energy and hope.

90%…

80%…

70%…

60%…

Because Lu Boyuan had held the upper hand at the start of the fight, Dancing Rain hadn’t been able to deal much damage to him. As a result, most of the damage had been dealt starting from this moment. Starting from around 90%, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s health dropped in chunks as he approached the stalagmite.

Not enough, no?

That was what everyone was thinking.

However, Su Mucheng had only now retracted her Mounted Gun. No, to be more precise, her Mounted Gun’s duration was up. She hadn’t cancelled it. Dancing Rain moved and began chasing Chaotic Cloudy Mountain.

But because she had been attacking from a fixed spot previously, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had moved away from the center of her firing line. Even though she could still reach him, her attack rate couldn’t compare to before and she couldn’t restrict his movements. As a result, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain began moving much faster than before. Soon, he was next to the stalagmite. Then, he circled around behind it. If Dancing Rain wanted to attack him, she would need to go around in a huge circle to get to a different angle.

That… was it?

The people who had been worried about Lu Boyuan felt like their worries had been for nothing. As for the people who had their hopes up for Su Mucheng, their hopes were destroyed.

“This… this…” Pan Lin and Li Yibo stuttered. They had been too afraid to make any statements when she set up a Mounted Gun. Now that they saw that nothing ended up happening with it, they were still too afraid to say anything. Everything else seemed to be a profound mystery, and the two didn’t know where to start.

The fight suddenly stopped.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, now hiding behind the stalagmite, had 42% of his health left. He had taken tons of damage escaping from Su Mucheng’s firing line. After all, Dancing Rain had set up a Mounted Gun. All of her attacks had been drastically buffed.

But he was able to escape. He had won an opportunity to turn things around. He likely would not have had as good of an outcome if he had advanced or retreated. Lu Boyuan was thankful for choosing the third option.

As for Su Mucheng?

From the eyes of the viewers, she had simply been trying to deal as much damage as possible. It didn’t seem as if she had any intentions of stopping him from reaching the stalagmite nor did it seem like she had any ideas for what would come afterwards. This shouldn’t be a mistake that a pro player made. People who liked conspiracy theories suspected that she was intentionally sandbagging. But thinking of Su Mucheng’s relationship with Ye Xiu and how she had practically volunteered to join a grassroots team like Happy, sandbagging didn’t make any sense.

What is she thinking?

Whether it was the fans who supported Samsara or the fans who supported Lu Boyuan, they all felt a little bit suspicious. Anyone with a bit of Glory knowledge would have given up on a bit of damage from Mounted Gun to chase after Lu Boyuan’s Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, no?

The camera focused on Dancing Rain. In this situation, Pan Lin and Li Yibo had to say something.

“Uh, Lu Boyuan has successfully escaped from Su Mucheng’s firing line!” Pan Lin summarized what had happened.

“Su Mucheng’s offense was very powerful because she didn’t stop using her Mounted Gun,” Li Yibo wasn’t going to fall behind.

“But why didn’t she stop using her Mounted Gun?” Pan Lin asked.

“Yes, why didn’t she?” Li Yibo said.

“YOU TWO!!” Someone from behind them shouted at them. People would usually be more respectful of Li Yibo since he was a guest commentator, but right now, Li Yibo was being yelled at along with Pan Lin. The director’s patience was reaching its limits.

“If Su Mucheng had given up on her Mounted Gun earlier and chased after Chaotic Cloudy Mountain, do you think she would be in a better spot, Coach Li?” Pan Lin could only move on to a different topic.

“On the surface, yes,” Li Yibo said.

“Okay!” Pan Lin nodded his head.

“But for some reason, she didn’t do that,” Li Yibo said.

“Yes yes,” Pan Lin nodded his head again. What was this reason? Everyone wanted to know what this reason was!

“We’ll see,” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin wanted to cry. To think Li Yibo would still use his trademark escape tactic at this crucial moment. Pan Lin was wondering whether “We’ll see” would become a trending meme tomorrow. Would people use that to make fun of their incompetence?

In any case, the words had been said. Li Yibo couldn’t say it again. Pan Lin didn’t want to bring trouble onto himself, so he might as well just let it be.

The camera focused on Dancing Rain. Nothing unexpected that was worthy of a “let’s wait and see” happened. Su Mucheng just calmly packed up her Mounted Gun and then started moving horizontally to get to a different angle.

Everything was calm as if none of the previous crazy attacks had happened. It was as if the match had reset back to when the two came across each other the first time. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain had taken cover behind a stalagmite, while Su Mucheng started searching for him bit by bit.

Everything was the same as before.

The only difference was that Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was at 42% health, while Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was at 87% health.

42% versus 87%. There was a difference in health between the two compared to before.Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was losing, and right now, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was far away from Dancing Rain. The situation seemed to favor Su Mucheng.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were at least able to make this sort of analysis. At the end, Li Yibo suddenly blanked out. A thought suddenly sprung into his mind as he watched Dancing Rain’s calm movements.

Could it be… Su Mucheng knew that even now, she held the advantage. There had been no need to use that opportunity before to kill off Chaotic Cloudy Mountain in one go. That was why she hadn’t cancelled her Mounted Gun, instead dealing as much damage as she could. She could still be calm now because she had a huge lead. There was no need to be nervous or worried. It was Lu Boyuan who would be feeling those emotions. The Lu Boyuan, who was still rejoicing that he had escaped from Su Mucheng’s firing line.

He would probably soon realize it. Escaping wasn’t anything worth celebrating. Su Mucheng wouldn’t let him easily recover from the lead that she had gotten. Su Mucheng was confidence in this, and this confidence was her true assault.

Chapter 1602 - A Fully Deserved Win

Artillery shells began being fired again.

Before Su Mucheng circled around to where she could see Lu Boyuan, she began using the splash damage from her Launcher attacks to hit behind the stalagmite. An Electronic Eye was released again to expand her view from another angle.

Step by step, steadily and surely. Su Mucheng played patiently. Her attacks weren’t dense, even though she was using more normal attacks. Normal attacks didn’t use mana. Their threat was low, but they were AoE attacks nonetheless. She didn’t know where exactly Chaotic Cloudy Mountain was located, but it didn’t matter if her attacks hit. If they hit, then it would deal some damage. If they didn’t, then it would scare him.

Lu Boyuan was indeed feeling the pressure. He had thought of the possibility that Su Mucheng would chase after him, but he hadn’t expected her to play so patiently.

Artillery shell after artillery shell landed beside Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. Sometimes, they landed far from him. Other times, they landed close to him. Evidently, the other side wasn’t certain of his location. But at the same time, Lu Boyuan didn’t know her location. When he had taken cover behind the stalagmite, he had turned around to confirm her location one last time. However, it had been some time since then.

As a result, he had no way of figuring out how far away Su Mucheng was from him. He had no way of knowing whether rushing out from hiding would be an opportunity for him. He also had no way of knowing how much cover the stalagmite was giving him.

All that remained was pressure.

Explosions were still happening all around him.

Lu Boyuan hadn’t forgotten that Su Mucheng had Electronic Eye. The Electronic Eye didn’t need to be placed right in front of him. As long as it was looking at him from a different angle than Dancing Rain, Su Mucheng would be able to attack him more precisely. Her calm attacks showed that she was still feeling him out.

He couldn’t keep waiting. He needed to act, but should he advance or retreat? He needed to make a decision.

Lu Boyuan checked his surroundings.

The terrain wasn’t ideal. He could try and move towards another stalagmite. It was somewhat far though, so this third option didn’t seem to be a good one this time. Could it be… Su Mucheng had intentionally let him move here? Had she known that this place was a dead end?

No, it couldn’t be considered a dead end.

Luo Boyuan was familiar with the map. When he had looked at this stalagmite, he had checked which nearby ones he could move to. But now…

Lu Boyuan turned around. The direction he wanted to move towards would leave him open to Dancing Rain’s attacks.

This path hadn’t originally been a dead end. However, Su Mucheng had blocked the path, turning it into one. He had fallen into Su Mucheng’s grasp. This was why she was calm and unhurried.

Okay!

Even if that was the case, he couldn’t hesitate. He was trapped in a corner, and his only choice was to force his way out of it.

Facing this predicament, Lu Boyuan didn’t become discouraged. Instead, he strengthened his resolve because there was no other way out. He would have to create his own bloody path.

Chaotic Cloudy Mountain spun around to the other side of the stalagmite, exposing half of his body to the open.

Dancing Rain saw him. Her Electronic Eye saw him too. Su Mucheng reacted quickly, immediately adjusting her aim and firing at him. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain hastily pulled back, but the explosion landed right beside him. The splash damage hit him, and Chaotic Cloudy Mountain rolled on the ground to reduce the knockback. Then, he got up and went to the other side to try again.

Left or right?

Su Mucheng only had two choices. As a result, Lu Boyuan had Chaotic Cloudy Mountain expose his left side to as a feint to shift her attention over to the left. Then, he immediately rushed out from the opposite side to the right. He was fighting for this tiny opening.

Last chance!

Lu Boyuan knew it was his last chance. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain moved like the wind as he charged towards Dancing Rain.

Boom!

Su Mucheng fired at him as she jumped back, using the recoil to retreat. Dancing Rain didn’t try to stand her ground and attack. With Chaotic Cloudy Mountain charging towards her relentlessly, she needed to keep away from him.

Fire and smoke surrounded Chaotic Cloudy Mountain. He dodged and ran. There was only one option left for him: get closer. If he could get close to her, even if he was at his last breath, he would still have a chance.

One advanced, while the other retreated.

A chase had begun. The distance was slowly closing, but Chaotic Cloudy Mountain’s health was slowly dropping too. From 42% to 35% to 30% to 20%…

I can catch her!

Lu Boyuan was ecstatic. He had calculated it. He would be able to hang on until he reached Dancing Rain. This was the small opening that he had fought for in the beginning. That small opening allowed Lu Boyuan to perceive that Su Mucheng’s offense wasn’t perfect. Her tempo was slightly off, and the distance hadn’t been perfect for her firing line. She had put pressure on him and blocked off his escape, but it wasn’t nearly as focused and oppressive as before.

I can do it! I can do it! This time, I have to seize this opportunity properly. I don’t have much health, but it doesn’t matter. 10% is enough as long as I don’t let Dancing Rain escape.

Five steps! Five steps away!

The next step he took would be the turning point. Once Su Mucheng was five steps away, there would be huge holes in her Launcher’s offense. Su Mucheng might be able to use her experience to cut that distance down to three or four steps, but nevertheless, with this next step, her threat would be drastically reduced. He would be the one in control!

Lu Boyuan stared intently at Dancing Rain. He couldn’t make any mistakes. Suddenly, he saw Dancing Rain suddenly put away her handcannon and take out a rifle.

Gun Switching Style?

Lu Boyuan felt his heart tighten. The Gun Switching Style or the Weapon Switching Style had its clever uses in combat. One of these uses was to help give the character another skill, since a skill could be attached to each weapon.

Dancing Rain had suddenly switched to a Rifle. Perhaps it was to increase her attack speed, but Launchers that didn’t use their class-specific weapon would deal significantly less damage. In addition, they lose the bonus from their class advancement skill “Heavy Gunfire Control”. All of their skills would become less effective. As a result, she wouldn’t be using her Launcher skills to retake control. What’s more, the rifle was only slightly faster than the handcannon.

Then… it was very likely that the bonus skill on the rifle could turn things around. What could it be?

Luckily, she wasn’t an unspecialized, so there was no need to consider skills from all 24 classes. He could narrow it down to the 4 Gunner classes. However, instantly coming up with an answer was too difficult. He could only be wary of it. At this moment, the rifle began to fire at him.

What is it?

Lu Boyuan opened his eyes wide. He noticed something rise up from Dancing Rain’s feet. It was a Mounted Gun.

What?

Lu Boyuan wasn’t the only one surprised. Hadn’t Mounted Gun just been used? This Level 75 skill’s cooldown wasn’t so short. It couldn’t a Mounted Gun from her rifle. If the skill added to the weapon wasn’t a new skill, then the skill level would be raised by one. It didn’t mean that the user would have two of the same skill.

It wasn’t possible for it to be a Mounted Gun. Switching to a rifle wouldn’t refresh the skill and get rid of its cooldown.

Uh? Refresh?

He understood now.

It was the Sharpshooter skill: Dual Load. It was a skill that let the user instantly refresh a skill on cooldown, and Su Mucheng had chosen to refresh Mounted Gun.

So it’s like that…

Lu Boyuan let out a bitter laugh. He hadn’t expected Su Mucheng to come out with this move. This was his loss.

Grappler grab skills were high priority moves, but there were things that couldn’t be grabbed such as the Summoner’s Devil World Flower. Once it put down its roots, it could not be moved. Grappler grab skills would only deal damage. There would be no secondary effects. To put it simply, grab skills only dealt damage when used against targets that could not be moved.

A Launcher using Mounted Gun was considered a target that could not be moved.

His grabs would only deal damage. He wouldn’t be able to stop Dancing Rain from attacking. Mounted Gun would increase her attack power by a massive amount. It would also increase her defense and give her Super Armor. There was no way to stop a Launcher using Mounted Gun from attacking. Su Mucheng could easily finish him off. She would simply have to sacrifice a bit of health to do so.

Boom!

A Satellite Beam descended, and Chaotic Cloudy Mountain fell. Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t have much health left. He could not retreat. During his final moments, he could only try to deal as much damage as possible to Dancing Rain. When he fell, he was able to take out 28% of Dancing Rain’s health. Even though his grabs didn’t have secondary effects, just the damage alone was frightening. Unfortunately, Chaotic Cloudy Mountain didn’t have much health left. If not, if he could survive a bit longer, it would be hard to say who would win.

Happy’s Su Mucheng had won with 59% health, giving Happy a substantial lead. This fight had the clearest winner and loser in the group arena so far. In the match between Jiang Botao and Mo Fan, when Jiang Botao had no skills available, Mo Fan had given him quite the beating. In this match, although Lu Boyuan was able to take out 28% of Dancing Rain’s health during his final moments, much more than what Su Mucheng did to him during that period of time, it couldn’t really be said that he had the upper hand the majority of the battle. Ever since Su Mucheng was able to escape from his grasp, Su Mucheng took complete control over the fight. She fully deserved this win.

Chapter 1603 - Believe in the Power of Love

In the group arena, Happy finally established a clear lead for themselves. Lu Boyuan quietly left the stage. The Samsara fans in the stadium didn’t blame him though.

In this round, no matter who won or lost, it would be very easy to widen the gap between the two teams. This was something that any experienced Glory player would understand, simply due to the two player’s classes. One was a Launcher, and the other was a Grappler. If an appropriate distance was maintained, the Grappler would simply have no way to land attacks on the Launcher; if the Grappler could close the distance and latch on to the Launcher, the Launcher wouldn’t be able to put up a proper fight.

Victory and defeat would be determined by the to-and-fro of controlling the distance. The resulting difference in health would definitely be influenced by the disparity in distance control between the two players, something decided by the uniqueness of their classes.

In the end, the result really was determined by such logic.

Samsara still had two players left. Would they be able to close the gap?

The audience gazed at Samsara’s player bench, waiting for their fourth player to take the stage.

Du Ming!

Samsara’s fourth player was Du Ming, meaning that one of their ace players, Sun Xiang, was set to come out as their fifth, a somewhat conservative arrangement. After Zhou Zekai was the first to take the stage, the one viewed as the second best in 1v1s, Sun Xiang, wasn’t their third or fourth player, but instead their last. The purpose for this was already something that people had started to discuss as soon as the list of players for the group arena had first been broadcasted.

But at this time, when Samsara had fallen behind, needing to win a two versus two and a half, having Du Ming go up first and Sun Xiang bringing up the rear seemed more stable.

Conservative, but also stable.

As Du Ming rose from the player benches while talking to his teammates, he couldn’t help but cast a glance at Happy’s player bench.

But no matter how many times he swept his gaze across, Tang Rou still continued to single-mindedly watch the review of the previous round that was being played on the large TV screen.

“What’s the point in looking, it’s not like anyone’s looking back!” Someone on Samsara’s side noticed Du Ming’s wandering gaze and said.

“Could she be avoiding me?” Du Ming said to himself.

“You joker! Quickly get on stage!” Most of the Samsara players couldn’t take it anymore.

Du Ming raised his head, looking at the list of players for both teams displayed on the large screen. If he wanted to face off against Tang Rou, he had no choice but to fight till the very end! That meant that not only did he have to beat Su Mucheng, whose character was still at 59% health, he also had to beat their next player, Fang Rui……

He had to do his best!

Du Ming silently clenched his fists, firmly walking towards the stage.

“Is this why you kept suggesting that he play fourth?” Jiang Botao watched all of Du Ming’s actions and asked the Cleric player, Fang Minghua.

“Believe in the power of love!” Fang Minghua wore an experienced look on his face. As one of the few married players in the Glory Alliance, he felt that he had a particular authority on the topic. On top of that, most of the players in the community were still very young, and were always on the computer, meaning that most of them didn’t even have a girlfriend.

“At the very least… it’s safe,” Jiang Botao evidently didn’t allow for this arrangement of players due to such a childish-sounding reason. More importantly, he believed that having Sun Xiang as the fifth player to bring up the rear was a more dependable decision. So in the end, Samsara’s decision meant that they would bear witness to “the power of love”.

“Happy’s group arena arrangements almost always seem to have Tang Rou as their anchor. By putting Du Ming as the fourth player, if he happens to directly run into Tang Rou, he will use everything he has to defeat her, to make her take note of his abilities. If he doesn’t run into Tang Rou, then he will use everything he has to kill his way to this goal.” Once again, Fang Minghua expounded on why he believed in this particular arrangement.

“Brilliant,” Jiang Botao nodded and said.

Everyone else was completely speechless. Perhaps only their vice-captain would be able to accept all of these things without batting an eyelid! Everyone felt that Du Ming’s looked extremely solemn and tragic as he walked onto the stage. What exactly was he fighting for?

Du Ming walked onto the stage and entered his player booth. A new round began as the characters loaded in.

Within Samsara, Du Ming could definitely be considered part of the main force, even though his fame wasn’t as resounding as Zhou Zekai and the rest. That being said, in the recent few years, Samsara had invested more and more into their team, making remarkable improvements to all of their characters. Even his Blade Master, Moon-Luring Frost could now be counted as being mostly kitted out in Silver gear. The Lightsaber in his hands, Ice Shards, didn’t have a high-class sounding name, but after repeated refinement, it was now considered to be one of “Glory’s Top Ten Swords” by many players, so it was clearly exceptional.

Deep breaths!

Du Ming calmed himself. At this time, he couldn’t afford to think too much about Tang Rou, who had yet to take the field. If he wanted to have a decisive battle with her, he still had to get past the next two obstacles. Now, he would concentrate and take out Su Mucheng first.

Battle start!

.

Du Ming’s attitude was resolute. Moon-Luring Frost quickly set off, directly moving towards the center path.

On Su Mucheng’s side, Dancing Rain also didn’t opt to take a roundabout way, and similarly headed for the centre. However, she knew that the center path had a stalactite running from top to bottom, which would block her view of the other side. As such, Dancing Rain strategically headed in a slightly slanted direction from the beginning, so that her view wouldn’t be blocked by the stalactite.

Advance!

The distance between the two characters continued to shrink.

Just when the respective players had advanced halfway, Du Ming’s Moon-Luring Frost instead changed his direction, heading horizontally to the side.

He didn’t resolutely take the middle path, as everyone had expected. Once he had taken the middle path halfway, he suddenly started to take a roundabout route.

The roundabout route wasn’t that far away, but with the field of view from the strategic angle that Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain take, she wouldn’t be able to notice Moon-Luring Frost’s movement.

With regards to using the stalagmites in this map, all of Samsara’s players were extremely masterful. With the final path that Du Ming’s Moon-Luring Frost took, instead of calling it a roundabout route, it was more like the strategic angle that Su Mucheng had taken, slightly offset from the centre. It was just that this slight slant made full use of the distributions of the stalactites. Obviously, this was a route that Samsara had researched to advance towards the center while still being able to conceal oneself.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain reached the middle of the map and stopped moving.

Seeing that her opponent hadn’t appeared, that meant that he hadn’t taken the middle path, or that he had hidden himself…

Even though she didn’t exactly know what trick Du Ming had pulled, after these few rounds, the way in which Samsara used the stalagmites in this map was something that an experienced player like Su Mucheng could already faintly infer.

Instead of advancing, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain use an Electronic Eye. Afterwards, Su Mucheng began advancing again, but she maintained an appropriate distance with each and every stalactite within her field of view.

Her footsteps were so soft that the match was suddenly devoid of sound, as if someone had muted it.

Through their omniscient point of view, the audience could see that both the characters were moving closer to each other, step by step. However, Dancing Rain maintaining a cautious distance from any stalagmite meant that Du Ming didn’t have any opportunity to make a move.

The Blade Master wasn’t like the Grappler that required a zero-distance confrontation, but it still couldn’t take a long-ranged fight. In reality, this match actually followed very similar logic to the previous one.

What would happen next? Everyone held their breaths and watched on.

Chapter 1604 - Extraordinary Du Ming

Moon Luring Frost’s head suddenly poked out from behind the stalagmite.

Boom!

Cannonfire immediately shot towards him. It was certainly unfortunate timing for Moon Luring Frost. He had come out just when Dancing Rain was aimed towards him. When Su Mucheng saw him, she immediately pulled the trigger.

The artillery shells were aimed at the edges of the stalagmite instead of directly towards Moon Luring Frost. Su Mucheng had taken into account that Du Ming’s Moon Luring Frost would be able to take cover in time. As a result, she went for the splash damage instead, while simultaneously having Dancing Rain circle around to get to a different angle.

However, Moon Luring Frost didn’t take cover. He came out of hiding completely.

The artillery shell exploded, and the shockwave spread out, but Moon Luring Frost was unaffected.

How?

Dancing Rain was startled. Moon Luring Frost suddenly rushed out. Behind him were one, two, three, four, five Moon Luring Frosts followed behind in quick succession.

Shadow Steps!

Du Ming had used Shadow Steps. The Moon Luring Frost that had been unaffected by the first shot was evidently a fake shadow.

The shadows created from Shadow Steps were different from Ninja shadow clones. Shadow Steps produced afterimages, which couldn’t be damaged. As long as the skill wasn’t interrupted, these afterimages could not be destroyed. To interrupt the skill, you needed to hit the true body. Du Ming was able to produce six shadows. He had the ability to produce more, but not to this level of perfection. Su Mucheng had already eliminated one of the possibilities with her first shot, but which one among the other five was the real one? Su Mucheng couldn’t distinguish between them from observation alone.

In that case, she could only test them out one by one using attacks.

Gatling Gun!

Dancing Rain lifted up a Gatling Gun and swept across. The bullets flew towards the five untested Moon Luring Frosts. However, the five Moon Luring Frosts weren’t just standing there like sitting ducks. Under Du Ming’s control, all of them went in different directions to hide and dodge the incoming attacks. The audience suddenly realized that when Du Ming chose to hide behind this specific stalagmite, his objective hadn’t simply been because he could no longer move covertly after reaching it. When the shadows from Shadow Steps scattered, the arrangement of the surrounding stalagmites was perfect for their escape. To dodge the Gatling Gun, the five shadows went straight for the closest stalagmite.

This didn’t seem to be an impromptu decision. It seemed more like something he had practiced. Du Ming had clearly studied this map on his own in order to coordinate his Shadow Step with the surrounding terrain.

Su Mucheng realized that the situation wasn’t good. With the shadows scattered, she didn’t know which one to target. She didn’t know which one posed the most threat to her. The terrain was perfect for Du Ming right now.

Retreat first.

Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain retreat. However, Du Ming didn’t stop to rest after disrupting Su Mucheng’s offense. The shadows immediately rushed out again, coming towards her from different directions.

Which one was real?

Let alone Su Mucheng, even the viewers didn’t know. Which one was the real threat?

Five shadows, five swords flashing with a dangerous light. Su Mucheng discovered that she had no safe way to escape. Under Du Ming’s meticulously practiced pursuit, from the scattered shadows back to a combined assault, all of her retreat paths were blocked.

Her only choice was to figure out which one was real and attack it, or run away and leave it up to luck.

Her chances were quite high. There was only one real one. All the others were fake and wouldn’t actually deal any damage to her. If she chose one to rush towards, there was a high probability that she would run into a fake one.

But pro Blade Masters wouldn’t just watch quietly as the opponent ran recklessly towards one of the shadows. They would adjust what their shadows did depending on their opponent’s movements. The shadow that you run towards might try to avoid you, but that didn’t mean it was necessarily the fake one. The shadow charging towards you filled with killing intent might not be the real one.

Experienced Blade Masters would control their shadows to make it very difficult to tell which one was real or fake. Choosing which one to go towards wasn’t as simple as a gambling on chance. It would also test the opponent’s courage and resolve.

Which one will she choose?

Du Ming stared intently at Dancing Rain. He was certain that Su Mucheng would end up choosing one of the shadows to move towards, but no matter which one she chose, Du Ming had a way to make Dancing Rain take damage. He was confident because he had practiced this Shadow Step formation numerous times. The distance between any two shadows seemed random, but in reality, the distance had been carefully studied so that it was optimal. And then, through practice, he was able to set up this formation in a short amount of time.

Come!

Choose one! Let’s end this fight.

Du Ming was waiting. Finally, Dancing Rain moved. However, she didn’t seem to move towards any of the shadows. She moved towards the center of their combined attacks.

What is she thinking?

Du Ming stared blankly at her. Dancing Rain lifted her arm, pointing her cannon into the air as if she were giving out a signal.

Satellite Beam!

Du Ming immediately recognized what skill she planned on using. Had she somehow figured out which one was real?

Impossible! Du Ming had even watched his own recordings when he practiced this five Shadow Step assault. He didn’t remember which one was the real body, and he couldn’t figure out which one was the real body either. Du Ming’s execution of this tactic had reached perfection.

There was no way she knew. She was probably bluffing, baiting me into making a mistake!

Du Ming concluded. His control over his Shadow Steps was unaffected. The shadows grew closer and closer. Boom! The Satellite Beam descended, unexpectedly with Dancing Rain in the middle. The smaller pillars of light spinning around the main pillar, swept through the surroundings.

Since I can’t get you to make a mistake, then I’ll just attack all five!

Six pillars of light spread outwards. The five shadows were too close. Two of them were immediately swallowed by two of the pillars. These two shadows weren’t affected by the attack, fakes.

Three more!

Su Mucheng was just about to check them, when a sword light flashed in front of her. A blue light tore through the Satellite Beam.

Meteor Form!

The sword light was like a meteor, weaving between two smaller light pillars, straight into the main light pillar. A streak of red blood splashed into the air.

Then, Curving Wind Form!

The blood suddenly curved back in the opposite direction, bringing Dancing Rain along with it.

Colliding Stab!

After two Level 75 Blade Master skills, Du Ming followed with a low-level Berserker skill. However, this skill was the key to breaking open this situation.

Moon Luring Frost’s weapon, Lingering Ice, pressed against Dancing Rain’s stomach. When a Blade Master used Colliding Stab, the attack wouldn’t have as fearsome of a knockback. But it was enough to carry along the opponent outwards. Moon Luring Frost escaped from the Satellite Beam’s range, dragging Dancing Rain along with him.

The stadium erupted with thunderous applause!

Du Ming had made a brilliant play. The AoE from the Launcher’s Satellite Beam seemed to be nonexistent to him. Such precise movements and attacks deserved the applause.

“Look, this is the power of love!!” Fang Minghua slapped his leg, laughing at Du Ming.

The other Samsara players nodded their heads and applauded. Whether it was the power of love or not, Du Ming had made a beautiful play. It was an exceptional display of skill that could definitely woo any girl. Thinking of this, several Samsara players glanced towards Happy’s seats, at Tang Rou. But what they saw was Tang Rou watching the match intently. She seemed to have an expression of worry on her face. It didn’t look like she had been enchanted at all by Du Ming’s incredible play.

It’s not enough, Du Ming! A bit more!

Du Ming’s teammates cheered him on.

Du Ming continued to perform, but he wasn’t thinking about all that. Beating the opponent in front of him was everything right now. He had to focus on this goal. Tang Rou? She might be one source of motivation, but she wouldn’t be on his mind right now.

He only had one thing on his mind: beat his opponent.

Sword light flashed.

With the Colliding Stab landing, he had closed the distance between himself and Dancing Rain. Moon Luring Frost immediately started his assault, using the blossoming blood to perform a brightly-colored dance.

Beautiful!

The crowd applauded again.

He had dragged Dancing Rain out of the Satellite Beam beautifully, and his follow-up had been beautiful as well. Su Mucheng wasn’t going to just have Dancing Rain stand there like a dead tree. She kept searching for a chance to escape, but the interweaving sword light locked her in place. She would occasionally find an opportunity to attack from close-range, but these attacks never created any substantial opportunities for her. She didn’t give up, but even when Dancing Rain fell, no opportunity had come.

One combo to death!

Even though Dancing Rain only had 59% health to begin with, killing her in one combo was an incredible performance from Du Ming. His Moon Luring Frost had only lost 12% of his health. Du Ming had closed the 59% lead by 47%. There was only a difference in 12% health between the two sides.

Du Ming didn’t get too pleased with himself over this point. The instant Dancing Rain was killed, he immediately waved away Su Mucheng from his mind.

Next! Du Ming was already thinking. There was a bit of a gap in his thoughts right afterwards: if I win the next one, then I can meet with Tang Rou.

And his next opponent was Fang Rui and his Boundless Sea.

Chapter 1605 - An Undeserving Pay

"Du Ming's in really good condition today. Be careful," Ye Xiu said to Fang Rui.

"In better condition than me?" Fang Rui scoffed.

"Haha," Ye Xiu laughed.

"What's 'haha' supposed to mean!" Fang Rui could feel the disdain from Ye Xiu's laugh.

"You're getting paid the most out of all of us. Please," Ye Xiu said.

"Peh!" Fang Rui wasn't going to fall for Ye Xiu's trap. He turned around and headed towards the stage.

However, his actions didn't match his thoughts. Ye Xiu wasn't wrong. He was the highest-paid player on Happy, and it wasn't even close. But ever since the playoffs began, what had he been able to accomplish?

He hadn't been completely useless, of course, but not being completely useless wasn't really deserving of having the highest pay on the team.

The core player on the team was usually the highest paid player. Fang Rui knew that he wasn't the core. Even so, he should at least be a deciding factor in the matches to correspond with that pay.

But what had he been able to do thus far?　

He had only been a bit of use in the playoffs. Wei Chen, who was practically a dying grandpa in the pro scene, had more highlights than him. There was also Luo Ji, a college student who barely even played in the regular season. All of them had made plays that had won the team the game.

As for him?

He couldn't compare with Ye Xiu, fine. But not being able to compare with a young rookie and an elderly grandpa? What's going on?

Fang Rui asked himself. In particular, in their third and final game against Tyranny, he had been carried by his teammates to victory. He had been extremely unhappy with his performance. He had been hoping to redeem himself against Samsara. In their first game against Samsara, he had been Happy's third player in the group arena. In the end, he had lost to Sun Xiang, who had been Samsara's third player as well. In the team competition, he continued to perform like he was just a placeholder in the team. The deepest impression that people got from him that match was when he was killed.

What am I doing?

He had repeatedly underperformed during the playoffs. Fang Rui felt like he should have already lost his position. However, Fang Rui continued to send him up. The team's trust in him only made him feel more pressured.

I have to change! What do I need to do?

Fang Rui said to himself as he came across Su Mucheng.

"Be careful. He's in really good condition today," Su Mucheng said to him.

"Fuck, are you two colluding?" Fang Rui replied.

"What?" Su Mucheng was a bit confused, but quickly realized that someone must have said something similar to Fang Rui, and she knew who that someone was.

"As if there was any need to collude," Su Mucheng chuckled.

Fang Rui was speechless.

True. It was pretty obvious that Du Ming was playing really well today. How could Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng not be able to tell? The two were just reminding him and also worrying for him.

"Relax," Fang Rui smiled at Su Mucheng, "I, Fang Rui, am worthy of my name!"

"Haha," Su Mucheng laughed.

"Haha, what haha. You're becoming more and more like him, you know that?" Fang Rui cursed.

"Good luck!" Su Mucheng didn't bother bickering with Fang Rui.

"Do you mind grabbing me some hot water? I'm going to need a drink after I beat him," Fang Rui waved his arms. Then, he turned around and continued to walk towards the stage.

He entered the player booth, sucked in a deep breath, swiped his account card, and loaded into the game.

The seventh round of the group arena. Happy's fourth player, Fang Rui, versus Samsara's fourth player, Du Ming.　

"Don't block my way!!" As soon as the match began, Fang Rui immediately yelled out into the chat.

"Don't block my way!" Du Ming wasn't going to be outdone. Moon Luring Frost rushed out.

"Come!" Fang Rui shouted. Boundless Sea ran around in a circle twice and then crouched down, hiding behind the closest stalagmite.

The crowd went into an uproar.

That was the Fang Rui that everyone knew. Saying such bravado and doing something else wasn't a feat that just anyone could accomplish.

Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost didn't use the terrain to hide himself as he moved this time. He went straight for the center of the map. As for Fang Rui's Boundless Sea, he just crouched down behind a stalagmite as if he were bored to death. From time to time, he would type into the chat: "Are you here yet?"

"Why are you so slow?"

It had been such an intense match so far, but now that the lazy Fang Rui had come, it was like an eggplant wilting from the frost. The Samsara fans felt like their energy was being sapped. Fang Rui had completely ruined the tense atmosphere in the stadium. The peak-level match had suddenly turned into an in-game 1v1 in the Glory Arena.

"I'm here. Where are you?" After Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost reached the center of the map, he replied in the chat. It looked like he was quite familiar with Fang Rui's personality. You could never believe Fang Rui's words. Moon Luring Frost looked around and then continued forward towards Happy's spawn point.

"I'm too tired to move. I'm waiting at the spawn point!" Fang Rui replied.

"Just wait there, so I can hurry up and finish this," Du Ming said. Moon Luring Frost continued to push forward. However, this time, he didn't move in a straight line. Instead, he did the same as when he played against Su Mucheng. He chose to use the terrain to move around covertly.

"If you're in such a hurry, why not just GG?" Fang Rui asked.

The crowd went in an uproar again. Enough of this bullshit. Can't you be more serious? A lot of people didn't like how unprofessional Fang Rui was. Samsara started mass booing for the first time, all towards Fang Rui.

Fang Rui couldn't hear them. He continued to talk nonsense. On the other hand, Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost was getting closer and closer. But because Fang Rui hadn't done anything since the start of the fight, Du Ming had no way of knowing where Fang Rui was. Was Boundless Sea hiding behind one of these stalagmites?

Du Ming didn't move rashly. The home team players knew better than the away team players on how to use the map. Moon Lure Frost quietly moved towards a stalagmite. He didn't overlook the possibility that Boundless Sea would happen to be hiding behind it. As a result, he put up his guard as he charged towards it.

There was no one there.

His lightsaber, Lingering Ice, hit nothing but air. Du Ming wasn't concerned. He went towards this stalagmite and suddenly jumped.

One jump, two jumps, three jumps, four jumps.

He went up and down four times before finally reaching the top of the stalagmite.

But it wasn't like the stalagmite was that tall. If he couldn't see anyone before, he still wouldn't be able to see anyone.

Du Ming's Moon Luring Frost didn't even look around. He stared straight at another stalagmite that was closeby.

Jump!

Moon Luring Frost jumped towards that stalagmite.